and everyone
that's involved in it.
This is a rough business,
you know, in Mykonos,
and it's only getting busier,
so I really don't have time
to take any weak links in.
I don't know.
I'm not sure what I'm gonna do.
Okay, boss.
(Sara)
Lindsay comes out of nowhere.
I feel like I'm gonna throw up
right now.
We decided to send you
to see your grandmother.
Oh, my God, yes.
Oh, my gosh.
I wanna milk a goat.
Wow, never felt more loved
in my life.
(Lindsay)
It's my first time firing
someone ever in my life.
I have a brand
and a business,
and I'm sorry, but I'm gonna
have to let you go.
(Juliette)
Lately, my relationship
with Chloe has gotten
pretty tense...
Stop
Don't push me, honey.
Don't put your hands on me.
(Juliette)
...and it's all because
of Alex's ex Cara.
Cara's definitely
his kryptonite.
he would come over
if I asked him to.
If you're siand rea,
we should definitely
exchange numbers.
(Juliette)
Garrett's so naive,
he actually thinks he has
a shot with her.
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
(Juliette)
Poor guy's still
rebounding from Kelsey,
who's being
her usual hot mess.
How are things with
the whole boyfriend?
He's in Arizona.
(Juliette)
But Kelsey's
commitment issues
are nothing compared
to Madisson's.
So what's the deal
with you guys?
We're both like, single.
If I tried to be
exclusive with you,
I could like,
ruin however we are.
(Juliette)
Ben's a dog and she knows it.
(Alex)
You are being
a brat right now.
(Juliette)
I thought my own relationship
was so much better
than any of theirs...
I do everything for you.
That's not fair.
(Juliette)
...but after tonight,
I just don't know.
Why do you want
to do this right now?
You're an idiot.
Do you not see
how rude that is?
Why would you say that?
♪♪
♪ I had a dream
or was it real? ♪
♪ We crossed
the line and it was on ♪
♪ I ♪ We crossed the line ♪
or was it real? ♪
♪ It was on this time
ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ I wanna cut through
the clouds ♪
♪ Break the ceiling ♪
♪ I wanna dance on the roof ♪
♪ You and me alone ♪
♪ I wanna cut
to the feeling, oh, yeah ♪
♪ I wanna cut to
the feeling ♪
♪ I wanna cut
to the feeling ♪♪
♪♪
Can you stop acting
like a drama queen?
'Cause I didn't do
anything wrong.
I don't wanna
talk about it right now.
All right, whatever.
Why can't you just be like,
"I'm sorry I made you upset?"
♪♪
Listen to me,
you're upset because
all he ever does is say,
"I do this for you,
and I do this for you."
And you're feeling like,
I do all these things for you
and you're making me feel like
a bad girlfriend when I'm not.
Wait, how did you
know that?
Because that's exactly right.
(Amanda)
Chloe has a way
of knowing things.
I love you,
and you're not wrong.
You guys just have to
communicate properly.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom
and fix my face.
You look fine, but go.
You look good.
Go fix your face.
♪♪
So... so far,
who do you like
and who do you not like?
I'll just say
I have my interests.
♪♪
Honestly, at this point,
I could care less.
(Chloe)
Did you see apparently...
They went on the beach.
Look. But look.
(Chloe)
They go to the beach
at 2:30 in the morning.
Jared literally posted
a picture in his...
Like, what,
did Kelsey take that?
Did her and her boyfriend
break up?
No.
I respect that
you have a boyfriend.
But I think you're
drop-dead gorgeous.
You better.
Hey...
we'll see.
♪ I am the bonfire ♪
♪ You make me stronger,
you make me lighter ♪
■■■■    ♪ With the shade
you throw on me... ♪♪
(Juliette)
Cara totally thinks
she's the new "it" girl
of Siesta Key.
Hi, how are you?
Hi!
(Juliette)
Sure, she's got
a sick beach house...
Your place
is literally insane.
(Juliette)
...and she loves to party.
mes with my boyfriend.
It's like, so obvious that
he still has a thing for me.
(Juliette)
And now she's talking
to my ex Garrett.
I'm really not
posting that.
It's a good picture,
though, why not?
Second date?
It's far too soon.
Story?
No.
Maybe put like, you know,
"Chillin' in paradise"
with a little
palm tree emoji.
Stories get people
in trouble.
Did you see, um,
Kelsey and Jared
hung out the other night
on Jared's story?
Oh, yeah, I did.
They were like,
skinny-dipping.
Isn't she worried
her boyfriend might see that?
That's awkward.
Yeah, so I'm definitely
not gonna story this then.
You know who that would
probably piss off?
Who?
Juliette.
All these exes of yours
that I have to worry about.
No, second date,
it's already been
better than any date
I've been on with Juliette.
Aww, that's so sweet,
thank you.
♪♪
You got it.
All right,
why am I a better date
than Juliette?
Um, you're
a lot more sweeter.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
She's like, said
a bunch of stuff
like you're still trying
to get with Alex.
Eww.
She says anything she can
to hate on me.
Well, is that like,
not true?
I'm not impressed by him
like she is,
that's for sure.
With the money and all that?
Yeah, I mean, like,
I've been around
that kind of (bleep)
my whole life.
Like, it's not
impressive to me.
Like, for me,
I've always had
to work for everything
that I've had.
Like, growing up like,
my parents weren't like,
wealthy or anything, but...
so I kinda grew up
staying humble,
but also having
somewhat success
just from hard work
and all that.
So what about you--
Sorry.
what're your plans
for your future?
What do you wanna do?
Plans?
Yeah, do you have any?
I applied to grad school.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, for teaching.
Like, what do you wanna teach?
Kindergarten,
first grade,
second grade?
Yeah?
Yeah, I'm good with
the little ones.
Are you?
Yeah.
Well, that's always good,
you know?
If you ever have
any of your own.
(both laughing)
All right, got it.
I got it...
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ But this is unexpected ♪
♪ I gotta go but you
keep turning me on ♪
♪ Turning me on ♪♪
♪ Bounce, bounce,
like a beach ball ♪
♪ Running 'round
in circles... ♪♪
(Carson)
Whoo, you ready, baby?
(Brandon)
Hell yeah.
I haven't packed yet.
m ready to get ready.
then you're not ready.
There you go,
all right.
Yo, should I bring
the white pants?
That's Miami, right?
Bring the white pants.
(Juliette)
You gotta hurry
and finish packing.
Amanda and Pauly
are gonna be here soon.
Dude, I hate packing.
You're not doing
very good.
Oh, thanks!
Juliette specifically told me
"Cara is not invited."
Of course she did.
And I was like, I know.
And even though
I want you to come...
Even though I want to come...
(all laughing)
(Kelsey)
I wish I was going,
but I feel like
there's just gonna be drama
with all these rumors
going around and stuff.
Like that Jared (bleep)?
Oh, my God.
That Jared (bleep)
is literally so stupid.
What happened?
On the way home,
we decided to go
to the beach
and that was it.
Yes, we have chemistry,
but I have a boyfriend
and I don't wanna ruin that.
As long as you
and Jacob are good.
That's all that matters.
Yeah, we're great.
I'm very happy about it.
(Alex)
We got white buffalo.
Let's not do that again.
Crazy.
Let's not do that again?
No, I don't wanna fight
with you anymore.
No, I don't wanna fight,
especially in public.
Really?
Well, I don't like
to do that.
'Cause then everyone's
like, "What's wrong?"
I don't wanna fight
in general, that's...
I mean, we're always gonna
get in like, little arguments.
(both giggling)
Did you see Chloe
apologized to me?
She seemed like she
really wanted to like,
rebuild our friendship,
and she apologized
about Cara
and said that she was...
Yeah, she admitted to me...
...bringing her around
to piss me off.
And I was like,
at least you admit it.
Yeah.
(Chloe)
I mean, Juliette and I obviously
aren't like,
back to complete normal.
But hopefully in Miami,
we can like,
rekindle our friendship
and like, remember why
we were all friends
in the beginning.
Yeah, I'm just sad,
now I have to wait a whole week
to see Garrett again.
So what is going on
with you and Garrett?
We've had two dates.
Have you kissed?
No.
We haven't done
anything yet.
Do you want to?
I mean, eventually.
But not like, right now.
I mean, half the fun
of seeing Garrett
is that he's always
around Alex and Juliette
and I know it
drives her crazy.
I'm kinda glad
I'm not going.
I wanna spend a little
more time with Tawni.
What do you mean?
Yeah, what is...
So we definitely
have a connection.
We spend so much
time together
and we're very similar people.
For sure.
I've always liked Tawni,
so maybe I can inch my way
into something else.
Really? Has she even
ever been with a girl?
No, but that's not something
that I'm not familiar with.
(Chloe)
Yeah, I guess that's true.
Well, I just don't want you
falling for someone
that can't fall for you
back the same way.
So just be careful.
(Madisson)
So guess who's coming?
Who?
Ben decided to
meet us in Miami.
Think you guys
are gonna talk about like,
where you stand
and all that, or...?
I mean, it's something
I'm dreading,
but I know that I have to.
Mm-hmm.
Ben and I have been
doing this casual thing
for five or six years now.
Yeah.
Obviously like, I want that
commitment from him...
Yeah.
...'cause it's just been
so surface level
for so long.
I mean, it's up to you,
but I really don't think
you should be with someone
if they're not gonna be willing
to be with you
on a deeper level.
So Garrett
is five minutes out.
Oh, perfect timing.
I thought I was rushing.
(Carson)
So how we gonna do shotgun?
Looks like I got
shotty, huh?
You guys ready?
(Brandon)
We're ready, man.
Hey!
Miami!
♪♪
■■■■T=T=T=T■T
Hi!
It's nice in here.
(Juliette)
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my God, babe.
It's giant.
I know, it's sweet.
So you approve?
(Juliette)
I-- yeah, I approve!
Oh, my God!
It's the suite, babe.
(gasping)
Oh, my God!
(chuckling)
It's so beautiful.
This is like
our own place.
Oh, my God!
This is so crazy!
You like it?
♪ No matter
how long you're gone ♪
♪ I'm always gonna
want you back ♪
♪ I know you know ♪
♪ I will never get over you
xx■■♪ No matter where I go ♪
♪ I'm always gonna
want you back... ♪♪
(Brandon)
Is Cara coming?
I told her she needs
to respect the fact
that I'm making up with her.
Oh, and plus this is like,
Juliette's thing.
Wait, you're not cool
with Cara here?
No, I am, I just like,
I have to respect the fact
that I'm friends with
Juliette and Amanda now,
and I explained that to her.
And I don't like,
wanna have to play sides.
So like, I'm going
to Miami with my friends,
I'll see you
when I get back.
I heard
Ben was coming, right?
He's on his way, right?
Should be.
He should've already
been here, but...
Speak of the guy...
(Madisson)
Hey!
Hi!
Cheers, guys.
To Miami.
♪♪
(Madisson)
It's cool that Alex
set this whole thing up
for Juliette.
I'm glad I got the invite.
I'm glad you came.
This is like, our first
"vacay" together.
We gonna bring out
"party Madisson"?
Well...
before you get
too excited, um...
This sounds like bad news.
I do want separate rooms.
Like conjoining rooms?
No like, I'm gonna
stay with Amanda
and I thought you could
have your own room.
I was under
the impression that
like, I'm staying with you.
I flew here to like,
hang out with you on vacation.
And I-- yeah, and we are
gonna hang out, of course.
But... I mean, I wanna
have separate rooms,
and I...
Okay, is there any reason?
You're not my boyfriend.
Us sharing
a hotel room,
that's like
a boyfriend-girlfriend thing.
You made it pretty clear
to Kelsey the other day
that you were single.
So like, are we committing,
or are we not?
Like, why-- what is--
what is the hold up?
What's wrong with me that, like,
you don't want, like, to commit?
That's-- there's nothing
wrong with you, Madisson.
There's a reason I'm here.
I've been screwed over
in the past,
and wanna be smarter
this time.
So until we make that
commitment to each other,
like, I don't want to make
that commitment to, like,
share a room with you.
♪♪
I will respect
whatever you want.
Should be a good week,
I promise.
(Juliette)
Coming up...
You should come down here.
Yay, I'm so excited.
If you wanna invite
my boyfriend's ex
who's probably still trying
to hook up with him,
don't come to my trip.
You can go.
That's literally
so (bleep) rude.
♪ If ■a■■aH2■X
Never ending is now even better
at Olive Garden.
All new Never Ending Stuffed
Pastas starting at $12.99.
Pick your favorite stuffed
pasta, sauce and topping.
It's all never ending.
All new
Never Ending Stuffed Pastas.
Only for a limited time,
at Olive Garden.
(Nationwide jingle)
You see Brad,
songs are really about
big life moments.
Baby shower here.
Big. Life. Moment.
What is in here? Ohh!
Oh, I hope it's
a life insurance policy.
Wh
It's a sensible gift.
Protection for you
and your family,
Nationwide has all the tools
to help you find
the right coverage.
Tiny baby shoes.
So close.
(Peyton)
Makes no sense.
Babies can't even walk.
Should have life insurance poli.
Plus it would have been
a great song.
Think about it,
the lyrics,
the beneficiaries...
Brad, where are you going?
♪♪
■>■■÷>■÷■ ■Q(X(■g■gd@■@■@
When I see Obstacles,
I create opportunities.
When I see adversity,
I find a way.
When I hear never,
I say now.
Southern New Hampshire
University is education
made to fit your goals.
With over 200 degreeams,
flexible class schedules
and some of the lowest online
tuition rates in the nation.
So, when I face barriers,
I can break through.
Break through at SNHU.edu.
(in-store music)
Need a change of scenery?
KAYAK searches hundreds of
travel sites
— even our competitors
— so you can be confident you're
getting the right flight
at the best price.
KAYAK. Search One and Done.■■
■■7♪ If you let him touch ya,
touch ya, touch ya... ♪♪
KAYAK. Search One and Done.■■
Hey.
Hey, baby.
Hey, love.
Ooh, you already
starting off without me?
I did, but I just got it.
I wa-- haven't been here long.
(Juliette)
As if dating in Siesta Key
isn't complicated enough,
Canvas is trying
to find out if her bestie
wants to be more than
just friends.
I'm enjoying the fact
that everyone's in Miami,
so we don't have
to deal with that.
Exactly.
Everyone that stayed
is cool, so we're good.
Don't have to worry about
people busting in our night.
♪♪
Is like, the tiki bar
you end goal for now?
I've been looking into like,
um, being a drug rep.
I can't think
of one normal job.
I want so much
out of my life
and sadly wanna do
a little bit of everything.
In life or in relationships?
Both.
(both laughing)
I like options.
I like variety.
Yeah, I need to work more
on being a flirt
and less of sleeping around.
I know, you-- your roster's
pretty full right now.
I'm kinda jealous.
I don't know why
I've always been
a person who like--
I just need the love
from other people
and I need the reassurance.
Honestly, it's not that
I'm against relationships,
I just know like,
I don't like to be vulnerable
and I don't like to get
my hopes up, like...
See, we're very different.
You throw walls up immediately
to keep from getting hurt,
where I am an open book
and I just let people in
because it's worth it
to me to get hurt
to actually have a chance
at something real.
Yeah, see,
I think the reason
I'm so much like too
on top of everything,
you know, like,
I don't have
the greatest relationship
with my dad.
He completely abandoned me
and like,
refuses to talk to me.
I needed a mom at that point.
I needed someone to
be able to talk to.
And like, when I was 16,
she moved to Australia.
I can't even imagine.
I've needed her
in so many situations
in my life,
and phone calls
don't really do it.
I'll figure it out
hopefully.
For sure.
So I can maybe understand
your jaded opinion
on love a little bit.
Yeah, you know...
What would be
your ideal girl?
I need someone who
can keep up with me.
I need someone who can
keep up with my mouth.
And like,
I like broken souls.
And just say (bleep) it
right now,
and I'm just gonna sit
my little pretty ass away
from like, all emotions.
Wait, so y--
you don't have
your eye on anybody
right now?
I mean...
we'll see.
♪♪
♪ Must've been high ♪
ust've been high... ♪♪
(Juliette)
It's our first night in Miami,
and we're all
going out to play.
Well, almost all of us.
(Brandon)
Hey, why didn't Madisson come?
She was like,
exhausted today, so...
(Brandon)
I know she was tired,
but I mean,
it's just limited time
out here, why not...
Yeah, I know, it's Miami.
You came out here
from Texas, (bleep).
Oh, well.
I still feel like
if I'm gonna be like,
making an effort
to go see a girl,
then I'm staying with her
in the same room.
Like, I feel like
you deserve that
as a-- as a man, like...
Yeah.
(Brandon)
But don't do what I did
with Madisson last year.
But that's what
I'm saying, though,
it's cool that she's like,
letting you out right now.
♪♪
So you took Cara out,
she told me.
I did, yeah.
How'd it go?
It went really good,
I thought.
She's cool.
She's-- she's a cool girl.
So you like her.
I'm trying to get her
to come here.
I'm probably gonna...
I don't think
that's a good idea.
...maybe FaceTime her.
I still wanna get
to know her more,
and I think like,
her coming to visit here
and stay in Miami would be
a good opportunity for us
to have like, a good time.
That puts me in
a bad position.
I just wanna be
a good friend
to Juliette.
I mean, you guys all
just sorted things out.
So you guys are good...
And one of the major rules
is "Chloe,
don't bring Cara around."
If you're gonna be
around Juliette,
just don't be around
Cara at the same time.
It's not gonna be
Chloe bringing her here,
it's gonna be Garrett
bringing her here.
Uh, so I think
it'll be all right.
I want nothing to do with it.
100%.
Cheers!
♪♪
(phone trilling)
Hi!
■÷
Yeah, I talked to Chloe.
I mean, I know
that you maybe
have talked to her already
and the whole
Juliette situation.
But, um, and she was like,
cool about it, so...
♪♪
♪ I'm just curious ♪♪
(Tawni)
Cheers.
♪♪
♪ I've been waiting
for someone to hold me ♪
♪ To hold me down ♪
♪ And I won't stop
running round ♪
♪ Till I find myself in
a one horse town ♪
♪ Sunlit bathed in
the Hollywood hills ♪
♪ Down a dead end street
where I can't be found ♪♪
♪♪
(Brandon)
There's the gang.
Rooftop!
(Chloe)
♪ Rooftop party ♪♪
Where's-- where's
the rest of our friends?
Who are we missing?
Yo, Garrett.
Garrett.
Where the (bleep)
is Garrett?
Garrett said Cara's coming.
(Juliette)
Of course Cara
would find a way
to scam her way into
my vacation.
Is Cara coming?
(Brandon)
He said Cara's coming, yeah.
(Juliette)
The only question
was who to blame?
Don't be upset.
I'm just like...
No one knew it was
happening until tonight.
You probably did, Chloe.
I didn't, no.
Garrett just
asked me tonight,
it was so (bleep) annoying.
Why do you give a (bleep)?
Like, clearly
I didn't invite her.
(Chloe)
No one's attacking you.
Yeah, stop attacking.
Don't attack her about it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Why do you care?
Why wouldn't I care?
It's just weird.
(Chloe)
No one invited her.
It's annoying.
(Brandon)
Garrett's not thinking
about Juliette,
Garrett's thinking about him.
This trip is for her.
It's up to Juliette.
I think Garrett shouldn't
be (bleep) Cara.
Garrett can do
a lot better.
No offense, I know
you're friends with her.
But I didn't invite her,
so I have nothing to do...
(Amanda)
No, I'm just saying,
I don't mind her
it's just I know she pisses
one of my best friends off.
What a desperate person.
Hi, Garrett.
Yo, homie.
Why would you invite
Cara here?
Uh, I'm trying to get
to know her better.
So you should go
know her better in Sarasota.
Where you going,
Juliette?
It's just like,
you should just
use common sense
that it's like,
incredibly rude.
I told him.
If you wanna invite
my boyfriend's ex
who's probably still trying
to hook up with him,
don't come on my trip.
You can go,
you can leave.
go to a different hotel.
(Alex)
Baby...
That's literally
so (bleep) rude.
(Juliette)
Coming up...
So you can sit here
and tell me that
you don't think we have
any chemistry together?
Jacob's about
to come in town,
and I want to keep
this quiet right now.
(announcer)
The need more space...
(grandma)
Is your mom in there?
(announcer)
...since Nana's moved in plan.
(daughter)
Nope!
Let us help
with your plan.
Yeah, we can do that.
Well, that
sounds like a plan.
Start a plan
that flexes with yours.
New York Life.
■vIs it TurboTax or H&R Block
Online?
We may never know.
(VO)
More people can file free with
H&R Block Online.
Block has your back.
♪ I'M A BIG KID NOW ♪
♪ WENT FROM BABY BOTTLES TO
DRINKING FROM SIPPY CUPS ♪
■á■á■á■á■2■■■■■■■ó■■■■■■■■■■■ R♪
♪ I'M A BIG KID NOW ♪
♪ WE'RE 50 MILLION STRONG ♪
♪ SO PUT ON YOUR PULL-UPS
AND HELP US SING THIS SONG ♪
6&6&6&11    (Jared)
It's a lot quieter in the Key
♪ WE'RE 50 MILLION STRONG ♪
now that the whole party crew
is off in Miami.
We're the party crew.
I mean, true.
(Juliette)
After Jared and Kelsey's
skinny-dipping video
got around...
Beach night
with the squad!
(Juliette)
...no one's wondering why
they decided to skip
our Miami trip
and stay home together.
(Kelsey)
And dismount.
(Juliette)
But everyone is wondering
what Kelsey's boyfriend
would say if he found out.
So how are things?
Kelsey's meeting me here
to talk.
Ahem.
Yikes.
You sound like you're about
to have a fun conversation.
Probably.
It's okay.
Well, you know,
I'm always here
to get you drunk
afterwards.
Or get you drunk now.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Speaking of,
I had a very
interesting night
the other night.
With whom?
With Tawni.
So that's a thing.
Um, I don't know if it's
a thing exactly yet.
Hopefully, we'll see.
I want the dirty deets.
I want all of it.
Juicy details.
Fill me up.
You know me and Tawni,
so you know it gets wild.
Dirty dancing,
and other things
happened after
dirty dancing.
So if I played baseball,
was it a home run, or...
I mean,
a lady never tells.
Enjoy your secrets.
I'll assume what I want.
So you think it's gonna
go somewhere or is it...
I think so.
I hope so.
How is your, uh,
love life?
Hey, you know me.
You're the talk
of the Key right now.
(exhaling)
No clue what
you're talkin' about.
Oh, 'cause I didn't get
the Snapchats you sent me.
I don't remember the last time
I went skinny-dipping
at a beach with a nice guy
and didn't do anything
inappropriate.
Yeah, I mean, I had
a great time with Kelsey.
I mean, she's a lot of fun.
We get along well
together, so...
Um, she's a lot of fun
and you had a great time?
■8Like, how great of a time
Well, a lady
never tells, Canvas.■■■■■■■
But it was, uh,
eventful and exciting.
We're fully aware that
she has a boyfriend, right?
Like, y-- you're fully
aware of that?
And we're fully aware
that she doesn't act
like she has a boyfriend,
right?
♪ When I put
my headphones on ♪
♪ All of a sudden
the world turns off ♪
♪ When everyone i ♪
♪ Flippin' through
my playlist ♪
♪ I find myself, yeah,
when I put my headphones on ♪♪
Hi, how are you?
Good, how are you?
You look great.
Excited?
A little nervous.
A little nervous?
Who are we meeting
right now?
Everybody.
Chloe, Alex...
Why are you
doing this to me?
...Brandon, Juliette.
It's fine,
you're my guest.
I'll take care of it.
Okay, so you have--
Yeah, please.
If there's any problems,
I'm there.
You're there with me.
You'll make sure
nothing goes wrong?
Make sure of it, yeah.
Ready to drink?
Yeah, definitely need a drink.
Let's do it.
♪ Ready or not, baby,
here I come ♪♪
(Juliette)
I'm trying like, so hard
to have fun in Miami.
And everything was awesome
until Garrett invited Cara.
q>q=        I just hope
he's not dumb enough
to bring her like,
to this bar.
Oh, no, he probably--
he's probably dumb enough.
Are you low-key
kinda happy she's coming?
No, I wish she wasn't.
Like, I wanna
have fun with my friends
and now that she's here,
now I'm put in the position
of, like...
who can I hang out with?
But, at the end
of the day,
I'm hanging out
with Juliette.
If she has
an issue with that,
then she should not
have came.
Well, I appreciate that.
♪♪
♪ You should see me
in a crown ♪
♪ I'm gonna run
this nothing town ♪
♪ Watch me make 'em bow
one by one ♪
Hey. Can I talk to you?
♪ One by, one by ♪
♪ You should me
in a crown ♪♪
What's up?
Well, like, I'm hearing
from everyone
about what happened
the beach night.
I don't understand
why you care so much
what everyone thinks.
I mean, it's kind
of a big deal for me.
It might not be for me
'cause you're single,
but, like, I have
a boyfriend,
so it kind of (bleep) up
my relationship.
Okay, well, if you had
a boyfriend
that was, like,
a serious relationship,
you know...
I know what?
Things wouldn't
have happened.
You kissed me,
I didn't kiss you.
And I pushed away
and I left.
I wouldn't say
you pushed away,
but yeah, you left.
♪♪
Seriously?
Yeah.
Wow. This might (bleep) up
my whole entire relationship.
I don't think
long distance
is for you.
'Kay.
It's just not for you.
Whenever that ends,
I'll still be here.
Well, it better not
be ending because of you.
♪♪
So you can sit here
and tell me that
you don't think we have
any chemistry together at all?
I am in a relationship
and I have a boyfriend,
and that's a whole different
type of feelings.
Right.
I mean, you can have
your whole different
type of feelings,
you can do your
long distance relationship,
whatever... what you
got going on.
What I have going on--
Jacob's about to come in town,
and I want to keep
this quiet right now.
You and I are friends,
and we're never gonna be
anything else.
You need
to understand that.
Yeah, understand
you leading me on
I hope you enjoy your
ghost boyfriend thing.
You're a (bleep) dick.
Have a good one.
(Juliette)
Coming up...
What is your problem?
I don't want my
boyfriend's
ex-girlfriend here.
I think that's very fine.
Okay, but, like,
he also (bleep) all
of your other friends.
Searching for a way to
help stop your cold sore?
Only Abreva can
get rid of it in...
...as little as 2 1/2 days
when used at the first sign.
Abreva starts to
work immediately
to block the virus and
protect healthy cells.
Abreva acts on it.
So you can too.
When did sleep become something
that requires effort?
With Tempur-Pedic, it doesn't.
Enjoy our most advanced
pressure-relieving material
for the deepest sleep
you've ever had.
This Presidents Day,
save up to $500
on select adjustable
mattress sets.
Find a retailer
at tempurpedic.com.
Announcer: 7:35 remaining...
Tatum, with the drive...
( ♪♪ )
...and slams it down!
Gatorade studies
the best athletes
to create the most advanced
range of sports fuel.
Gatorade. You fuel us.
We fuel you.
to create the most advanced
range of sports fuel.
Kick off the new year
with the new iPhone included
-Mobile.
The amazing iPhone XR is perfect
for all those new year, new you
selfies.
And only T-Mobile has unlimited
with iPhone XR included for
just 40 bucks.
from the most loved in wireless.
Bring your family to T-Mobile
and get the amazing iPhone
XR included
for just $40 per line.
Yeast infection?
Get relief 4 times faster with
Monistat.
The #1 gynecologist recommended
brand.
Get Monistat. Get Cured.
And get back to you.
♪♪
Get Monistat. Get Cured.
(Amanda)
Oh, my God,
she's right there.
(groaning)
(Amanda)
Cheers to that.
There goes the peace
out the window!
Somebody wave
the white flag!
What's going on?
How are you guys?
Hey.
Hello, Chloe.
How are you?
Mwah!
(indistinct)
(Garrett)
Good to see you.
Love that shirt, bro.
Did she say hi to you?
No.
No?
She has to feel
awkward being here.
Like, there's no way
she can feel normal
being here right now.
Oh, I know.
(Pauly)
Cara! You come to the bar,
you don't say hello
to your long-lost friend
Pauly Paul?
Give her a rest, Garret!
Get down here, Cara!
Oh, my God.
It's been way too long!
I miss-- I miss
your nonsense.
How are you?
I miss you.
You look good.
I'm glad you're here.
I like your bun.
Are you?
I am glad you're here.
I'm trying to figure out
why you're here,
but I'm glad you're here.
(Pauly laughs)
When did you become
in Garrett?
You're talking
about boring.
Dude, he's my friend.
What the (bleep) is wrong
with hanging out with Garrett?
Oh, just friends?
Yes.
I mean, it's just,
like, Garrett,
he's chasing
Alex's exes around.
(Alex)
All right, whatever.
Wait, hey.
Would you mind
saying hi to Juliette?
Like, I know you guys
don't love each other.
This is for her,
and, like, it's kinda ballsy
for you to come
down here and...
I was invited.
I know you were.
I would love
to say hi to her.
I have no problem
with her.
So, yeah.
(Alex)
Mean a lot.
Thank you.
How are you?
Hi.
You look beautiful.
♪♪
All right, cool.
All right, nice talking
to you, Cara.
Yeah. Sure thing.
Thanks for coming.
Her hands are cold.
It's like, what ice person
is touching me?
Cold like her soul.
I literally
have never been
anything but nice
to that girl.
Like, ever. Ever!
Like, get the (bleep)
over it.
It's not fair to you.
Yeah, she's not
meeting you half way.
I feel like these--
there's so many weird
relationships going on
right now.
What about Ben
and Madisson?
He flew all the way
from Texas
and they're not even sleeping
in the same room together.
They're not?
No.
No, they're not.
Yo, Ben!
Are you guys staying
in the same room, or no?
(Ben)
Last night I was out
at a bar until 2:00,
and she went to bed
at 9:00 pm.
But you got two
separate rooms?
(Madisson)
Yeah.
(Ben)
We have two
separate rooms, yeah.
Guys, we're still, like,
figuring things out.
(Chloe)
It's going somewhere.
(Pauly)
Give Ben a chance.
I'm... I'm working
on it, Paul.
You're such a romantic.
(Alex)
Invite him over.
He has been over.
We're good.
(Ben)
Here, Pauly,
we'll send you
some Snaps next time.
Look, they're doing it, okay?
Guys, they (bleep).
Get over it.
Like, shut up.
♪ Scooby Doo Pa Pa ♪
♪ Tú quieres hookah,
pásamelo, vente ♪
pásamelo, vente ♪♪
(fizz hisses)
ll reacting)
(Pauly)
Let's turn this party up!
Get the (bleep) bottles.
I don't want that.
I want a bottle!
♪♪
■=w
Yo, dawg.
Cara and Garrett,
how are you guys?
We're good friends.
Thank you for asking.
Savage Amanda.
I was just asking
how you guys are.
Like, you're here together.
We're good friends.
Thank you for asking.
No, genuinely,
we are good friends.
Thank you for asking.
Good.
I thought that was
a great question.
I did, too, but apparently
they didn't.
I thought it was
a normal, polite question.
And I-- Did I not
answer it politely?
No, you didn't
answer it.
How?
Just wasn't polite,
the way you answered it.
I said "We're good,
thank you."
You don't know
what polite is.
♪♪
Am I the only one that thinks
this is an awkward situation?
a
(Garrett)
It's a little
(bleep) scenario.
Like, it's blown out
of proportion at this point.
(Juliette)
You definitely
added to it, Garrett.
Did I?
Yeah.
Dude, like, you won't
even make
eye contact with me.
'Cause I don't
want you here.
Like, are we not
over this?
It's like,
what is your problem?
Babe...
It's not that--
I don't have, like,
a problem with you personally,
I just don't
want you here.
Okay, and I understand that,
but I want you to understand
I'm not here to interfere
with your relationship.
I don't want my boyfriend's
ex-girlfriend here.
I think that's very fine.
Okay, but, like,
he also (bleep) all
of your other friends.
That was a year ago.
(Cara)
Is that not...
You're really
gonna say that?
You're not even
welcome here.
You're really gonna bring
that up in front of everyone?
Okay...
All right, I'm gonna--
I'm gonna pour everybody
some shots, don't worry.
(Juliette)
You really wanna have
this conversation
and you wanna say
something like that,
it better not be
in front of all these people.
One, two, three...
I'm uncomfortable.
Are you uncomfortable?
ause I'm uncomfortable.
I don't wanna get
in this argument but, like,
ause I'm uncomfortable.
I think you're somewhat
of a smart person.
I would hope.
Garrett, not so sure.
But, you know,
like, you should know
I'm not your biggest fan.
Would I want you here
at this, like,
intimate little trip?
You-- I think
you know that.
What have I done to you,
Juliette, personally?
The fact that
you're even here, Cara,
is proving my point.
Right?
But what have I done to you?
All right.
Okay, I just answered
your question.
Nothing.
Okay, so I'll reiterate
my point.
Say it one more time.
And the fact that
you're even here
is proving my point.
Do I need
to say it again?
Sure, go ahead.
Anyone didn't hear that?
Can you say it again, though?
(laughter)
We heard it.
No, we heard it.
Don't be rude.
I'm--
No, dawg,
I'm not being rude.
I just, like--
You are being rude.
You're just
being sarcastic.
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
You're half-deaf,
half-rude,
mostly stupid.
♪♪
(Juliette)
Coming up...
I miss you
and, like, it sucks.
(Chloe)
She was in her clothes
from last night,
and she goes,
"Well, like,
he did go down
on me."
Once you start smoking,
the consequences
will find you.
Package for James Meiser?
Cigarettes may leave
you with stained teeth,
gum disease and more.
Is your dry skin cream not doing
enough?
Try Eucerin Advanced Repair
cream.
For 48hour dry skin relief...
Goes beyond ceramides with
moisturizing factors
naturally found in skin...
Eucerin Advanced Repair Cream
For healthier looking skin.
IF YOUR WORLD IS FULL OF SAME
OLD, LAME OLD HAMBURGERS...
HIT RESET.
BECAUSE WENDY'S WENT AND
MADE A WHOLE NEW WORLD
WITH THE NEW MADE TO CRAVE MENU.
FEATURING THE PEPPERCORN
MUSHROOM MELT
WITH SAVORY MUSHROOMS.
THE BARBECUE CHEESEBURGER WITH
SWEET AND SMOKY BARBECUE SAUCE,
AND THE S'AWESOME
BACON CHEESEBURGER
WITH BACON FOR DAYS.
CUZ IT'S YOUR WORLD NOW
AND WENDY'S JUST ROCKED IT.
TRY THE THREE NEW HAMBURGERS ON
THE MADE TO CRAVE MENU TODAY.
Searching for a way to
help stop your cold sore?
Only Abreva can
get rid of it in...
...as little as 2 1/2 days
when used at the first sign.
Abreva starts to
work immediately
to block the virus and
protect healthy cells.
Abreva acts on it.
So you can too.
Okay recap.
I was stuck reliving
the same day.
Over and over again.
I thought it
ended the loop.
I went back.
Everything's different.
This time the killer's
coming after all of us.
This is crazy man.
So I'm gonna have to
die over and over
to save all of you?
Yeah.
grunt ]
♪ ♪
Who are you?
This is Dell Cinema technology
with CinemaStream for
less buffering,
CinemaSound for
brilliant clarity,
Experience Dell Cinema
on the XPS 13
with an 8th Gen Intel
Core i7 processor.
♪
I try so hard 8th Gen Intel
to be nice and she just,.
like, "Oh, I hate you,
I hate you, I hate you."
Just a bunch
of negative stuff.
"You're a slut."
And I'm like, okay.
You're gross.
That's not, like,
fair to you.
(Juliette)
I'm sorry, but Cara got
what was coming to her.
She should have known better
than to crash my party.
You know, I'm here
for you, um...
I know.
...if anything goes down, so.
I appreciate you.
I don't think
you should, like,
let the stupid
little bull(bleep)
effect you.
Like, I want you
to loosen up,
have a good time,
forget the whole
Juliette thing.
Like, eu5u■uepa reason.
Okay, so we'll just
have a good time.■y■y Yeah.
You're still
a mystery.
Obviously.
♪♪
♪ Tell me you love me ♪
♪ Tell me
you want me ♪
♪ Tell me you love me ♪
♪ Tell me
you want me ♪
♪ Tell me you love me ♪
♪ Tell me you want me
and I'm the only one ♪♪
♪♪
♪ (singing in Spanish) ♪♪
All the way!
All the way.
(Madisson)
Chloe, did you put
sunscreen on?
Yes.
Good.
I'm exhausted.
(Brandon)
Last night was wild, man.
I wasn't expecting to go,
like, that hard last night.
Can't drink all day
unless you start in the morning.
Speaking of last night,
where's, uh, Cara at?
But last night was fun,
like, with her.
Cara came to my room
this morning.
Mm-hm.
She was in her clothes
from last night.
Oh, boy!
And her makeup.
And she goes, "Well, like,
nothing happened,
but he did
go down on me."
I mean, there you go, bro.
She had fun.
For sure.
The night definitely
ended better thThat's for sure.
She's like, "Well, I'm just
a little worried,
"because I feel like
it's, like,
him, like, compensating
for something else."
She's worried about...
No way!
(Pauly)
To today and maybe
all the way!
(Garrett)
All the way!
(Brandon)
Let's do it.
So, how are you
feeling about
the whole, like, Cara thing
and everything?
This situation,
like, the fact that
she came into this
on Juliette's weekend,
and it...
it a little bit
worries me, like,
what her intentions are.
Well, now it's like
she has to understand, like,
if you're coming here,
like, I can't be, like,
BFFs with you and, like,
of course I can
be nice and stuff,
but, like, I'm here
for Juliette.
And, like-- so she
is my first priority.
When we were having dinner,
like, on the rooftop,
Juliette was, like,
literally, like,
letting Cara see
all her emotions,
and then Cara was just
sitting there
so calm and relaxed...
Yeah.
...and, like, smiling,
and I was like,
"Oh, that must
kill Juliette."
Like, that sucks.
It seemed like Cara
was almost
too vindictive and,
like, patronizing,
and I hope I'm wrong.
My hope is that
she really does
like Garrett,
and that's, like,
why she's here.
I would hope so.
So, how are things?
You glad Ben's here?
I'm really glad.
I'm still going to...
figure out
where we really are.
Yeah.
And, in this group,
it's a little more intense.
It's like, "What are
you guys doing?
"What rooms are
you staying in?
Like, who's sleeping with who?
What's happening?"
Do you feel, like,
pressured, you mean,
to have this conversation,
or are you just, like,
you wanna give it
a little more time
and feel it out?
I-I feel like
my guard is so up
just because
it's been so long
and it hasn't gone
to that level.
I mean, honestly,
if he's not
gonna commit,
I don't think
we have a future.
(Juliette)
Coming up...
You bring a lot of drama.
That'sy thing.
Hey, can you not
touch hands?
(laughing)
■■
♪
Congrats, Kim!
You got your own car,
with your own insurance.
No more driving
that old hand-me-down.
Did you trade it in?
My parents handed it
down to my little brother.
You ready?
Yeah...
■
SURPRISE!
No. Not Beige Betty!
You guys can't
do this to me, seriously?!
My car is like
a rite of passage.
How do you expect
me to drive this?!
Just turn the key...
and yeah, it's just uh...
Some of this...
...it's automatic...
...dual cupholders.
Go with the one that's
here to help life go right.
State Farm.
UGH, ANOTHER DELAY...
BUT... YOU KEEP BOUNCING
LIKE I'M A BOUNCY CASTLE!
OH YEAH!! 5 STOPS, 0 LEAKS.
WE'RE CRUSHING THIS COMMUTE!
HUGGIES LITTLE MOVERS.
OUR BEST FITTING DIAPER
THAT FITS LIKE A HUGG.
HUGG ON.
wwwwEwEww@w@wbwbwáwáñJñJ■g■=a=a■
at Olive Garden.
With all new
Never Entuffed Pastas
starting at just $12.99.
Pick your favorite
stuffed pasta
like our new
Stuffed Ziti Fritta,
with your choice of
sauce and topping...
then try another
delicious combination.
Plus unlimited
salad and breadsticks.
It's all never ending.
Here's to more from
beginning to endless.
All New Never Ending Stuffed
Pastas starting at $12.99.
Only for a limited time,
at Olive Garden.
Why are we doing this?
Why are we doing what?
Using my Old Spice moisturize
with Shea Butter Body Wash...
All I wanted was to use your
body wash
And all I wanted was to have a
Body Wash.
ww■[
KFC's ç=ç=ç=ç=ç=ç=ç=ç=ç=■>
Son of a biscuit.
Well, that worked out.
♪ Survivor... ♪
■■■■
♪ I'm stronger
than I ever used to be ♪♪
Looking good.
(Juliette)
Madisson took Ben
on vacation
and made him sleep
in a separate room,
which is an interesting way
to get a guy to commit.
How's the water?
It's pretty good.
You been having fun?
Yeah, I have!
Me, too.
I'm glad you came.
I've been enjoying
having you.
I mean,
Miami's cool, yeah,
but Madisson's in Miami;
that's why I'm here.
(laughs)
You know that.
You know that's true.
I do know that,
and that's why it was,
like, it's so special
that you have
come out here.
But, I guess I'm just
trying to, like...
figure out
what it means?
'Cause it's...
a little confusing.
I don't just wanna be
the backburner.
I wanna be with you
and you know that.
♪♪
Like, is that
too much to ask for?
No, it's not.
It's been sitting
on my mind lately,
and this Miami trip
was something where
I definitely thought,
hey, like,
what are you doing?
Like, like, um...
♪♪
You wanna be
my girlfriend?
♪♪
Yes.
(chuckles)
I do.
You're so weird.
You're weird!
♪♪
(chuckles)
'Kay.
♪♪
About damn time.
(Juliette)
One more night
to party in Miami.
I'm still super irritated
that Cara's here,
but I'm keeping
my eye on her.
Thank you for having me.
You're welcome.
Oh, look at Garrett...
(Amanda laughs)
I was thinking
the same thing.
No, I didn't know
you were coming, but, like,
I don't have a problem
with you.
Yeah, I get it.
You handled it well,
and, I mean,
I think...
I'm trying to.
Whatever. I can
see everything.
Why are you always
looking at me?
You--
You know, I miss you
and, like, it sucks.
♪♪
Yeah.
We gotta make sure.
We're all good.
We're fine here.
It's so much
girl drama that, like,
I'm just, like,
overwhelmed.
Dude, I don't
deal with that.
I want you to have
a good time.
You know I don't
deal with that.
Like, I don't...
I mean, I just, like...
Hey, can you not
touch hands?
You bring
a lot of drama.
You don't--
That's not my thing.
I still haven't figured out
what this one's up to.
I'm still
trying to learn myself.
(laughs)
Dude, you're gonna be
working on that
for a long time.
■■■■■■ ■■■■a■2óó■
Once you start smoking,
the consequences
will find you.
Package for James Meiser?
Cigarettes may leave
you with stained teeth,
gum disease and more.
I call him "RoboChild."
Hey buddy! What do you wanna
be when you grow up?
I would like to be a
TurboTax Live CPA.
Don't you want to
be something else?
Yeah RoboChild, you
could be anything!
I want to help people get
their best possible refund.
Let's just break
it down, okay?
All TurboTax Live
CPAs
are human beings
with real emotions...
you're never going to be
emotionally complex enough
for that job.
I am sad. HAHAHAHA. HAHAHAHA.
Still perfecting emotion.
TurboTax Live now with
CPA's on Demand.
You know the worst
part about burning fat?
Jitters. They suck.
I mean really suck.
LeanFire XT from Force Factor
utilizes thermovigilance
to burn fat without
caffeine jitters,
helping you unleash
your potential.
Now available
at retailers nationwide.
(rain and thunder)
Need a change of scenery?
KAYAK searches hundreds of
travel sites
and lets you filter by take-off
time,
layovers and more,
so you can be confident
you're getting the right flight
at the best price.
♪ ♪
KAYAK. Search One and Done.
■ú■p■p■
♪♪
When did sleep become something
that requires effort?
With Tempur-Pedic, it doesn't.
Enjoy our most advanced
pressure-relieving material
for the deepest sleep
you've ever had.
This Presidents Day,
save up to $500
on select adjustable
mattress sets.
Find a retailer
at tempurpedic.com.
Searching for a way to
help stop your cold sore?
on select adjustable
mattress sets.
Only Abreva can
get rid of it in...
...as little as 2 1/2 days
when used at the first sign.
Abreva starts to
work immediately
to block the virus and
protect healthy cells.
Abreva acts on it.
So you can too.
Wow,
Right?
Crispy bacon is the best t■■s'!
McDonald's World
Famous Fries...
Featuring Bacon.
Or is the crispy bacon
giving the fries
some street
I'm gonna let
bacon think that.
What's that?
Couldn't hear you over
the bacon-ovation.
McDonald's Classics with
Baco happen to our Classics?me.>
Or to bacon?
Try for yourself
and decide.
■
♪♪
Juliette...
(Juliette)
My whole trip was a disaster,
and at the end of it,
I'm more convinced than ever
that Cara
is here to steal Alex.
Overall, did you have
a good time?
Cara really
ruined it for you?
♪♪
♪ Everybody says
you're no good ♪
♪ You were the best
I ever had... ♪
(Madisson)
I'm so tired.
I'm so dreading
this four-hour
car ride.
I don't know how
I'm gonna do it, honestly.
♪ House in the hills,
all right ♪
♪ Kinda look like
an Apple store ♪
♪ Sober, but that's all right ♪
♪ Kinda Can you pass me
from the nightthat bottle?
Not, like...
(laughter)
He's like...
♪♪
What's up?
What's going on?
Honestly, like,
from what I know
about Cara...