give you two
bucks for the chair.
Two?! That's a Victorian
antique!
All right, how much for the
recliner, then?
Wait wait... how did that get
out here?
That is definitely not for sale!
Is this a yard sale?
If it's in the yard then it's...
for sale.
Oh, here we go.
GEICO. It's easy to switch
and save
on homeowners and renters
insurance.
HAVE A GREAT MONDAY.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> YO, EVERYBODY.
HAPPY MONDAY.
>> HAPPY, HAPPY MONDAY.
>> YEAH.
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE SOME
CUPCAKES TODAY WITH BRIAN ORAKPO
AND MICHAEL GRIFFIN.
WE'RE GOING TO TALK ABOUT THE
SUPER BOWL.
>> WE'RE GOING TO REVEAL WHO
WON.
>> YEAH.
>> WAIT ON THE EDGE OF YOUR
SEATS.
>> WE'RE GOING TO TALK ABOUT DAD
CODE AND WORDS YOU DON'T WANT TO
USE.
WE HAVE A WHOLE BIG SHOW COMING
FOR YOU TODAY.
A LITTLE FASHION, A LITTLE
EVERYTHING AND THE GREATEST
AUDIENCE IN TV.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> FROM THE CROSS ROADS OF THE
WORLD, TIMES SQUARE, NEW YORK
CITY, IT'S "STRAHAN AND SARA."
ESCAPE FOR AN HOUR.
WE ALL NEED IT.
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> BOY, BOY, BOY.
>> OH.
>> HAPPY MONDAY.
HAPPY MONDAY, EVERYBODY.
THANK YOU GUYS FOR JOINING US
TODAY.
>> YEAH.
>> AND YOU KNOW, ON FRIDAY'S
SHOW -- HOW ARE YOU DOING BY THE
WAY?
HOW WAS YOUR WEEKEND?
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> I'M DOING GOOD.
I WAS JUST WITH YOU.
I FEEL LIKE WE JUST SAW EACH
OTHER.
>> CAN'T GET AWAY FROM EACH
>> NOTHING LIKE HANGING OUT FOR
THE SUPER BOWL WITH A HALL OF
FAMER.
>> WAY FUN.
>> MY REAL ESTATE JUST WENT WAY
UP.
>> YOU SAID THAT LIKE WE WERE UP
TO SOMETHING BAD.
>> NO.
GOOD PEOPLE.
>> MY HUSBAND WAS THERE.
NO.
IT'S GETTING WEIRD.
>> MAX, YOU WERE THERE.
ON FRIDAY'S SHOW, WE READ YOU A
TWEET WE GOT FROM LIDS, WHICH
IS THE HAT STORE THAT SELLS HATS
RIGHT ACROSS THE STREET FROM OUR
STUDIO, AND THEY WROTE, LOOK,
MOM.
I'M ON TV.
SHOUTOUT TO @STRAHANANDSARA,
BECAUSE WITH OUR NEW SET, YOU
CAN SEE THE SIGN FOR THEIR
STORE.
IT'S LITERALLY RIGHT ACROSS THE
STREET.
>> FREE ADVERTISING.
>> IT'S FREE, RIGHT?
SO WE PUT UP OUR OWN SIGN TO
BLOCK THEIR SIGN, AND OF COURSE,
WE'LL TAKE IT DOWN JUST AS SOON
AS YOU SEND US "STRAHAN AND
SARA" HATS, RIGHT?
THEY WATCH OUR SHOW.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WE'RE GLAD AND ON FRIDAY THEY
TWEETED, CHALLENGE ACCEPTED.
AND SURE ENOUGH,
8:00 A.M., A MESSAGE ARRIVED AT
THE STUDIO WITH THESE HATS, AND
WE HAVE THE HATS.
BRING THEM IN.
THERE WE GO.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YEAH.
YES.
THAT'S A LITTLE SMALL FOR ME.
>> WAIT.
I THINK I GOT THE WRONG HAT,
MICHAEL.
>> I DON'T HAVE TIME TO ADJUST.
>> WAIT.
THIS IS CUTE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I LIKE THAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT, LIDS?
[ APPLAUSE ]
SINCE YOU LIVE UP TO YOUR WORD,
WE'RE GOING TO LIVE UP TO OUR
WORD.
THERE YOU GO.
ALL THE ADVERTISING YOU WANT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
AND, YOU KNOW, I'LL BE HONEST
WITH YOU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT WORKED.
SO WE SHOULD KEEP USING THIS TO
OUR ADVANTAGE.
>> OH, NO.
I'M AHEAD OF YOU ON THIS ONE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> I LIKE THAT.
I LIKE THE WAY YOU THINK.
PRETTY GOOD.
YEAH.
I NEED A NEW RIDE, ELON.
>> I PULL MY WEIGHT HERE.
>> SO WHAT ELSE IS GOING ON?
WHAT ELSE WE GOT HERE?
SUPER BOWL.
>> NO.
ON FRIDAY I PROMISED THAT WE
WOULD REVEAL THE WINNER OF LAST
NIGHT'S SUPER BOWL.
RIGHT HERE ON OUR SHOW.
THIS IS THE TYPE OF BIG REVEAL
THAT CAN REALLY GENERATE SOME
BUZZ FOR A SHOW LIKE OURS, LIKE,
WHOA.
SARA HAINES AND THAT FELLA THAT
SITS NEXT TO HER ARE REALLY
PLUGGED IN TO WHAT'S HAPPENING
IN AMERICA.
SO THE SUPER BOWL CHAMPION IS --
I ACTUALLY LEFT EARLY.
>> YEAH.
IT WAS 3-3 WHEN YOU LEFT.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW WHO WON, DO
YOU?
DO YOU KNOW WHO WON?
>> I HAVE READ.
IT'S THE --
>> THE PATRIOTS.
>> YEAH.
TOM BRADY.
>> YEAH, THE PATRIOTS.
OH, YOU KNOW.
THE PATRIOTS BEAT THE RAMS 13-3,
AND --
>> THAT WAS THE LOWEST SCORING
GAME, WASN'T IT?
>> THE LOWEST SCORING GAME IN
NFL HISTORY, AND I KNOW YOU'RE A
LITTLE UPSET, BUT FOR A LOT OF
PEOPLE OUT THERE, I THINK IT'S
GREAT THAT BOSTON FINALLY GOT
SOME GOOD SPORTS NEWS.
I MEAN, THEY HAVE BEEN ON A
3 1/2-MONTH CHAMPIONSHIP DROUGHT
EVER SINCE THE RED SOX WON.
THAT CITY DESERVES GOOD NEWS.
>> I KNOW.
I WAS JUST HOPING -- I LIKE TO
CHEER ON THE UNDERDOG.
>> I LIKE CHEERING ON THE
UNDERDOG, BUT I LOOK AT IT
ALSO -- TOM BRADY IS THE
G.O.A.T.
HE'S THE GREATEST QUARTERBACK TO
EVER PLAY THE GAME, BUT FOR
EVERY ONE OF THOSE SIX
CHAMPIONSHIPS, IT IS ONE OF
THOSE GUYS' FIRST TIME WINNING.
>> THAT'S TRUE, MICHAEL.
THAT'S A GOOD WAY TO LOOK AT IT.
>> I LOOK AT THE YOUNG GUYS THAT
NEVER HAD A CHANCE TO WIN.
WE WATCHED THE GAME TOGETHER.
>> OH.
>> IT WAS FUN UNTIL YOU LEFT
EARLY.
>> IT WAS SUCH GOOD FOOD.
WELL, I CAME FOR THE FOOD.
MICHAEL'S FIRST RESPONSE WHEN I
GOT THERE WAS, YOU'RE HERE
EARLY.
I WAS, LIKE, THIS IS WHAT TIME
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO BE HERE AND
I'M ALREADY, LIKE, AT THE
BUFFET.
MAX IS, LIKE, I THINK YOU CAN
HELP YOURSELF BECAUSE YOU'RE
PREGNANT.
I WAS, LIKE, THEY'RE SETTING THE
FOOD UP.
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
TAKE IT WHILE THEY'RE SETTING IT
UP.
IT WAS SO GOOD.
WE POSTED A PICTURE BECAUSE YOU
HIT IT KIND OF HARD ON THE
DESSERT TRAY.
>> I DID.
WHY NOT?
>> THE BUFFET, ONE OF
EVERYTHING.
THE DESSERT, YOU PICK ONE.
YOU TOOK ONE OF EVERYTHING ON
THE DESSERT.
>> IT WAS MAGNOLIA BAKERY, WHICH
IS, LIKE, ADDICTIVE, AND
THEN YOU HAVE THE COOKIES FROM
THE BAKERY WHICH IS EVEN MORE,
AND THEN YOU HAD THE CUPCAKES
AND ALL THAT STUFF WHICH I'M
EXCITED BECAUSE WE HAVE MORE
CUPCAKES TODAY ON THE SHOW.
>> YOU HAD A TEN-DAY CHALLENGE
THAT YOU BROKE, AND I WOULD LIKE
TO CALL YOU OUT ON THIS.
>> I DIDN'T NECESSARILY BREAK
IT.
>> IF MY MATH SERVES ME
CORRECTLY, YOU MADE IT SEVEN
DAYS.
THAT'S A LITTLE SHY OF TEN.
>> I DID SEVEN.
YOU KNOW, TEN DAYS --
J-LO AND ALEX WANTED ME TO DO
TEN DAYS AND I RESPECT THEM, BUT
YOU TWO ARE ON YOUR OWN JOURNEY.
DON'T BRING ME INTO THAT.
I EAT WELL ANYWAY, AND I WORK
OUT AND I DO ALL THAT STUFF I
SEE THEM DO ON INSTAGRAM.
>> HE'S, LIKE, I WORK OUT.
I LOOK GOOD.
I EAT WHAT I WANT.
I WAS, LIKE, OH MY GOSH,
MICHAEL.
>> LITERALLY JUST TRYING TO
JUSTIFY THE FACT THAT I CUT IT
TO SEVEN DAYS INSTEAD OF TEN.
BUT IT WAS SUPER BOWL.
WHO WANTS TO EAT ON THE SUPER
BOWL?
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THAT WAS -- IT WAS A SILLY
MATH PROBLEM.
WE SHOULD NEVER HAVE SIGNED YOU
UP FOR THAT.
>> IT WAS A SILLY -- BUT THINK
ABOUT IT.
WHEN I THINK ABOUT IT AND I
THINK ABOUT THE FOOD THAT WAS
THERE, HOW COULD I NOT HAVE
BROKEN THE CHALLENGE?
>> THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN, LIKE,
NO.
AND DID YOU SEE WHAT THEY DID
END AT THE END OF THEIR
CHALLENGE?
DID YOU WATCH THEIR POST?
>> I SAW.
I SAW WHAT THEY DID.
THAT'S HOW THEY CELEBRATED.
PIZZAS AND YOU NAME IT.
HE HAD IT, BUT I GUARANTEE HE
DIDN'T EAT ALL OF THAT.
>> I KNOW HE DIDN'T.
I BET HE POSED AND HE TOOK,
LIKE, A NIBBLE.
I HAVE DONE THIS BEFORE AND
WALKED AWAY, LIKE, I'M SO
SKINNY.
NOW I CAN JUST SAY MICHAEL'S THE
REAL DEAL BECAUSE HE STUFFED HIS
FACE AND I WITNESSED IT.
>> YEAH.
I WENT IN.
LIKE, IF I'M GOING, I'M GOING
HARD.
I DON'T BACK OFF OF IT, BUT
YEAH.
CONGRATULATIONS TO THEM ON THEIR
TEN DAYS.
I'M HAPPY WITH MY WEEK.
>> YOU MADE IT A POWER SEVEN.
>> BUT I'LL BE GOOD.
I'LL STILL -- I'LL STILL, YOU
KNOW, DIBBLE AND DABBLE IN IT.
>> YOU PROMISED AN AFTER PICTURE
BY THE WAY.
I'M CURIOUS WHAT THE SEVEN-DAY
ABS LOOK LIKE.
>> THERE IS AN AFTER PICTURE.
I FORGOT ABOUT THAT.
I'M SORRY.
>> SO MANY BROKEN PROMISES.
I'M JUST SAYING.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
I AM GOING TO POST AN AFTER
PICTURE.
>> PLEASE DO THAT.
>> TOMORROW, WE'LL HAVE THE
BEFORE AND WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
THE AFTER PICTURE.
>> AND THEY'RE GOING TO BE SO
DIFFERENT IT'S GOING TO INSPIRE
ALL OF YOU GUYS.
>> YOU KNOW.
YOU WAIT UNTIL YOU SEE WHAT'S
UNDER ALL THIS.
JUST MIGHT SURPRISE YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> I CAN'T -- I CAN'T WAIT.
>> BUT THE ONE THING EVERYBODY
TALKED ABOUT OF COURSE, IS
HALFTIME.
THE HALFTIME SHOW, THE
COMMERCIALS.
>> COMMERCIALS, YEAH.
>> AND I LOVE THE COMMERCIALS.
ONE OF MY FAVORITE THINGS TO DO,
AND I KNOW YOU LIKE THEM --
>> THEY'RE BETTER THAN SOME OF
THE GAMES IF WE'RE BEING HONEST.
>> THIS GAME WAS A LITTLE QUIET.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IN THESE
COMMERCIALS, DO YOU REALIZE HOW
MUCH THESE COMMERCIALS COST FOR
30 SECONDS?
>> SO MUCH.
>> $5.25 MILLION.
$5.25 MILLION
JUST FOR 30 SECONDS.
>> AND WE HAND IT OUT FOR FREE
TO LIDS.
I MEAN -- SAMESIES.
>> WHICH IS JUST GIVING IT AWAY.
GIVING IT AWAY.
>> GIVING IT AWAY.
>> BUT I TELL YOU WHAT.
WE HERE WERE SO HAPPY AT THIS
SHOW --
>> YEAH.
HONORED.
>> THAT THE NETWORK DECIDED THAT
THEY WERE GOING TO MAKE US A
SUPER BOWL AD, AND $5.25 MILLION
FOR 30 SECONDS AND HERE'S WHAT
THEY DID FOR US.
>> YO.
>> LUNCHTIME AT 1:00 EASTERN
12:00 CENTRAL AND PACIFIC ON
ABC.
>> ABOUT RIGHT.
THAT'S ABOUT RIGHT.
YOU NOTICED THAT BECAUSE MY NAME
COMES SECOND, WE BARELY GOT SARA
ON THERE BEFORE WE FADED TO
BLACK.
>> WE ONLY HAD FOUR SECONDS.
WE HAD FOUR SECONDS AND YOU KNOW
WHAT?
NONE OF YOU GUYS ARE GETTING
PAID FOR BEING HERE TODAY.
JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT.
HAD TO CUT INTO THE BUDGET.
BUT IT WAS COOL.
>> YOUR COMMERCIAL WAS MY
FAVORITE.
THE FOOTBALL ONE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> THE NFL COMMERCIAL.
>> WELL, THE MICHAEL STRAHAN
COMMERCIAL.
I RECOGNIZED YOU AND KNEW THE
OTHER PEOPLE WERE SUPER
IMPORTANT.
I WAS, LIKE, OH MY GOSH.
ALL THESE FOOTBALL PLAYERS AND
KNEW NONE OF THEM.
IT WAS LIKE "WEDDING CRASHERS".
>> IT WAS ONLY EVERY --
>> GREAT PLAYER EVER.
>> GREAT PLAYER OF COURSE, WHO
IS STILL LIVING AND THE
100-YEAR ANNIVERSARY OF THE NFL.
IT WAS A LOT OF FUN, AND WHEN
YOU ARE THERE FOR ME SHOOTING
IT, I'M AMAZED.
I'M, LIKE, OH MY GOODNESS.
THERE'S JIM BROWN, THERE'S JERRY
RICE, THERE'S DEION SANDERS, AND
JOE MONTANA.
THERE'S MICHAEL SINGLETARY.
THESE ARE ALL GUYS I GREW UP
WATCHING AND THEN
THE WHOLE COMMERCIAL COMES
TOGETHER WITH BAKER MAYFIELD AND
BRADY AND ALL THESE GUYS AS
WELL.
ODELL, AND IT'S, LIKE, WOW.
SAQUON, KEEP ON NAMING GUYS.
>> AND YOU POSTED SOME FUNNY
MOMENTS BEHIND THE SCENES.
I CAN ONLY IMAGINE IT'S PROBABLY
LIKE HERDING CATS WHEN YOU GET
TOGETHER.
JUST HAVING FUN.
>> I WAS DOING MOST OF MY STUFF
WITH PEYTON AND I WAS TRYING TO
GET HIM TO CRACK UP.
SO I POSTED SOME
BEHIND-THE-SCENES SCENES THAT
DIDN'T MAKE IT AND I SAID, YOU
KNOW, PEYTON, YOU HAVE NEVER
LIVED UNTIL YOU GET GRABBED
UNDER THE PILE.
TWO HANDS.
AND THEN HE'S SITTING THERE AND
HE'S, LIKE, YEAH, YEAH.
THEN I GO, YOU GOT TO CLENCH
YOUR BUTT CHEEKS REAL TIGHT.
THAT GOT HIM TO LAUGH.
HE BROKE.
I BROKE HIM.
BUT IT WAS GOOD.
COMMERCIALS ARE ONE OF MY
FAVORITE THINGS.
>> AND THE "GAME OF THRONES"
ONE.
>> YOU'RE A THRONY.
>> IT'S A THRONER.
IT'S A THRONER.
WHO IS A THRONER OUT HERE?
I LOVE THIS WOMAN'S QUIZZICAL
LOOK.
SHE'S, LIKE, WHAT IS THIS?
ANYONE WHO IS OBSESSED
WITH "GAME OF THRONES."
>> I APPRECIATE THE SHOW.
I REALLY DO.
I THINK IT'S SO THEATRICAL, BUT
YOU HAVE TO START WRITING DOWN
NAMES AND WHO IS WITH WHO AND
THE FACTIONS AND I JUST -- MAN.
THIS IS, LIKE, WORK.
>> YOU JUST EVENTUALLY GET IT.
YOU JUST KEEP WATCHING.
>> IT'S KIND OF LIKE MARRIAGE,
HUH?
JUST HANG IN THERE.
>> HANG IN THERE AND HOLD ON.
EVENTUALLY SOME OF IT WILL MAKE
SENSE.
>> WE'RE SO OFF TRACK Y'ALL HAVE
NO IDEA.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW OFF TRACK
WE ARE.
WE HAVE 30 SECONDS.
WHAT YOU GOT?
GIVE ME SOMETHING FOR 30
SECONDS.
>> CAN WE DO THE LITTLE BOY?
EARLIER IN THE WEEK, WE COVERED
A STORY OF A LITTLE BOY WHO
CALLED 911 FOR HELP WITH HIS
HOMEWORK AND THAT WAS SO SWEET.
HERE'S A CALL THAT WAS MADE TO
EMERGENCY SERVICES FAR SLIGHTLY
DIFFERENT REASON.
THE AVON FIRE AND RESCUE IN THE
UK GOT A CALL RECENTLY TO HELP A
YOUNG BOY AND THIS IS WHAT THEY
FOUND.
THAT GUY DARED TO CHAIR A LITTLE
TOO HARD.
THAT YOUNG BOY GOT HIS HEAD
CAUGHT IN THE HOLE OF A POTTY
TRAINING SEAT.
THIS IS WHY PARENTING IS SO
DANGEROUS.
LOOK AT THIS.
>> NO.
THAT'S WHY -- YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT'S JUST BAD PARENTING.
THEY TOLD HIM TO PUT THE WRONG
END IN THAT, YOU KNOW.
COME ON, PARENTS.
I BLAME YOU FOR THAT.
>> THEY DID HAVE TO CUT IT OUT.
THAT POTTY SEAT WILL NEVER BE
THE SAME AGAIN.
AND THAT KID WILL PROBABLY BE IN
DIAPERS UNTIL HE'S 12.
>> I TELL YOU RIGHT NOW.
[ APPLAUSE ]
TO SUM IT UP, I'LL BE HONEST
WITH YOU.
HE'LL NEVER PUT THE SEAT DOWN,
LADIES.
THERE WE GO.
>>> COMING UP, EVERYBODY, IF YOU
ARE A RAMS FAN AND YOU'RE
FEELING BLUE TODAY, WE
UNDERSTAND.
WE HAVE THE PERFECT WAY TO
BRIGHTEN YOUR DAY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
STAY RIGHT THERE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
-Ah, the old crew!
Remember when we all used to go
to the cafeteria
and just chow down midday?
-You mean, like, lunch?
-Come on. Voted
"Most Likely to Help People
Save $668 When They Switch."
-At this school?
-Didn't you get caught
in the laminating machine?
-Ha. [ Sighs ]
-"Box, have a great summer.
Danielle."
Ooh.
Danielle, control yourself.
I'd like to slow it down here
with a special discount
for a special girl.
Danielle, this one's for you.
with a special discount
for a special girl.
It's just a cough.
Yeah right.
And the earth is flat.
Ahhh!!
Treat your cough seriously
with Robitussin CF Max.
Nothing lasts longer
and treats more symptoms for
your cough, cold and flu.
Robitussin. Because
it's never just a cough.
I've just met this,
this incredible woman.
It's quite new so I don't
want to come in too hot.
Sophisticated.
Whoa...yeah.
I mean, in a good way.
What's her name?
Daisy.
Now in 6 bold flavors.
>> TECH: At Safelite AutoGlass
we know that when you're
spending time with the grandkids
every minute counts.
And you don't have time
for a cracked windshield.
That's why we
show you exactly
when we'll be there.
Saving you time, so you
can keep saving the world.
>> KIDS: ♪ Safelite repair,
Safelite replace ♪
Gentle means everything,
so we improved everything.
We used 50% fewer ingredients
Added one handed pumps
And beat the
top safety standards
The new JOHNSON'S®
Choose Gentle
♪♪
Your toothpaste may taste fresh,
but is it removing
enough harmful plaque
from hard to reach areas?
Try Arm & Hammer Complete Care.
Its unique 50% baking soda
formula neutralizes acid
and removes
up to 5X more plaque.
Try Arm & Hammer Complete Care.
♪ ♪
Do you feel the call?
Black Opium.
L'eau de parfum.
Yves Saint Laurent.
(Alarm ringing)
Wake up
to great tasting flavor.
(Alarm stops)
belVita Breakfast Biscuits.
Flavors like
delicious blueberry
or decadent chocolate,
gently baked
in a tasty biscuit.
(Alarm ringing)
belVita Breakfast Biscuits.
It's time to Taste the Day.
I wanted more from
my COPD medicine...
...that's why I've got the Power
of 1-2-3 medicines with TRELEGY.
The only FDA-approved
3-in-1 COPD treatment.
♪ TRELEGY. The Power of 1-2-3 ♪
♪ TRELEGY 1-2-3 TRELEGY ♪
With TRELEGY and the Power of
1-2-3, I'm breathing better.
TRELEGY works 3 ways to...
...open airways,...
...keep them open...
...and reduce inflammation...
...for 24 hours
of better breathing.
TRELEGY won't replace
a rescue inhaler
for sudden breathing problems.
TRELEGY is NOT for asthma.
Tell your doctor if you
have a heart condition
or high blood pressure
before taking it.
Do not take TRELEGY
more than prescribed.
TRELEGY may increase your
risk of thrush, pneumonia,
and osteoporosis.
Call your doctor if worsened
breathing, chest pain,
mouth or tongue swelling,..
...problems urinating, vision
changes, or eye pain occur.
Think your COPD
medicine is doing enough?
Maybe you should think again.
Ask your doctor about once-daily
TRELEGY and the
Power of 1-2-3.
♪ TRELEGY 1-2-3 ♪
Save at TRELEGY.com.
Olay Ultra Moisture Body Wash
Gives skin the nourishment it
needs
And keeps it there longer with
lock-in moisture technology.
Skin is petal smooth.
Because your best skin starts
with Olay.
>>> OKAY.
SO WE GOT A NEW NAME.
>> I'M SARA.
HE'S STRAHAN.
>> IF YOU DIDN'T KNOW.
>> BUT ONE LOYAL VIEWER HAD
SOMETHING TO SAY.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO WANT TO SEE
THIS.
THIS GUY LOOKS FAMILIAR.
>> CONGRATS ON THE SHOW,
"STRAHAN AND SARA." I WANT TO
SAY I THINK THE NAME SUCKS
BECAUSE IT HAS STRAHAN FIRST.
IT SHOULD BE SARA FIRST.
SARA AND STRAHAN.
>> THE ROCK, THE DOOR IS
UNLOCKED.
>> AND THIS WEEK, LOOK WHO'S
HANGING OUT.
MARIE KONDO AND WILL ARNETT.
>> DON'T WE WANT TO JUST HAVE
SOME FUN?
>> "STRAHAN AND SARA."
>> WE GOT IT ALL.
>> LUNCHTIME ON ABC.
>>> WELCOME BACK.
THERE WERE A LOT OF COMMERCIALS
DURING THE SUPER BOWL LAST
NIGHT, AND FOR THOSE WATCHING IN
HOUSTON, THIS AWESOME AD
DEFINITELY CAUGHT YOUR
ATTENTION.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> THIS IS SMASH THERAPY IN
NORTH SPRING, TEXAS.
IT'S A PLACE TO FIND INNER
PEACE.
♪
>> OUR SPONSOR, HEAD & SHOULDERS
DECIDED TO CELEBRATE UNIQUE
BUSINESSES LIKE JENNIFER'S
HOUSTON-BASED SMASH THERAPY AS
PART OF THEIR NEW CAMPAIGN
CHAMPIONING PEOPLE WHO ARE
HEADSTRONG AND OVERCOME DOUBT
AND FEAR TO START SUCCESSFUL
LOCAL BUSINESSES.
HOW COOL WAS THAT?
>> OH MY GOD.
I'M JUST, LIKE, TAKING IT IN ALL
RIGHT NOW.
>> I HEARD YOU SAY ON "GMA" THAT
THIS WAS, LIKE, REALLY THE FIRST
TIME IT WAS HITTING YOU.
>> YEAH.
YEAH.
JUST, LIKE, THIS MORNING I WAS,
LIKE, WAS I REALLY ON THE SUPER
BOWL?
THAT'S SO COOL.
>> THAT'S BEYOND COOL.
THAT'S, LIKE, THE COOLEST THING
EVER.
>> I KNOW.
I'M, LIKE, SWEATING.
>> NOW YOU DECIDED TO OPEN A
PLACE WHERE PEOPLE CAN SMASH
THINGS AND YOU THOUGHT IT WOULD
NEVER WORK.
>> OH, NO.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD WORK.
THEY DIDN'T THINK IT WOULD WORK.
I WAS, LIKE, LET'S STAY
HEADSTRONG HERE, AND THIS IS
WHAT I WANT TO DO, AND I'M GOING
TO DO IT.
EVERYBODY ELSE, THEY'RE GOING TO
FALL IN LINE.
>> AND THEY DID.
>> THEY DID, AND THEY WILL.
>> WHAT KEPT YOU MOTIVATED?
>> I JUST HAD A BABY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I HAD JUST HAD MY FIRST BABY AND
I WAS, LIKE, I WANT TO OPEN A
BUSINESS.
I DID ALL THESE THINGS FOR ALL
THESE PEOPLE AND I THOUGHT I WAS
GOING TO BE ABLE TO, YOU KNOW,
MAKE MY SCHEDULE, AND I WANTED
TO HELP PEOPLE.
THAT'S WHAT I DO ALREADY.
I WORK IN A MENTAL HEALTH
HOSPITAL, AND I WAS, LIKE,
EVERYBODY NEEDS A BREAK AND
LET'S JUST DO THIS SO PEOPLE
DON'T FEEL LIKE, HEY.
I'M CRAZY.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
>> I LIKE YOUR FORM OF THERAPY.
WE NEED MORE OF YOU, CLOSER TO
NEW YORK.
MICHAEL IS OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW
WITH A FEW PEOPLE WHO COULD USE
SOME SMASH THERAPY.
>> YEAH, YOU KNOW, I KNOW WHAT
IT FEELS LIKE TO WIN THE
CHAMPIONSHIP, BUT I ALSO KNOW
WHAT IT FEELS LIKE WHEN YOUR
TEAM DOESN'T BECAUSE I LOST ONE
AS WELL.
I'M HERE WITH ARMAND AND VINCE
AND THEY'RE FEELING THE PAIN
BECAUSE THEIR RAMS WERE THE
LOSING TEAM LAST NIGHT.
SO WE DECIDED THERE IS NO BETTER
WAY TO HELP THEM OUT THAN WITH A
LITTLE SMASH THERAPY.
THIS IS WHAT YOU GUYS NEEDED.
YOU NEED THIS, RIGHT?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> WE'RE NOT GOING TO HOLD BACK
ON IT.
WE'RE GOING TO GET READY.
ARMAND, YOU'RE FIRST.
WE'RE GOING TO PUT YOU IN THE
SMASH TANK VEHICLE.
HOP IN, MY FRIEND.
YOU HAVE 15 SECONDS TO GO FOR IT
AND TAKE OUT ALL THAT
FRUSTRATION ON YOUR RAMS LOSS.
PUT YOUR MASK DOWN.
YOU READY?
15 SECONDS.
GO.
GET IT OUT.
OH, HE'S MAD.
OH.
OH, THE HAMMERS AND HE'S GOING
AT IT.
OH.
HOLD UP, BUD.
OKAY.
REAL QUICK, HOW DID THAT FEEL?
>> IT FELT AMAZING.
>> AMAZING?
>> AMAZING.
>> STILL NOT ENOUGH TO GET OVER
THE LOSS, BUT IT'S A LITTLE
SOMETHING WE CAN DO FOR YOU.
>> OH YEAH.
>> VINCE, YOU'RE UP.
HOW TALL ARE YOU?
>> 6'6".
>> IF YOU WOULD HAVE PLAYED LAST
NIGHT, THEY MAY HAVE WON.
GO AHEAD AND HOP IN THERE,
VINCE.
WE HAVE BATS IN HERE.
WE HAVE HAMMERS AND WE HAVE GOT
EVERYTHING.
15 SECONDS, VINCE.
TAKE OUT THAT AGGRESSION.
CLOSE THAT DOOR, MAN.
HERE WE GO.
VINCE.
READY, GO.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
OH, BOY.
OKAY.
LET VINCE OUT OF THERE, MAN.
HE'S -- VINCE, I FEEL IS
DANGEROUS.
COME ON OUT, MAN.
TELL YOU RIGHT NOW, I DON'T WANT
TO MAKE YOU MAD AT A FAMILY
HOLIDAY PARTY.
YOU'LL TEAR UP THE WHOLE HOUSE.
HOW DID IT FEEL?
>> FELT GREAT.
>> REALLY?
>> WAITED 17 YEARS FOR BRADY TO
GET ANOTHER CHOICE AND THEY
SCORED 3 POINTS, BUT THAT FEELS
GOOD.
>> THE RAMS ARE YOUNG AND THEY
HAVE A GOOD TEAM.
THEY'LL BE BACK.
HOPEFULLY YOU WON'T BE IN OUR
SMASH TANK.
>> SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
>> AND I WANT TO THANK YOU SO
MUCH.
YOU KNOW, SARA.
JENNIFER WHO IS UP THERE WITH
YOU, WE WENT TO THE SAME
COLLEGE, SAME SCHOOL.
I WANTED TO SAY HEY, ALUMNI.
>> HEY.
>> YOU GUYS ARE 20 YEARS APART.
THAT WAS AN IMPORTANT
DISTINCTION.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE,
JENNIFER.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WE WANT TO THANK OUR SPONSOR,
HEAD & SHOULDERS FOR THAT
SEGMENT.
WE'LL BE BACK WITH ONE OF THE
STARS FROM "AMERICAN HOUSEWIFE,"
MEG DONNELLY.
♪
This is Smash Therapy in North
Spring, Texas.
It's a place to find inner
peace.
People said it wouldn't work.
A place where you smash things?
That's stupid.
But Jennifer is a Headstrong
Business owner.
So give me a call.
I'll get you smashing in no
time.
Head & Shoulders made this Super
Bowl commercial
so Jennifer could stay
Headstrong.
Woman:
This is your wake-up call.
If you have moderate to
severe rheumatoid arthritis,
month after month,
the clock is ticking
on irreversible joint damage.
Ongoing pain and stiffness
are signs of joint erosion.
HUMIRA can help stop the clock.
Prescribed for 15 years,
HUMIRA targets and blocks
a source of inflammation
that contributes
to joint pain
and irreversible damage.
VO: HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes
fatal infections
including tuberculosis,
and cancers, including
lymphoma, have happened,
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal
infections are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Woman:
Help stop the clock
on further irreversible
joint damage.
Talk to your rheumatologist.
Right here. Right now.
HUMIRA.
♪Your hunger's so bad that this
pasta looks good.♪
♪Here comes a 90, 10, 1 crew
with a Protein One bar for you.♪
♪Protein One♪
♪For all your snack
emergencies.♪
♪Protein One♪
90 calories
10 grams of protein
1 gram of sugar
♪ ♪
Do you feel the call?
Black Opium.
L'eau de parfum.
Yves Saint Laurent.
No more excuses
with Cologuard.
We all make excuses for the
things we don't want to do.
But when it comes to
colon cancer screening...
I'm not doin' that.
I eat plenty of kale.
Ahem, as I was saying...
...with Cologuard,
you don't need an excuse...
All that prep?
No thanks.
That drink tastes horrible!
But...there's no
prep with Cologuard...
I can't take the
time off work.
Who has two days?
And I feel fine -
no symptoms!
Everybody, listen!
All you need is a
trip to the bathroom.
If you're 50 or older
and at average risk,
Cologuard is the
noninvasive option
that finds 92%
of colon cancers.
You just get the
kit in the mail,
go to the bathroom,
collect your sample,
then ship it to the lab!
This is your year!
Own it!
Cologuard is not right
for everyone.
It is not for high
risk individuals,
including those with a
history of colon cancer
or precancer, IBD, certain
hereditary cancer syndromes,
or a family history
of colon cancer.
Ask your doctor if Cologuard
is right for you.
Covered by Medicare and
most major insurers.
>>> GUESS WHAT, MRS. OTTO?
YOU ARE NOW LOOKING AT THE TWO
LEADS OF "LITTLE SHOP OF
HORRORS."
>> OH MY GOD.
HONEY, THAT IS AWESOME.
BUT WEREN'T YOU JUST THE
UNDERSTUDY?
>> I WAS, BUT THEN JULIE HAD A
BREAKDOWN FROM ALL THE PRESSURE
SO SHE SPRAY PAINTED DIRTY WORDS
ON THE DRAMA TEACHER'S CAR.
>> THAT WAS MEG DONNELLY IN THE
HIT SHOW, "AMERICAN HOUSEWIFE,"
AND LUCKY FOR US, MEG IS ALSO
OUR VERY OWN RESIDENT TEEN
EXPERT.
>> YES, SHE IS.
NOW MEG IS HERE TO HELP --
YOU'RE HERE TO HELP US AS WELL
AS PARENTS EVERYWHERE UNDERSTAND
JUST WHAT THE HECK THEIR TEENS
ARE TALKING ABOUT IN A SEGMENT
WE'RE CALLING "DECODE YOUR
TEEN."
>> YES.
DECODE YOUR TEEN.
>> IT'S A THING.
WE WANT TO MAKE THIS CLEAR.
THESE ARE WORDS US PARENTS CAN
LEARN, BUT YOU SHOULD NOT --
SHOULD NOT ATTEMPT TO USE THEM
YOURSELF.
>> NO.
>> PARENTS.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, MEG?
>> YES.
THAT'S VERY RIGHT.
MY DAD USES THE WORD, LIT, AND
IT'S THE MOST EMBARRASSING THING
EVER.
PLEASE DON'T.
PLEASE DON'T, OKAY?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> OKAY.
>> FIRST UP, WE'RE GOING TO
START OUT WITH THE TEA.
>> THE TEA.
DOES ANYONE HAVE ANY GUESSES FOR
WHAT THE TEA IS?
>> I KNOW WHAT THE TEA IS.
>> IS IT A SPECIAL DRINK?
>> NO.
>> LIKE SPECIAL OTHER THAN TEA.
>> I THINK I KNOW THIS ONE.
>> THE TEA IS ANOTHER WORD FOR
GOSSIP.
SO, YOU KNOW, SPILL THE TEA.
DO YOU HAVE SOME HOT TEA, WHAT'S
THE TEA?
WHEN YOU TELL GOSSIP, YOU HAVE A
CUP OF TEA AND YOU'RE, LIKE,
THAT.
THAT'S KIND OF WHAT IT IS.
>> DO YOU GUYS EVEN DRINK TEA?
>> NOT REALLY.
WE DRINK COFFEE.
>> THEY SPILL TEA.
THEY DON'T DRINK IT.
THAT'S WHY YOU SHOULDN'T USE IT.
YOU SHOULDN'T USE IT.
>> I'M STILL VERY YOUNG,
MICHAEL.
>> NEXT UP.
NEXT UP IS SNACK.
>> SNACK.
>> OH, I KNOW THIS ONE.
>> YOU DO?
>> IS IT, LIKE, A HOT PERSON?
YOU'RE, LIKE, OH, HE'S A SNACK.
>> YES, EXACTLY.
YEAH.
WHEN SOMEONE'S REALLY
ATTRACTIVE, YOU'RE, LIKE, OH.
THAT'S A SNACK.
YOU KNOW?
>> IF YOU ARE LOOKING AT
MICHAEL, YOU'RE, LIKE, IT'S A
WHOLE VENDING MACHINE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> DANG.
OKAY.
>> YOU STILL CAN'T USE THE WORD,
BUT YOU MAY HAVE CREATED A NEW
ONE.
>> VENDING MACHINE.
>> I'M SUCH A TEEN.
NEXT IS CANCELED.
>> CANCELED.
IT'S KIND OF SELF-EXPLANATORY.
WHEN SOMEONE DOES REALLY BAD,
THEY'RE CANCELED.
>> A FRIEND, A BOO, ANYTHING?
>> THEY'RE JUST CANCELED.
CANCELED OUT OF YOUR LIFE.
LIKE --
>> YOU TELL THEM THEY'RE
CANCELED OR CAN YOU GHOST?
>> YOU CAN GHOST IF YOU WANT TO,
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER.
THEY'RE JUST CANCELED.
>> DON'T RENEW YOUR
SUBSCRIPTION.
IT'S OVER.
>> THIS WHOLE SEGMENT IS ABOUT
STUFF NOT TO USE.
YOU USING GHOST WAS NO.
DON'T DO IT.
YOU'RE ADDING WORDS.
>> I'M ONE OF THOSE COOL MOMS.
>> YEAH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY HAS AN OPINION OF
THEMSELVES.
HERE'S THE NEXT ONE WE GOT.
THIRST TRAP.
>> I DON'T KNOW THIS ONE.
>> DOES ANYONE HAVE A GUESS FOR
THIS ONE?
>> I KNOW WHAT A THIRST TRAP IS.
>> IT'S A PICTURE THAT YOU POST
PROBABLY AT THE BEACH OR MAYBE
IN THE GYM THAT YOU WANT PEOPLE
TO, LIKE, PAY ATTENTION TO YOU,
LIKE, GET THOSE DMs, YOU KNOW,
GOING.
>> YOU WANT SOMEONE TO SLIP INTO
YOUR DMs.
>> IT'S JUST A PICTURE THAT YOU
LOOK REALLY GOOD IN THAT YOU
POST.
>> YOU MAKE SOMEBODY THIRSTY FOR
YOU.
>> EXACTLY.
EXACTLY, YOU KNOW, LIKE -- JUST
GOT NEW EARRINGS.
>> IS IT, LIKE, A SELFIE?
I CAN'T GET MY GOODS PARTS WITH
A SELFIE.
>> I MEAN, IT CAN BE A SELFIE.
>> ARE YOU THIRSTY?
[ APPLAUSE ]
SOMEONE ELSE CAN TAKE A THIRST
TRAP.
>> OF COURSE.
>> I WANT TO USE IT PROPERLY.
OUR LAST ONE IS GLOW UP.
>> I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THIS IS.
>> IS THAT WHEN YOUR SOCIAL
MEDIA GOES CRAZY AND YOU'RE,
LIKE, IT'S GLOWING UP?
>> NO.
IT'S, LIKE --
>> I'M, LIKE, DAD RIGHT NOW.
>> BROKE ON THAT ONE.
WHAT IS GLOW UP?
>> IT'S KIND OF A
TRANSFORMATION.
SO SOME PEOPLE POST PICTURES OF,
LIKE, MIDDLE SCHOOL AND THEN
THEM NOW AND IT'S, LIKE, I
GLOWED UP.
I LOOK BETTER NOW.
YOU KNOW?
>> LIKE A METAMORPHOSIS OF
SORTS?
>> EXACTLY.
YEAH.
SURE.
>> LIKE INTERCHANGEABLE.
>> TOTALLY.
>> YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
THIS IS ONE OF THE MOST
INFORMATIVE SEGMENTS WE HAVE
EVER HAD.
>> WE NEED UP.
WE NEED YOU.
>> WE'RE GOING TO DO THESE.
WE HAVE THESE NEW TEEN PHRASES
THAT WE HAVE RIGHT HERE AND OUR
"STRAHAN AND SARA" RESIDENT DAD,
JACK, IS IN THE HOUSE.
DAD'S GOING TO GIVE THEM A TRY.
WHAT'S UP, JACK?
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WELL, FIRST OF ALL, MEG, SO
FAR THIS SEGMENT IS REALLY LIT.
SO I WAS JUST OUTSIDE CLEANING
OUT THE SHOW GUTTERS BECAUSE DAD
RULE NUMBER ONE, NEVER HAVE A
DIRTY GUTTER, RIGHT?
>> THE WEIRD THING IS WE DON'T
HAVE GUTTERS HERE AT THE SHOW.
BUT GO AHEAD.
>> I'M GOING TO TRY OUT ALL
THESE PHRASES.
I'M GOING TO GET THIS RIGHT.
OKAY.
I'M GOING TO GIVE IT THE OLD
COLLEGE TRY AS WE SAY.
OKAY.
I'M ABOUT TO SPILL THE TEA.
I WAS FEELING PRETTY CANCELED
AROUND THE WIFE LATELY, BUT I
HAVE BEEN HITTING THE GYM SO,
THE GLOW UP IS REAL.
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT, I'LL BE
DEVELOPING SOME PHOTOS AT THE
DRUGSTORE TO SEND THEM THIRST
TRAPS BECAUSE I'M GOING TO BE A
REAL SNACK.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
YOU'RE FIRED.
>> WHAT?
>> YOU'RE FIRED.
>> HONEY, WE'RE NOT GOING TO BE
ABLE TO AFFORD THE BREAKFAST.
I'M SORRY.
>> THANK YOU TO OUR RESIDENT
DAD, JACK.
AND A BIG THANK YOU -- COME ON
OVER HERE, MEG.
COME ON, MEG.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU TO MEG.
"AMERICAN HOUSEWIFE" HAS NEW
EPISODES AT A NEW TIME ON
TUESDAYS AT 8:00 P.M. ON ABC.
MAKE SURE YOU CHECK IT OUT.
COMING UP, WE'RE GOING TO MAKE
CUPCAKES.
>> CUPCAKES.
>> WITH NFL SUPERSTARS.
IT DOESN'T GET ANY BETTER THAN
THAT.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
Let's see, ALEVE is
proven better on pain
than Tylenol Extra Strength.
And last longer
with fewer pills.
So why am I still
thinking about this?
I'll take Aleve.
ALEVE.
Proven better on pain.
This time, it's his turn.
You have 4.3 minutes
to yourself.
This calls for a
taste of cheesecake.
Philadelphia Cheesecake Cups.
Rich, creamy cheesecake
with real strawberries.
Find them with the
refrigerated desserts.
(VO) Combine the right things.
And something amazing happens.
That's our inspiration for Fancy
Feast Medleys.
Wild Salmon Primavera.
Tastes amazing.
Also in pate.
Fancy Feast Medleys.
IF YOU FEEL LIKE YOU SPEND
TOO MUCH TIME IN THE BATHROOM
WITH RECURRING
CONSTIPATION AND BELLY PAIN
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
AND SAY YESSS! TO LINZESS.
♪ ♪ ♪
YESSS!
LINZESS TREATS ADULTS WITH IBS
WITH CONSTIPATION
OR CHRONIC CONSTIPATION.
LINZESS CAN HELP RELIEVE
YOUR BELLY PAIN
AND LETS YOU HAVE MORE FREQUENT
AND COMPLETE BOWEL MOVEMENTS.
LINZESS IS NOT A LAXATIVE.
IT WORKS DIFFERENTLY TO
HELP YOU GET AHEAD OF YOUR
RECURRING CONSTIPATION
AND BELLY PAIN.
DO NOT GIVE LINZESS
TO CHILDREN LESS THAN 6,
AND IT SHOULD NOT BE GIVEN TO
CHILDREN 6 TO LESS THAN 18,
IT MAY HARM THEM.
DO NOT TAKE LINZESS IF
YOU HAVE A BOWEL BLOCKAGE.
GET IMMEDIATE HELP
IF YOU DEVELOP
UNUSUAL OR SEVERE STOMACH PAIN,
ESPECIALLY WITH
BLOODY OR BLACK STOOLS.
THE MOST COMMON SIDE EFFECT IS
DIARRHEA, SOMETIMES SEVERE.
IF IT'S SEVERE,
STOP TAKING LINZESS AND
CALL YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
OTHER SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE GAS,
STOMACH-AREA PAIN, AND SWELLING.
SO SAY YESSS!
TO HELP FOR
RECURRING CONSTIPATION.
YESSS! TO HELP FOR BELLY PAIN.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
AND SAY YESSS! LINZESS.
Stronger is blasting
her tumors...
without risking her bones.
It's training her
good cells...
to fight the bad guys.
Stronger is less pain...
new hope...
more fight.
It's doing everything
in your power...
and everything in ours.
Stronger, is changing even
faster than they do.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.
What would she do without me?
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> WELCOME BACK.
MEG AND I ARE TAKING A BREAK.
WE'RE GOING TO SIT BACK AND LET
THESE THREE BURLY MEN MAKE US
CUPCAKES.
THE WAY IT ALWAYS SHOULD HAVE
BEEN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
PLEASE WELCOME FORMER NFL PRO
BOWLERS BRIAN ORAKPO AND MICHAEL
GRIFFIN.
>> I HAVE GOT TO SAY.
YOU THOUGHT THESE GUYS WERE
GREAT ALL PRO FOOTBALL PLAYERS.
THEY'RE BETTER CUPCAKE MAKERS BY
THE WAY.
I NEVER THOUGHT WE WOULD BE
HANGING OUT WITH APRONS ON
NATIONAL TV MAKING CUPCAKES.
WHAT WE GOING TO DO, MICHAEL?
WHAT WE GOT?
>> WE'RE GOING TO START -- I'M
THE HEAD BAKER RIGHT HERE.
I'M GOING TO HAVE YOU HELP ME
RIGHT HERE.
>> YOU'RE A SOUS CHEF, MICHAEL.
>> PUT THAT IN THERE RIGHT NOW.
>> WHAT ARE WE MAKING?
BE WE'RE MAKING A WEDDING CAKE.
IT'S A WHITE CAKE, BUT IT'S MY
FAVORITE.
>> MAKE YOU WANT TO GET MARRIED.
OKAY.
I GOT THE EGGS?
>> THAT'S THE OIL.
I'M GOING TO PUT THE OIL IN, AND
PUT THIS OVER THERE, AND PUT
THAT VANILLA RIGHT THERE.
>> VANILLA.
>> A VANILLA RIGHT THERE, WE'LL
KNOCK THIS OUT REAL QUICK.
>> HOW ARE YOU DOING, LADIES?
>> SO FAR, NOT A LOT OF ROOM FOR
ERROR.
>> THIS IS THE TRICKY PART.
>> MY VANILLA GOT ON IT.
>> HAVE YOU ALWAYS BAKED OR IS
THIS A NEW HOBBY?
>> I BAKED.
IF YOU LOOK RIGHT HERE, I BURNED
MYSELF THE LAST TIME.
>> IT'S LAST MINUTE, HONESTLY.
WE KIND OF PERFECTED IT.
>> I HAVE VISIONS OF YOU COMING
FROM FOOTBALL PRACTICE AND
HITTING THE KITCHEN HARD.
>> YOU HAVE TO PUT THE FLOUR IN
THERE SLOW.
REAL SLOW.
>> I DID IT MY FIRST TIME AND IT
WAS SMOKEY.
>> SMOKEY.
>> CLEANUP ON AISLE ONE.
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> THAT IS SOUR CREAM RIGHT
THERE.
IT BRINGS THAT TEXTURE, AND
GIVES IT FLAVOR.
MIKE, YOU BE IN THE KITCHEN OR
NO?
>> WHY YOU GOING TO CALL A
BROTHER OUT LIKE THAT?
I CAN BURN, MAN.
I CAN BURN IT.
>> JUST MAKING SURE WE'RE GOOD.
>> TURN THAT THING UP.
>> WE'RE GOING TO WHIP IT IN
THERE, BUT NOW WE'RE GOING TO DO
IT.
WHEN IT ALL GETS GOOD, IT TURNS
INTO THIS RIGHT HERE.
TURNS RIGHT HERE.
>> IT TURNS INTO THIS, AND THIS
IS WHERE WE START BAKING NOW.
YOU GET A SCOOP.
>> MAKE SURE YOU COME TO THE
SIDE.
YOU GOT TOO MUCH.
>> ARE WE SUPPOSED TO BE DOING
SOMETHING DOWN HERE?
>> I LIKE MY CUPCAKES FULL.
>> MAKE SURE THE SCOOP IS LIKE
YOU SAID, AT THE LINE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU SCARED OF?
>> I AM A LITTLE TERRIFIED OF
THIS.
>> I GOT YOU.
>> VERY SIMPLE.
THERE YOU GO.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> TRYING TO FEED A LOT OF
PEOPLE AND YOU GOT TO GET IN
THERE AND YOU GOT TO GET QUICK.
>> LET'S GET TO THIS.
>> I'M MAKING THESE CUPCAKES.
THAT ONE DON'T COUNT.
>> 325 IN THE OVEN.
>> 20 TO 22 MINUTES.
>> 20 TO 22?
>> LET'S GET TO THE DECORATING.
I'M THE HEAD DECORATOR NOW.
[ APPLAUSE ]
NOW MIKE, WE'RE TALLER GUYS.
WHAT I LIKE TO DO IN MY
KITCHEN --
>> GET LOW.
>> YOU GOT TO GET LOW LIKE IN A
STANCE.
THERE YOU GO.
SQUEEZE IT.
LITERALLY WE DO A GIGI SWIRL.
>> WHAT IS A GIGI SWIRL?
>> ALL YOU CAN DO IS EITHER SIDE
TO SIDE AND PLOP --
>> AMAZING WORK.
>> OR YOU CAN DO, LIKE --
>> I WANT TO SEE YOU PLOP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> WE DO THAT.
>> THAT'S A DISCOUNTED CUPCAKE
RIGHT THERE.
>> THIS IS DISCOUNTED THOUGH.
>> THAT'S A DISCOUNT TOO?
>> JUST KEEP PLAYING WITH IT.
>> HEY.
>> CHARGE THEM MORE.
CHARGE THEM MORE THEIR THAT ONE.
THAT AIN'T NO DISCOUNT.
>> IS THIS OKAY?
>> THAT'S GOOD.
>> THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
>> PUT SOME SPRINKLES ON IT.
>> NOW WE'RE GOING TO PUT
SPRINKLES ON IT.
>> THAT ONE'S PROBABLY THE
DISCOUNTED ONE, RIGHT?
>> PUT YOUR SPRINKLES ON IT.
>> YOU'RE MESSING ALL UP THE
SPRINKLES.
I NEED A JOB BECAUSE I DROP
THEM.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> MICHAEL IS THE DECORATION
MAN.
WHAT PART OF YOUR FOOTBALL
CAREERS HELPED YOU WITH THIS?
>> JUST THE HARD WORK AND THE
DEDICATION.
ONE THING WHEN WE OPENED UP THIS
BUSINESS, WE MADE SURE OUR
SIGNIFICANT OTHERS, AND OUR
WIVES COULD NOT BE APART OF
THIS.
WE WANTED TO MAKE SURE WE CAN
ALWAYS BE THERE.
THIS IS OUR FIRST TIME THAT NOT
ALL THREE OF US ARE IN AUSTIN
THERE AT THE LOCATION, BUT
AGAIN, WE JUST MADE SURE THIS IS
SOMETHING WE'RE GOING TO BE ON
BOARD.
>> DO YOU HAVE A MINIMUM OF HOW
MANY YOU CAN EAT A DAY?
>> IT'S HARD.
WHEN YOU ARE WORKING, IT'S HARD.
>> I TRY TO STAY AWAY FROM IT,
BUT I CAN LITERALLY GO A DOZEN
IF I WANT TO.
>> WOW.
>> BUT I TRY.
NOT DURING SEASON THOUGH.
NOT DURING SEASON.
>> THE CUPCAKES ARE GOOD
CUPCAKES, MAN.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
I LOVE THE FACT THAT YOU WENT
FOR THE NFL.
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR
CUPCAKE, MICHAEL?
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
IT'S ON THE DISCOUNTED RACK.
>> MAN DOWN.
MAN DOWN.
CLEANUP ON AISLE ONE.
>> IT'S TOP HEAVY.
WHAT CAN I SAY?
YOU GUYS WENT INTO BUSINESS AND
YOU WENT TO COLLEGE TOGETHER.
YOU PLAYED TOGETHER, AND NOW
YOU'RE STICKING TOGETHER IN
BUSINESS.
IT'S GREAT TO SEE THAT.
>> NOW YOU FROST TOGETHER.
>> THAT BROTHERHOOD, MAN.
NOW YOU FROST TOGETHER.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
THIS IS THE PERFECT CUPCAKE, AND
IF YOU ARE IN THE AUSTIN AREA,
MAKE SURE YOU CHECK OUT GIGI'S
CUPCAKES AND HANG OUT WITH THESE
TWO, AND THEY WILL PUT THEM
TOGETHER FOR YOU.
>>> COMING UP, WE HAVE FASHION
TRENDS THAT GO FOR YOU AT ANY
AGE.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
MOVING?
THAT'S HARDER NOW BECAUSE
OF PSORIATIC ARTHRITIS.
BUT YOU'RE STILL MOVED
BY MOMENTS LIKE THIS.
DON'T LET PSORIATIC
ARTHRITIS TAKE THEM AWAY.
TALTZ REDUCES JOINT
PAIN AND STIFFNESS
AND HELPS STOP THE
PROGRESSION OF JOINT DAMAGE.
FOR PEOPLE WITH MODERATE
TO SEVERE PSORIASIS,
90% SAW SIGNIFICANT IMPROVEMENT.
TALTZ EVEN GIVES YOU A CHANCE
AT COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
DON'T USE IF YOU'RE
ALLERGIC TO TALTZ.
BEFORE STARTING, YOU SHOULD
BE CHECKED FOR TUBERCULOSIS.
TALTZ MAY INCREASE
RISK OF INFECTIONS
AND LOWER YOUR
ABILITY TO FIGHT THEM.
TELL YOUR
DOCTOR IF YOU
HAVE AN
INFECTION,
SYMPTOMS,
OR RECEIVED A
VACCINE OR PLAN TO.
INFLAMMATORY BOWEL DISEASE
CAN HAPPEN WITH TALTZ,
INCLUDING WORSENING OF SYMPTOMS.
SERIOUS ALLERGIC
REACTIONS CAN OCCUR.
FOR ALL THE THINGS
THAT MOVE YOU.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT TALTZ.
I've just met this,
this incredible woman.
It's quite new so I don't
want to come in too hot.
Sophisticated.
Whoa...yeah.
I mean, in a good way.
What's her name?
Daisy.
Now in 6 bold flavors.
Sometimes, the pressures of
today's world can make it tough
to take care
of yourself.
But Nature's Bounty
has innovative ways
to help you
maintain balance
and help keep you
active and well-rested.
Because hey,
tomorrow's
coming up fast.
Nature's Bounty.
Because you're
better off healthy.
This is Charlie not coughing
because he took Delsym 12-hour.
Nature's Bounty.
And this is Charlie still not
coughing
while trying his hardest not to
wake Zeus.
Delsym 12-hour.
Nothing lasts
longer for powerful
cough relief.
Oui is so thick and creamy, it
can stay upside down.
Oui the french style yogurt.
YQ by Yoplait.
40% less sugar than the leading
Greek yogurt
and packed with protein.
Now that's smart.
♪ ♪
Do you feel the call?
Black Opium.
L'eau de parfum.
Yves Saint Laurent.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR DENTAL
INSURANCE, HUMANA HAS A VARIETY
OF PLANS TO FIT THE WHOLE
FAMILY'S NEEDS AND BUDGET.
GRANDMA! GRANDMA! I LOST A
TOOTH! IT'S MY FIRST ONE, SEE?
YOU'LL HAVE A LOT TO SMILE
ABOUT, BECAUSE HUMANA DENTAL
PLANS START AT JUST $17/MONTH.
TO FIND OUT MORE, CALL THE
NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN, AND WE'LL
SEND YOU A FREE, PERSONALIZED
INFORMATION BOOKLET THAT
INCLUDES A FREE QUOTE. OR VISIT
US ONLINE AT
SIGNUPFORHUMANADENTAL.COM. WITH
A HUMANA DENTAL PLAN, YOU'LL PAY
LITTLE OR NOTHING FOR OFFICE
VISITS. PLUS, YOU CAN GET 100%
COVERAGE FOR IN-NETWORK
PREVENTIVE CARE, SUCH AS
CLEANINGS, ORAL EXAMS, AND
X-RAYS TOO. THERE ARE NO
EXCLUSIONS FOR PREEXISTING
CONDITIONS, AND NO AGE
REQUIREMENTS. THE TOOTH FAIRY IS
GOING TO VISIT ME, GRANDPA. IS
THAT SO? TONIGHT! AND YOU GET TO
CHOOSE FROM A LARGE NETWORK OF
DENTISTS AND SPECIALISTS AT OVER
200,000 LOCATIONS NATIONWIDE. SO
CALL THE NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN
OR VISIT US ONLINE AT
SIGNUPFORHUMANADENTAL.COM, AND
WE'LL SEND YOU THIS FREE,
PERSONALIZED INFORMATION BOOKLET
AND FREE QUOTE. HUMANA ALSO HAS
VISION PLANS, WITH PAYMENTS
STARTING AT $15 A MONTH. AND
THEY INCLUDE ANNUAL EYE EXAMS
FOR ONLY A $15 COPAYMENT. SO,
WHETHER YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A
DENTAL PLAN, A VISION PLAN, OR
BOTH, GIVE US A CALL. AND WHEN
YOU DO, BE SURE TO ASK ABOUT OUR
PLANS DESIGNED EXCLUSIVELY FOR
VETERANS AND THEIR FAMILIES. I
LOST ANOTHER ONE! CALL THE
NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN FOR YOUR
FREE PERSONALIZED INFORMATION
BOOKLET THAT INCLUDES A FREE
QUOTE. YOU CAN'T BE TURNED DOWN.
SO CALL HUMANA NOW, AND WE'LL
HELP YOU FIND A PLAN FOR THE
WHOLE FAMILY. CALL THE NUMBER ON
YOUR SCREEN OR VISIT US ONLINE
AT SIGNUPFORHUMANADENTAL.COM.
Ok I'll admit. I didn't keep my
place as clean as I would like
'cuz I'm way too busy.
Who's got the time to chase
around down dirt, dust and hair?
So now, I use Heavy Duty Swiffer
Sweeper and Dusters.
For hard-to-reach places, Duster
makes it easy to clean.
It captures dust in one swipe.
Ha! Gotcha!
And Sweeper Heavy
Duty cloths lock away
twice as much dirt and dust.
It gets stuff deep in the
grooves other tools can miss.
Y'know what? My place... is a
lot cleaner now.
Stop cleaning. Start Swiffering.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> WELCOME BACK.
WE ARE HANGING WITH OUR FRIEND
AND FOUNDER OF "THE 12ISH
STYLE," KATIE STURINO.
SHE'S KEEPING US IN STYLE FOR
2019.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> WE NEED YOU.
WHAT CAN WE LOOK FORWARD TO THIS
YEAR?
>> THE '90s ARE BACK.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU LOVED THE
'90s.
I LOVED THE '90s.
I WAS A LITTLE YOUNG, BUT HERE
WE ARE.
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW TO
DRESS -- WE'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU
HOW TO DRESS FOR THE '90s TODAY.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU SAID, I WAS A LITTLE YOUNG
IN THE '90s.
I HAD A FULL-TIME JOB.
COME ON, KATIE.
>> CLOSE IT BACK A LITTLE.
>> WE'RE GOING BACK TO THE '90s
WHICH IS A GOOD TIME IF YOU
DON'T REMEMBER.
WHAT IS OUR FIRST LOOK?
>> WELL, OUR FIRST LOOK IS A
CARDIGAN.
SO THE '90s WERE VERY BIG FOR
CARDIGANS, BUT WE HAVE GOT AN
UPDATED TWIST.
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW TO WEAR THEM
AT ALL DIFFERENT AGES.
WE'LL START WITH SHANTAY.
SHE'S WEARING IT THE WAY
JENNIFER ANISTON WORE IT
IN "FRIENDS."
BUTTONED DOWN AT THE TOP AND UP
AT THE BOTTOM.
YOU CAN WEAR IT WITH PRINTS,
JEANS, WHATEVER.
IT'S EASY.
GIVE IT A TRY.
>> THE ANIMAL PRINT KEEPS IT.
>> THE ANIMAL PRINT IS REALLY
CUTE.
THEN WE HAVE GOT KATE WHO IS
MODELING OUR 40s LOOK.
THIS IS THE WAY THAT I'M
CHOOSING TO WEAR CARDIGANS MOST
OFTEN RECENTLY.
YOU TUCK THEM INTO A LONG SKIRT
AND IT CREATES SUCH A CUTE SHAPE
FOR YOUR BODY.
IT'S FLATTERING REALLY ON
EVERYBODY, AND YOU JUST WEAR IT
AS A TOP.
SHE'S ALSO READY FOR VALENTINE'S
DAY AND I WANT TO WEAR THAT
OUTFIT.
>> SHE HAS GOT TO BE READY
BECAUSE THAT RING IS BLINDING
ME.
>> OH, I JUST SAW THAT.
>> THANK YOU.
MY HUSBAND WILL BE VERY
THANKFUL.
SHOUTOUT FOR HIM, RIGHT?
>> AND SOME WOMEN IN THEIR 60s
ARE REQUIRING A BIT MORE
COVERAGE.
SO FOR CAROL, WHAT WE HAVE DONE
IS WE HAVE TAKEN THE LOOK OF A
TURTLENECK UNDER A CARDIGAN.
>> THAT'S CUTE WITH A SCARF.
>> WITH A SCARF, RIGHT?
THE SCARF SITS IN AS THE
TURTLENECK AND WE PAIRED WIT --
IT WITH A PUNCHY RED TOP AND
SPORTY PANTS, AND CAROL IS GOING
TO RIDE AROUND TOWN LOOKING
CUTE.
>> TOTALLY.
YOU LOOK SO CUTE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THANK YOU.
>> SO WHAT IS -- WHAT IS THE
NEXT TREND?
>> UP NEXT, WE HAVE GOT
WIDE-LEGGED PANTS FOR EVERY AGE
GROUP COMING AT YOU.
>> I LOVE THAT.
>> SO WIDE-LEGGED PANTS ARE NOW
HOW YOU'RE PICTURING THEM.
THEY'RE NOT GRUNGY.
THEY'RE ACTUALLY SUPER CUTE
BECAUSE THEY'RE CROPPED.
WE'RE STARTING OFF WITH DANIELLA
IN HER 20s.
DANIELLA, IN YOUR 20s, IT'S A
GREAT TIME TO PLAY WITH PRINT
AND COLOR, BUT IF YOU ARE PETITE
LIKE DANIELLA IS, YOU WON'T WANT
TO WEAR PRINT HEAD TO TOE.
WE HAVE KEPT THE PRINT IN THE
PANT AND KEPT A SIMPLE TOP.
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE LOOKS GREAT.
I LIKE IT.
>> YOU MENTIONED THEY ARE ALL
TOP.
THAT'S THE DISTINCTION.
THE CROP IS IN STYLE.
>> THAT'S WHAT MAKES IT MODERN.
IN YOUR 40s, WE HAVE GOT GILLY,
AND SHE IS WEARING A BOXY
JACKET.
IT HAS A THROWBACK, GRUNGE VIBE.
BUT IT'S COOL.
>> SEXY GRUNGE.
>> DOESN'T LOOK LIKE SHE
BORROWED IT FROM HER KID.
IT LOOKS LIKE SHE'S WEARING IT
ON HER OWN.
>> THEY'RE GOING TO WANT TO
BORROW IT FROM ME.
>> THEY'LL WANT TO BORROW IT
FROM YOU.
EXACTLY.
IT'S AN UPDATED MODERN GRUNGE
FOR EVERYONE.
AND THEN ARLENE IS IN HER 60s
AND SOMETIMES AGAIN, WOMEN IN
THEIR 60s ARE WANTING A BIT MORE
COVERAGE.
SO WE HAVE TAKEN THE WIDE-LEGGED
PANT ALL THE WAY DOWN TO THE
FLOOR, AND WE PAIRED IT WITH A
BLAZER THAT'S GOING TO BRING IN
HER WAIST AND IT'S SUCH A PRETTY
COLOR AND SHE'S COVERED AND
FEELING GOOD.
>> THEY LOOK COMFORTABLE THOUGH.
>> THEY ARE ALL DIFFERENT
LENGTHS.
>> THEY ARE DIFFERENT LENGTHS
AND IT VARIES DIFFERENT ON KIND
OF HOW TALL YOU ARE, BUT REALLY
THE OTHER THING ABOUT A
WIDE-LEGGED PANT IS IT FEELS
LIKE PAJAMAS.
>> THAT'S WHY I'M ON BOARD WITH
THE WIDE LEG.
>> GET INTO A WIDE-LEGGED PANT
AND FORGET YOUR WORRIES.
>> I LOVE IT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
YOU ALWAYS TEACH US SO MUCH.
>> BRING EVERYBODY OUT.
>> FOR A BREAKDOWN OF ALL OF
THESE, CHECK OUT OUR INSTAGRAM
PAGE.
WE'RE GOING TO BE RIGHT BACK.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I work hard to protect
this Tookus.
To take care of any
messy situations.
And put irritation in its place.
And if I can get comfortable
keeping this Tookus
safe and protected...
you can get comfortable doing
the same with yours.
PREPARATION H.
Get comfortable with it.
To most, he's
Phil Mickelson...
..pro golfer.
To me, he's...
...well, Dad.
So when his
joint pain from
psoriatic arthritis
got really bad, it scared me.
And what could that pain mean?
Joint pain could
mean joint damage.
ENBREL helps
relieve joint pain...
...helps stop irreversible
joint damage...
and helps skin get clearer.
ENBREL may lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious, sometimes
fatal events...
including infections,
tuberculosis...
lymphoma, other cancers,...
nervous system and
blood disorders...
and allergic
reactions have occurred.
Tell your
doctor if you've
been some place where
fungal infections are common.
Or, if you're
prone to infections,
have cuts or sores,
have had hepatitis B,
have been treated
for heart failure...
or if you have
persistent fever...
bruising, bleeding, or paleness.
Don't start ENBREL...
if you have an
infection like the flu.
Since ENBREL...
Dad's back to being... Dad.
Visit Enbrel.com...
and use the Joint
Damage Simulator
to see how your joint
damage could be progressing.
Ask about ENBREL.
ENBREL.
FDA approved for
over 16 years.
Sorry...
Hey.
He just likes cute dogs.
And pretty ladies.
Or is this your
buddy's kid over there
and you're just
using him as bait?
I'm blaming my friend
entirely because...
Thank you. Thank you.
That was not your dog.
Now in 6 bold flavors.
♪ ♪
Do you feel the call?
Black Opium.
L'eau de parfum.
Yves Saint Laurent.
Searching for a way to
help stop your cold sore?
Only Abreva can
get rid of it in...
...as little as 2 1/2 days
when used at the first sign.
Abreva starts to
work immediately
to block the virus and
protect healthy cells.
Abreva acts on it.
So you can too.
(Girl) My mom washes the dishes
before she puts them in the
dishwasher.
So what does the dishwasher do?
(VO) Cascade Platinum does the
work for you.
Prewashing and removing
stuck-on foods, the first time.
(Mom) Wow! That's clean!
(VO) Cascade Platinum.
New Trident Spearmint Rush Vibes
start with a light crystal
coating,
then change into a smooth gum.
With bursts of spearmint flavor
that pop, pop, pop.
New Trident Vibes.
A Burst of Something New.
At Redfin, we charge
you a 1% listing fee.
And because Redfin.com is
America's #1 brokerage site
our agents get more
eyes on your home
so you sell for
thousands more
than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin Agent.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> ALL RIGHT.
A BIG THANK YOU TO OUR FRIEND,
LIDS.
HEY.
AND EVERYBODY FOR WATCHING THE
SHOW TODAY.
ON TOMORROW'S SHOW, MARIE KONDO
IS HERE.
WE APPRECIATE YOU.
>> SHE'S GOING TO BE SPARKING