>>> WELCOME TO THE SHOW.
WE HAVE GOT THE HILARIOUS ALI
WENTWORTH TODAY.
>> AND CARLA HALL IS HERE AS
WELL.
THERE SHE IS JUMPING IN THE
BACKGROUND.
PLUS WE HAVE SOME TRAILBLAZING
DESIGNERS AS WELL.
AND WE HAVE THE GREATEST
AUDIENCE IN TELEVISION.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> FROM THE CROSS ROADS OF THE
WORLD, TIMES SQUARE, NEW YORK
CITY, IT'S "STRAHAN AND SARA."
ESCAPE FOR AN HOUR.
WE ALL NEED IT.
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> OH.
HAVE A SEAT.
WELCOME TO THE SHOW, EVERYBODY.
HAPPY HUMP DAY.
HAPPY WEDNESDAY AND WE'RE
EXCITED BECAUSE WE HAVE CARLA
HALL HERE COOKING WITH US THIS
MORNING.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> I'M SO EXCITED TO BE HERE.
THIS IS, LIKE, FIRST TIME IN THE
NEW DIGS.
I LIKE IT.
>> WHAT ARE YOU MAKING FOR
LUNCH?
>> I'M MAKING A CHICKEN SALAD ON
DARK BREAD WITH RAISINS AND
OPEN-FACE JOHNNYCAKE SANDWICHES
IN THE SHAPE OF A HEART.
I KNOW IT'S THAT TIME OF YEAR.
>> TODAY IS GALENTINE'S DAY.
TODAY IS GALENTINE'S DAY.
>> GALENTINE'S.
>> THAT'S A PERFECTLY SHAPED
SANDWICH FOR TODAY FOR ALL THE
LADIES IN THE HOUSE.
>> SO GALENTINE'S FOR THE GALS.
>> IT'S A THING.
THE 13th IS GALENTINE'S DAY
AND THE 14th IS VALENTINE'S DAY.
>> WHY DO THEY KEEP MAKING STUFF
UP?
>> WE HAVE SO MUCH TIME ON OUR
HANDS.
IT'S, LIKE, THE GIRL POWER DAY
WHERE WE LIFT EACH OTHER UP.
WHICH WE ALL NEED.
>> IT'S GALENTINE'S AND
VALENTINE'S.
THEN THERE'S --
>> LIKE MOST THINGS, WOMEN LIFT
FIRST AND THEN THE MEN FOLLOW
NEXT.
>> FOR THE MALE, IT'S
MALENTINE'S DAY.
YEAH.
PUT OUR FLAG DOWN.
STAKE OUR CLAIM.
>> I WANTED TO START OFF WITH
THE CUTEST VIDEO THAT I SAW -- I
SAW IT ON "GMA."
I OCCASIONALLY WATCH THAT SHOW.
YOU'RE ON IT, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, SOMETIMES.
>> BUT THERE IS LITERALLY THIS
DOG.
THIS IS SO CUTE.
IT'S IN AUSTRALIA NAMED MOLLY
WHO UNFORTUNATELY LOST A LITTER
OF PUPPIES.
SO DAYS LATER, SHE ADOPTS A NEW
BABY, A BABY POSSUM.
MOLLY AND HER NEW BABY LIKE TO
SLEEP TOGETHER.
THEY PLAY TOGETHER AND TAKE LONG
WALKS TOGETHER.
LOOK AT THEM.
>> I MEAN IT'S CUTE NOW.
>> IT'S ADORABLE.
>> IT'S ADORABLE, AND I GET IT,
YOU KNOW, I JUST DON'T
UNDERSTAND HOW IT'S GOING TO BE
LATER ON BECAUSE MY
UNDERSTANDING IS THE DOG WAITS
UNDER THE THE TREE EVERY DAY FOR
THE POSSUM TO COME BACK AND COME
DOWN AND GET ON ITS BACK AND IT
GIVES HIM A RIDE, BUT, YOU KNOW,
POSSUMS, THEY GET OLDER.
MAYBE A LITTLE MORE AGGRESSIVE.
I WOULD BE WORRIED ABOUT RABIES
AND THEN A POSSUM ON YOUR POOR
DOG'S BACK, THAT COULD BE BAD
FOR THE BACK.
>> THIS WAS SUCH A JOYFUL,
BLISSFUL STORY THAT I FEEL WAS,
LIKE, JUST POOPED ON.
>> I'M JUST SAYING.
>> CARLA, IS IT NOT SO CUTE?
>> OKAY.
IT IS CUTE, BUT ALL OF A SUDDEN,
WHEN I SAW THE VIDEO, I'M, LIKE,
THAT'S A RAT ON THAT DOG'S BACK.
>> AND THEN ONE DAY --
>> YOU HAVE BEEN IN NEW YORK FOR
TOO LONG.
>> WHAT HAPPENS WHEN THE DOG
DECIDES TO COME IN THE HOUSE
WITH THE POSSUM ON THE BACK?
THAT'S ANOTHER PROBLEM.
>> WELL, YEAH.
IT'S MORE OF AN OUTDOOR DOG AND
POSSUM, BUT IT'S SO CUTE.
CROSS-SPECIES LOVE DEFIES HUMAN
NATURE.
>> IT'S CUTE FOR YOU NOW.
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT.
>> IT'S SUPER ADORABLE.
THE AUDIENCE AGREES.
>> THEY DON'T AGREE.
>> THEY DO.
>> THERE WAS AN INTERVIEW WITH
KATY PERRY.
SHE IS OPENING UP ABOUT LIVING
WITH HER BOYFRIEND, ORLANDO
BLOOM.
>> YES.
>> PHYSICALLY THE FACT THAT SHE
THROWS SOME OF HIS THINGS OUT
WHEN HE'S NOT LOOKING.
I MEAN THE MOMENT YOU LEAVE THE
HOUSE, STUFF GOES IN THE TRASH.
NOW SHE SAID SHE WARNED HIM
ABOUT THIS ONCE, AND SHE ADMITS
THAT THEY ARE BOTH HOARDERS BY
NATURE DUE TO ALWAYS WORRYING
ABOUT MONEY GROWING UP AND NOT
HAVING ENOUGH AND NOW THAT THEY
HAVE THINGS, THEY JUST KEEP IT.
SHE SAYS, MY GARAGE IS NOT FULL
OF CARS.
IT'S YOU FULL OF STUFF.
CLOTHES OR WHATEVER IT MAY BE.
>> CLOTHES.
>> DO YOU THROW OR HAVE YOU
THROWN SOME OF YOUR HUSBAND'S
STUFF AWAY WHEN THEY ARE NOT
LOOKING?
>> NO BECAUSE I'M THE ONE WITH
TOO MUCH STUFF.
THERE WAS A PAIR OF CARGO PANTS
THAT I MISS ALREADY THAT MY
BROTHER, MY BEST FRIEND AND MY
HUSBAND WERE SO DISGUSTED BY
THAT THEY ONCE PLOTTED AND
REMOVED THOSE PANTS FROM THE
HOUSE AND I HAVEN'T SEEN THEM
SINCE.
>> I'M GOOD SOMETIMES OF TAKING
A FEW HOURS AND PURGING THE
CLOSET AND GRABBING EVERYTHING.
>> SEE WHAT SPARKS YOUR JOY?
>> YEAH.
AND I PUT IT IN THE BAGS TO GET
RID OF IT, BUT THEN I PUT THE
BAG BY THE DOOR AND IT SITS
THERE FOR, LIKE, A MONTH.
>> YES.
>> WHO SHOULD I GIVE IT TO?
WHO CAN WEAR MY SIZE?
THAT'S HALF THE PROBLEM.
>> NOT MANY PEOPLE, BUT YOU CAN
CUT IT INTO A FEW PIECES FOR US.
>> CARLA, HAVE YOU EVER DONE
THAT?
HAVE YOU EVER HAD IT DONE FOR
YOU?
>> YOU HAD A MAGAZINE FROM 2008
IN YOUR HOUSE.
>> I DID.
I FOUND A MAGAZINE FROM 2008 AND
ONE FROM 2013.
WHAT I HEAR YOU ALL SAYING IS
PEOPLE ARE THROWING YOUR STUFF
AWAY BECAUSE IT DOESN'T SPARK
JOY FOR THEM.
>> RIGHT.
SUPER SELFISH.
>> THAT IS WRONG.
>> A MAGAZINE FROM 2008, THAT'S
KIND OF PUSHING JOY FROM
EVERYBODY.
CARLA IS A HOARDER.
>> I'M A HOARDER.
HI.
I'M CARLA, I'M A HOARDER.
CARLA, KEEP COMING BACK.
I'M A HOARDER.
>> YOU'RE ADMITTING MAYBE YOU'RE
WRONG IN KEEPING THE MAGAZINE.
>> CORRECT.
>> THAT LEADS US INTO OUR NEXT
STORY.
HOW TO OWN BEING WRONG.
>> OKAY.
>> THERE WAS A RECENT ARTICLE.
SEE HOW I DID THAT?
>> SHE TOTALLY OWNED IT.
>> OWNED IT.
>> IT WAS IN "THE HARVARD
BUSINESS REVIEW," WHICH I READ
AS LIGHT READING SOMETIMES.
[ LAUGHTER ]
IT WAS ENTITLED "WHAT TO DO WHEN
YOU REALIZE YOU HAVE MADE A
MISTAKE."
NOW THE ARTICLE POINTS OUT THAT
FOR MANY OF US, FINDING OUT THAT
WE WERE WRONG CAN FEEL LIKE A
THREAT TO OUR SELF-IDENTITY AND
IT GIVES THIS QUOTE FROM THE
BOOK, BEING WRONG ADVENTURES IN
THE MARGIN OF ERROR.
OUR LOVE OF BEING RIGHT IS BEST
UNDERSTOOD AS OUR FEAR OF BEING
WRONG.
>> THAT'S DEEP.
>> I MEAN, HOW MANY OF YOU GUYS
KNOW -- BECAUSE THEY'RE PROBABLY
IN YOUR FAMILY, BUT YOU DON'T
HAVE TO NAME THEM, THOSE PEOPLE
THAT NEVER APOLOGIZE, THAT ARE
NEVER WRONG?
DO YOU KNOW SOMEONE?
MICHAEL, WE DIDN'T ASK YOU IF
YOU DO IT, BUT -- BECAUSE -- SO
THE WHOLE POINT IS THIS WAS THE
HELPFUL ADVICE.
IT'S ONE OF THE FEW THINGS I'M
GOOD AT.
I'M QUICK TO APOLOGIZE.
I THINK I KNEW PEOPLE SOMEWHERE
ALONG THE WAY THAT DIDN'T.
I'M GOOD AT IT.
>> ARE YOU APOLOGIZING BECAUSE
YOU'RE WRONG OR BECAUSE YOU
FEEL, LIKE, YOU KNOW --
>> THIS IS THE KEY.
THE FIRST TIP IS TAKE
RESPONSIBILITY.
MICHAEL SAID EARLIER, I SAY I'M
SORRY WHEN I'M JUST TIRED OF
TALKING ABOUT IT.
>> WHOA.
SO BASICALLY YOU'RE SORRY THAT
THEY'RE STILL TALKING ABOUT IT.
>> SO PRETTY MUCH HE JUST,
LIKE -- HE PETERS OUT.
>> I'M GETTING SICK OF TALKING
ABOUT THE SAME THING 100 TIMES.
LIKE, OKAY.
OBVIOUSLY WE'RE NOT AGREEING.
HEY, I'M SORRY.
LET'S MOVE ONTO THE NEXT THING
TO APOLOGIZE ABOUT.
>> THIS IS A TIP.
>> HELP ME OUT HERE.
HOW CAN I GET BETTER?
>> TAKE RESPONSIBILITY.
DON'T SAY, MISTAKES WERE MADE OR
I'M SORRY YOU'RE OFFENDED OR I'M
TIRED OF TALKING ABOUT THIS.
I ADDED THAT PART.
>> OKAY.
>> TAKE RESPONSIBILITY.
THEN IT SAYS
ADDRESS WHAT YOU NEED TO DO
RIGHT NOW AND SHARE WHAT YOU
WILL DO DIFFERENTLY NEXT TIME.
>> OH.
I WILL APOLOGIZE SOONER.
I MEAN, NO.
>> YOU DO REMEMBER THE TITLE WAS
HOW TO OWN YOU'RE WRONG?
>> I CAN OWN WHEN I'M WRONG.
I CAN REALLY OWN WHEN I'M WRONG.
I DO APOLOGIZE, BUT THERE ARE
TIMES WHEN I JUST DON'T FEEL
LIKE I AM WRONG.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> BUT THE OTHER PERSON DOESN'T
EITHER AND YOU GET FATIGUED AND
I'M READY TO MOVE ON.
I THINK I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE WHO
IS GUILTY OF APOLOGIZING WHEN
YOU DON'T NECESSARILY FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE WRONG.
YOU KNOW WHAT I LOVE?
[ APPLAUSE ]
AND YOU KNOW HOW I KNOW I'M NOT
ALONE IN THIS?
BECAUSE THE YOUNG MAN IN THE
FRONT ROW LOOKED AT HIS GIRL AND
DID, LIKE, THIS AND THEN LOOKED
AT ME, LIKE, MICHAEL, DON'T LOOK
AT ME.
DON'T LOOK AT ME.
SHE'S LOOKING AT ME.
>> I LIKE THAT THE FIRST PERSON
WHO CLAPPED WAS RORY OUR BOSS.
HE'S, LIKE, AMEN.
>> I AGREE.
APOLOGIZE WHEN YOU ARE WRONG.
>> YOU HAVE GOT TO OWN IT.
NOT THE WAY MICHAEL DOES.
EXHIBIT "A."
>> EXHIBIT "A."
BUT THIS MOTHER IS OWNING WITH
HER DAUGHTER.
THEY ARE OWNING BLACK HISTORY
MONTH, AND HER NAME IS SASHA.
SHE IS IN NORTH CAROLINA.
THAT'S THE MOTHER'S NAME AND SHE
HAS BEEN DOING A SPECIAL PROJECT
ON INSTAGRAM WITH HER DAUGHTER
IN HONOR OF BLACK HISTORY MONTH.
>> THIS IS SO CUTE.
>> EACH DAY SHE POSTS A PICTURE
OF HER DAUGHTER -- NAMED RILEY,
DRESSED AS A DIFFERENT ICONIC
BLACK WOMAN.
HERE ARE JUST A FEW.
THERE SHE IS AT BEYONCE.
HERE SHE IS FROM "BLACK
PANTHER."
AND ALSO.
>> MY FAVORITE.
WHOOPI.
>> WHOOPI FROM "SESAME STREET."
WE LOVE THAT.
WE REACHED OUT TO SASHA AND THIS
IS WHAT SHE TOLD US.
VERY, VERY GOOD THING.
SHE SAID, MY INTENTIONS WERE
SOLELY JUST TO EDUCATE MY BABY.
I WANT HER TO KNOW SHE CAN BE
AND DO ANYTHING IN LIFE WHEN SHE
GETS A LITTLE OLDER.
SHE WILL KNOW ALL THESE WOMEN,
WHO THEY ARE AND SHE WILL SEE
HERSELF IN THEM AND KNOW THAT
THERE IS NO LIMIT TO THE THINGS
SHE CAN DO.
WELL DONE, SASHA.
WELL DONE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
GREAT JOB.
>> THAT STORY IS PERFECTION.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT'S PERFECTION?
WHEN WE COME BACK, WE'RE GOING
TO TALK ABOUT LOVE AND
RELATIONSHIPS WITH ALI
WENTWORTH, EVERYBODY.
YEAH.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Okay, Max...time
to help Mrs. Tyler
reach her health goals!
I'm in! But first...
Shelfie!
The great-tasting
nutrition of Ensure.
With up to 30
grams of protein
and 26 vitamins
and minerals!
Ensure.
For Strength and Energy.
Gentle means everything,
so we improved everything.
We used 50% fewer ingredients
Added one handed pumps
And beat the
top safety standards
The new JOHNSON'S®
Choose Gentle
To most, he's
Phil Mickelson...
..pro golfer.
To me, he's...
...well, Dad.
So when his
joint pain from
psoriatic arthritis
got really bad, it scared me.
And what could that pain mean?
Joint pain could
mean joint damage.
ENBREL helps
relieve joint pain...
...helps stop irreversible
joint damage...
and helps skin get clearer.
ENBREL may lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious, sometimes
fatal events...
including infections,
tuberculosis...
lymphoma, other cancers,...
nervous system and
blood disorders...
and allergic
reactions have occurred.
Tell your
doctor if you've
been some place where
fungal infections are common.
Or, if you're
prone to infections,
have cuts or sores,
have had hepatitis B,
have been treated
for heart failure...
or if you have
persistent fever...
bruising, bleeding, or paleness.
Don't start ENBREL...
if you have an
infection like the flu.
Since ENBREL...
Dad's back to being... Dad.
Visit Enbrel.com...
and use the Joint
Damage Simulator
to see how your joint
damage could be progressing.
Ask about ENBREL.
ENBREL.
FDA approved for
over 16 years.
You're going to do your thing.
And no period is going to slow
you down!
With Tampax, you get protection
that moves with you for total
comfort.
Choose Pearl for your chill,
Pocket for your moves,
and Active for your hustle.
Do your thing with Tampax.
At last, one red that works on
everyone.
New Made for All lip color from
Maybelline New York.
Tested on 50 skin tones.
Sensational on all.
New Made for All.
Only from Maybelline New York.
If only there was a place nearby
you could get one of these.
Or these.
Good thing they're
sold literally
everywhere business is done.
I'm pretty sure you could
buy them at a bank.
Not Sorry.
Reese's.
In an era of online retail,
Not Sorry.
where everything
is just a few clicks away,
buying a car should be
no different.
That's why, at Carvana,
you can buy a car
100% online.
We made it easy
to browse, view,
and buy from over 10,000 cars.
You can even trade-in
your old car
all while binge watching
your favorite TV show.
Afterwards, we'll deliver
your car to you.
Or you can pick it up
from one of our
car vending machines.
Either way, your car comes with
a 7-day return policy.
So grab a seat,
relax in your comfy pants,
and enjoy the new way to buy
a car-- at Carvana.
With Advil Liqui-Gels,
you'll ask...
What stiff joints?
What bad back?
Advil is... Relief that's
fast. Strength that lasts.
You'll ask...
What pain?
With Advil Liqui-Gels.
>>> TOMORROW ON "STRAHAN AND
SARA," KELSEY GRAMMER IS POPPING
BY, AND WE'RE KICKING IT WITH
K-POP SENSATION, BLACKPINK.
♪
ON "STRAHAN AND SARA."
>> WE GOT IT ALL.
>> LUNCHTIME AT 1:00 EASTERN,
12:00 CENTRAL AND PACIFIC ON
ABC.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>>> TOMORROW IS VALENTINE'S DAY
SO I KNOW A LOT OF PEOPLE IN OUR
AUDIENCE ARE FILLED WITH
QUESTIONS ABOUT ROMANCE AND
RELATIONSHIPS.
>> AND A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE
SITTING UP HERE.
SO AS A PUBLIC SERVICE, WE
BROUGHT IN ONE OF THE WISEST
PEOPLE WE KNOW WHEN IT COMES TO
RELATIONSHIPS.
>> YES.
WISEST.
>> OR REALLY JUST ABOUT ANY
TOPIC.
IF YOU ARE CONFUSED OR CURIOUS,
YOU CAN ALWAYS ASK ALI.
THAT'S RIGHT.
PLEASE WELCOME ALI WENTWORTH.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> HELLO.
>> HELLO, HELLO.
>> I'M SO EXCITED TO BE HERE.
>> IN CASE PEOPLE DON'T KNOW,
ALI WENTWORTH IS THE BETTER HALF
OF THE GEORGE STEPHANOPOULOS AND
ALI WENTWORTH MARRIAGE.
>> YES.
>> I'M VERY OPEN ABOUT THAT.
>> I'M THE SERIOUS, SMART ONE.
>> SERIOUS, SMART ONE RIGHT
HERE, YES.
I'M SURE A LOT OF THIS ADVICE
COMES FROM YOUR ADORABLY PERFECT
MARRIAGE WITH GEORGE.
>> YES.
I'M JUST SAYING THAT BECAUSE
HE'S ON ABC.
YES.
I DO WHAT HE SAYS AND WE HAVE A
PERFECT MARRIAGE.
>> HE DIDN'T EVEN SAY THAT WAS
THE WAY IT WENT.
HE IS CUTE AND WELL-TRAINED.
>> HE IS.
>> HE SAYS, YOU MAKE THE
DECISIONS.
>> LIKE A PUPPY.
I DO PUSH HIS NOSE IN IT A
LITTLE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I LOVE TO GIVE
ADVICE BECAUSE MY MOTHER IS A
BIG ADVICE GIVER.
NOT GOOD ADVICE, YOU KNOW.
SHE'S, LIKE, YOU'RE DEPRESSED?
CLOSE YOUR EYES AND THINK ABOUT
CHRISTMAS.
THAT KIND OF THING AND REMEMBER
I HAD JUST GIVEN BIRTH.
MY HAIR WAS, LIKE, MATTED TO MY
FACE AND THEY HAD TAKEN THE BABY
AND GEORGE WENT TO GET ME HONEY
NUT CHEERIOS AND SHE WAS, LIKE,
IT WOULDN'T HURT YOU TO PUT LIP
GLOSS ON BEFORE GEORGE COMES
BACK.
I WAS, LIKE, I JUST HAD A BABY.
AS I GOT OLDER, I STARTED TO
REALIZE WITH MY TEENAGE GIRLS,
I'M GOING TO START GIVING
ADVICE.
I KNOW A LITTLE BIT ABOUT A FEW
THINGS AND I HAVE A NETWORK OF
GIRLFRIENDS AND THAT'S WHERE WE
GET OUR ADVICE AND HERE IT IS,
VALENTINE'S DAY AND I GET A LOT
OF LOVE QUESTIONS FROM MY
FRIENDS.
I'M CONSTANTLY TRYING TO SET
THEM UP, AND I KNOW THAT OUR
AUDIENCE HAS SOME QUESTIONS,
RIGHT?
>> YES.
>> YEAH, THEY DO.
>> LET'S BRING UP OUR FIRST ONE.
>> I'M EXCITED.
>> WHAT IS YOUR NAME AND WHAT'S
YOUR QUESTION?
>> I'M CALLAN ALEXANDER FROM
SANTA CRUZ, CALIFORNIA.
MY QUESTION FOR YOU GUYS TODAY
IS -- SO.
I MET A GUY ONLINE AND WE HAVE
BEEN DATING FOR ABOUT FOUR
MONTHS NOW, AND I WAS WONDERING
WHEN THE APPROPRIATE TIME TO
HAVE A DISCUSSION OF DELETING
PROFILES IS.
>> WHEN YOU SAY ONLINE IS IT,
LIKE, THE DARK WEB OR A DATING
APP?
WHEN PEOPLE SAY ONLINE, I'M
JUST, LIKE, WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> WHICH PART OF IT.
>> THE IT'S THE WILD WEST OUT
THERE.
>> ON YOUR USUAL SWIPING APPS.
>> PET FINDER.
>> WHAT I NEED TO BE ON.
>> HERE'S MY ADVICE TO YOU.
I SAY -- IS IT A HIM OR A HER OR
A THEY?
>> HIM.
>> A HIM.
I WOULD LET HIM TAKE CONTROL OF
THAT.
IF YOU SEE ONE DAY THAT HE SAYS
IN A RELATIONSHIP AND FINGERS
CROSSED IT'S YOU, THEN YOU CAN
DO THE SAME THING, BUT DON'T BE
THE FIRST -- DON'T BE THE PERSON
TO DO THAT.
DO YOUR SHOPPING AROUND.
>> I THINK FOUR MONTHS, IT
DEPENDS ON WHAT YOUR
RELATIONSHIP IS LIKE.
FOR ME IF IT'S, LIKE, TIGHT AND
YOU FEEL LIKE THERE IS SOMETHING
THERE, BUT I DON'T KNOW IF I
WOULD NECESSARILY BE THE FIRST
ONE.
WOMEN ARE MORE PROACTIVE
NOWADAYS.
>> SOMETIMES IT GETS A LITTLE
SCARY FOR THE MEN IF WE'RE,
LIKE, PUT A RING ON IT AFTER
DINNER THE FIRST TIME.
SHE'S AN INDEPENDENT WOMAN.
SHE DOESN'T NEED TO DECLARE HER
RELATIONSHIP STATUS.
>> I MET MY HUSBAND ONLINE AND
HE SAID TO ME A FEW MONTHS IN, I
JUST WANTED YOU TO KNOW, I DON'T
WANT TO MEET ANYONE ELSE RIGHT
NOW SO I'M GOING TO TAKE MINE
DOWN.
I WAS STILL A SINGLE LADY SO
LIKE ALI SAID, I WAS FLYING
LOOSE.
>> LADY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
>> SHE'S PREGNANT.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WE NEED TO GET AWAY FROM THAT.
>> WHERE DID THAT COME FROM,
ALI?
>> PLEASE TELL ME YOU'RE NOT
FLYING LOOSE LIKE THIS ONE.
>> NO, NO, NO.
>> WHAT YOU GOT?
>> I'M BRIAN SULLIVAN FROM NEW
JERSEY AND I HAVE A QUESTION FOR
YOU GUYS.
I'M A SINGLE GUY IN MY MID 30s
AND GOD HELP ME.
I WORK BRUTAL 13-PLUS HOUR DAYS.
HOW DO I FIND THE TIME TO MEET
ANYONE?
>> OKAY.
THAT'S A GREAT QUESTION.
WHAT DO YOU DO FOR A LIVING?
>> I'M IN SHOW BUSINESS.
>> OH.
WELL -- THIS IS A FRIENDSHIP
RING.
I WOULD SAY IT'S HARD TO MEET
PEOPLE AT WORK NOW BECAUSE OF
THE WHOLE ME TOO MOVEMENT.
I WOULD GET ON THE APP THAT THE
NICE WOMAN EARLIER WAS ON.
I WOULD TRY TO MEET SOMEBODY
ONLINE.
>> ONLINE.
>> THAT'S THE ONLY WAY YOU CAN
DO IT.
>> OKAY.
>> DON'T LET YOUR MAMA SET YOU
UP.
I CAN TELL YOU RIGHT NOW THAT'S
NOT GOING TO WORK OUT.
YOU SEEM LIKE A GREAT GUY.
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT A SERIAL
KILLER.
>> I'M NOT.
>> TALK TO THAT BEAUTIFUL BLONDE
ABOUT WHAT APP SHE'S ON.
>> OKAY.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S GRINDR
OR EHARMONY, BUT SHE'LL TELL
YOU.
>> THANK YOU, BRIAN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
HELLO.
>> HI.
I'M TERESA FROM HOUSTON, TEXAS.
>> TERESA.
>> YES.
>> SO AS A MOM AND A WIFE, I AM
CONSTANTLY JUGGLING EVERYTHING
AND MY QUESTION TO YOU IS, HOW
DO YOU FIND BALANCE IN IT ALL
AND STILL MAKE TIME FOR YOUR
FRIENDS AND OTHER IMPORTANT
RELATIONSHIPS BESIDES THOSE?
>> I PUT MY FRIENDS WAY AHEAD OF
MY FAMILY.
NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THE TRUTH IS I'M VERY
DOMESTICATED LIKE A CAT AND WHAT
I DO IS I MAKE -- WE HAVE FAMILY
DINNER EVERY NIGHT.
I HAVE TWO TEENAGE GIRLS.
SO YOU CAN IMAGINE HOW MUCH
XANAX I'M POPPING, BUT WITH MY
FRIENDS WHO I DON'T GET TO SEE A
LOT, WE HAVE A TEXT --
>> A TEXT CHAIN.
>> #SQUAD AND ALL WE DO IS GO,
OH MY GOD.
I'M FEELING REALLY SAD AND
THAT'S A WAY TO CONNECT VERY
QUICKLY WITHOUT HAVING TO GO OUT
AND HAVE DRINKS WITH THEM.
ESPECIALLY IF YOU ARE LIKE SARA
AND DRINK ALONE.
>> FLY LOOSE.
ALL ALONE.
>> SET UP A GIRLFRIEND CHAT AS A
WAY TO FEEL CONNECTED TO THEM.
>> I HAVE THAT WITH THE GUYS.
WE HAVE A GUY CHAT.
>> OH, YOU DO?
LOOK AT YOU.
#HOT.
>> #SQUAD.
#BOYSONLY.
>> MINE IS #DLINE.
IT'S THE DEFENSIVE LINE FROM
BACK WHEN I PLAYED IN THE NFL.
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT OUR SQUAD IS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
>> MY TWO CENTS --
>> I HAVE FEELINGS TOO.
>> I DON'T THINK YOU EVER FEEL
BALANCE AND IF YOU EVER ERR ON
THE SIDE OF -- EAR MUFFS, ALI,
FAMILY FIRST, YOU CAN'T GO
WRONG, BUT I DON'T THINK IT EVER
FEELS BALANCED.
>> OKAY.
>> NEW YORK C
>> NO, IT DOESN'T, BUT THE
GIRLFRIENDS ARE JUST AS
IMPORTANT AS EVERYTHING ELSE.
THAT'S WHERE I --
>> SUPER INTENSIVE.
>> YOU SHOULD PUT THE -- TAKE
CARE.
UNTIL THEY'RE, LIKE, 11.
>> THANK YOU.
WE HAVE ONE MORE QUESTION.
ONE MORE QUESTION.
>> OKAY.
>> HELLO.
>> HI, GUYS.
>> SO I HAVE BEEN DATING SOMEONE
WHO LIVES OUT OF STATE FOR A
COUPLE OF MONTHS NOW SO MY
QUESTION IS HOW DO I KEEP THINGS
SPICY?
>> I THINK BEING OUT OF STATE IS
SPICY ENOUGH.
HERE'S MY ADVICE TO YOU.
I'M TELLING YOU RIGHT NOW.
DON'T SEND SEXY PICS OR NUDIES.
>> NO.
>> DON'T DO IT.
>> THEY LIVE FOREVER.
>> THEY LIVE FOREVER AND YOUR
GRANDCHILDREN ARE GOING TO BE
DOING YOUR EULOGY AND THEY ARE
GOING TO COME UPON ALL THIS
STUFF AND IT'S NOT GOING TO BE
GOOD.
KEEP IT SPICY VERBALLY, BUT THE
FACT THAT YOU GUYS ARE LONG
DISTANCE, LIKE, GEORGE AND I
WERE LONG DISTANCE AT THE
BEGINNING OF OUR RELATIONSHIP
AND THAT WAS SPICY ENOUGH
BECAUSE YOU GET SO EXCITED TO
SEE THE PERSON.
>> HOW OFTEN DO YOU SEE HIM?
>> SO FAR --
>> HAVE YOU MET HIM?
>> OF COURSE.
>> JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE HE'S
NOT A CATFISH.
>> NO.
HE HAS TRAVELED UP HERE AND I
HAVE TRAVELED DOWN SOUTH SO
MAYBE ABOUT FOUR TIMES SO FAR.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S SPICY.
>> THAT'S SPICY.
>> DO SOMETHING CUTE FOR
VALENTINE'S DAY.
>> BUT NOT ON YOUR PHONE.
>> OKAY.
THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
AND GOOD LUCK IN LOVE, EVERYBODY
AND IN BALANCE AS WELL.
ALI, THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE THE BEST.
>> I LOVE GIVING OUT ADVICE.
>> I TELL YOU WHAT.
IF YOU WANT MORE ADVICE FROM
ALI, YOU CAN GET A COPY OF HER
BOOK.
IT'S CALLED "GO ASK ALI."
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH FASHION
TRAILBLAZER BRANDICE DANIEL.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
Smooth, easy strokes.
When you're raising a child...
Pinch.
be soft.
Ah.
When you're doing
it alone, be strong.
Thanks, dad.
Life takes softness and
strength, which is why
we make Angel Soft
with a balance of both.
It's your weekend to save,
during Pier 1's storewide
Presidents Day Sale.
February 14th through the 18th.
Get up to $100 off
our most loved items.
Get started on
your spring refresh
with big savings this weekend.
In store and at pier1.com.
In the water, in the water,
You ready for this? She doesn't
like it... you've gotta get in
there.
Okay.
Careful not to get it in her
eyes.
I know, I know what a bath is...
Smile honey.
This thing is like...
First kid.
Here we go.
Second kid.
You coming in mommy?
Ahh not a chance!
By  their second kid, every
parent is an expert and more
likely to choose LUVS than first
time parents.
LUVS with Nightlock plus absorbs
wetness faster than
Huggies Snug and Dry for
outstanding overnight
protection at a fraction of the
cost.
Live, Learn and Get Luvs.
♪♪
HEYYYYY!
It's the little things
that make life rich.
Ritz.
So there you are with
your depression
and your dirty laundry that you
just don't want to deal with.
Because depression is
multiple symptoms.
Yeah, time for a change.
And your doctor tells you
about TRINTELLIX,
a prescription medicine
for depression.
So you're feeling this
overall relief.
And TRINTELLIX had no
significant impact on weight
in clinical trials.
You got this.
Tell your doctor right away if
you have worsening depression,
unusual changes in
mood, behavior
or thoughts of suicide.
Antidepressants can increase
these in children, teens,
and young adults.
Do not take with MAOIs.
Tell your doctor about your
medications including
migraine, psychiatric and
depression medications to avoid
a potentially life-threatening
condition.
Increased risk of bleeding and
bruising may occur especially
if taken with NSAID pain
relievers, aspirin
or blood thinners.
Manic episodes or vision
problems may occur
in some people.
May cause low sodium levels.
Common side effects include
nausea, constipation
and vomiting.
Not living in sweatpants.
Ask your doctor about changing
to Trintellix.
Lash Paradise Mascara
from L'Oréal Paris.
Voluptuous Volume.
Intense Length.
Feathery-Soft Lashes.
This is what
paradise looks like.
Lash Paradise Mascara
from L'Oréal Paris.
Take your lashes to paradise.
>>> LAST CHANCE TO SAVE BIG ON
OUR "DEALS & STEALS."
GET TO STRAHANANDSARA.COM, NOW.
WE PARTNERED WITH COMPANIES FOR
HALF OFF ON SOLUTIONS FOR YOUR
EVERYDAY PROBLEMS.
BUT HURRY.
THESE DEALS ONLY LAST UNTIL
MIDNIGHT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> OUR NEXT GUEST IS FASHION
TRAILBLAZER AND OWNER OF
HARLEM'S FASHION ROW WHICH IS
PARTNERED WITH NIKE AND LeBRON
JAMES AND IT WAS PART OF NEW
YORK'S FASHION WEEK.
PLEASE GIVE A WARM WELCOME TO
BRANDICE DANIEL.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> HI.
WELCOME.
>> THANK YOU.
I'M SO EXCITED TO BE HERE.
>> SO NICE TO SEE YOU.
>> HARLEM'S FASHION ROW, HOW DID
YOU COME UP WITH THIS IDEA?
HOW WAS IT BORN?
>> I WAS LIVING IN HARLEM AT THE
TIME AND HAD AN IDEA THAT I
WANTED TO DO A SHOW FEATURING
BLACK DESIGNERS IN HARLEM.
NO ONE KNEW ME.
I WAS A TOTAL FASHION OUTSIDER.
I'M FROM MEMPHIS, BUT I KEPT
GOING TO PEOPLE AND
CONVINCING THEM TO BE APART OF
THIS, AND WHEN I RESEARCHED AND
FOUND THAT AFRICAN-AMERICANS
SPENT OVER $22 BILLION A YEAR,
BUT REPRESENT LESS THAN 1% OF
DESIGNERS IN MAJOR DEPARTMENT
STORES, I KNEW I WANTED TO BE A
SOLUTION.
>> AND A SOLUTION YOU ARE, AND
IT REALLY IS AMAZING BECAUSE WE
LOOK BACK AT BLACK HISTORY MONTH
AND WE LOOK BACK AT EVERYTHING
IN THE PAST, BUT WE ALSO NEED TO
LOOK FORWARD TO TRAILBLAZERS
LIKE YOURSELF AND WHAT YOU ARE
DOING IN THE COMMUNITY.
I APPLAUD YOU FOR THAT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND YOU MADE HISTORY BECAUSE
YOU DESIGNED THIS LeBRON JAMES
16 SNEAKER WHICH WAS THE FIRST
LeBRON SIGNATURE SHOE DESIGNED
BY WOMEN FOR WOMEN.
>> YES.
>> THAT IS, LIKE, WOW.
>> IT SOLD OUT IN FIVE MINUTES.
WHAT WAS IT LIKE SEEING THIS
COME TO FRUITION?
>> LOOK.
I'M STILL DIGESTING THIS.
IT STILL FEELS LIKE A DREAM, BUT
I REMEMBER WHEN ME AND THE
DESIGNERS WENT INTO NIKE'S
OFFICES FROM DAY ONE.
THEY SHOWED THE DESIGNERS SO
MUCH RESPECT AND THERE WAS A
POINT IN TIME WHERE THE
DESIGNERS, THEY WERE, LIKE, IN A
ZONE AND I LOOKED AT THEM AND I
WAS, LIKE, THIS PROJECT IS GOING
TO BE SPECIAL.
THEN WE GOT TO SHOW THE SHOE TO
LeBRON, AND WHILE WE'RE SHOWING
HIM THE SHOE, ONE OF THE
DESIGNERS SAID, LeBRON, THIS
SHOE IS AMAZING, BUT WHAT'S EVEN
MORE AMAZING IS THE FACT THAT ME
AND THESE OTHER TWO DESIGNERS
HAVE COME TOGETHER AND FORMED A
SISTERHOOD AND THAT WE REALLY
HAVE LEARNED THAT COLLABORATION
IS SO MUCH BETTER THAN
COMPETITION.
AND HE SAID, THAT'S THE STORY I
WANT TO TELL.
>> GOOD FOR LeBRON.
THAT MAKES ME LOVE IT MORE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> YEAH.
I THINK THAT WAS AMAZING AND THE
SHOES ARE ONLY AVAILABLE FOR
WOMEN.
COLLABORATE ON SIZE 14s.
NOW IT'S TIME -- WE'RE GOING TO
SEE SOME OF YOUR DESIGNERS.
THEY'RE GOING TO SHOW THEIR
DESIGNS, BUT FIRST WE HAVE LOOKS
FROM UNDRA CELESTE.
>> SO UNTRA CELESTE IS A
DESIGNER FOR THE EVERYDAY WOMAN
WHO WANTS A LITTLE BIT OF EDGE
AND LOVE POPS OF COLOR.
THIS PARTICULAR COLLECTION, THE
BRIGHT SIDE WAS RECENTLY SHOWN
IN NEW YORK FASHION WEEK.
SOMEHOW HER PIECES MANAGED TO
MAKE YOU FEEL HAPPY AND FIERCE
AT THE SAME TIME.
>> YES.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW SHE DOES
THAT.
>> LOVE IT.
>> WE HAVE A COUPLE MODELS.
WE'LL HAVE THEM COME OUT.
>> AND THE COLOR.
THE COLOR MAKES YOU HAPPY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> YES.
>> THE KALEIDOSCOPE FRINGE DRESS
HAS BEEN AN ABSOLUTE FAVORITE.
THAT DRESS IS ABSOLUTELY A SHOW
STOPPER AND THIS IS HER BEST
SELLER.
THIS IS THE JOY DRESS.
SHE BRINGS IT OUT EVERY SEASON
IN DIFFERENT COLORS.
IT'S ABSOLUTELY BEAUTIFUL ON ALL
BODY TYPES.
>> ABSOLUTELY BECAUSE IT
EMBRACES CURVY WOMEN AND I'M
CURVY AND THAT'S THE KIND OF
THING I WANT.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
AND WE HAVE THE DESIGNER HERE,
UNDRA CELESTE, NEW YORK.
>> WELCOME, UNDRA.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
>> TELL US WHAT INSPIRED THIS
LINE.
>> THIS COLLECTION, THE BRIGHT
SIDE WAS INSPIRED BY MY FAMILY,
THE WOMEN IN MY FAMILY I SHOULD
SAY.
THEY CAME TO -- MY FAMILY IS
FROM THE WEST INDIES AND THEY
CAME HERE LOOKING FOR A BETTER
LIFE AND WORKED IN A LOT OF
DOMESTIC CAPACITIES WHEN THEY
FIRST GOT HERE, BUT ON THE
WEEKENDS, LIKE, THESE WOMEN, SIX
SISTERS, WOULD TRANSFORM AND I
THINK THE BEST WAY TO DESCRIBE
THEM IS THEY WOULD TRANSFORM
INTO, LIKE, DONNA SUMMERS AND
DIANA ROSS.
SO, YOU KNOW, ALTHOUGH THEIR
WEEKS WEREN'T THAT BRIGHT, THEIR
WEEKEND WAS THE BRIGHT SIDE.
THEY GOT TOGETHER AND CAME
TOGETHER AS SISTERS, OVERDRESSED
FOR EVERYTHING THAT THEY WENT TO
AND I WAS REALLY -- I ACTUALLY
WENT BACK AND LOOKED AT OLD
PHOTO ALBUMS AND PICTURES OF
THEM.
THEY WERE FIERCE.
THEY WERE AMAZING.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> THANK YOU.
SO MUCH.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
YOU KNOW, NEXT WE HAVE FE NOEL.
>> NOW THE FE KNOLL COLLECTION
HONESTLY JUST MAKES ME WANT TO
LUXURIATE ON A BEACH.
IT'S SO REGAL YET RELAXED.
HER CLOTHES HAVE A WAY OF I
THINK MAKING WOMEN FEEL LIKE
GODDESSES WHILE DOING HER
EVERYDAY CHORES.
AND NOW, SARA, AS A MOM, YOU
WILL LOVE HER PIECES.
YOU WILL FEEL GLAMOROUS WHILE
YOU'RE CHANGING DIAPERS.
>> YES.
>> AND HERE ARE OUR MODELS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> SO ELEGANT.
>> YES.
AND SO THIS IS A PRINTED CHIFFON
DRESS.
I'M SORRY.
THIS IS A ROBE HERE.
THE ROBE WITH WIDE-LEGGED PANT.
>> THIS IS SO CUTE.
>> AND THIS IS A BELT HERE.
IT IS BEAUTIFUL.
IT WILL JAZZ UP EVERY OUTFIT,
AND WE HAVE THE DESIGNER HERE
WITH US.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WE HAVE TO KNOW WHAT INSPIRED
THIS, LIKE, LUXURIATING ON THE
BEACH LOOK.
>> SO I'M FROM A CARIBBEAN
BACKGROUND AND THIS COLLECTION
IS INSPIRED BY MY MOTHER.
SHE CAME FROM A CARIBBEAN ISLAND
CALLED GRENADA AND SHE CREATED A
BEAUTIFUL LIFE FOR HERSELF, SO I
WANTED TO PAY HOMAGE TO HER BY
DESIGNING A COLLECTION THAT
SHOWED HOW I VIEWED HER AS A
QUEEN, BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
I'M A NEW MOM AND I WANTED TO BE
COMFORTABLE AND LOOSE AND FLOWY.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
>> TELL YOU WHAT.
EVERYBODY COME ON OUT.
>> COME ON OUT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> WE CAN'T GET OUT OF HERE
WITHOUT LOOKING AT THE DESIGNERS
AGAIN.
WE WANT TO TELL YOU THAT YOU CAN
FIND MORE OF THESE GREAT
FASHIONS AT
HARLEMSFASHIONROW.COM.
AMAZING JOB, EVERYBODY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, BRANDICE.
COMING UP, WE HAVE INCREDIBLE
ART MADE FROM KISSES.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
In terms of treating
sensitivity,
3 days is really fast.
The dentist
is going to be able to provide
that to their patients.
Sensodyne Rapid Relief in my
opinion is a game changer.
It's going to let the dentist
offer their patient
sensitivity relief in 3 days.
It has a formulation
that lays down a barrier of
protection against sensitivity.
Within 3 days, say over the
course of a weekend
you're going to start feeling
significant results.
To say that it works in
3 days really is
a big deal.
This is Charlie not coughing
because he took Delsym 12-hour.
And this is Charlie still not
coughing
while trying his hardest not to
wake Zeus.
Delsym 12-hour.
Nothing lasts
longer for powerful
cough relief.
♪ ♪ ♪
THE THINGS THAT MATTER MOST
HAPPEN ONE MORNING
AND ONE CUP AT A TIME.
♪ ♪ ♪
You might take something
for your heart...
or joints.
HAPPEN ONE MORNING
AND ONE CUP AT A TIME.
But do you take something
for your brain.
With an ingredient originally
discovered in jellyfish,
Prevagen has been shown
in clinical trials
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. Healthier Brain.
Better Life.
Alice loves the smell
of Gain so much,
she wished it came in
a fabric softener too.
[throat clears]
Say hello to your fairy
godmother, Alice.
Oh and look they got Gain scent
beads and dryer sheets too!
Oui is so thick and creamy, it
can stay upside down.
Oui the french style yogurt.
YQ by Yoplait.
40% less sugar than the leading
Greek yogurt
and packed with protein.
Now that's smart.
(James)
I can't believe it could take
weeks to get our tax refund.
(Lisa)
At H&R Block, you could get an
Advance Refund up to
$3,000 the day you file.
(James)
We can get a pool table.
(Cori)
Or we can get the car fixed.
(Lisa VO) ♪
Up to $3,000 the day
you file at H&R Block.
Block has your back.
At Children's National,
stronger is caring for
a baby's heart
in the first 12 weeks
of pregnancy.
And a future when
prenatal pediatrics
leads to healthier children.
It's being the
number one newborn
intensive care unit
in the country.
And giving parents
peace of mind.
It's less recovering
in our bed,
and more jumping on yours.
Stronger is standing out
and standing proud.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>>> WELCOME BACK.
OUR NEXT GUEST IS AN ARTIST WHO
USES A VERY UNUSUAL MEDIUM FOR
HER WORK.
TAKE A LOOK.
♪
>> WOW.
>> PLEASE WELCOME ALEXIS FRASER,
AKA LIPSTICK LEX.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
SO HAPPY TO BE HERE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> HOW DO YOU FIGURE OUT YOU
COULD DO THIS?
TO DO THIS?
>> YEAH.
LET ME TELL YOU ABOUT THAT.
SO I USED TO BE, LIKE, A NORMAL
ARTIST.
I USED TO PAINT WITH REGULAR,
TRADITIONAL MATERIALS AND IT WAS
BACK IN 2006 I WAS WORKING WITH
A LOT OF OILS AND ACRYLICS AND I
WAS ALSO DABBLING IN A LOT OF
UNCONVENTIONAL METHODS BECAUSE I
WANTED TO DIFFERENTIATE MYSELF
IN THE WORLD OF ART.
I WANTED TO DO SOMETHING
DIFFERENT AND I WAS DABBLING IN
ALL THESE UNCONVENTIONAL METHODS
AND AT THAT TIME, I HAD SOMEBODY
CHALLENGE ME.
IF YOU CAN DO ALL THIS OTHER
UNCONVENTIONAL STUFF,
COULD YOU DO A PORTRAIT OF
MARILYN MONROE IN A WAY THAT
INCORPORATES MARILYN MONROE
WITHOUT USING PAINTS?
I WAS, LIKE, OH.
I HAD A PRETTY GOOD
BRAINSTORMING SESH, AND I
THOUGHT, WHAT IF I MADE MARILYN
OUT OF LIPSTICK AND MY KISSES
BECAUSE SHE WAS SO ICONIC FOR
BLOWING KISSES.
I HAD NO IDEA IF IT WOULD WORK,
AND IT DID, AND I LOVED IT AND
MY HUSBAND WORK LOVED IT.
>> CAN YOU SHOW US?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
HERE'S A PIECE THAT I'M WORKING
ON RIGHT NOW.
THIS PART, THE KISS FOR
VALENTINE'S DAY, WAS ALL
HAND-PAINTED WITH LIPSTICK, BUT
THIS PART RIGHT HERE,
I LEFT A LITTLE TAPE ON HERE
BECAUSE THIS IS LOOKING LIKE IT
NEEDS A COUPLE MORE KISSES.
>> FEW KISSES SHY OF A PAINTING.
>> EXACTLY.
I'M GOING TO PUT ON MY LIPSTICK
AND JUST KISS THE CANVAS.
SO THEN I TAKE OFF MY TAPE AND
THEN --
>> VOILA.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
VOILA.
>> CAN YOU SHOW US HOW TO DO IT?
>> YES.
OF COURSE.
>> I REALLY WANT TO SEE HOW THIS
IS DONE.
>> I HAVE NEVER PUT ON LIPSTICK.
>> WELL, THERE'S A FIRST TIME
FOR EVERYTHING.
>> YEAH.
THIS IS GOING TO BE INTERESTING.
>> WHAT COLORS ARE WE GOING FOR?
>> BLACK.
YOU ARE EDGY.
>> GIRL.
WHEN YOU SEE AN OPPORTUNITY --
>> THAT'S SO CUTE.
THAT'S SO CUTE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> YEP.
OH.
LOOK AT THAT.
SEE?
BEAUTIFUL TECHNIQUE.
LOOK AT THAT.
>> IT'S LIKE TOO LONG.
>> WHAM, BAM.
THERE WE GO.
YEAH.
AND SARA, LET ME SEE YOURS.
YOU WENT FOR THE BLACK ROSE.
>> I'M GOING FOR, LIKE,
LOVE/HATE OF A ROSE.
>> THAT'S PERFECT FOR
VALENTINE'S DAY.
WHAT WERE YOU WORKING ON?
>> I SAW YOUR PORTRAIT.
SARA --
>> SAMESIES.
>> BUT YOU NEVER HAVE SOMEBODY
DO A KISS PORTRAIT OF YOU
BEFORE.
SO HAPPY VALENTINE'S DAY.
>> YOU DID A PORTRAIT OF US?
>> YES.
YES.
>> IS THIS IT?
>> LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
YOU'RE LAUGHING AT MY LIPS, BUT
I CAN'T HELP IT.
>> DRUM ROLL, PLEASE.
>> LOOK HOW CUTE WE ARE.
>> WOW.
>> HOW DID YOU GET THE GAP?
WITH EXTRA TAPE?
>> THAT IS AMAZING.
>> THAT IS GORGEOUS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> IT'S AMAZING.
>> THAT IS SO BEAUTIFUL.
>> OH, BOY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND YOU DON'T HAVE TO ADJUST
THE COLOR OF YOUR TV.
YES, I AM WEARING LIPSTICK.
LIPSTICK LEX, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THIS IS REALLY AMAZING,
EVERYBODY.
YOU CAN SEE ALL DIFFERENT WAYS
TO DO OTHER THINGS.
TO MAKE IT MORE CREATIVE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU CAN PURCHASE HER WORK BY
VISITING LIPSTICKLEX.COM.
MAKE SURE YOU DO THAT.
NEXT UP, WE'RE COOKING WITH
CARLA HALL.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
old cre!
Remember when we all used to go
to the cafeteria
and just chow down midday?
-You mean, like, lunch?
-Come on. Voted
"Most Likely to Help People
Save $668 When They Switch."
-At this school?
-Didn't you get caught
in the laminating machine?
-Ha. [ Sighs ]
-"Box, have a great summer.
Danielle."
Ooh.
Danielle, control yourself.
I'd like to slow it down here
with a special discount
for a special girl.
Danielle, this one's for you.
(AVO) When a nasty cold won't
with a special discount
for a special girl.
let you sleep, try new NyQuil
Severe with Vicks VapoCOOL.
(Acapella) Whoa!
(AVO) And vaporize it.
(Acapella) Ahhhh!
(Acapella) Shhhh!
(AVO) New NyQuil Severe with
Vicks VapoCOOL.
The Vaporizing, Nighttime,
Coughing, Aching,
Stuffy head, Best sleep with a
cold, medicine.
Mom, Dinosaurs only eat Meat.
Actually, the biggest Dinos
only ate plants,
and Country Crock
is made with plants.
Country Crock has always
been made
with the goodness of plants.
It has real simple ingredients
and that same Country
fresh taste you love.
mmMMmmMMmm!
Welcome to Crock Country.
I'm a fighter.
Always have been.
When I found out I had
Age-related Macular
Degeneration,
AMD,
I wanted to fight back.
My doctor and I came up
with a plan.
It includes
PreserVision.
Only PreserVision
AREDS 2
has the exact
nutrient formula
recommended by the
National Eye Institute
to help reduce the risk
of progression of moderate
to advanced AMD.
That's why I fight.
Because it's
my vision.
PreserVision.
Also, in a great-tasting
chewable.
A dazzling place I never knew.
A new fantastic point of view.
No one to tell us no,
or where to go.
Or say we're only dreaming.
Let me share this whole
new world with you.
>> TECH: At Safelite AutoGlass
we know that when you're
spending time with the grandkids
every minute counts.
And you don't have time
for a cracked windshield.
That's why we
show you exactly
when we'll be there.
Saving you time, so you
can keep saving the world.
>> KIDS: ♪ Safelite repair,
Safelite replace ♪
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
You can't put a price on love.
But if you did,
it'd cost the exact same
as a Reese's.
Turns out love's kinda
inexpensive.
Not Sorry. Reese's.
Does removing makeup
feel like this?
Your skin deserves better.
Garnier Micellar Cleansing Water
with micelles that
work like a magnet.
It's a pure way to remove
stubborn makeup
without harsh rubbing.
Cleansing, reinvented.
Micellar Water.
By Garnier,
Naturally!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> WE ARE BACK NOW WITH OUR
FOOD CONTRIBUTOR AND JUST
IN-HOUSE GIRL, CARLA HALL.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE FOR US TODAY?
I SAW THE --
>> KISSES.
>> AND KISSES.
WE BARELY GOT THAT LIPSTICK OFF,
CARLA.
>> WHAT ARE WE MAKING?
>> TODAY WE'RE MAKING OPEN FACE
JOHNNYCAKE SANDWICHES.
THEY'RE IN THE SHAPE OF HEARTS.
>> WHAT IS A JOHNNYCAKE?
>> IT'S A CORNCAKE.
IT'S A CORN PANCAKE AND IT WAS A
CAKE THAT YOU WOULD MAKE THAT
WOULDN'T GET FLAT THAT PEOPLE
WOULD TRAVEL WITH.
>> FILLING.
>> FILLING AND DELICIOUS.
YOU'RE GOING TO PUT TOGETHER ALL
THE DRY INGREDIENTS INTO THAT
LARGE BOWL.
I HAVE CORNMEAL AND FLOUR,
BAKING POWDER, SALT AND A LITTLE
BIT OF SUGAR.
>> ALL OF IT?
>> YEP.
ALL OF IT.
ALL MEASURED.
>> YES.
YOU KNOW BETTER, CARLA.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO MIX THAT UP.
MIX THAT UP AND WHILE YOU'RE
DOING THAT, I'M GOING TO GET
YOUR DRY INGREDIENTS TOGETHER.
I HAVE EGGS.
GOING TO PUT IN SOME BUTTERMILK.
>> BUTTERMILK.
>> AND THEN I'M GOING TO ADD OIL
AND HAVE YOU MIX THE WET
INGREDIENTS.
THIS GOES IN HERE, AND THEN WE
HAVE SOME OIL.
THAT GETS MIXED UP.
WHILE YOU'RE MIXING THAT UP,
SARA, I'M GOING TO HAVE YOU
START THE FILLINGS.
>> COME ON, SARA.
>> TWO DIFFERENT KINDS OF
SANDWICHES.
AVOCADO.
SOMETHING ABOUT THE AVOCADO.
OKAY?
>> STIR IT WITH THAT KNIFE.
>> YEP.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE THAT
AVOCADO AND WHILE YOU GUYS ARE
MAKING THAT, I'M GOING TO GO
AHEAD AND MAKE MY JOHNNYCAKE.
>> I'M ALL WHIPPED UP HERE.
>> THAT LOOKS GREAT.
SO YOU CAN ACTUALLY PROBABLY DO
THE MAKING.
>> OF COURSE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO --
[ APPLAUSE ]
SARA.
>> I'M LEARNING.
>> SARA.
>> WHAT A BEAUTIFUL AVOCADO THAT
IS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I'M JUST SO --
>> TAKE THE SPOON AND SCOOP IT
OUT INTO THIS BOWL.
YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE ROUNDS AND
MAKE THE ROUNDS ABOUT THAT BIG
BECAUSE WE'RE --
>> HOW MUCH?
LIKE THAT?
>> ENOUGH TO PUNCH OUT HERE.
SO LARGER.
YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE THOSE
ROUNDS, OKAY?
AND SARA, WE'RE GOING TO TAKE
THIS -- THIS LOOKS BEAUTIFUL,
AND WHEN YOU ARE MAKING
PANCAKES, MAKE SURE THE GRIDDLE
IS HOT ENOUGH AND THE
JOHNNYCAKES ARE BUBBLING UP AND
PANCAKES WILL BE NICE AND BROWN
AND YOU WILL FLIP THEM.
SARA, YOU'LL PUT IN A LITTLE
SALT IN HERE, AND THEN WE'RE
GOING TO ADD A LITTLE BIT OF
LEMON JUICE.
CHUNKY, YOU'RE GOING TO MIX THAT
UP, OKAY?
>> LIKE WITH A FORK?
>> YEAH.
WITH A FORK.
HERE'S A TIP FOR YOU.
SO WHEN YOU ARE TRYING TO KEEP
YOUR AVOCADOS GREEN OR YOUR
GUACG
GUACAMOLE --
>> I NEED TO KNOW THIS.
MINE BROWN.
>> ADD THE PITS.
WHAT THE PIT IS DOING IS
COVERING THE SPACE WHERE THE
AVOCADO IS.
BUT IF YOU TAKE A PIECE OF
PLASTIC AND JUST PRESS RIGHT
ONTO THE AVOCADO, THEN THAT WILL
BE DELICIOUS TOO.
WE'RE GOING TO LET THOSE COOK.
HERE WE HAVE SOME RIGHT HERE.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S WHAT THAT'S GOING TO LOOK
LIKE ONCE I STAMP THEM OUT.
>> WE'RE GOING TO PUNCH THEM
OUT.
WE HAVE THE LOVE RIGHT HERE.
MICHAEL, WE'RE GOING TO TAKE
SOME MUSTARD.
WE TAKE OUR HAM AND WE'RE GOING
TO PUT THAT ON THERE.
>> IS MUSTARD THAT EXCITING?
>> I KNOW.
IT'S EXCITING, AND WHILE YOU'RE
OVER THERE, I'M GOING TO CUT
SOME EGGS.
SARA, CAN I HAVE YOUR KNIFE?
I'M GOING TO SHE YOU A TRICK.
WHERE IS THAT KNIFE, SARA?
>> I COULDN'T GET IT OFF.
WE DIDN'T COVER THAT.
>> I'M GOING TO CUT THE EGGS,
SPRAY MY KNIFE.
>> THIS IS A LITTLE TRICK.
>> WITH A LITTLE BIT OF OIL, AND
THE YOLK DOES NOT --
>> YOU SPRAY THE KNIFE.
OH.
I WAS WONDERING HOW YOU DID
THAT.
>> YES.
YES.
THEN WE'RE GOING TO TAKE OUR EGG
AND PUT IT ON HERE.
SARA, WHAT WHAT ABOUT PUTTING
GUACAMOLE ON HERE?
ARE YOU EATING ALREADY?
>> NOPE, NOPE, NOPE.
>> YOU CAN BE.
YOU CAN BE EATING ALREADY.
WE'RE GOING TO DO THIS.
PUT SOME MORE EGG ON TOP.
EGG ON THERE.
>> PUT YOUR EGG ON TOP, YEAH.
>> THAT LOOKS SO GORGEOUS.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
>> EGG ON TOP.
>> CAN I THROW SOME CHIVES?
>> CHIVES.
>> YOU WANT TO BE SALT BAE,
MICHAEL.
>> NO.
I'M KIND OF --
>> THIS IS SO GOOD, AND WHAT I
LOVE ABOUT THIS, MIX UP YOUR
OPENED-FACE SANDWICHES AND IT'S
DELICIOUS.
>> IT'S VERY DELICIOUS AND I
TELL YOU RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE GOING TO EAT AND WE'LL BE
RIGHT BACK, EVERYBODY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
We're Oscar Mayer Deli Fresh and
you may remember us from...
Your very first sandwich,
Your move-in-day...feast.
Your bold canine caper.
[child] That's not for you,
Bandit!
Your dinner in the dark.
Your mammoth masterpiece.
[whispering] Your 3:47 AM snack.
And...whatever happened here...
Because we make Deli Fresh
with all the good of the deli,
no artificial preservatives and
no added nitrates or nitrites.
Make every sandwich count
with Oscar Mayer Deli Fresh.
In one week...
a lot will happen in your life.
Wrinkles just
won't.
Neutrogena®
Rapid Wrinkle
Repair's
derm-proven retinol
works so fast,
it takes only one week
to reveal younger looking skin.
Neutrogena®
90% of women
have a skincare routine.
But what about a
lip care routine?
Pay your lips some attention.
The ChapStick Total
Hydration Collection.
Exfoliate
Nourish
Naturally enhance
your lips.
ChapStick.
Put your lips first.
When your blanket's freshness
fades
before the binge-watching
begins...
that's when you know,
it's half-washed.
Next time,
add Downy Fabric Conditioner
for up to 7 days of Downy
freshness.
Downy and it's done.
♪
Cats will do anything
for the irresistible taste of
TEMPTATIONS™ treats.
What are you doing?
Oh hey, check this out.
TEMPTATIONS ™.
All
It Takes
Is A Shake™.
Now, eyeliner goes NYC-proof.
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil
All
It Takes
from Maybelline New York.
Smudge resistant.
Sweat resistant.
Waterproof.
Up to 36-hour wear.
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil.
Only from Maybelline New York.
>>> JUSSIE SMOLLETT, IS STAR OF
THE HIT SHOW, "EMPIRE."
HIS STORY SHOCKED THE NATION.
>> WHAT HAPPENED THAT NIGHT?
>> NOW TOMORROW HE SPEAKS OUT TO
ROBIN ROBERTS IN HIS FIRST
INTERVIEW.
>> AT ANY POINT DURING THE
ATTACK, DID YOU FEAR FOR YOUR
LIFE?
>> THE EXCLUSIVE TOMORROW ONLY
ON "GMA."
>>> SO THERE'S A NEW BABYSITTER
IN DAYTIME?
>> I'M GOING TO GO TO YOUR HOUSE
AND YOU'RE TRUSTING ME WITH YOUR
KIDS.
>> MICHAEL STRAHAN IS COMING TO
PLAY WITH YOU NEXT WEEK.
>> BIG BLACK MAN IS HERE.
SURPRISE.
YOU WAIT.
WHEN YOU COME HOME, THEY'RE
GOING TO BE, LIKE, MAMA WHO?
>> AND TOMORROW, KELSEY GRAMMER
IS POPPING BY.
THIS WEEK WE'RE KICKING IT UP
WITH K-POP SENSATION BLACKPINK
ON "STRAHAN AND SARA."
>> WE GOT IT ALL.
>> LUNCHTIME ON ABC.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS.
JOIN US TOMORROW FOR VALENTINE'S
DAY.
KELSEY GRAMMER WILL BE HERE.
WE WANT TO THANK EVERYBODY FOR
WATCHING.
>> THANK YOU, CARLA, FOR FEEDING
US ONCE AGAIN.
>> NO PROBLEM.
>> HAVE A GREAT --
>> LET ME SAY IT.
HAVE A GREAT DAY, EVERYBODY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]