>>> HI, YOU GUYS.
COMING UP ON THE SHOW TODAY,
"REAL HOUSEWIVES OF BEVERLY
HILLS" STAR KYLE RICHARDS IS
HERE.
>> AND MAGICIAN ROB LAKE.
>> YES, AND WE HAVE A BOWLING
PIG.
>> PIGGY.
>> I SAID IT, AND WE HAVE THE
GREATEST AUDIENCE IN TELEVISION.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> FROM THE CROSS ROADS OF THE
WORLD, TIMES SQUARE, NEW YORK
CITY, IT'S "STRAHAN AND SARA."
ESCAPE FOR AN HOUR.
WE ALL NEED IT.
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> YO, YO, YO, YO.
HELLO, HELLO, HELLO, EVERYBODY.
HOW YOU DOING, SARA HAINES?
>> I'LL BEGIN IN A SECOND.
I THINK IT'S ON.
>> IT'S ON?
THERE WE GO.
KEEP IT GOING.
>> MAMA LIKEY.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU PICKED
THAT CHAIR YESTERDAY.
I'LL BE HONEST WITH YOU.
>> SOMETIMES I NEED A PEDICURE
JUST TO GET INTO THE CHAIR.
DAYS ARE ROUGH SOMETIMES.
>> DAYS ARE ROUGH SOMETIMES, BUT
SPEAKING OF ROUGH DAYS, I SAW
THIS CLIP LAST NIGHT, OKAY?
IT IS AN EXPLOSIVE INTERVIEW.
IT WAS GIVEN ON MORNING
TELEVISION IN AUSTRALIA.
>> OKAY.
>> AND I'LL TELL YOU RIGHT NOW.
YOU GUYS -- I'M GLAD YOU'RE
SITTING DOWN.
BUCKLE UP.
BUCKLE UP BECAUSE -- GET READY
FOR THIS.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
>> MICHAEL BOLTON JOINS US LIVE
FROM FLORIDA.
GOOD MORNING AND WELCOME BACK TO
THE SHOW.
MICHAEL, YOU GOT US OKAY?
MAYBE HE'S JUST ON INSTAGRAM.
>> HI, MICHAEL.
WE'RE WITH YOU LIVE.
>> IT'S GONE SILENT.
>> MICHAEL, CAN YOU HEAR US
AFTER SUCH A GREAT INTRO?
WE DON'T WANT TO WASTE --
MICHAEL BOLTON, LIVE IN FLORIDA.
CAN YOU HEAR US?
>> DID YOU HEAR HIM?
HE GOES, IT'S GONE SILENT.
IT'S, LIKE, HE'S LISTENING TO
HIS OWN MUSIC.
I LOVE ME SOME MICHAEL BOLTON,
BUT THAT STUFF IS SOOTHING.
>> THEY TRIED TO SAY IT WAS A
TECHNICAL GLITCH.
>> HOW DO YOU SAVE THAT ONE?
>> THERE'S NO WAY OF SAVING THAT
ONE.
>> YOU CAN'T COME BACK.
>> MY MAN WAS TIRED.
WHAT CAN YOU SAY?
I LOVE MICHAEL BOLTON.
>> I DO TOO.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU ALSO KNOW THAT I LOVE A GOOD
NETFLIX BINGE.
I HAVE BEEN WATCHING THE
DOCUMENTARY
SERIES "CONVERSATIONS WITH A
KILLER: THE TED BUNDY TAPES",
AND THE CENTER SEEMED TO NOTE
SOMETHING ABOUT THE THE FAMED
SERIAL KILLER WHICH I THINK WAS
NOTABLE AT THE TIME.
HE IS A GOOD-LOOKING GUY.
TITAN HAS PAID $9 MILLION TO
ACQUIRE THE RIGHTS TO THE
FILM, "EXTREMELY WICKED,
SHOCKINGLY VIOLENT AND EVIL."
THIS IS A BIOPIC STARRING ZAC
EF
EFRON WHO IS ALSO GOOD LOOKING.
NETFLIX TWEETED, I HAVE SEEN A
LOT OF TALK ABOUT TED BUNDY'S
ALLEGED HOTNESS, AND WOULD LIKE
TO GENTLY REMIND EVERYONE THAT
THERE ARE LITERALLY THOUSANDS OF
HOT MEN ON THE SERVICE, ALMOST
ALL OF WHOM ARE NOT CONVICTED
SERIAL KILLERS.
>> TRUE.
>> THAT'S A GOOD POINT.
IT RAISES A GOOD CONVERSATION
FLOATING AROUND THE INTERNET
RIGHT NOW.
ARE WE ROMANTICIZING TED BUNDY?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> WELL, NO.
YOU CAN SAY HE'S A GOOD-LOOKING
GUY, BUT BEING A GOOD-LOOKING
GUY IS THE REASON HE GOT AWAY
WITH WHAT HE WAS DOING FOR SO
LONG.
IF YOU ARE DOING A STORY ABOUT
TED BUNDY, YOU HAVE TO DO IT IN
THE MOST ACCURATE WAY AS
POSSIBLE.
IT WAS MADE SO PEOPLE CAN BE
AWARE THAT THERE IS MORE THAN
ONE LOOK TO A SERIAL KILLER.
>> YEAH, AND I THINK THAT'S WHY
ASIDE FROM HIM USING THAT AT THE
TIME, WE HADN'T SEEN SERIAL
KILLERS AT ALL, AND PEOPLE
AUTOMATICALLY ASSOCIATED A
CERTAIN LOOK WITH WHAT A
CRIMINAL WAS.
SO WITHOUT THIS ELEMENT OF THE
STORY, YOU WOULD BE BETRAYING
THE WHOLE STORY.
SO I DON'T THINK IT'S MAKING IT
ROMANTIC BY SEEING THESE TAPES
BY THE WAY.
THE MOVIE IS NOT OUT YET.
THE TAPES MAKE HIM A VILE
CREATURE.
NOTHING ABOUT WHEN YOU LOOK AT
HIM IS GOOD-LOOKING.
IT'S, LIKE, A BAD DATE WHERE THE
GUY IS REALLY HOT AND HE'S,
LIKE -- WHEN I WATCH TED BUNDY,
I SEE DEATH AND EVIL IN HIS EYES
AND THERE IS NOTHING
GOOD-LOOKING ABOUT THAT.
>> WHEN HE'S UP ON TRIAL FOR
SERIAL KILLING, ALL THESE
WOMEN --
>> YEAH.
>> WERE STILL COMING TO SEE HIM
AND WRITING HIM LETTERS AND I
DON'T UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> WELL, THAT'S A UNIQUE
PSYCHOLOGY.
YOU SEE THAT WITH A LOT OF
PEOPLE.
YOU SEE IT WITH R. KELLY
ACTUALLY.
WOMEN THAT SHOW UP AT COURT.
>> TRUE.
>> THERE IS A STRAIN OF WOMEN
THAT THERE IS SOMETHING THAT
NEEDS TO BE STUDIED THERE, BUT
THAT IS NOT REPRESENTATIVE OF
THE SOCIETY AS A WHOLE.
MAMA SHOPS ELSEWHERE FOR HER
MEN, OKAY?
>> SO WE GOT THE TED -- WE NEED
ANOTHER DOCUMENTARY CALLED "WHAT
THE HELL IS WRONG WITH YOU?"
>> NEXT YEAR.
NEXT YEAR.
>> NEXT YEAR'S DOCUMENTARY.
OKAY.
YOU KNOW -- I LOVE HAWAII.
DO YOU LOVE HAWAII?
>> OH, YES.
ALOHA.
>> RIGHT?
BUT YOU MAY NOT IF YOU ARE A
SMOKER BECAUSE THERE IS A NEW
BILL THAT'S BEING CONSIDERED BY
LAWMAKERS IN HAWAII THAT COULD
RAISE THE LEGAL SMOKING AGE FROM
21 TO 100.
YES.
>> SO ALL TEN PEOPLE THAT TURNED
100 CAN SMOKE IN HAWAII.
>> THERE IS A DIFFERENT CREDIT.
HIS NAME IS RICHARD KRIEGEN AND
HE USED TO BE AN EMERGENCY ROOM
PHYSICIAN.
BEFORE HE BECAME ELECTED STATE
REPRESENTATIVE AND HE IS SAYING
IT'S THE DEADLIEST ARTIFACT IN
HUMAN HISTORY, SMOKING IS.
HE WANTS TO CHANGE IT FROM 21 TO
100 BECAUSE NICOTINE IS AS
ADDICTIVE AS HEROIN.
>> SAY THAT AGAIN.
>> IT IS AS ADDICTIVE AS HEROIN.
HE'S WORRIED ABOUT THAT, AND DO
YOU THINK IT'S RIGHT FOR THE
GOVERNMENT TO BE ABLE TO TELL
YOU WHAT TO DO WITH YOUR BODY
WHEN YOU ARE OVER 21?
>> IN MOST INSTANCES, NO.
WHEN IT COMES TO, LIKE, SODA
BANS AND EVERYTHING ELSE, STAY
OUT OF MY HOUSE.
I DON'T THINK HEROIN SHOULD BE
LEGAL.
I DON'T THINK SMOKING SHOULD BE
I ACTUALLY AM OKAY WITH --
BECAUSE I DON'T THINK TAXING
HELPS BECAUSE IT'S AN ADDICTION
AND AN ILLNESS.
YOU'RE MONETIZING SOMEONE'S
SICKNESS.
WE SHOULD NOT MAKE MONEY OFF OF
IT BY SAYING WE DON'T APPROVE OF
THIS.
IT'S REALLY DANGEROUS FOR YOU.
I THINK THAT WOULD BE A GOOD
STEP IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
I'M MOVING TO HAWAII.
>> BUT I KIND OF FEEL LIKE IF
I'M OVER -- I'M 21 AND OVER, I
SHOULD BE ABLE TO DO WHAT I WANT
TO DO.
I MEAN, I DON'T WANT TO BE 88
YEARS OLD AND I'M GOING TO THE
GROCERY STORE.
CAN I GET A PACK OF SMOKES?
AND THEY CARD ME.
I'M 88.
88-YEAR-OLD MAN GETTING CARDED
FOR CIGARETTES?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
>> IF YOU SMOKE, YOU'LL BE LUCKY
TO MAKE IT TO 88, AND I DON'T
THINK SHE SHOULD BE -- I DON'T
THINK CIGARETTES SHOULD BE SOLD
NEXT TO THE SKITTLES.
I JUST DON'T.
[ APPLAUSE ]
THAT'S ME TAPPING YOU OUT.
A LITTLE MOVE ON.
>> OF ALL THE THINGS, YOU PICK
ON THE SKITTLES.
GIRL, LEAVE THE SKITTLES ALONE.
I LOVE SKITTLES.
I COULD NOT WAIT TO GET TO THIS
STORY.
>> YOU'RE SO EXCITED ABOUT THIS.
>> DID YOU HEAR THIS?
I'M A KING.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> MICHAEL.
MICHAEL.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> FIRST OF ALL, YOU NEED TO
ADDRESS ME AS KING MICHAEL, BUT
DID YOU WATCH THE SEGMENT ON
ANCESTRY, "GOOD MORNING AMERICA"
YESTERDAY?
>> YOU'RE ON, LIKE, 58 SHOWS.
THERE ARE NOT ENOUGH HOURS IN
THE DAY.
I MIGHT HAVE MISSED THAT ONE.
>> I WATCH ALL YOUR SHOWS.
>> I'M ON ONE SHOW, AND I SIT
THREE FEET FROM YOU.
YOU BETTER BE WATCHING.
>> WHATEVER.
BUT ANYWAY, ALL I KNOW IS THAT
RENOWNED HISTORIC PROFESSOR
HENRY LOUIS GATES JR., HE TRACED
MY LINEAGE BACK THROUGH THE
CENTURIES.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> WHEN WE TRACED MY LINEAGE
EVEN FURTHER BACK -- I'M A KING,
Y'ALL.
>> CHARLAMAGNE IS YOUR 39th
GREAT GRANDFATHER.
>> WHAT?
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> YES.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, BABY THAT'S
RIGHT.
I AM A DESCENDENT OF
CHARLAMAGNE.
YES.
NO.
NOT THAT CHARLAMAGNE.
THE OTHER ONE.
THE OTHER CHARLAMAGNE.
YES, THE KING OF THE FRANKS.
THAT'S HIM RIGHT THERE.
WHAT'S UP, GREAT GRANDPA?
HOLLER AT ME.
YOU CAN JUST CALL ME KING
STRAHAN.
>> MICHAEL, ONE, I HAVE
CELEBRATED HALLOWEEN AS WELL.
TWO, THIS IS NOT A MONARCHY,
OKAY?
WE DO NOT LIVE IN A MONARCHY.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER BECAUSE IF
YOU HAVE ONE DROP OF ROYAL BLOOD
FLOWING THROUGH YOUR VEINS LIKE
I DO, YOU'RE A KING.
YOU'RE A KING.
>> I DON'T THINK THAT'S HOW IT
WORKS.
>> THEY GREW UP IN GERMANY.
DOES THAT MAKE ME THE RIGHTFUL
KING OF GERMANY?
RORY.
>> YEAH, MICHAEL?
I MEAN, MY LIEGE?
>> THAT'S BETTER.
RORY, CALL ANGELA MERKEL.
I WANT THE TRANSFER OF POWER TO
GO AS SMOOTHLY AS POSSIBLE,
OKAY?
I'M TAKING OVER.
>> YOU KNOW, I LOVE YOU MORE
THAN ANYTHING IN THE WORLD.
YOU'RE NOT A KING.
>> I'LL TELL YOU RIGHT NOW.
IF I'M NOT A KING, EXPLAIN THIS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WHY DO YOU DO THIS, YOU GUYS?
YOU'RE FEEDING IT.
THAT IS SAL.
HE'S ONE OF OUR STAGE HANDS.
HE LITERALLY -- IT'S HIS JOB TO
HAND YOU THINGS.
>> HE ONLY DID IT BECAUSE I'M
KING.
>> HE WOULD DO IT FOR ME IF I
ASKED.
>> SHE'S RIGHT, MR. KING
STRAHAN.
SHE'S RIGHT.
>> BACK TO THE DUNGEON.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> POOR SAL.
>> WOULD YOU MIND TASTING THAT?
>> NO.
MICHAEL, NO ONE'S POISONING YOU.
>> MY ENEMIES.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE ANY ENEMIES.
EVERYBODY LOVES YOU.
>> OTHER SHOWS ARE ENEMIES.
LIKE "THE TONIGHT SHOW WITH
JIMMY FALLON."
>> "THE TONIGHT SHOW" ISN'T EVEN
ON THE SAME TIME WE ARE.
>> I BELIEVE IT'S TIME TO LAY
SEED TO THE CLAN OF THE 30 ROCK.
I HEREBY DECLARE WAR ON "THE
TONIGHT SHOW."
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
TWO CAN PLAY AT THIS GAME.
I MAY NOT COME FROM ROYAL BLOOD,
BUT I DECLARE MY -- WINTER IS
COMING.
♪ DUN DUN DUN DUN DUN DUN ♪
I DECLARE MYSELF QUEEN WITH MY
DRAGONS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THE KING HAS CHOSEN TO END
THIS SEGMENT.
THAT IS RIGHT.
>>> COMING UP, WE HAVE GOT A PIG
THAT BOWLS.
THIS PLEASES THE KING.
BRING ON THE PIG.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I tell everyone to
take the AncestryDNA test
if you want to
get the most details
about your
family history.
My pie chart showed that
I'm from all over Europe,
but then it
got super specific.
I learned my
people came from
a small
region in Poland
and even a little
bit of the history
about why they might have
migrated during that time.
Those migration
patterns are more
than just
lines on a map,
they're really
your family's story.
I can't wait to see what
I'm going to discover next.
20 million members
have connected
to a deeper family story.
Order your kit at Ancestry.com.
I use this
every day
But is Beth's soap
as clean rinsing as Dove?
My soap's still leaving
plenty of things behind
But Dove is cleaner rinsing
My soap,
...Dove.
Made with 1/4
moisturizing cream...
Dove cleans and cares
beautifully.
♪ If you love me, love me,
love me like you say ♪
♪ Darling, tell me
all the ways ♪
♪ Tell me all the ways ♪
♪ All the ways ♪
At the store, or to your door.
Target Run and Done.
This is why we no
longer have to worry
about flushing too
much toilet paper.
Rid-X contains
billions of enzymes
proven to break down even paper
to help keep your whole
septic system healthy.
For paper, grease or waste
breakdown,
use Rid-X.
Stop fearing your alarm clock...
With ZzzQuil PURE Zzzs.
A drug-free blend of botanicals
with melatonin
that supports your natural sleep
cycle
so you can seize the morning.
ZzzQuil PURE Zzzs.
Gentle means everything,
so we improved everything.
We used 50% fewer ingredients
Added one handed pumps
And beat the
top safety standards
The new JOHNSON'S®
Choose Gentle
From our crazy delicious family
to yours.
Crave those crazy squares.
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
♪♪
Your toothpaste may taste fresh,
but is it removing
enough harmful plaque
from hard to reach areas?
Try Arm & Hammer Complete Care.
Its unique 50% baking soda
formula neutralizes acid
and removes
up to 5X more plaque.
Try Arm & Hammer Complete Care.
Hey! It's me! Your dry skin!
I'm craving something
we're missing.
The ceramides in CeraVe.
They help restore
my natural barrier,
so I can lock in moisture...
and keep us protected.
We've got to have
each other's backs...
and fronts.
CeraVe. What your skin CraVes.
>>> HEY, MICHAEL.
HOW BIG IS YOUR CHAIR?
>> SOMETHING'S DIFFERENT ABOUT
YOU.
>> MY HAIR.
I GOT IT TRIMMED.
YOU'RE SO CUTE.
MAX DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE.
>> NO.
IT'S NOT ABOUT YOUR HAIR.
YOU GOT A NEW CHAIR.
YOU'RE SO HIGH UP.
I SHOULD HAVE GOT A NEW CHAIR.
>> IT'S NOT ABOUT THE SIZE OF
THE CHAIR, MICHAEL.
>> ANYWAY.
>> THIS WEEK, LOOK WHO'S HANGING
HERE.
IT'S WILL ARNETT.
>> YES.
DON'T WE JUST WANT TO HAVE SOME
FUN?
>> "STRAHAN AND SARA."
>> WE GOT IT ALL.
>> LUNCHTIME AT 1:00 EASTERN,
12:00 CENTRAL AND PACIFIC RIGHT
HERE ON ABC.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>>> WELCOME BACK TO THE SHOW.
AND YES, YOU HAVE GOT TO ADJUST
YOUR TELEVISIONS.
WE ARE HOLDING PIGS BECAUSE WE
WANTED TO CELEBRATE THE CHINESE
NEW YEAR WHICH IS THE YEAR OF
THE PIG.
JOINING US IS ANIMAL TRAINER
GRANT KIMMERER.
HEY.
HEY, GRANT.
>> GLAD TO BE HERE.
>> ONE OF THEM POOPED.
WAS THAT YOURS OR MINE?
>> MINE.
THANK YOU FOR POINTING THAT OUT.
>> SPOILER ALERT.
THERE IS A PIG THAT BOWLS
THOUGH.
>> I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THAT.
>> AND I HAVE GOT SO SAY,
USUALLY THE WAY I'M HOLDING THE
PIG IS HOW I HOLD A FOOTBALL.
SO I APOLOGIZE.
AND THIS PIG IS GETTING ME BACK
BECAUSE IT'S COMING FROM BOTH
ENDS ALL OVER ME.
SO WHAT IS THE NAME OF THIS --
THIS NICE LITTLE FELLOW?
>> YOU'RE HOLDING POLLY.
>> POLLY.
>> THAT IS JANET.
>> JANET.
>> YOU NAMED THIS PIG JANET?
>> SURE.
PIGS NEED NAMES.
>> PIGS NEED NAMES, YEAH.
>> THIS IS A 2-MONTH-OLD AND A
4-MONTH-OLD KUNEKUNE PIG AND IT
IS A NEW ZEALAND BREED OF
DOM
DOMESTICATED PIG THAT TRANSLATES
TO ROUND AND FAT.
>> THAT'S WHAT IT MEANS?
>> QUITE APPROPRIATE.
>> THAT EXPLAINS A LOT.
ARE PIGS SAFE TO HAVE?
MILEY CYRUS HAS ONE.
ARIANA GRANDE HAS ONE.
NOW MICHAEL AND I HAVE ONE.
>> THEY'RE ABSOLUTELY SAFE, BUT
AS FAR AS BEING A GOOD PET,
THAT'S A DIFFERENT CONVERSATION.
>> DO THEY BITE?
THERE ARE SOME TEETH ON THIS
LITTLE --
>> ABSOLUTELY THEY CAN BITE.
THEY ARE BORN WITH A FULL SET OF
TEETH AND THEY WILL BITE EACH
OTHER.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY, BUT THE
THING ABOUT PIGS AS A PET, YOU
KNOW, LIKE ANY PET, YOU NEED TO
BE EMPATHETIC.
YOU NEED TO BE CONCERNED WITH
THE ANIMAL'S NEEDS AND YOU DON'T
WANT TO JUST GET ONE ON A WHIM
AND WIND UP NOT WANTING IT.
GETTING RID OF IT,
IT'S NOT A GOOD LIFE FOR THE
ANIMAL.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE GET PIGS AND
REALIZE WE CAN'T TAKE CARE OF
IT.
>> PETS IN GENERAL.
>> LET'S GO TO THE NEW
SMITHSONIAN CHANNEL DOCUMENTARY.
TRYING TO TAKE MY READ HERE.
IT'S COMING OUT SOON.
IT'S CALLED "AMAZING PIGS," AND
WHAT'S THE ONE THING YOU
LEARNED --
>> IN THE BAHAMAS, I FED THOSE.
>> WHAT'S THE ONE THING THAT
BLEW YOUR MIND?
>> EXACTLY.
THE PIGS IN THE BAHAMAS.
ANY FOUR-LEGGED MAMMAL CAN SWIM,
BUT THEY DOGGY PADDLE.
SLOTHS CAN SWIM.
BUT THESE PIGS IN THE BAHAMAS,
15, 20 FEET OF WATER.
THEY'RE PADDLING AROUND.
>> THEY COME AT YOU.
>> THEY'RE SMART, AND THEY LEARN
WITH THESE BOATS AND TWO-LEGGED
CREATURES AND IT MEANS FOOD.
THEY SWIM RIGHT OUT TO GET IT.
IT'S PHENOMENAL.
THEY HAVE TAKEN OVER EVERY
CONTINENT ON THE PLANET OTHER
THAN ANTARCTICA.
>> PIG BOWLING, MAN.
YOU PROMISED US SOME PIG
BOWLING.
>> YES.
>> WE'RE GOING TO BRING OUT THE
WILD BOAR OF THE BOWLING -- FROM
THE BOWLING ALLEY.
THIS IS HAMMY THE PIG.
>> HAMMY.
>> WHAT KIND OF PIG IS HAMMY?
>> HE'S A TEACUP.
THIS IS THE PIG THAT, YOU
KNOW, --
>> THAT'S THE LITTLE ONE?
>> THEY GROW TO BE MUCH LARGER
THAN WHAT YOU WOULD SUSPECT.
KEEP IN MIND.
HAMMY CAN GET 100 TO EVEN 200
POUNDS.
>> WHAT IS HAMMY RIGHT NOW?
>> HE'S A SOLID 25 POUNDS.
SO A LOT OF GROWTH.
A LOT MORE GROWTH.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
HE PULLED A HAMSTRING IN
REHEARSAL SO WE'LL MAKE IT A
LITTLE BIT EASIER FOR HIM.
HE'S A MUCH LIGHTER ONE.
>> YOU SAY HE WAS PUSHING JUST
FROM THE OTHER END.
>> THERE YOU GO.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
OH, MAN.
>> YOU'RE EXCITED TOO.
THERE WE GO.
OH.
>> I GOT IT.
I GOT HER.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COMING.
>> DON'T STEP.
DON'T STEP.
>> I GOT -- HEY.
I GOT TO THANK YOU.
THANK YOU FOR STOPPING BY.
THANK YOU GUYS JUST FOR DROPPING
WHEN YOU CAME OUT.
IF YOU ARE A PIG LOVER, YOU CAN
CATCH "AMAZING PIGS"
ON THE SMITHSONIAN -- DON'T BE
AFRAID TO COME UP HERE WITH THE
PIGGIES.
IT'S ON THE SMITHSONIAN CHANNEL
FEBRUARY THE 13th AT 8:00 P.M.
I HAD A PET PIG BACK IN THE DAY.
THEY ARE AMAZING.
>> DON'T ASK WHAT HAPPENED TO
THE PIG.
>> WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
>>> COMING UP, "REAL HOUSEWIVES"
STAR KYLE RICHARDS IS HERE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> IT'S YOUR LAST CHANCE TO
SAVE BIG ON OUR "DEALS &
STEALS."
GET TO GOODMORNINGAMERICA.COM
NOW.
WE PARTNER WITH COMPANIES ON
ITEMS THAT ARE ALL UNDER $20,
BUT HURRY BECAUSE THESE DEALS
LAST ONLY TILL MIDNIGHT.
♪
She's doing it again.
(VO) No cover up spray here...
It's the irresistibly fresh
scent of Febreze Air Effects.
Cheaper aerosols can cover up
odors,
burying the smell in a
flowery fog.
Switch to Febreze Air Effects!
Febreze eliminates even the
toughest odors from the air.
And it uses an all-natural
propellant to leave behind
a pleasant scent you'll love.
Use anywhere odors can spread.
Freshen up, don't cover up.
Febreze Air Effects.
(coughs)
Hi Susan!
Honey? I respect that.
But that cough looks
pretty bad...
try this NEW Robitussin Honey.
The real honey you love...
Plus the powerful cough
relief you need.
Mind if I root through
your trash?
New Robitussin Honey.
Because it's never just a cough.
Mascara in a snap.
New Snapscara from
Maybelline New York.
Smooth, clump-free volume.
Pure pigment formula means...
it's on & off in a snap!
No raccoon eyes.
Smooth, clump-free volume.
New Snapscara!
Only from Maybelline New York.
This is nice.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is nice.
Mmmm how did you make the
dip so rich and creamy?
Oh, it's a Philadelphia-
-Family Recipe.
Can I see it?
No.
New Philadelphia Dips.
So good,
you'll take all the credit.
I've always been amazed
by what's next.
And still going for my best,
even though I live with
a higher risk of stroke
due to Afib not caused by
a heart valve problem.
So if there's a better treatment
than warfarin...
I want that too.
ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS is proven
to reduce stroke risk
better than warfarin.
Plus has significantly less
major bleeding than warfarin.
ELIQUIS is FDA-approved
and has both.
What's next?
Reeling in a nice one.
Don't stop taking ELIQUIS
unless your doctor tells you to,
as stopping increases your risk
of having a stroke.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS If you have
an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily
and it may take longer than
usual for any bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care
for sudden sign of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase your
bleeding risk
if you take certain medicines.
Tell your doctor
about all planned medical
or dental procedures.
ELIQUIS, the number one
cardiologist-prescribed
blood thinner.
Ask your doctor if ELIQUIS
is what's next for you.
You might take something
for your heart...
or joints.
But do you take something
for your brain.
With an ingredient originally
discovered in jellyfish,
Prevagen has been shown
in clinical trials
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. Healthier Brain.
Better Life.
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
Allergies with sinus
congestion and pressure?
You won't find relief here.
Go to the pharmacy counter
for powerful Claritin-D.
While the leading allergy spray
only relieves 6 symptoms,
Claritin-D relieves 8, including
sinus congestion and pressure.
Claritin-D relieves more.
>>> CAN WE GET MORE ROLEXS ON
THE ROCKS, NO SALT?
[ CHEERS ]
>> BONJOUR.
A HOT AIR BALLOON WILL BE
PICKING YOU UP AT NOON.
>> JUST REALLY MAKES YOU FEEL
LIKE YOU'RE IN EUROPE.
>> WE ARE IN EUROPE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> WOW.
>> NOW THAT SOUNDS LIKE A GOOD
TIME AND THAT'S WHAT 50 LOOKS
LIKE FOR OUR NEXT GUEST.
#GOALS.
PLEASE WELCOME OUR NEXT GUEST
FROM BEVERLY HILLS, KYLE
RICHARDS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> HI.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> GREAT TO SEE YOU.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> GREAT.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> WHERE ARE WE GOING?
>> HAVE A SEAT.
>> I ALMOST FELT BAD HUGGING HER
BECAUSE WE JUST HELD PIGS.
>> I WANTED TO HOLD A PIG.
THE BEVERLY HILLS AIR KISS.
>> YEAH.
>> I LOVE THOSE LITTLE PIGS.
I WANTED TO FEED ONE FROM A
BOTTLE.
I DON'T WANT TO BE POOPED ON
THOUGH.
>> IT'S NOT TOO LATE.
>> I'M SURE WE CAN STOP THEM IN
THE BACK.
>> I'LL TAKE ONE HOME ON THE
PLANE WITH ME.
>> HAPPY BELATED BIRTHDAY.
>> THANK YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I'M ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE THAT
SAYS IT EMPOWERS WOMEN THE MORE
WE TALK ABOUT EMBRACING AGE.
IT'S INEVITABLE, GUYS.
WE CAN'T STOP IT.
WHAT ADVICE DO YOU HAVE FOR
WOMEN TO HOLD ON AND OWN THEIR
NUMBERS?
>> I WAS ACTUALLY REALLY SCARED.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME I HAVE
SAID IT ON CAMERA, THAT I JUST
TURNED 50.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I WAS SO AFRAID, BUT THEN I WAS,
LIKE, YOU KNOW, I HAVE ALWAYS
BEEN SCARED OF DYING SINCE I WAS
12 YEARS OLD.
I'M GRATEFUL THAT I HAVE
SURVIVED THIS LONG.
WHAT AM I COMPLAINING ABOUT?
I DID EVERYTHING IN MY POWER TO
BE AS HEALTHY AND LOOK AND FEEL
AS GOOD AS POSSIBLE.
I HAD MY BIG BIRTHDAY AND I FEEL
REALLY GREAT.
>> YOU LOOK REALLY GOOD.
>> YES, YOU ARE.
I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
YOU'RE, LIKE, THERE'S NO WAY TO
STOP IT.
THERE'S ONE WAY TO STOP IT, BUT
THAT'S NOT WHAT WE ALL WANT.
STOP IT THAT WAY.
YOU EMBRACE IT.
I'M SORRY.
I WAS JUST HOLDING A PIG.
YOU ARE A MOM, AN ACTRESS AND
YOUR LIFE HAS PLAYED OUT IN
FRONT OF THE CAMERAS, BUT THAT
MUST BE KIND OF DIFFICULT.
WHAT CAN WE EXPECT FROM THIS
SEASON OF THE SHOW BECAUSE THIS
SHOW IS --
>> ON FIRE.
>> I LOVE IT.
IT IS SO GOOD.
>> THIS SEASON IS A VERY, VERY
CRAZY SEASON, BUT FOR THE
VIEWERS I THINK IT'S GOING TO BE
ONE OF THEIR FAVORITE SEASONS.
THAT MEANS FOR THE CAST MEMBERS,
IT'S A TORTURE SEASON.
WHEN WE'RE TORTURED, THE
AUDIENCE IS HAPPY.
>> YES.
>> THANK YOU?
>> BUT, YOU KNOW, THERE IS JUST
SO MUCH GOING ON.
IT IS A LOT TO JUGGLE.
I HAVE FOUR KIDS AND MY HUSBAND
AND FIVE DOGS, BUT, YOU KNOW,
THEY CAPTURE A LOT OF THAT, YOU
KNOW, BUT THEY, YOU KNOW, SEE US
WOMEN GOING CRAZY AND OUR
COMPLEX RELATIONSHIPS.
>> SPEAKING OF THOSE COMPLEX
RELATIONSHIPS, LISA VANDERPUMP
WAS HERE A FEW WEEKS AGO, AND
FANS HAVE WATCHED THE
RELATIONSHIP TAKE UPS AND DOWNS.
DO YOU THINK IT WILL SURVIVE
THIS SEASON?
>> WELL, IT DIDN'T SO FAR.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, WE'RE NOT IN A
GOOD PLACE RIGHT NOW.
YOU KNOW, YOU KIND OF SEE IT IN
THE TEASER OF THE SEASON, THE
TRAILER, BUT I'M HOPEFUL THAT
ONE DAY WE'LL GET BACK TO WHERE
WE WERE BECAUSE I CARE ABOUT
LISA A LOT.
WE HAVE HAD A LOT OF TIME, WITH
YOU IT'S DIFFICULT WITH
EVERYTHING THAT GOES ON.
I'M HOPEFUL WE'LL GET BACK THERE
ONE DAY.
>> ARE YOU THE TYPE OF PERSON
THAT APOLOGIZES FIRST OR ARE YOU
THE KIND THAT WAITS FOR AN
APOLOGY?
>> I HAVE NO -- I HAVE NO
PROBLEM APOLOGIZING.
>> WHEN YOU ARE WRONG.
>> WHEN I'M WRONG.
OF COURSE, YEAH.
BUT YEAH.
I'M JUST GOING TO LEAVE IT AT
THAT.
I CAN'T TELL OF THE
REPERCUSSIONS OF WHAT I WAS
THINKING.
>> THAT HAPPENS TO ME ALL THE
TIME.
YOUR SISTER, KIM, IS BACK ON THE
SHOW.
[ APPLAUSE ]
SHE ISN'T HOUSEWIFE,
BUT SHE HAS BEEN BACK FOR SOME
EPISODES.
HOW ARE YOU HANDLING THAT?
>> WE HAVE GONE THROUGH VERY,
VERY DIFFICULT TIMES ON THE
SHOW, BUT I LOVE WHEN SHE'S ON
THE SHOW.
I WISH SHE WAS THERE ALL THE
TIME.
MY KIDS SAY SHE'S THEIR FAVORITE
HOUSEWIFE.
SHE'S JUST FUNNY AND YOU NEVER
KNOW WHAT KIM IS GOING TO SAY OR
DO.
I LOVE THAT ABOUT HER.
>> YOU SAY YOU HAVE FOUR KIDS, A
HUSBAND --
>> FIVE DOGS.
>> FIVE DOGS, AND YOU HAD YOUR
FIRST DAUGHTER WHEN YOU WERE 19
AND YOUR LAST WHEN YOU WERE 39.
WHAT IS THE DIFFERENCE FOR YOU
RAISING A DAUGHTER AT 19 AS
OPPOSED TO RAISING A DAUGHTER
NOW?
>> PEOPLE ALWAYS ASK ME THAT
AND, YOU KNOW, WHEN I WAS 19, I
WAS THE MOM WITH THE BIRTHDAY
PARTY WITH THE JUMPY HOUSE AND I
JUMPING WITH ALL THE KIDS AND I
HAD SO MUCH ENERGY AND, LIKE,
NOT AS MUCH PATIENCE.
NOW I HAVE SO MUCH PATIENCE AND
NOT AS MUCH ENERGY.
I ACTUALLY DO, BUT I'M NOT THE
MOM JUMPING IN THE BOUNCY HOUSE,
BUT, YOU KNOW, I THINK YOU RELAX
BY THE FOURTH.
I'M STILL WORRIED AND NEUROTIC
AND, YOU KNOW, STRESSED.
>> WISER TOO.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S IMPORTANT.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
MY KIDS LAUGH, LIKE, MOM, YOU
WOULD NEVER HAVE LET ME DO THAT.
THE FOURTH ONE, YOU ARE
DEFINITELY MORE KICK BACK ABOUT
THINGS, BUT YOU WORRY THE SAME
NO MATTER HOW MANY KIDS.
>> DEFINITELY THERE IS A VIDEO
YOU WANT TO SHOW BECAUSE YOU
KICK THAT WELL.
>> WHAT HAVE I DONE NOW?
>> THIS IS -- SO SHE SAYS -- YOU
SAY YOU ARE NOT IN THE BOUNCY
HOUSE, BUT THERE IS A LOT OF
BOUNCING GOING ON RIGHT HERE.
>> YEAH.
YEAH.
>> ENERGY DOESN'T SEEM TO BE A
PROBLEM FOR YOU.
>> I HAVE GOOD ENERGY LEVELS.
WE CAN EMBARRASS OUR KIDS TOO.
I LOVE IT.
IT'S FUN.
>> EVERY PARENT SHOULD EMBARRASS
YOUR KIDS.
ALL OF YOU, EMBARRASS YOUR KIDS.
>> IN A GOOD WAY.
KYLE, WE LOVE HAVING YOU HERE
AND TELL YOUR HUSBAND I SAID
HELLO.
ALWAYS A NICE MAN TO ME.
GOOD LUCK WITH THE SEASON.
>> WE'RE NOT LETTING HER GO
ANYWHERE THOUGH.
>> WE'RE NOT?
>> SHE'S STICKING AROUND.
>> WHAT?
>> SHE'S GOING TO STAY.
>> EVEN BETTER.
>> YOU CAN ASK US ANYTHING YOU
WANT TO KNOW.
>> THEY WILL ANSWER WHATEVER
THEY WANT TO KNOW?
>> NO, BUT SHE IS.
>> WHATEVER YOU WANT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
We'd love some help with
laundry.
Here's how you do it.
Spray and scrub anything with a
stain.
Soak your nasty jersey. It
stinks!
Wash the really dirty clothes
separately.
Remember - hard work builds
character!
New Tide PODS with upgraded
4-in-1 technology
unleash a foolproof clean in one
step.
Aww, you did the laundry!
But you didn't fold it.
Oh, that wasn't in the note.
Should have sent a text.
#1 stain and odor fighter,
#1 trusted.
It's got to be Tide.
L'OREAL PARIS INTRODUCES
ROUGE SIGNATURE
MATTE COLORED INK
LESS TEXTURE
MORE COLOR
LESS EXCESS
MORE IMPACT
ALL DAY MATTE
BARE LIP SENSATION
ROUGE SIGNATURE
MATTE COLORED INK
BY L'OREAL PARIS
WE'RE WORTH IT
Sometimes,
bipolar I disorder can
make you feel like
you have no limits.
But mania, such as unusual
changes in your mood,
activity or energy levels,
can leave you on...
shaky ground.
Help take control by asking
your healthcare provider
about VRAYLAR.
VRAYLAR treats acute mania
of bipolar I disorder.
VRAYLAR significantly reduces
overall manic symptoms,
and was proven in adults with
mixed episodes who have
both mania and depression.
VRAYLAR should not be used
in elderly patients with
dementia, due to increased
risk of death or stroke.
Call your doctor about fever,
stiff muscles, or confusion,
which may mean a
life-threatening reaction
or uncontrollable
muscle movements,
which may be permanent.
Side effects may not appear
for several weeks.
High cholesterol and weight
gain; high blood sugar, which
can lead to coma or death;
decreased white blood cells,
which can be fatal;
dizziness upon standing;
falls; seizures; impaired
judgement; heat sensitivity; and
trouble swallowing may occur.
You're more than
just your bipolar I.
People everywhereVRAYLAR.
are confusing Quilted Northern
for robes.
They're both cushiony,
comforting,
and add elegance to your home.
But Quilted Northern
is not a robe.
It's just really nice
toilet paper.
♪
There it is the coffee ring,
it's been sitting
there all week.
And just like
that, it's shining.
Look at you.
Beautify it with pledge.
S.C. Johnson.
♪♪
-Morning.
-What do we got?
-Keep an eye on that branch.
Might get windy.
Have a good shift.
Fire pit.
Last use -- 0600.
I'd stay close.
Morning.
♪♪
Get ready to switch.
Protected by Flo.
Should say, "Protected
by Alan and Jamie."
-Right?
-Should it?
When you bundle
home and auto...
Run, Alan!
...you get more
than just savings.
You get 'round-the-clock
protection.
♪♪
...you get more
than just savings.
♪ 'Cos I know what it means ♪
♪ To walk along the lonely
street of dreams ♪
♪ Here I go again on my--- ♪
You realize your vows are a
Whitesnake song?
I do.
If you ride, you get it.
GEICO Motorcycle.
15 minutes
could save you 15% or more.
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> WE ARE BACK WITH THE
REALEST -- THAT'S NOT A WORD --
HOUSEWIFE, KYLE RICHARDS.
IT'S TIME FOR A SEGMENT CALLED
ASK US ANYTHING.
WE'RE GIVING MEMBERS OF OUR
TERRIFIC STUDIO AUDIENCE A
CHANCE TO ASK US QUESTIONS THEY
HAVE ALWAYS WANTED TO KNOW.
LET'S GET TO OUR FIRST QUESTION.
WHERE IS LUCY?
>> HEY, LUCY.
>> HI.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WHAT YOU GOT?
>> HI, KYLE.
>> HI.
>> I KNOW YOU HAVE FOUR CHILDREN
SO I WAS WONDERING, WILL YOUR
CHILDREN FOLLOW YOU INTO THE
PROFESSION OF ACTING AND IF SO,
DO YOU FULLY SUPPORT THEM IN
THAT DECISION?
>> THE ONLY ONE WHO HAS SHOWED
ANY INTEREST IS MY YOUNGEST,
PORTIA, AND YES, I WOULD SUPPORT
HER 100%.
SHE'S GOOD AT IT.
IF SHE'S GOOD AT SOMETHING, I'LL
ENCOURAGE IT, ABSOLUTELY.
>> THAT'S A GOOD ANSWER.
THAT'S A GOOD ANSWER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU HAVE LITTLE, YOUNG BABIES.
>> MY KID'S A PERFORMER, BUT
HE'S 3.
THEY ALL ARE AT 3.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
NEXT UP IS BEATRICE.
BEATRICE, WHERE ARE YOU?
HEY.
>> HI, KYLE.
I KNOW YOU HAVE BEEN MARRIED FOR
23 YEARS.
WHAT'S YOUR SECRET TO A
SUCCESSFUL MARRIAGE?
>> I THINK IT STARTS WITH
CHOOSING THE RIGHT PARTNER.
A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE, LIKE, WE'RE
DATING AND IN COUPLE'S THERAPY.
THAT'S KIND OF A RED FLAG.
LIFE IS GOING TO THROW YOU SO
MANY CURVEBALLS.
YOU HAVE TO START OUT WITH THE
RIGHT PARTNER, AND THEN
FROM THERE HONESTLY, YOU KNOW,
PICKING SOMEONE THAT YOU ENJOY
THE SAME THINGS AND LETTING THE
OTHER PERSON BE THEMSELVES, YOU
KNOW, WE GOT MARRIED IN OUR 20s.
WE WERE KIDS AND YOU CHANGE A
LOT OVER THOSE YEARS.
GROWING WITH THAT PERSON,
ALLOWING THEM TO BE WHO THEY ARE
AND SUPPORTING THAT.
>> AND LAUGHING.
>> LAUGHING.
>> SOMEONE YOU CAN LAUGH AND
HAVE FUN WITH.
>> NEXT UP, WHERE IS JARED?
>> HERE.
>> HI, JARED.
>> HI.
IF YOU COULD BRING BACK ANY PAST
HOUSEWIFE, WHO WOULD IT BE?
>> YOU LIKE THAT QUESTION,
DIDN'T YOU?
>> I THINK WE HAVE AN AMEN IN
ROW FOUR.
>> I SAY MY SISTER, KIM.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> SHE LOVES HER SISTER.
>> GET RID OF LISA RINNA.
>> STOP IT.
STOP IT.
>> SHE WASN'T KICKING ONE OUT.
IT WAS BRINGING ONE ON.
>> THIS IS THE MOST INTERACTIVE
AUDIENCE WE HAVE EVER HAD.
WHERE IS MY MAN, KEITH?
HEY, KEITH.
WHAT YOU GOT?
>> HOWDY.
WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE PART ABOUT
BEING A TV PERSONALITY?
AND SARA, YOUR CHEEKBONES ARE
KILLING IT.
>> THESE LITTLE THINGS?
THEY'RE STARTING TO BLEND IN
WITH MY WHOLE FACE AS I GAIN
BABY WEIGHT UP HERE.
>> WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE PART?
>> WHAT'S MY FAVORITE PART?
THERE IS A LOT OF PERKS AND A
LOT OF GOOD THINGS THAT, YOU
KNOW, COME WITH IT, BUT THERE IS
A LOT OF DOWNSIDE WITH MY JOB IN
PARTICULAR, BUT I DON'T KNOW.
OBVIOUSLY WE GET TO DO A LOT OF
FUN THINGS AND I HAVE GREAT HOME
VIDEOS FOR MY KIDS BECAUSE I
STOPPED DOING THAT EVER SINCE WE
GOT THE iPHONES.
>> YEAH.
>> I THINK JUST HAVING THE
PLATFORM TO TALK ABOUT THINGS
THAT ARE IMPORTANT AND, YOU
KNOW, TO HAVE A VOICE FOR THINGS
THAT ARE IMPORTANT TO GET OUT
THERE.
>> I WOULD SAY MY FAVORITE PART
IS GETTING PEOPLE TO LAUGH.
WHEN SOMEONE TWEETS OR REACHES
OUT AND SAYS, I WAS HAVING A
ROUGH DAY OR MY MOM'S IN SURGERY
AND I WAS WATCHING YOU AND FELT
A MOMENT OF ESCAPE, IT IS, LIKE,
THE BEST THING I EVER HEAR IS
KNOWING FOR ONE MINUTE, YOU MADE
SOMEONE HAPPY.
>> I AGREE.
I AGREE WITH THAT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I THINK BOTH OF THAT.
JUST HAVING, LIKE, A LOG OF YOUR
LIFE IN A LOT OF DIFFERENT WAYS
AND ALSO ENTERTAINING PEOPLE AND
MAKING PEOPLE LAUGH.
TO ME, IT'S, LIKE, THE
ONE-ON-ONE THING HERE IN THE
STUDIO.
I LOVE ALL THAT.
WE LOVED HAVING YOU GUYS HERE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> NEXT UP, WE HAVE GOT -- WHERE
IS DEAN?
>> OH MY GOD.
MY CHAIR.
>> DEAN?
>> HI.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
KYLE, YOU'RE KNOWN FOR DANCING
ON TABLES AT PARTIES.
THAT'S KIND OF YOUR THING.
>> AVID WATCHER.
>> THAT'S YOUR THING.
WE HAVE A TABLE.
WOULD YOU KIND OF DANCE US OUT
TO BREAK?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE.
>> OH MY GOD.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> BRING IT ON.
>> EVERYBODY, STAY TUNED IN
FEBRUARY THE 12th.
THE SEASON PREMIERE OF "THE REAL
HOUSEWIVES" ON BRAVO.
CHECK OUT KYLE RICHARDS.
>>> COMING UP, WE'RE GOING TO
BLOW YOUR MIND.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
JARDIANCE asked:
When it comes to managing
your type 2 diabetes,
what matters to you?
Let's see.
Most of you say lower A1C.
But only a few of you
are thinking about your heart.
Fact is, even though
it helps to manage A1C,
type 2 diabetes still
increases your risk
of a fatal heart
attack or stroke.
JARDIANCE is the first
type 2 diabetes pill
with a lifesaving
cardiovascular benefit
for adults who have type 2
diabetes and heart disease,
JARDIANCE significantly
reduces the risk of dying
from a cardiovascular event
and lowers A1C,
with diet and exercise.
Let's give it another try.
JARDIANCE can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration.
This may cause you
to feel dizzy, faint,
or lightheaded,
or weak upon standing.
Ketoacidosis
is a serious side effect
that may be fatal.
Symptoms include nausea,
vomiting, stomach pain,
tiredness,
and trouble breathing.
A rare but life-threatening
bacterial infection
in the skin of the genital
area could also occur.
Stop taking JARDIANCE
and call your doctor right away
if you have symptoms
of this bacterial infection,
ketoacidosis
or an allergic reaction.
Symptoms of an allergic
reaction include rash,
swelling, and difficulty
breathing or swallowing.
Do not take JARDIANCE
if you are on dialysis
or have severe kidney problems.
Other side effects are
sudden kidney problems,
genital yeast infections,
increased bad cholesterol,
and urinary tract infections,
which may be serious.
Taking JARDIANCE with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may cause low blood sugar.
Tell your doctor about
all the medicines you take
and if you have any
medical conditions.
Isn't it time to rethink your
type 2 diabetes medication?
Ask your doctor about JARDIANCE
and get to the heart
of what matters.
Ask your doctor about JARDIANCE
Think only specialty stores have
what's new?
Olay has this season's hottest
debut.
Like new Clay Stick Masks.
All Mask, No Mess.
Olay Hydrating Facial Mist.
For hydration on the go.
And our breakthrough Brightening
Eye Cream.
Boosted with Vitamin C.
Get your new beauty fix.
Only by Olay.
I work hard to protect
this Tookus.
To take care of any
messy situations.
And put irritation in its place.
And if I can get comfortable
keeping this Tookus
safe and protected...
you can get comfortable doing
the same with yours.
PREPARATION H.
Get comfortable with it.
In an era of online retail,
where everything
is just a few clicks away,
buying a car should be
no different.
That's why, at Carvana,
you can buy a car
100% online.
We made it easy
to browse, view,
and buy from over 10,000 cars.
You can even trade-in
your old car
all while binge watching
your favorite TV show.
Afterwards, we'll deliver
your car to you.
Or you can pick it up
from one of our
car vending machines.
Either way, your car comes with
a 7-day return policy.
So grab a seat,
relax in your comfy pants,
and enjoy the new way to buy
a car-- at Carvana.
What is this?
Nongenemodi.
Nongen.
Oh, Triscuit!
Is non-genetically modified.
nongenemodiscuit.
Triscuit is non-GMO
project verified.
Triscuit. Make
'Scuit Happen.
I am also not
genetically-modified.
I wanted more from
my COPD medicine...
...that's why I've got the Power
of 1-2-3 medicines with TRELEGY.
The only FDA-approved
3-in-1 COPD treatment.
♪ TRELEGY. The Power of 1-2-3 ♪
♪ TRELEGY 1-2-3 TRELEGY ♪
With TRELEGY and the Power of
1-2-3, I'm breathing better.
TRELEGY works 3 ways to...
...open airways,...
...keep them open...
...and reduce inflammation...
...for 24 hours
of better breathing.
TRELEGY won't replace
a rescue inhaler
for sudden breathing problems.
TRELEGY is NOT for asthma.
Tell your doctor if you
have a heart condition
or high blood pressure
before taking it.
Do not take TRELEGY
more than prescribed.
TRELEGY may increase your
risk of thrush, pneumonia,
and osteoporosis.
Call your doctor if worsened
breathing, chest pain,
mouth or tongue swelling,..
...problems urinating, vision
changes, or eye pain occur.
Think your COPD
medicine is doing enough?
Maybe you should think again.
Ask your doctor about once-daily
TRELEGY and the
Power of 1-2-3.
♪ TRELEGY 1-2-3 ♪
Save at TRELEGY.com.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> WELCOME BACK.
NEXT UP WE HAVE A WONDERFUL
ILLUSIONIST.
>> YES.
I HAVE SUMMONED THE CASTLE
WIZARD TO ENTERTAIN YOU.
>> YOU'RE NOT A KING, MICHAEL.
>> SAYS WHO?
>> PLEASE WELCOME ONE OF THE
WORLD'S TOP ILLUSIONISTS.
GIVE IT UP FOR ROB LAKE.
>> WELCOME, ROB.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> HOW DO YOU GET INTO SOMETHING
LIKE THIS?
>> WHEN I WAS 10 YEARS OLD, I
SAW A MAGIC SHOW AND I KNEW
IMMEDIATELY THAT IS WHAT I WOULD
DO WITH MY WHOLE LIFE.
>> WOW.
10.
>> I BASICALLY NEVER GREW UP.
>> HAVE YOU EVER HAD AN ACCIDENT
HAPPEN, LIKE, A MISHAP?
>> IT'S A LIVE SHOW SO THINGS
CAN GO WRONG.
I TRY TO PLAY IT FOR EVERY
CONTINGENCY, BUT ONE TIME I GOT
CUT BY A SWORD.
I HAD TO GET STITCHES.
I HAVE A LITTLE BIT OF A SCAR
LEFT, BUT I STILL FINISHED THE
SHOW AND WENT TO GET STITCHES
AFTERWARDS.
>> WOW.
THE MAN IS COMMITTED TO HIS
CRAFT.
>> DEDICATION.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO SHOW US
TODAY?
>> ALMOST 100 YEARS AGO, AN
UNKNOWN MAGICIAN CREATED THE
FAMOUS ILLUSION OF ALL TIME.
HE CALLED IT SAWING A WOMAN IN
HALF.
>> WHY DOES IT ALWAYS HAVE TO BE
A WOMAN?
>> IT IS.
>> I'M GOOD.
>> EVEN THOUGH EVERY MAGICIAN
HAS COPIED THIS, THE ORIGINAL
VERSION IS A MYSTERY.
NOBODY KNOWS HOW IT COULD HAVE
BEEN DONE.
TODAY I'M GOING TO RECREATE THIS
EXACTLY HOW IT WOULD HAVE LOOKED
IF WE WERE BACK IN 100 YEARS
AGO, BUT I NEED THE HELP FROM
BOTH OF YOU.
>> PLEASE DON'T ASK ME TO GET IN
THAT BOX.
>> NO WORRIES, SAY ARE.
IF YOU WILL COME TO THIS SIDE,
AND MICHAEL, THIS SIDE.
>> OKAY.
>> CHECK OUT THIS BOX, AND
MICHAEL, CHECK OUT THIS BOX AS
WELL.
>> GOOD.
>> SARA, I HAVE THE COLLAR.
>> WHY DOES THIS ALWAYS START
THIS WAY?
>> CHECK OUT THE BUCKLE.
CHECK OUT THE STRAP.
MAKE SURE NOTHING COMES OFF OR
ATTACHES.
>> ONE OF THE BEST LEASHES I
HAVE SEEN.
>> SECURE?
SOLID?
>> SOLID.
>> JUST LIKE THE ONE AT HOME?
>> YEAH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I'LL BE HONEST WITH YOU, MAN.
YOU HAVE BEEN PEEKING THROUGH MY
WINDOWS.
>> MAGIC.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT THEY CALL IT?
50 SHADES OF STRAY.
THAT'S FOR ANOTHER SHOW, ROB.
CONTINUE.
>> TAKE THE END OF THIS LEASH
AND PUT IT THROUGH THE HOLE OF
THE TABLE RIGHT HERE.
THIS TABLE IS A SURGICAL
OPERATION TABLE FROM THE CIVIL
WAR ERA.
BACK THEN, THEY DID NOT HAVE
ANAESTHESIA, SO THEY WOULD HOLD
VICTIMS IN PLACE WITH STRAPS
LIKE JUST LIKE THESE STRAPS
HERE.
YEAH.
I WOULD LIKE YOU TO PLEASE LOCK
MY ASSISTANT'S ANKLES IN PLACE,
AND IF YOU WOULD WALK TO THE
BACK HERE.
>> OKAY.
>> PICK UP THIS COLLAR AND I
WANT YOU TO PUT IT ON HER NECK
VERY TIGHT, BUT TRY NOT TO CHOKE
HER.
>> WHAT KIND OF TRICK IS THIS?
>> TRY NOT TO CHOKE HER.
I NEED TO KEEP HER ALIVE FOR MY
OTHER SHOWS.
>> SORRY.
>> BACK IN THE CIVIL WAR ERA,
THEY HAD NO ANAESTHESIA, SO
THESE STRAPS WERE REQUIRED TO A
VICTIM WOULD REMAIN IN PLACE AND
NOT MOVE DURING SURGERY.
SARA, IF YOU WILL HOLD THIS
LEASH RIGHT HERE.
HOLD TIGHT WITH TWO HANDS, AND
MICHAEL, YOU HOLD AS WELL.
DO NOT LET GO.
>> DON'T PULL ON HER.
CUT HER APART.
NOT RIP HER APART.
>> EVEN THOUGH SHE'S MOMENTARILY
COVERED.
YOU WILL BE ABLE TO SEE HER BODY
THROUGH THESE WINDOWS HERE IN
THE FRONT.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> EVERY TIME I OPEN THESE
WINDOWS -- KEEP HER LEASH TIGHT
AND MAKE SURE SHE'S STILL THERE
AND LOCKED IN PLACE.
LET EVERYONE AT HOME KNOW WITH A
THUMBS UP.
EXCELLENT.
GREAT ENTHUSIASM.
BOTH CHECK IT.
MAKE SURE IT IS SOLID.
PERFECT.
EXCELLENT.
NOW I WANT YOU BOTH TO WATCH
CAREFULLY AS I PLACE THIS BLADE
INSIDE OF THE BOX.
YOU CAN SEE THE BLADE COMPLETELY
FILLS THE BOX ALL THE WAY FRONT
TO BACK AND ALL THE WAY ACROSS,
YES?
RIGHT NOW, THIS BLADE IS RESTING
ON HER BODY.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> THERE IS NOWHERE ELSE SHE CAN
GO AND WHERE THE BLADE CAN GO.
>> KEEP IT TIGHT.
KEEP IT TIGHT.
>> GIVE US A SIGN IF IT'S NOT
WORKING OUT.
>> HOLD TIGHT WITH BOTH HANDS.
>> DON'T LET GO.
>> DO NOT LET GO, SARA.
>> THEY DON'T PAY ME ENOUGH TO
DO THIS.
>> NOW MICHAEL, LOOK DOWN BELOW.
MAKE SURE YOU CAN SEE THE BLADE
PASS THROUGH THE ENTIRE BOX.
>> I'M LOOKING TO SEE BLOOD.
>> ALL THE WAY TO THE BOTTOM.
>> OH, WOW.
>> CHECK OUT YOUR WINDOW.
MAKE SURE SHE'S STILL THERE.
>> OH MY GOSH.
>> IT'S OKAY, SWEETIE.
>> DO NOT LET GO.
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE THINGS ONE
STEP FURTHER.
HOLD TIGHT.
>> DON'T MAKE ME PULL THIS
APART.
>> TWO HANDS.
>> EW.
>> SARA, IT SEEMS LIKE YOUR SIDE
MUST HAVE SHIFTED.
I THINK WE HAD TOO MUCH SLACK
THERE.
GIVE YOUR LEASH A LITTLE PULL.
ONE, TWO, THREE --
>> I'M SORRY.
>> GIVE IT A TUG.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHAT YOU JUST
DID?
OH, MAN.
OH, NO.
>> IS SHE -- SHE'S NOT.
>> DO NOT LET GO.
>> I'M NOT LETTING GO.
>> WE NOW HAVE A WOMAN DIVIDED.
LET'S PUT HER BACK.
>> THAT IS RESILIENT.
HOLD TIGHT, TWO HANDS.
ONE FINAL TIME.
CHECK OUT YOUR WINDOW AND MAKE
SURE SHE'S STILL THERE.
LOCKED IN PLACE.
GIVE IT A THUMBS UP.
DO NOT LET GO OF YOUR LEASH JUST
YET, AND PLEASE COME TO THE
TABLE.
RELEASE HER.
LET HER OUT OF THE STRAPS.
>> OH MY GOSH.
OH, YOU POOR THING.
SHE LOOKS REALLY GOOD.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> THANK YOU.
>> COME BACK IN HERE.
COME BACK OVER HERE.
>> COME BACK.
>> WE PUT YOU BACK TOGETHER.
GET IN HERE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> TARA.
>> TARA, THANK YOU.
YOU REALLY MADE A SACRIFICE FOR
US TODAY.
>> I HAVE TO SAY, ROB, THE KING
IS VERY PLEASED.
>> PERFECT.
>> THANK YOU, MAN.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH, ROB.
>> THANK YOU.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK, YOU GUYS.
THAT WAS AWESOME.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
To most, he's
Phil Mickelson...
..pro golfer.
To me, he's...
...well, Dad.
So when his
joint pain from
psoriatic arthritis
got really bad, it scared me.
And what could that pain mean?
Joint pain could
mean joint damage.
ENBREL helps
relieve joint pain...
...helps stop irreversible
joint damage...
and helps skin get clearer.
ENBREL may lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious, sometimes
fatal events...
including infections,
tuberculosis...
lymphoma, other cancers,...
nervous system and
blood disorders...
and allergic
reactions have occurred.
Tell your
doctor if you've
been some place where
fungal infections are common.
Or, if you're
prone to infections,
have cuts or sores,
have had hepatitis B,
have been treated
for heart failure...
or if you have
persistent fever...
bruising, bleeding, or paleness.
Don't start ENBREL...
if you have an
infection like the flu.
Since ENBREL...
Dad's back to being... Dad.
Visit Enbrel.com...
and use the Joint
Damage Simulator
to see how your joint
damage could be progressing.
Ask about ENBREL.
ENBREL.
FDA approved for
over 16 years.
I use this
every day
But is Beth's soap
as clean rinsing as Dove?
My soap's still leaving
plenty of things behind
But Dove is cleaner rinsing
My soap,
...Dove.
Made with 1/4
moisturizing cream...
Dove cleans and cares
beautifully.
♪ If you love me, love me,
love me like you say ♪
♪ Darling, tell me
all the ways ♪
♪ Tell me all the ways ♪
♪ All the ways ♪
At the store, or to your door.
Target Run and Done.
Still fresh...
♪
Unstopables In-Wash Scent
Booster
♪
Downy Unstopables
♪ ♪
Do you feel the call?
Black Opium.
L'eau de parfum.
Yves Saint Laurent.
Kids, ah!
First day of school.
Ugh, at least she has shoes on.
Good morning.
Frozen now...
...thawed by lunch.
Have a good day at school.
Nailed it.
Yoplait and Go Gurt.
Gentle means everything,
so we improved everything.
We used 50% fewer ingredients
Added one handed pumps
And beat the
top safety standards
The new JOHNSON'S®
Choose Gentle
I had this chest cold, but my
medicine kept wearing off.
(coughs)
Ah!
I missed you!
Then I discovered Mucinex.
One pill lasts 12 hours,
and I'm good.
Mucinex releases fast
and lasts 12 hours, not 4.
Let's End This.
Stronger is blasting
her tumors...
without risking her bones.
It's training her
good cells...
to fight the bad guys.
Stronger is less pain...
new hope...
more fight.
It's doing everything
in your power...
and everything in ours.
Stronger, is changing even
faster than they do.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>>> OKAY.
SO WE GOT A NEW NAME.
>> I'M SARA.
HE'S STRAHAN.
>> IF YOU DIDN'T KNOW.
>> THIS WEEK, LOOK WHO'S HANGING
HERE.
IT'S WILL ARNETT.
>> DOES EVERYBODY JUST WANT TO
HAVE SOME FUN?
>> "STRAHAN AND SARA."
>> WE GOT IT ALL.
>> LUNCHTIME AT 1:00 EASTERN,
12:00 CENTRAL AND PACIFIC ON
ABC.
>>> THANK YOU TO ROB LAKE AND
THANK ALL OF YOU FOR WATCHING
AND YOUR WHOLE TEAM HERE.
>> YES.
>> THE SHOW, WE CELEBRATE
FETUCCINE AL FRAYFREDO DAY.
IT'S A BIG HOLIDAY, AND WE'RE
CELEBRATING WITH A CHEF.
>> AND THE RAPPING GIRL SCOUT WE
FOCUSED ON YESTERDAY WILL BE
HERE.
WE WANT YOU GUYS TO HAVE A
WONDERFUL REST OF YOUR
WEDNESDAY, AND THANK YOU GUYS
FOR THE GREAT ILLUSIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> CAN YOU MAKE US ALL DISAPPEAR
NOW?
>> SEE YOU TOMORROW.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪