>> Announcer: LIVE FROM
NEW YORK CITY, IT'S
"THE WENDY WILLIAMS SHOW."
♪ ♪
NOW, HERE'S NICK CANNON!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Nick: OH!
OH!
OH, YEAH!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
YES, YES!
WHAT'S UP, Y'ALL?
THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT!
THANK YOU! [CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU!
I DON'T DO IT WELL, I'M GOING TO
TRY.
HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> Audience: HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> Nick: I'M GOING TO WORK ON
IT.
GREETINGS, Y'ALL.
THINK OF HAVING HAVING ME.
IT'S AN HONOR TO BE HERE
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
IT'S A BLESSING.
I GOT TO SAY IT OFF THE TOP,
Y'ALL.
EVERYBODY WANTS TO KNOW.
I SPOKE TO RANDY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I TALKED TO HER!
HONESTLY, SHE SOUNDED AMAZING,
Y'ALL.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WE JUMPED ON THE PHONE FOR THE
FIRST THING SHE SAID WAS, "NICK
CANNON, HOW YOU DOIN'?
"HONESTLY, I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO
EXPECT AT FIRST.
BUT HER SPIRIT WAS SO BIG.
IT WAS SO AMAZING.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WHAT WAS ALSO AWESOME, I HAD A
CONVERSATION WITH HER AND HER
WHOLE FAMILY.
SHE SAID SHE WANTED TO SPEAK AS
A FAMILY UNIT.
I TALKED TO HER, KEVIN, LITTLE
KEVIN.
THEY SAID THEY ALL GOOD.
THE LOVE AND THE PASSION IS
STILL THERE.
THAT'S WHAT YOU NEED IN TIMES
LIKE THIS.
FOR YOUR FAMILY TO STICK
TOGETHER WITH YOU.
HONESTLY, I GOT A LITTLE
EMOTIONAL.
IT DID.
WHEN I SPOKE TO HER, SHE SAID
SHE FEELS Y'ALL LOVE.
SHE KNOWS THAT THERE ARE
PROBABLY A LOT OF QUESTIONS THAT
HAVEN'T BEEN ANSWERED AND STUFF.
AS SOMEBODY ALSO DEALS WITH AN
AUTOIMMUNE CONDITION, I'M
DIAGNOSED WITH LUPUS, AND I KNOW
THAT WHEN YOU GO THROUGH THESE
THINGS AND FLARE UP SOME STUFF,
YOU NEVER KNOW.
IT'S DAY BY DAY, Y'ALL.
ONE DAY YOU COULD BE STRONG, AND
THE NEXT YOU CAN'T GET OUT OF
BED.
SHE SOUNDED STRONG PRICK SHE
WANTED TO
THANK EACH AND EVERYONE OF YOU.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
SHE WAS TEARING UP, SHE SAID
SOMETHING THAT WAS REALLY
POWERFUL.
YOU KNOW ME AND WENDY, WE'VE HAD
A LOVE-HATE RELATIONSHIP OVER
THE YEARS!
IT'S NOTHING BUT LOVE.
I LOVE MY QUEEN.
WHEN SHE SAID THIS, SHE SAID
THERE COULD BE NEGATIVITY OUT
THERE.
SHE HEARS THE THINGS, PEOPLE
TALKING ABOUT HER FAMILY UNIT
AND ALL THAT AND WHAT'S GOING
ON.
SHE WAS LIKE, "YOU KNOW WHAT
CUSTOMER AGREE TO WANT TO BRING
THAT NEGATIVE ENERGY WHEN WE ARE
TRYING TO HEAL."
[APPLAUSE]
YOU NEED YOUR FAMILY AND FRIENDS
IN MOMENTS LIKE THIS.
THAT'S WHEN LOVE IS TRULY
TESTED, WHEN YOU KNOW "I'M GOING
TO STICK TO THIS REGARDLESS OF
WHAT'S GOING ON."
SO I SPOKE TO EVERYBODY AS YOU
DO AND WE WILL GIVE THE SAME
TYPE OF LOVE BECAUSE IT'S ALL
ABOUT THIS UNIT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
SHE SAID, SHE SAID, "HAVE FUN,
BUT DON'T GET TOO COMFORTABLE
BECAUSE I'M COMING BACK!"
[LAUGHTER]
SO I WILL SAY IT LIKE THIS -- WE
WILL TAKE OF THE I OUT OF
ILLNESS, ADD WE, AND GET
WELLNESS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I WANT Y'ALL TO SAY IT.
GO AHEAD, SAY, "WE LOVE YOU,
WENDY!"
>> Audience: WE LOVE YOU,
>> Nick: THAT'S WHAT I'M
TALKING ABOUT.
I SPOKE TO ANOTHER POWERFUL
WOMAN, MY MAMA.
I TALKED TO MY MAMA.
I ALSO TALKED TO MY GRANDMAMMA.
THEN I TALKED TO MY GREAT GRAND
MAMA.
OVER THERE IN NORTH CAROLINA.
SHE'S 99.
MS. KAREN CANNON
SHE SAID, "DON'T GET ON THERE
AND BE TOO MESSY, NOW!
DON'T MAKE YOUR FAMILY LOOK BAD!
DON'T BE UP THERE BEING MESSY!"
SO I'M GOING TO TRY TO TAKE MY
MATRIARCHS ADVICE AND TRY NOT TO
BE TOO MESSY.
BUT IT'S TIME FOR "HOT TOPICS."
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
IT'S GONE DOWN.
YEAH.
WE'RE GOING TO TALK ABOUT IT.
NOW, DID I GET THE SHOE CAM?
Y'ALL GOT TO GET THIS!
♪ ♪
WOW!
STUNTING ON 'EM!
THAT'S A HOT TOPIC.
THIS IS WENDY'S THING, THE HOT
TOPICS.
WE TALK ABOUT THE GOSSIP AND
THINGS GOING ON.
WE'RE GOING TO COVER ALL OF
THAT.
I'M A BIT OF A CONSPIRACY
THEORIST MYSELF.
I FEEL LIKE A LOT OF THIS GOSSIP
JUST BE DISTRACTIONS FROM THE
REAL THINGS GOING ON IN THE
WORLD.
COME ON, JESUS!
COME ON, SOMEBODY!
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
IT'S A DISTRACTION!
SO WE'RE GOING TO COVER THE
"HOT TOPICS," BUT WE ALSO GOING
TO TALK ABOUT THE NOT TOPICS!
NICK'S NOT TOPICS, THE THINGS
THAT THEY NOT TALKING ABOUT!
HOW THEY TRYING TO DISTRACT YOU!
ONE OF THE HOT TOPICS OBVIOUSLY
IS THAT LAST NIGHT WAS THE
SUPER BOWL.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
[BOOING]
IT WASN'T SO SUPER, I HEARD!
I DIDN'T WATCH IT.
AS YOU ALL NO, Y'ALL SAW THE
HASHTAG, I'M WITH KAEP.
I ACTUALLY WAS WITH HIM!
THAT'S ME AND MY MAN!
THAT'S ME AND COLIN RIGHT THERE,
TWO BROTHERS TALKING IN THE
DARK!
IT WAS GOING DOWN!
WE WAS HAVING A SECRET MEETING!
HONESTLY, COLLIN CAP RIDDICK IS
ONE OF MY CLOSEST FRIENDS OUT
HERE
WE DIDN'T EVEN TURN THE TV ON,
WE WENT AND GOT SOME CHINESE
VEGAN FOOD.
I THOUGHT IT WAS GOING TO BE
DISGUSTING, BUT IT WAS AMAZING!
A PEACEFUL PROTEST.
WE DIDN'T WANT NO BEEF.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Audience: WE LOVE THAT!
>> Nick: THIS IS MY THING --
YELLOW, FAMILY, WHERE YOU AT?
>> Audience: WE LOVE THAT!
>> Nick: HONESTLY, WITH ALL
THE DRAMA WITH THE SUPER BOWL
GOING ON, BEING THE WORLD'S
BIGGEST DISPLAY OF CAPITALISM
EVER, THAT PEOPLE FORGOT ABOUT
THE TRUE REASON WHY HE WAS
PROTESTING.
IT'S SYSTEMIC OPPRESSION, THAT'S
ONE OF AMERICA'S BIGGEST
PROBLEMS.
THIS MAN PUT $150 MILLION ON THE
LINE FOR HIS PEOPLE.
[APPLAUSE]
UNTIL THIS DAY, I COMMEND HIM.
I KNOW THE SUPER BOWL IS A BIG
DEAL.
ALL THIS STUFF.
BUT I COMMEND A TRUE SOLDIER, A
TRUE CAT THAT IS STANDINGG FIRM
AND ROCKING.
I HAVE TO SUPPORT MY FRIEND, AND
I WAS WITH MY FRIEND.
[APPLAUSE]
HONESTLY, IT'S FUNNY BECAUSE,
AGAIN, THOUGH NOT TOPIC A BIT
ALL THAT EVERYBODY JUST SEEM TO
HAVE FORGOTTEN.
IT'S BLACK HISTORY MONTH, Y'ALL!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
Y'ALL WANT TO TALK ABOUT THE
SUPER BOWL?
COLIN KAEPERNICK IS BLACK
HISTORY!
BUT TODAY IS ACTUALLY ROSA
PARKS' BIRTHDAY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
SHOUT OUT TO THE QUEEN.
LAST WEEK, ON JANUARY 31ST,
JACKIE ROBINSON TURNED 100 YEARS
OLD!
I WAS HAVING A CONVERSATION WITH
COLIN KAEPERNICK LAST NIGHT,
"YOU ARE REALLY ARE GENERATION'S
VERSION OF JACKIE ROBERTSON IN A
WAY, WITH A LITTLE ROSA THROWN
IN THERE!"
BECAUSE WHEN YOU THINK OF THE
SACRIFICE -- WE HONOR BUT JACKIE
ROBINSON OUTCOME BUT IT WAS LIKE
THE BACK OF THE DAY.
THEY WERE THREATENING TO CHILL
JACKIE ROBINSON.
THERE WERE RACIAL SLURS.
IF YOU READ THAT AUTOBIOGRAPHY,
IT'S AMAZING.
HE SAID THIS, THIS IS THE JACKIE
ROBINSON QUOTE, "I CANNOT STAND
AND SING ANTHEM, I CANNOT SALUTE
THE FLAG.
I KNOW THAT I AM A BLACK MAN AND
A WHITE WORLD."
[APPLAUSE]
THAT'S JACKIE ROBINSON.
THAT'S THE SAME THING THAT
COLIN KAEPERNICK IS SAYING!
I JUST ENCOURAGE EVERYONE OUT
THERE, DON'T BE ON THE WRONG
SIDE OF HISTORY, Y'ALL.
YOU CAN BELIEVE WHAT YOU WANT TO
BELIEVE, JACKIE ROBINSON WAS A
VETERAN.
I LOVE AND SUPPORT ALL OF OUR
VETERANS WHO FIGHT FOR OUR
FREEDOM TO BE ABLE TO HAVE A
PEACEFUL PROTEST AND NOT GET UP
THERE AND HAVE TO BE PUNISHED
BECAUSE YOU ARE PROTESTING
PEACEFULLY.
I WANT TO SEE MY MAN
COLIN KAEPERNICK PLAYING ONE
MORE TIME.
WE WORK OUT TOGETHER, AND THE
MAN'S ARM IS CRAZY.
IT'S CRAZY!
SPEAKING FOR THE PEOPLE THAT DID
WATCH THE SUPER BOWL -- I DIDN'T
WATCH, BUT I HEARD THE HALFTIME
SHOW WAS SOMETHING THAT WASN'T
TO WATCH.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
I HEARD IT WAS THE FYRE FESTIVAL
OF HALFTIME SHOWS!
[LAUGHTER]
MAROON 5 PERFORMED.
SHOUTS OUT TO ADAM LEVINE AND
EVERYBODY.
I DIDN'T SEE IT, BUT I HEARD
THEY HAD AN ALL-WHITE DRUM LINE
IN ATLANTA?
DURING BLACK HISTORY MONTH?
I STARTED "DRUM LINE," I WASN'T
AVAILABLE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THAT'S BEFORE THE MUSCLES!
SO, WAIT -- Y'ALL COULDN'T FIND
NO BLACK DRUMMERS IN ATLANTA?
I GUESS EVERYBODY WAS WITH KAEP.
OH, THEY GOT ONE BROTHER RIGHT
THERE.
WE LOVE EVERYBODY.
ALL RIGHT.
THEN -- BECAUSE I DIDN'T SEE IT,
BUT THEN I HEARD OF ALL THE
TRIBUTES TO MAKE AND TO GET OUT
THERE, BLACK HISTORY MONTH, THEY
WERE WAITING FOR THEM TO MAKE A
STATEMENT, TO HONOR SOMEBODY,
AND HE HONORS SPONGEBOB.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
SHOUTS OUT TO MY NICKELODEON
FAMILY, I LOVE SPONGEBOB!
BUT I DIDN'T KNOW -- I HEARD HOW
IT CAME OUT, I HEARD THAT TRAVIS
SCOTT SHOT OUT OF SPONGEBOB'S --
OR SOMETHING?
IT WAS FIRE, A FIREBALL, TRAVIS
SCOTT ARRIVED OUT THE BIKINI
BOTTOM?
[LAUGHTER]
I DIDN'T SEE IT.
THIS IS JUST WHAT I HEARD.
I HOPE TRAVIS WAS OUT THERE --
WHAT IS THAT AROUND HIS WAIST?
HE'S GOT ON A WAIST TRAINER!
[LAUGHTER]
THE KARDASHIANS IS GETTING TO
HIM, BOY!
I'M TRYING NOT TO BE MESSY.
I'M SORRY.
I HEARD HE WAS OUT THERE FOR A
FEW SECONDS, HE DIDN'T GET TO DO
THE WHOLE --
FELL INTO THE AUDIENCE.
HEY, MORE POWER TO EVERYBODY.
THE ARTISTS.
BUT THE NOT TOPIC IS -- I
REALIZED DURING THE SUPER BOWL
HALFTIME SHOW'S BACK IN THE DAY,
THEY BANNED JANET JACKSON FOR
SHOWING ONE NIPPLE, BUT ADAM
LEVINE WAS OUT THERE WITH ALL
HIS NIPPLES OUT!
ALL OF THEM!
HE'S GOT THE TRIPLE NIPPLE!
WHAT IS THIS?
THAT'S A DOUBLE STANDARD, NFL!
JANET CAN'T HAVE ONE COMPANY CAN
HAVE THREE OF HIS OUT?
JUST SAYING, BROWN NIPPLES
MATTER.
THAT'S ALL I'M SAYING.
[APPLAUSE]
ATLANTA WAS HOT THIS WEEKEND, WE
AGREE TO KEEP GOING, I'M TRYING
NOT TO BE MESSY, Y'ALL.
I'M TRYING.
[LAUGHS]
SPEAKING OF ATLANTA, A SERIOUS
NOTE -- A LOVE GOT TO SAY IS 321
SAVAGE.
[APPLAUSE]
HE WAS ARRESTED IN ATLANTA BY
ICE.
I DON'T MESS WITH THEM,
ESPECIALLY THE BLACK ICE.
THEY WILL CATCH YOU SLIPPING
EVERY TIME.
WHAT DOES IT STAND FOR?
IMMIGRATION CUSTOMS ENFORCEMENT
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
WE LEARNED A LOT ABOUT 21
SAVAGE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I SO WANTED TO
MESS WITH 21, BUT APPARENTLY
HE'S BRITISH!
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
SHOUTS OUT TO THE BRITISH ROW
OVER THERE!
21 SAVAGE'S REAL NAME -- HELLO.
HELLO, 21.
APPARENTLY, THE REASON WHY THEY
BOTHER HIM BACK IN 2005, HE CAME
HERE AT 13 YEARS OLD.
LEGALLY.
AND HE NEVER RENEWED HIS VISA.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
YOU FORGET!
THERE'S A LOT ON HIS MIND AT
THAT AGE!
13-YEAR-OLD SAVAGE GOT A LOT OF
STUFF TO THINK ABOUT!
HE ATE ALWAYS GOT TIME TO -- A T
OF PEOPLE WHERE IT RESTED IN
ATLANTA THIS WEEKEND.
BOW WOW.
NO!
TAKE IT AWAY!
WERE NOT GOING TO TALK ABOUT
THAT!
HE'S MY FRIEND.
SO IS THE WILD TO WILDIN' OUT
GIRL.
WE'RE GOING TO GET OUT THE
DETAILS AND SPEAK TO BOTH OF
THEM.
BOW WOW, CALL ME!
[APPLAUSE]
I TOLD YOU ABOUT THOSE GIRLS,
YOU DON'T KNOW THERE AND INTO
FORCE!
THEY GET DOWN!
WE WILL TALK ABOUT THAT TOMORRO
TOMORROW.
BOW OUT AS A FRIEND OF MINE.
HOPEFULLY I CAN CHOP IT UP WITH
THEM AND GET THE REAL STORY.
THERE IS NOTHING FUNNY ABOUT
DOMESTIC VIOLENCE ON EITHER
SIDE.
BUT WE WILL GET TO IT.
BACK TO 21 SAVAGE.
ALSO, THERE'S NOTHING FUNNY
ABOUT A YOUNG MAN FROM OUR
COMMUNITY GETTING INCARCERATED.
THAT'S NOT FUNNY, EITHER.
I KNOW 21, HE'S A GOOD GUY.
HE STARTED A FINANCIAL LITERACY
CAMPAIGN FOR HIS COMMUNITY.
HE KEEPS SCHOOL SUPPLIES TO OVER
2,000 STUDENTS OUT THERE.
HE DOES GOOD FOR THE COMMUNITY.
LIKE I SAID, FREE 21.
THIS IS A SERIOUS MATTER.
THEIR PEOPLE ONLINE TALKING
ABOUT IT AND JOKING ABOUT.
THE FAMILY CAME OUT IT THE HARD
WAY.
DEMI LOVATO FOUND THAT OUT.
SHE TWEETED THIS LAST NIGHT, SHE
SAID, "SO FAR 21 SAVAGE MEANS
HAVE BEEN MY FAVORITE PART OF
THE SUPER BOWL."
THE KEY MATTER, Y'ALL.
THEY GOT TO ROOSTING QUICKLY.
SOMEBODY LIKE HER WHO HAS BEEN
THROUGH A LOT OF HARD TIMES AND
SUFFERED SOME ADVERSITIES AND
THINGS OF THAT NATURE, SHE
SHOULD HAVE PROBABLY KNEW THAT
OTHER PEOPLE'S DOWNFALLS AND
ISSUES AREN'T REALLY FUNNY.
THE FAMILY LET HER KNOW.
THEY DEFINITELY LET HER KNOW.
SHE QUIT TWITTER, SHE QUIT
INSTAGRAM, SHE QUIT BLACKPLANET,
AMAZON...
[LAUGHTER]
SHE QUIT IT ALL.
I THINK SHE EVEN QUIT CHRISTIAN
MINGLE.
SHE SAYS SHE DON'T WANT NO PARTS
OF THE INTERNET.
BUT, DEMI, CALL ME.
I'LL GET THEM OFF YOU.
I WILL CALL THE FAMILY OFF.
[APPLAUSE]
THE FAMILY DON'T PLAY THAT, WHEN
YOU TALK ABOUT ONE OF US.
WE'VE GOT PROBLEMS.
SO HIT ME UP.
THIS JUST IN -- THEY DONE FOUND
THE CULPRIT WHO SNITCHED ON 21
SAVAGE!
IT'S TEKASHI 6IX9INE!
YOU TELLING ON EVERYBODY!
[LAUGHTER]
JA RULE, WATCH OUT!
HE SNITCHING ON ALL THE RAPPERS!
[LAUGHTER]
FOR THOSE OF YOU DON'T KNOW WHO
TEKASHI IS, HE'S A VERY COLORFUL
WRAPPER.
TATTOOS, RAINBOW HAIR, ALL THAT.
TEKASHI THOUGHT HE WAS ABOUT
THAT LIFE.
APPARENTLY HE'S REALLY NOT.
HE PLED GUILTY TO NINE CHARGES
AFTER SNITCHING ON ALL OF HIS
CREW MEMBERS.
HE USED TO COME OUT AND DO
INTERVIEWS, "I'M NEVER GOING TO
JAIL!"
ALL THAT.
HE WOULD DO ALL OF THE STUFF.
BUT APPARENTLY, MAN, I DON'T
KNOW WHAT TO SAY IN THE
SITUATION LIKE THAT.
IT'S UNFORTUNATE.
I DON'T WISH PRISON ON ANYONE.
BUT, YOU KNOW HE WAS ALWAYS
TALKING ABOUT IT.
SAYING HOMOPHOBIC SLAYERS,
"YOU'RE GOING TO DO THIS TO ME,"
BUT NOW YOU'RE GOING TO BE IN
PRISON AND YOU WILL FIND ALL
THAT OUT!
THEY WILL PUT YOU TO THE TEST!
[APPLAUSE]
THE NOT TOPIC ABOUT THIS ONE, I
THINK IT'S REPORTEDLY 47 YEARS?
HOLD UP.
I'M NOT THE GREATEST
MATHEMATICIAN IN THE WORLD, BUT
47 YEARS, AND HE IS 22 YEARS
OLD...
THAT MEANS IT'S ACTUALLY --
TEKASHI WILL GET OUT OF PRISON
WHEN HE IS 69!
[LAUGHTER]
MAY BE YOUR NAME SHOULD HAVE
BEEN TEKASHI TWO AND A HALF!
YOU KEEP SNITCHING ON PEOPLE,
IT'S GOING TO BE TEKASHI FIVE TO
SEVEN.
AGAIN, WE CAN DO IS SEND OUR
PRAYERS.
THIS IS AN UNFORTUNATE
SITUATION.
LET THIS BE A LESSON TO ALL THE
YOUNG PEOPLE OUT THERE WHO
GLAMORIZE AND ADMIRE GANG
VIOLENCE IN ANY TYPE OF
VIOLENCE.
IF YOU AIN'T REALLY ABOUT IT,
IT'S NOTHING TO PLAY WITH,
Y'ALL.
THIS IS PEOPLE'S REAL LIVES.
[APPLAUSE]
OTHER BIG NEWS THIS WEEKEND --
[LAUGHS]
SHOUTS OUT TO MY GUY, PETE
DAVIDSON, Y'ALL.
25 YEARS OLD, HAS MOVED ON FROM
ARIANA GRANDE TO 45-YEAR-OLD
KATE BECKINSALE!
[APPLAUSE]
MAKING ME PROUD!
MAKE ME PROUD, PETE!
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU ALL KNOW
THIS, BUT PETE IS LITERALLY MY
LITTLE BROTHER.
I'LL TELL YOU A STORY -- I USED
TO DO MORNINGS HERE IN
NEW YORK CITY.
EVERY MORNING ON MY RADIO SHOW,
A 15-YEAR-OLD KID USED TO CALL
IN AND TELL ME HOW FUNNY HE WAS.
I THOUGHT, "THIS KID IS
ANNOYING."
AND ICE TO DO COMEDY SHOWS
AROUND THE CITY, THE GOTHAM
COMEDY CLUB COME ALL THE
DIFFERENT COMEDY CLUBS OUT
THERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT, LITTLE BOY
CUSTOMER, BUT I WILL PUT YOU ON
STAGE!
HE GOT ON STAGE.
IT WAS THE YOUNG PETE DAVIDSON.
HE ROCKED IT, Y'ALL.
I MADE A PROMISE TO HIM.
I SAID, "YOU BET WILL NOT GO
BACK AND FINISH HIGH SCHOOL, I
PROMISE IT WILL TAKE ON THE ROAD
WITH ME."
AND I TOOK THEM ALL OF THE
COUNTRY.
WE DID MY FIRST STAND-UP SPECIA
SPECIAL.
I PUT THEM IN HIS FIRST MOVIE
CALLED "SCHOOL DANCE."
THEN I ALSO PUT HIM ON "WILD N'
OUT," AND THE REST IS HISTORY.
HE'S ACTUALLY FLYING IN TONIGHT,
BUT YOU'RE GOING TO DO SOME
COMEDY AROUND THE SEAT SITE.
IF YOU SEE IS OUT THERE, WE'RE
GOING TO GO PULL UP.
IT'S FUNNY, HE ALWAYS USED TO
TELL ME, "MAN, I'M FOLLOWING IN
YOUR FOOTSTEPS."
AND I SAID, "YOU DEFINITELY ARE,
DATING ALL THESE COUGARS!"
IT'S DEFINITELY GOING DOWN.
[LAUGHTER]
THE KING OF COUGARS, I HEARD
LIAM PAYNE AND NAOMI CAMPBELL
ARE DATING?
THE NOT TOPIC ABOUT THAT, I
DIDN'T KNOW NAOMI WAS SINGLE!
WOULD HAPPEN, NAOMI?
SHE WAS IN MY TOP THREE, Y'ALL!
IT WAS MARIAH CAREY -- GOT HURT.
HALLE BERRY, AND NAOMI!
YOU BETTER TREAT HER RIGHT,
BECAUSE THERE ARE SOME CHOCOLATE
WAITING!
I'M WAITING!
[LAUGHTER]
WHERE HAVING GOOD TIME.
IN ALL SERIOUSNESS COME I WANT
TO CLOSE ON THIS ONE.
JUSSIE SMOLLETT SPOKE OUT FOR
THE FIRST TIME SINCE HIS BRUTAL
ATTACK.
PEOPLE HAVE BEEN REALLY NEGATIVE
SINCE THEY DIDN'T HAVE ALL THE
INFORMATION OF THE DON'T KNOW
THE STORY.
BUT HE WANTED TO CLEAR SOME
THINGS THAT.
SO TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
HE GOT TO SPEAK --
>> I WAS BRUISED, BUT MY RIBS
WERE NOT CRACKS.
THEY WERE NOT BROKEN.
I WENT TO THE DOCTOR
IMMEDIATELY.
I WAS NOT HOSPITALIZED.
ABOVE ALL, I THOUGHT THE [BLEEP]
ATTACKER.
>> Nick: HE SAID HE'S THE GAY
TUPAC!
LET'S FOCUS ON THE RIGHT THING.
HE SAID HE IS FIGHTING BACK.
THAT'S A BEAUTIFUL THING.
I DON'T CARE WHAT'S ON HIS
CELL PHONE COME ALL THAT
INFORMATION.
THIS MAN PUT HIS LIFE ON THE
LINE.
HE'S PRETTY MUCH THE MINOR'S
CANARY.
THIS OF THE RAGE IN THE COAL
MINE, THEY SENT A CANARY INTO
THE COAL MINE AND THEY GET IN
THERE TO TEST ALL THE DANGEROUS
GASES AND STUFF.
IF THE CANARY DIDN'T COME BACK,
THEN THE HUMANS WOULD GO DOWN
THERE.
SO THE LGBTQ COMMUNITY, THE
BLACK MUNI, THEY ARE THE
CANARIES OF OUR TIME IN OUR
SOCIETY.
HE PUT HIS LIFE IN THE LINE.
WE ROCKING WITH YOU.
WE APPRECIATE THAT STRENGTH,
MAN.
WE STAND WITH YOU.
TO SUPPORT MY MAN JUSSIE, I'M
GOING TO MAKE A CONTRIBUTION
PAID WE ARE ALL GOING TO PICK
COUNTRIES INTO ONE OF HIS
FAVORITE ORGANIZATIONS, THE
NATIVE SON.
IT'S A GROUP THAT AIMS TO HONOR
THE BLACK GAY MALE COMMUNITY
WHERE THEY CELEBRATE AND EMPOWER
EACH OTHER.
WE ARE ROCKING WITH YOU, GAY
TUPAC!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WE'VE GOT A LOT MORE GREAT SHOW
COMING UP!
"THE REAL HOUSEWIVES OF
ATLANTA."
I LOVE HER, ALSO SPEED WE WILL
GET THE TALKING.
GRANDPA'S NOT, WERE GOING TO
COME ON BACK.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Nick: WE HERE TO PARTY!
IT'S GOING DOWN, Y'ALL!
WELCOME BACK!
WHERE MY FAMILY OUT?
>> Audience: WE LOVE THAT!
>> Nick: ABSOLUTELY COME OVER
HAVING A GOOD TIME.
UP TO SEE AGAIN, IF YOU'RE
WATCHING --
I LIKE SOME SEASON, Y'ALL KNOW!
I DON'T LIKE CALLING THEM
COUGARS.
I LIKE THEM ARE, LIKE WINE.
SPEAKING OF FINE, OUR FIRST
GUEST IS ONE OF THE STARS ON
"THE REAL HOUSEWIVES OF
ATLANTA."
TAKE A LOOK.
>> MIKE IS HERE.
MIKE IS HERE.
LIKE IT, I HAVE THEM IN THE
FLESH.
I COULD TOUCH HIM, I CAN FEEL
THEM, I CAN KISS HIM, I CAN HUG
HIM.
I'M SO HAPPY.
SERIOUSLY, I'M SO HAPPY HE'S
HERE!
>> REMEMBER THE COUNTER?
[LAUGHS]
>> YEAH, I REMEMBER THE COUNTER.
>> WHAT YOU REMEMBER ABOUT THE
COUNTER?
>> IT'S A STRONG COUNTER!
IT'S VERY STURDY.
REMEMBER THAT?
>> WHAT HAPPENED ON THE COUNTER?
>> [LAUGHS]
I WAS SERVED.
>> Nick: WE DEFINITELY GOING
TO TALK ABOUT THAT!
I WANT TO HEAR ABOUT THE
COUNTER!
PLEASE WELCOME, CYNTHIA BAILEY!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Nick: HAVE A SEAT!
STANDING!
>> Cynthia: THANK YOU!
>> Nick: WE'VE GOT TO GET THE
SHOE CAM.
GO AHEAD AND STOMPED ON IT ONE
TIME.
WITH THE PRETTY TOES OUT!
GOT THE PRETTY TOES OUT!
I LOVE IT.
HOW YOU BEEN?
>> Cynthia: I'VE BEEN GOOD!
>> Nick: IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU!
>> Cynthia: THANK YOU!
YOU LOOKING GOOD.
>> Nick: WE LOOK GOOD
TOGETHER!
SHE GOT A MAN.
WE'RE GOING TO TALK ABOUT THE
COUNTER AND ALL THAT TYPE OF
STUFF.
FIRST, ONE OF THE HOT TOPICS --
IT'S A BIG WEEK AND FROM YOUR
CITY, ATLANTA.
WERE YOU DOWN THERE?
DID YOU GO TO ANY GOOD PARTIES
GOOD PARTIES?
>> Cynthia: I DID.
I HUNG OUT ALL WEEKEND LONG.
I WAS GOING TO GO TO THE
SUPER BOWL BUT I HAD TO COME
HERE, SO HAD TO CUT IT SHORT.
BUT I DID -- MICRO KENYA, AND --
ALL THAT FINE CHOCOLATE.
>> Nick: ROBIN GIVENS?
>> Cynthia: IT WAS GOOD.
I MET SOME REALLY COOL PEOPLE
THIS WEEK.
AND IT'S A GREAT PEOPLE THIS
WEEK.
>> Nick: I HEARD -- TELL ME
ABOUT THIS -- YOU MIGHT HAVE RAN
INTO TOM BRADY?
>> Cynthia: I DID!
I THOUGHT I RAN INTO TOM BRADY.
BE CLEAR, HIS NAME STILL COULD
BE TOM BRADY.
IT JUST NOT MAY BE TOM BRADY.
>> Nick: THAT'S TOM AND JERRY.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Cynthia: KNOW!
YOU DON'T THINK HE LOOKS LIKE
TOM BRADY?
>> Nick: ALL WHITE PEOPLE
DON'T LOOK ALIKE, CYNTHIA!
[LAUGHTER]
>> Cynthia: HEAR OF SOMETHING,
IT WAS SUPER BOWL WEEKEND!
ATLANTA, I KNEW HE WAS IN TOWN.
I SAW THIS GUY --
>> Nick: THE QUARTERBACK IS
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE!
I KNOW TOM BRADY'S IN IN THE
MALL SOMEWHERE!
>> Cynthia: HE'S A
SPORTSCASTER PROVED THIS KIND OF
THE WORLD I'M IN NOW.
I WAS LIKE, "MIKE IS GOING TO
DIE WHEN I TELL HIM I RENTED
TOM BRADY AND GOT A PICTURE!"
SO I SENT THEM A PICTURE, AND
THE RESPONSE WAS, "WHO IS THIS?
">> Cynthia: "TOM BRADY,
HELLO!"
AND HE WAS LIKE, "BABY, THAT'S
NOT TOM BRADY."
>> Nick: ANY POST THIS?
>> Cynthia: YES, BECAUSE AT
THAT POINT I LEFT.
WHEN I MET NOT TO TOM BRADY --
[LAUGHS]
>> Nick: TOM AND JERRY.
>> Cynthia: I DID THE CARPETS
AT ALL THE PARTIES, AND THEY ASK
HOW THE SUPER BOWL WAS GOING.
AND I SAID, "IT'S GREAT, I JUST
MET TOM BRADY!"
SO IT CAN'T GET NO BETTER THAN
THIS!
>> Nick: HILARIOUS.
IT SOUNDS LIKE YOUR MAN, YOUR
BOYFRIEND, MIKE, IS AN AMAZING
GUY.
[APPLAUSE]
Y'ALL LOOK GOOD TOGETHER!
STEVE HARVEY SET Y'ALL UP?
>> Cynthia: YES, STEVE SET US
UP.
HE'S A FRIEND.
I WENT ON HIS SHOW TO GET A
LITTLE UPDATE ON THE SINGLE
LIFE, DATING LIFE.
I WAS LIKE, "YEAH, I'M OUT OF
CLEANING UP, BLAH, BLAH, BLAH."
IT WAS HARD MEETING SOMEONE.
HE SAID, "I KNOW A LOT OF GUYS
WHO WOULD GO OUT WITH YOU,
CYNTHIA."
AND I SAID, "YOU THINK YOU CAN
FIND SOMEBODY BETTER THAN I CAN
CUSTOMER GOATS DO IT."
I WENT IN WITH AN EXPECTATION.
AND WHY WHAT MIKE, HE WAS REALLE
GUY.
>> Nick: WOULD YOU EVER GET
MARRIED AGAIN CUSTOMER GREENERY
BEEN MADE BEFORE.
IF YOU CANDIDATE?
>> Cynthia: I WOULD SAY THAT I
WILL DEFINITELY GET MARRIED
AGAIN.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
LET ME CLEAR IT UP >> Nick: I
WANT!
>> Cynthia: I USED TO SAY THAT
I WOULDN'T.
>> Nick: I'M STILL SAYING
THAT!
>> Cynthia: YOU CAN'T SAY
>> Nick: I'M SINGLE AS A SLICE
OF CHEESE!
[LAUGHTER]
BUT FOR YOU, IT WORKS.
I UNDERSTAND.
>> Cynthia: WHAT I GET MARRIED
AGAIN?
IF GOD BLESSES ME TO GET MARRIED
AGAIN, YES.
BUT DO I THINK I WOULD MARRY
MIKE?
ABSOLUTELY.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: IS AWESOME.
HOW DO Y'ALL MAKE THAT WORK?
HE'S IN L.A., YOU'RE IN ATLANTA.
>> Cynthia: YES, WE'VE GOT
SOME RULES.
THERE ARE RULES IN THIS GAME.
HE LIVES IN L.A., I LIVE IN
ATLANTA.
WE HAVE A TWO WEEK RULE.
I GO TO HIM OR HE COMES TO ME.
THEN WE ONLY FACE TIME.
IT HELPS.
>> Nick: TO SEE HIS FACE EVERY
DAY AND NEVER MORE THAN TWO
WEEKS.
>> Cynthia: MULTIPLE TIMES A
DAY.
YOU CAN DO A LOT WITH THE PHONE
NOW.
>> Nick: THIS IS A DAYTIME
KIND OF SHOW!
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR ABOUT WHAT
Y'ALL BE DOING ON THE PHONE!
[LAUGHTER]
AND WHAT HAPPENED ON THE COUNTE
COUNTER?
>> Cynthia: OH, WELL...
>> Nick: WHAT THE PHONES
INVOLVE?
KEEP IT TO YOURSELF, BABY.
RECENTLY, ANDY COHEN -- HE HAD A
BABY SHOWER, EVERYBODY WAS
THERE.
YOU WERE THERE.
>> Cynthia: I WAS THERE!
>> Nick: THEY WAS TURNING UP!
ALL THE HOUSEWIVES!
OH!
LOW!
WHERE YOU UP ON THE TABLE DOING
THAT, TOO?
>> Cynthia: I WAS!
THERE MAY BE EIGHT       A TWERF
ME.
IT [CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
OH, MY GOSH, !
I DID KNOW THAT WAS GOING TO DO
THE VIDEO!
[LAUGHS]
>> Nick: CYNTHIA, THAT'S NOT
REALLY A TWERK!
THAT'S NOT HOW IT WORKS!
SPECIE LET ME EXPLAIN.
I'M NOT THE BEST TWERKER, BUT
I'M TRYING.
I PUT MY OWN SPIN ON IT.
A LITTLE FROGGY THING.
FROGGY-SAY.
DON'T DO IT DOGGY STYLE COMING
TO A FROGGY STYLE.
>> Wendy: YOU'RE GOING THROUGH
YOUR BACK OUT DOING THAT!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Cynthia: MIKE ISN'T
COMPLAINING.
[LAUGHS]
>> Nick: THAT'S A LOT OF FUN.
TELL ME WHAT YOU WE CAN EXPECT
FROM THE REST OF THE SEASON.
>> Cynthia: OH, WELL MIKE.
WE'RE STILL IN TOKYO.
TOKYO WAS GREAT.
>> Nick: ANYBODY FIGHTING?
>> Cynthia: OF COURSE!
NOT PHYSICALLY FIGHTING, BUT A
LOT OF SHADE.
A LOT OF READING.
A LOT OF GETTING READ.
>> Nick: IT'S LIKE A LIBRARY.
THEY READ, THEY SHADE.
>> Cynthia: READING IS GOOD!
>> Nick: YOU GOT TO PUT A
COUPLE PEOPLE IN THEY PLACE!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Cynthia: HERE'S THE THING.
I'M IN SUCH A GREAT PLACE IN MY
LIFE, AND I WILL TALK ABOUT OUR
SHOOT THAT WE DID.
>> Nick: NEED TO DO A PHOTO
SHOOT!
DID MIKE GET JEALOUS?
>> Cynthia: THAT WAS BEFORE
MIKE.
THAT HELPED ME MEET MIKE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: JUST SAYING.
>> Cynthia: [LAUGHS]
WE DID THAT!
DID WE DO THAT?
THAT'S ME!
>> Nick: MIKE, YOU BETTER TAKE
CARE OF HER, PLAYER!
YOU BETTER TAKE CARE OF HER, I'M
JUST SAYING!
I HAVE NO PROBLEM BEING A SIDE
DUDE!
[LAUGHTER]
I WOULD BE THE MACARONI AND
CHEESE TO THE STAKE!
>> Cynthia: THIS IS WHAT I WAS
ABOUT THIS.
I'M BEING SERIOUS NOW.
YOU COULD HAVE CHOSEN ANY MODEL
THAT YOU WANTED TO BE PART OF
THE SHOOT, AND I HAD JUST TURNED
50.
I WAS SO HONORED AND FLATTERED
THAT YOU CHOSE ME, BECAUSE I
REALLY GO HARD FOR THE 50
CLOTHES!
I EMBRACE IT.
>> Nick: 50 CENT!
>> Cynthia: YES, 50 CENT!
LOOK AT ALL THIS INSPIRATION.
>> Wendy: YOU ARE AN
INSPIRATION, CLEAN!
THANK YOU.
AND THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
"THE REAL HOUSEWIVES OF ATLANTA"
AIRS SUNDAY NIGHT AT 8:00 ON
BRAVO.
UP NEXT, THE JERSEY BOYS PIZZA
ARE HERE!
YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS IT.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
Got it?
Got it.
Nooooo...
Quick, the Quicker Picker Upper!
Bounty picks up messes quicker
and is 2x more absorbent.
Bounty, the Quicker Picker
Upper.
♪ There's no better two ♪
♪ than the two of us. ♪
♪ I think you're forgetting
about Dunkin' Go2s. ♪
Dunkin' Go2s,
a great deal for $2, $4, or $5.
America Runs on Dunkin'.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: WELCOME BACK TO "THE
WENDY SHOW"!
Y'ALL HAVING A GOOD TIME?
FAMILY, WHERE WE HAD?
WE LOVE THAT!
SPEAKING TO FAMILY AND THINGS
THAT WE LOVE, I REALLY LOVE
HANGING OUT WITH MY KIDS, GIVING
DINNER TIME.
BECAUSE I'M A HORRIBLE COOK.
I'M SUCH A BAD COOK, BUT ONE OF
MY FAVORITES TO DO WITH ALL
THREE OF MY KIDS IS MAKE THOSE
LITTLE ENGLISH MUFFIN PIZZAS.
THAT'S WHAT WE USED TO DO BACK
IN THE PROJECTS!
IT AIN'T REAL PIZZA, WE JUST
TAKE SOME BALONEY AND RED SAUCE
ON AN ENGLISH MUFFIN.
ME AND MY KIDS LOVE MAKING THAT
SO MUCH, WE LOVE PIZZA.
SO TODAY, SOMEBODY'S GOING TO
HELP ME STEP MY PIZZA GAME OUT.
GIVE IT UP FOR THE JERSEY PIZZA
BOYS!
MICHAEL AND NICHOLAS!
THAT'S AMAZING!
Y'ALL ARE LIKE SOME PIZZA
NINJAS!
LITTLE PIZZA IN THE JUST.
WHAT'S UP, MIKE!
WHAT'S GOING ON, NICK!
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN WORKING
IN PIZZAS?
YOU'RE TOO YOUNG TO HAVE JOBS!
THEY GOT CHILD LABOR LAWS!
[LAUGHTER]
HOW LONG Y'ALL BEEN DOING THIS?
>> I'VE BEEN DOING THIS FOR
SEVEN YEARS.
>> Nick: THAT'S ALL YOUR LIFE,
NICK!
>> I'M 12.
>> Nick: SORRY.
I WAS LITTLE, TOO.
WILL Y'ALL HELP ME OUT OF HERE?
ON THE DOME I CAN KNOW LADIES
LOVE CHEFS AND COOKS AND STUFF.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I CANNOT COOK AT ALL, YELL.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE TO START.
>> YOU WANT TO START WITH THE
FLOOR.
FLOWER THE DOUGH.
>> Nick: WE AIN'T GOT A THEIR
HANDS?
>> YOU ALREADY DID!
>> MAKE SURE YOU FLOUR THE
ROLLING PIN.
>> Nick: I THOUGHT YOU GET
WHIPPINGS WITH THAT!
I CAN DO IT?
>> JUST ROLL THE DOUGH OUT.
>> COME ON COME A LITTLE MORE!
>> Nick: IT'S A RACE?
>> I PUT TEN BUCKS ON NICK!
>> I'M YOUR BROTHER!
>> NOW YOU WANT TO STRETCH IT O.
JUST MASSAGE IT.
>> Nick: I'M GOOD AT THAT.
HEY, BABY.
[LAUGHTER]
MASSAGE THE DOUGH.
I GOT THAT.
LIKE THAT?
>> IF YOU WANT TO TOSS IT NOW?
>> Nick: [LAUGHS]
CHILDREN, YES, I WANT TO TOSS
IT.
>> YOU PLAY BASKETBALL BEFORE,
RIGHT?
TO SHOOT A THREE DON'T LIKE
FREE THROW HIS ACT LIKE THAT.
IT'S ALL IN THE WRIST.
>> Nick: I DIDN'T SAY I WAS
GOOD AT BASKETBALL!
I WILL LEAVE IT TO
PROFESSIONALS.
CAN WE JUST WORK WITH YOURS?
SORRY, NICK.
I APOLOGIZE.
>> IT'S A GOOD SIZE.
>> Nick: DON'T WORRY ABOUT
THAT.
FOCUS.
>> WE DON'T HAVE TO USE THAT
ONE.
WE HAVE TO MOVE OVER HERE.
>> Nick: AND THIS IS THE
TOPPINGS?
>> YES.
AFTER THE SUPER BOWL IF YOU HAVE
ANY LEFT OVER WINGS --
>> Nick: THAT'S SMART!
LEFTOVERS!
>> NOW YOU WANT TO GET A FULL
HANDFUL.
>> Nick: HANDFUL OF CHICKEN.
>> Wendy: ALL RIGHT.
GET SOME CHEESE.
SPREAD IT OUT, ALL RIGHT.
CHICKEN.
CHEESE.
>> AND NOW HANDFUL OF CHEESE.
DROP IN A HANDFUL OF CHEESE,
DOUGH, AND LOOKED OVER NASTY
CHICKEN.
ALL RIGHT.
[LAUGHTER]
>> WHY DOES HAVE TO BE NASTY?
IT'S GOOD CHICKEN!
>> IF IT WAS FROM YESTERDAY,
IT'S NASTY!
I TOLD YOU THAT COLIN AND I HAD
VEGAN CHINESE FOOD YESTERDAY.
>> NOW YOU WANT TO PUT IT IN THE
OVEN AT 500 DEGREES FOR
5 MINUTES.
UNTIL IT'S GOLDEN BROWN.
NOW YOU WANT TO PUT SOME HOT
SAUCE ON IT.
>> Nick: FACTS.
ALL RIGHT.
>> NOW YOU WANT TO MAKE THREE
RINGS.
>> YOU CONTRITE WITH THE BLUE
CHEESE.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S MAKE A HAPPY FACE.
>> Wendy: GO-AHEAD, NICK.
IT IS UP.
>> Nick: CAN I TASTE IT?
I LIKE SPICY!
HAVEN'T YOU SEEN MY DATING
RECORD?
I LIKE THEM SPICY!
[LAUGHTER]
>> IS A GOOD?
>> Nick: IT CAN Y'ALL SHOW US
SOME MORE OF Y'ALL MOVES?
YEAH, YEAH!
♪ ♪
>> Nick: ME?
>> GET DOWN!
>> YOUR GOOD, YOUR GOOD
!
♪ ♪
>> READY?
>> Nick: LET'S MAKE SOME NOISE
FOR THE JERSEY PIZZA BOYS COME
UP MICHAEL AND NICHOLAS!
HERE AT "THE WENDY SHOW" WE GOT
Y'ALL A GIFT.
WE HAD TO HOOK Y'ALL UP.
READY FOR THIS?
WE HAD TO BRING YOU OUT SOME
LITTLE CHEF HATS.
MAKE SOME NOISE!
THERE WE GO.
>> THAT'S A HEAVY HAT!
>> Nick: BECAUSE IT'S ICED
OUT, BABY!
YOU DRIPPING NOW!
THE JERSEY PIZZA BOYS, MICHAEL
AND NICHOLAS.
YOU DEFINITELY LOOK AT SEXY.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
-We're doing karaoke later,
and you're gonna sing.
-Jamie, this is your house?
-I know, it's not much,
but it's home.
Right, kids?
-Kids?
-Papa, Papa!
-[ Laughs ]
-You didn't tell me
your friends were coming.
-Oh, yeah.
-This one is tiny like a child.
-Yeah, she is.
Oh, but seriously,
it's good to be surrounded
by what matters most --
a home and auto bundle
from Progressive.
-Oh, sweetie,
please, play for us.
-Oh, no, I couldn't.
-Please.
-Okay.
[ Singing in Spanish ]
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: WELCOME BACK!
I'M A HUGE FAN.
Y'ALL HAVING A GOOD TIME?
FAMILY, WHERE WE AT?
>> Audience: WE LOVE THAT!
>> Nick: I LOVE THE SEGMENT ON
THE SHOW, "ASK WENDY" SO MUCH
THAT I WANTED TO GIVE IT A TRY
MYSELF.
WENDY BE GIVING SOME GREAT
ADVICE.
MINE IS GOING TO BE A LITTLE
LOOSE.
WE'RE GOING TO CALL THE SEGMENT
"LOOSE CANNON!"
FORGIVE ME IF I SAY ANYTHING TO
OFFEND ANYBODY, BUT I AM
BRUTALLY HONEST!
YOU'RE GOING TO SIT WITH YOU,
MA'AM.
HEY, QUEEN, WHERE ARE YOU FROM
AND WHAT'S HER NAME?
>> MY NAME IS GYPSY AND I'M FROM
VIRGINIA.
B23?
>> Nick: I CAN'T DO IT.
MY MOUTH DON'T DO THAT.
Y'ALL SAY IT.
>> Audience: HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> Nick: I'LL WORK ON IT.
WHAT'S YOUR QUESTION?
>> WE HAD A FRIEND, AND WE
RECENTLY HAD A THREESOME WITH --
>> Nick: SLOW IT DOWN.
I NEED SOME POPCORN AND SOME
LOTION.
YOU HAD A WHAT?
>> WHEN SHE INTRODUCED ME TO ONE
OF HER FRIENDS WITH BENEFITS AND
WE HAD A THREESOME, BUT NOW ME
AND IN MY DATING.
>> Nick: I LIKE THIS.
I WOULD GO SEE THIS MOVIE.
WHERE IT PLAYING AT?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I SHOULD TELL
HER COME OR SHE SHOULD COME OR
WHAT WE SHOULD DO.
>> Nick: YOU BETTER CALL HER
AND SAY, "GIRL, IT'S POPPING UP
HERE!"
YOU ALREADY HAVE THE THREESOME,
WAS THE PROBLEM?
>> GIRL CODE!
>> Nick: ALWAYS BE HONEST.
IT'S FRIENDS BEFORE THAT.
THAT WAS YOUR FRIEND BEFORE THAT
DUDE WALKED IN.
SO KEEP SELLING WITH YOUR GIRL.
Y'ALL HAD FUN, YOU HAD YOUR
LITTLE THREESOME.
IF YOU DON'T WORK OUT, CALL ME!
[APPLAUSE]
>> I GOT YOU!
>> Nick: WILL BE RIGHT BACK,
YEAH.
WE WILL KEEP IT GOING WITH
"LOOSE CANNON."
IS A GOOD MUSICAL
Jimmy's gotten used to his whole
room smelling like sweaty odors.
Yup, he's gone Noseblind.
He thinks it smells fine, but
his mom smells this...
Luckily for all your
hard-to-wash fabrics...
...there's Febreze
Fabric Refresher.
Febreze doesn't just mask, it
eliminates odors you've...
...gone noseblind to.
And try Febreze
Unstopables for fabric.
With up to twice the fresh scent
power, you'll want to try it...
...again and again and maybe
just one more time.
Indulge in irresistible
freshness.
Febreze Unstopables.
Breathe Happy.
>> Nick: IT'S GOING DOWN,
Y'ALL!
WE HAVING A GOOD TIME HERE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
SHE WAS HELPING ME, SHE SAID MY
DRAWS WERE SHOWING WHEN I WAS
DANCING.
I STARTED TWERKING.
IT'S ALL ABOUT GOOD MUSIC,
Y'ALL.
SPEAKING OF GOOD MUSIC, I'VE GOT
A NEW SINGLE OUT CALLED "NOBODY
ELSE."
TYPE
DOLLAR SIGN
OF GOVERNOR MAGIC NOVEL.
MY BOOK, KING OF THE DANCE HALL
COMES OUT RIGHT NOW.
IT'S AVAILABLE NOW.
IF YOU WANT TO GET SEXY AND DO
SOME POPCORN AND LOTION.
ALL Y'ALL GET A COPY!
IT'S AVAILABLE.
WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
>> Wendy: WE ARE HAVING A
GREAT TIME HERE!
HERE IS ONE OF THE AUDIENCE
MEMBERS, FROM OHIO.
HE HAS BEEN MY CLOSET!
HE DONE UPSTAGE ME, CAME OUT
HERE ALL FLY!
IF YOU'RE EVER IN THE
NEW YORK CITY AREA AND WANT TO
BE PART OF THE STUDIO AUDIENCE
WITH ONE OF OUR SPECIAL GUEST
HOSTS, COME OUT AND JOIN US.
WE ARE HAVING A GOOD TIME,
RIGHT, Y'ALL?
GO TO WendyShow.com.
THE TICKETS ARE FREE AND A GOOD
TIME IS GUARANTEED.
WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
HE LOOKS LIKE --
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
Stouffer's Lasagna With Meat &
Sauce
has two times the beef of the
leading meat sauce lasagna.
That's double the tender ground
beef
baked into every cheesy,
mouthwatering bite.
When it comes to irresistible
taste,
more is always more.
Stouffer's.
Alright, I brought in
Ensure Max Protein...
To give you
the Protein you need
with less of
the sugar you don't.
(Straining)
I'll take that.
(Cheers)
30 grams of protein
and 1 gram of sugar.
Ensure Max Protein.
In two great flavors.
Never ending is now even better
at Olive Garden.
All new Never Ending Stuffed
Pastas starting at $12.99.
Pick your favorite stuffed
pasta, sauce and topping.
It's all never ending.
All new
Never Ending Stuffed Pastas.
Only for a limited time,
at Olive Garden.
>> Nick: WE ARE BACK!
WE HAVING FUN, Y'ALL.
A FAMILY, WHERE YOU AT?
WE LOVE THAT!
I'VE GOT A QUEEN NEXT TO ME.
I'M DONE, HOW DID I DO?
DID I DO GOOD?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I FEEL LIKE I WANT TO -- I
WOULDN'T BE HERE, I'VE GOT A
GOOD VIEW MOVIE STAR.
I WILL BE HERE TOMORROW.
MY BRO KENAN THOMPSON WILL BE
HERE.
THAT'S ONE OF MY BEST FRIENDS.
Y'ALL KNOW HIM FROM
"SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE," ALL THAT.
NAOMI,
♪
It hasn't always
been easy, has it?
♪
There have been days
when you doubted yourself.
♪
And days when you
were ready to quit.
♪
But you didn't.
Because you had the courage to
venture into something powerful.
Education.
If I leave you with just
three words of advice:
never...stop...growing.
[cheering]
>> TODAY, ON GIRL CHAT, JANET
JACKSON FANS ARE OUTRAGED OVER A