♪
>> Ridge: I hope seeing Steffy's
new baby isn't too hard on your
daughter.
>> Brooke: [ Clears throat ]
Yeah.
She had so many questions.
It was just consuming her.
So I thought it would be
good for Hope to do that.
I mean, maybe I was wrong.
>> Ridge: No, I-I don't think
you were.
I don't think she would have
gone if she didn't think she was
ready.
>> Brooke: And Liam's there, so
she's not gonna be alone.
>> Ridge: You know what I
appreciate?
I appreciate your daughter
trying to be excited for Steffy.
>> Brooke: Me too.
She's being very brave about
this adoption.
>> Ridge: It's amazing how fast
it all happened, huh?
>> Brooke: I know.
Steffy is accepting another
little girl into her family,
and that's wonderful.
But I can't help but wonder
how it's going to affect Hope.
>> Hope: Look at you.
It's nice to meet you, Phoebe.
We're so glad you came into this
world, and...
now you're a part of this
family.
>> Hope: You're gonna have the
best life.
And you're gonna be so,
so loved.
>> Charlie: Ladies,
what have I told you about
riding those scooters
up and down the hallway?
Hm? Hm? Hm?
>> Tiffany: You saw that?
>> Charlie: I'm head of
security.
I got eyes everywhere.
>> Zoe: Okay, well, then,
obviously you can see how
quickly we've been getting
things done.
Yeah.
We've been zipping from here to
there, and it's been a lot more
efficient.
>> Tiffany: You should try it,
Charlie.
Think of how fast you could take
down a perp on one of those
bad boys.
>> Charlie: You know, I guess I
would look pretty good on one
of those copper scooters, huh?
[ Zoe and Tiffany chuckle ]
>> Reese: Hey.
>> Zoe: Dad!
Oh, I'm so glad
that you're here.
I've really been
worried about you.
>> Reese: Well, you don't need
to worry about me anymore.
And, thank God, I don't have to
worry about you, either.
>> Zoe: Dad, what are you
talking about?
♪
>> Charlie: Well, I can assure
you, Dr. Buckingham, you don't
have to have any safety concerns
here at Forrester Creations.
I have everything under control.
>> Reese: [ Chuckles ]
I appreciate that, Charlie.
In fact, I'm counting on you to
take care of my little girl and
her buddy Tiffany, there.
>> Tiffany: Thanks, Dr. B.
>> Zoe: Uh, sorry, but
you're just acting rather weird,
okay?
So what's going on?
>> Reese: Well, honey, that's
part of why I came,
is to say goodbye.
>> Zoe: What?
>> Reese: I'm leaving
Los Angeles.
I'm headed back to London.
>> Ridge: We can worry about
this as much as we want.
It's not gonna change anything.
It's gonna be difficult.
It's gonna bring up a lot of
feelings for your daughter.
>> Brooke: I'm glad you
understand.
>> Ridge: I do.
>> Taylor: Hey -- Oh.
>> Ridge: Oh.
>> Taylor: Whoa. Wow.
>> Ridge: Hey.
>> Taylor: Uh, sorry.
>> Brooke: Taylor.
>> Taylor: Uh...
>> Brooke: Uh, I didn't realize
that you were here.
>> Taylor: Yeah.
Um, Brooke, I wanted to
talk to you.
I'm -- I'm sure you know by now
about baby Phoebe.
>> Brooke: Oh, yes.
Congratulations.
>> Ridge: And we're excited to
meet our new granddaughter.
How's she doing?
>> Taylor: She's doing great.
Um... And Steffy, she's
overwhelmed, of course,
but ecstatic.
But I want to talk to you about
how this whole thing might be
affecting Hope.
>> Ridge: Well, Hope already
knows.
It was only fair to
give her a heads up.
>> Taylor: [ Inhales sharply ]
How did she react?
>> Brooke: She's emotional.
But she's very excited for
Steffy.
In fact, she's over there with
Liam, meeting baby Phoebe
right now.
>> Hope: She's beautiful,
Steffy.
>> Steffy: I wish I could take
the credit, but the birth
parents are responsible for
that.
She's just so tiny. So innocent.
You're gonna be a good little
sister to Kelly, aren't you?
She's just gonna adore you.
She's gonna be protective of
you, and she might even let you
borrow her clothes.
Yeah.
She's such a sweetheart.
She feels like family.
Every day, people are fighting
type 2 diabetes with food,
family and FARXIGA,
the pill that starts with "f."
FARXIGA, along with
diet and exercise,
helps lower A1C in adults
with type 2 diabetes.
It's one pill a day.
And although it's not a
weight-loss drug,
it may help you lose weight.
Do not take if
allergic to FARXIGA.
If you experience symptoms
of a serious allergic reaction
such as rash, swelling,
difficulty breathing
or swallowing,
stop taking and seek
medical help right away.
Do not take FARXIGA if you
have severe kidney problems,
are on dialysis or
have bladder cancer.
Tell your doctor right
away if you have blood
or red color in your urine
or pain while you urinate.
FARXIGA can cause serious side
effects including dehydration,
genital yeast infections
in women and men,
serious urinary
tract infections,
low blood sugar,
and kidney problems.
Stop taking FARXIGA and
call your doctor right away
if you have signs
of ketoacidosis
which is serious and
may lead to death.
Ask your doctor about the pill
that starts with "f"
and visit FARXIGA.com
for savings.
If you can't afford
your medication,
AstraZeneca may be
able to help.
>> Brooke: You think it was a
mistake?
>> Taylor: Well, I -- I just
don't think it was very wise
for her emotions to go and
see Phoebe right now.
>> Brooke: I'm the one who
suggested it, but Hope decided
to go over there to Steffy's.
>> Ridge: She wants to be
supportive.
She knows it's an important time
for Steffy.
>> Brooke: And for Kelly.
She always wants to put the
children first.
>> Ridge: It's true.
They made that bargain.
Whatever happens between
the three of them,
the kids always come first.
You got to admire that.
>> Taylor: Okay.
Well, I mean, it seems like Hope
is handling the adoption very
well so far, and I appreciate
the effort she's making, but...
[ Sighs ]
You know, it just seems to me...
Being around Phoebe,
it's got to be so painful
for her to -- to --
It's got to be a reminder
of what she lost.
>> Brooke: Well, you know what's
remarkable to me is that an
infant was placed with Steffy so
quickly.
So, you said this was through a
connection of yours?
>> Taylor: Yes. Heh...
It all just sort of fell into
place.
Steffy was very lucky.
>> Ridge: And that baby's
pretty lucky, too.
>> Taylor: Yeah.
I mean, the timing is not great.
I know that.
But a baby is a gift.
I mean, I really believe
that this baby was always meant
to be a part of our family.
>> Zoe: Dad, you can't just
spring this on me.
I mean, when were you even
planning on leaving?
>> Reese: Today. [ Sighs ]
>> Zoe: Today?!
Why? Did --
Did something happen?
>> Reese: Look, I'm -- I'm not
in any trouble, if that's
what you're wondering.
I'm just transferring back.
There's been a lot of
re-shuffling.
Plus, I can re-focus on my
research.
I just think that going back to
London is the best idea,
especially for your sake.
>> Zoe: Why would you say that?
I-I don't want you to go.
>> Reese: Zoe, me being here
stresses you out.
I know it does.
>> Zoe: Okay, at first.
I mean, I'll admit, when you
just showed up out of the blue,
it really did worry me.
But...
Dad, I've actually enjoyed
having you here.
>> Reese: And I've loved our
time together.
But I don't want to complicate
your life any more than I have.
Plus, I have my work.
>> Zoe: Yeah, but you have your
job at the hospital,
and the clinic on Catalina.
Okay, you don't need to go back
to England.
>> Reese: I wish it --
>> Zoe: You can just -- Listen.
You can build your practice
here.
>> Reese: I wish it were that
simple.
You'll be good.
I know you will be.
You're a kind, honest person.
And I love you
more than anything.
I've loved being here with you.
And I couldn't be any prouder.
My girl, modeling
for Forrester Creations?
What? That is something!
>> Zoe: Dad...
[ Voice breaking ] You really
don't have to leave.
>> Reese: I'll come back,
and I'll visit,
and you'll come home,
and you'll see me.
It doesn't matter where I am
or how grown you are.
I'll always be your dad.
And anytime you need me,
I'll come running.
You keep making your dreams
happen.
You keep it up with your
painting.
>> Zoe: [ Sobs, sighs ]
>> Reese: You do what makes you
happy.
You don't let this city
change you.
>> Zoe: I won't.
>> Reese: I love you
more than anything, kiddo.
You mean the world to me.
>> Zoe: [ Sniffles ]
I love you, too, Dad.
>> Hope: I can't stop
staring at her.
>> Steffy: Yeah, she has that
effect on me, too.
Look, she's already falling in
love with her Aunt Hope.
Looks like you two have a
special bond.
>> Hope: Gosh, she's such a good
baby.
I'm so happy that she found her
family.
>> Steffy: I'm glad you got to
meet her.
>> Liam: Um, I mean, maybe --
maybe it's time for a bottle?
>> Steffy: Oh, no.
She'll let us know
when she's hungry.
>> Liam: Okay.
>> Hope: Are you hungry, Phoebe?
No? You're all cozy right here?
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah, me too.
Searching for a way to
help stop your cold sore?
Only Abreva can
get rid of it in...
...as little as 2 1/2 days
when used at the first sign.
Abreva starts to
work immediately
to block the virus and
protect healthy cells.
Abreva acts on it.
So you can too.
In one week...
a lot will happen in your life.
Wrinkles just
won't.
Neutrogena®
Rapid Wrinkle
Repair's
derm-proven retinol
works so fast,
it takes only one week
to reveal younger looking skin.
Neutrogena®
All Tyson Any'tizers Chicken,
is raised with no
antibiotics ever.
[ music winding down ]
They're a great
decision for snacktime.
Allowing the band to
practice at your house...
Not a great decision.
Keep it real. Keep it
Tyson Any'tizers.
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
♪
There it is the coffee ring,
it's been sitting
there all week.
And just like
that, it's shining.
Look at you.
Beautify it with pledge.
S.C. Johnson.
Gas?
Bloating?
Discomfort?
Don't get bent out of shape.
Get relief fast with Phazyme.
Double the medicine of
Gas-X Extra Strength.
Next time, Phazyme.
>> Ridge: That went as well as
could be expected.
>> Brooke: Ah, Taylor and I know
how to put aside our differences
and focus on the children.
>> Ridge: Hey.
I'm proud of you.
I'm proud of how you're
handling this adoption.
>> Brooke: Well, it does bother
me on some level, being so close
to losing Beth.
>> Ridge: Well, you're dealing
with your own grief.
And you're there for Hope.
It's not an easy position
to be in.
>> Brooke: And I would do
anything I could to take away
Hope's pain.
But I think it's just gonna
take some time.
Time for her to heal.
>> Ridge: And family.
If she allows us to be there.
>> Brooke: [ Sighs ]
I just can't believe that
Steffy is going to have two
daughters in her family, and
Hope...
Do you think she'll ever
hold her own child?
>> Ridge: [ Sighs ]
Yeah, she will.
>> Brooke: I mean, it would
break my heart if she --
she never got to experience
that bond between a mother
and a-a baby.
>> Ridge: Well, she's still
struggling.
But she's got you. She's got us.
She's got Liam.
>> Brooke: [ Sighs ]
>> Ridge: We'll get her
through this.
>> Brooke: Yeah, I know. I know.
>> Ridge: And Phoebe is gonna be
great for everybody.
>> Brooke: Heh.
>> Ridge: Right? Even Hope.
Kids, little babies, they're --
they heal things, right?
>> Brooke: Yes. You're right.
Children are a blessing.
And we're gonna love this
Phoebe.
Welcome her into our family.
And eventually...
Hope will do that, too.
[ Knock on door ]
>> Taylor: Reese?
>> Reese: Taylor.
>> Taylor: Whoa! Heh...
Hi.
Wow, you -- It's true.
You really are leaving.
>> Reese: Yep.
The transfer came through.
I'm leaving on a red-eye
tonight.
>> Taylor: Well, I'm -- I'm glad
I caught you before you left.
>> Reese: Me too.
How's the baby?
>> Taylor: Oh, Phoebe is
amazing.
Steffy's just absolutely
thrilled.
>> Reese: Well, I'm glad
to hear that.
>> Taylor: She is a wonderful
mother, Reese.
>> Reese: I have no doubt.
That's why I felt comfortable
introducing you to the
birth mother.
>> Taylor: Yes,
and I'm so grateful.
[ Stammers ]
I will never be able to thank
you enough for what you've done
for me and Steffy.
[ Kelly cries on monitor ]
>> Steffy: Oh.
Did you hear that?
Phoebe, your older sister's up.
I'll be right back.
>> Liam: Okay.
>> Steffy: Ohh. Look who it is.
>> Liam: Hi, Kelly!
>> Hope: Hi.
>> Steffy: Kelly, here she is.
Do you remember your
little sister?
>> Hope: Oh, my gosh.
I swear I just saw a smile.
>> Steffy: [ Chuckles ]
>> Hope: Did you just smile,
Phoebe?
>> Liam: I'm telling you,
they're already in cahoots with
each other.
>> Steffy: Well -- ha -- that's
already destroying my life,
clearly.
[ Laughs ]
>> Liam: [ Chuckles ]
>> Hope: Oh, they're gonna be
the best of friends.
>> Steffy: Yeah, yeah.
>> Hope: Can you imagine all the
fun they're gonna have together?
>> Steffy: Gosh!
Kelly is so much bigger than
Phoebe.
>> Liam: I was just thinking
the same thing.
>> Hope: They're so lucky
to have each other.
And this is how we originally
saw it.
Me holding my daughter,
and you holding Kelly.
That's how it was supposed to be
with Beth.
>> Steffy: Hope, I'm gonna need
some help.
And Phoebe's gonna need
all the family she can get.
I understand if this is
difficult for you, but I'd like
for you to be part of her life.
>> Hope: I'd like that, too.
The day after chemo
shouldn't mean going
back to the doctor
just for a shot.
With Neulasta Onpro
patients get their day back...
to be with family,
or just to sleep in.
Strong chemo can put you at
risk of serious infection.
In a key study Neulasta
reduced the risk of infection
from 17% to 1%,
a 94% decrease.
Neulasta Onpro is designed
to deliver Neulasta
the day after chemo
and is used by most patients
today.
Neulasta is for certain
cancer patients
receiving strong chemotherapy.
Do not take Neulasta if you're
allergic to it
or Neupogen (filgrastim).
An incomplete dose could
increase infection risk.
Ruptured spleen,
sometimes fatal as well as
serious lung problems,
allergic reactions,
kidney injuries and capillary
leak syndrome have occurred.
Report abdominal or shoulder
tip pain, trouble breathing
or allergic reactions to
your doctor right away.
In patients with sickle
cell disorders,
serious, sometimes fatal crises
can occur.
The most common side effect
is bone and muscle ache.
Ask your doctor about
Neulasta Onpro.
Pay no more than $5 per dose
with copay card.
New Trident Spearmint Rush Vibes
start with a light crystal
coating,
then change into a smooth gum.
With bursts of spearmint flavor
that pop, pop, pop.
New Trident Vibes.
A Burst of Something New.
♪ Seed to the oat to the O ♪
♪ To the honey in each bite ♪
♪ Healthy hearts make life
sweeter ♪
♪ So you can live it right ♪
♪ Good goes around and around
and around and around ♪
What does help for Heart Failure
look like?
It looks like George having a
busy day.
♪ THE BEAT GOES ON ♪
George has ENTRESTO,
a Heart Failure medicine that
helps his heart...
so he can keep on doing
what he loves.
In the largest Heart Failure
study ever,
ENTRESTO was proven superior at
helping people stay alive
and out of the hospital.
It helps improve your heart's
ability to pump blood
to the body.
Don't take ENTRESTO if pregnant;
it can cause harm or death
to an unborn baby.
Don't take ENTRESTO with
an ACE inhibitor or aliskiren,
or if you've had angioedema
with an ACE or ARB.
The most serious side effects
are angioedema,
low blood pressure,
kidney problems,
or high blood potassium.
♪ THE BEAT GOES ON ♪
Ask your doctor about ENTRESTO
for Heart Failure.
That was great!
Entrust your heart to ENTRESTO.
♪ THE BEAT GOES ON ♪
>> Taylor: Well, I'm sad
to see you go.
I-I didn't know you were going
back to London so soon.
>> Reese: It's time.
>> Taylor: You weren't
here that long.
>> Reese: I accomplished
what I needed to do.
>> Taylor: Right, right.
And one of those things was
making sure your daughter got
settled into L.A.
>> Reese: Yeah.
My daughter means
the world to me.
I would do anything to make sure
that she is safe and happy.
>> Taylor: I am gonna miss you,
Reese.
And you've made such a huge
impact on Steffy and my life in
such a short amount of time.
The way you came into our life,
and you -- you helped us find
that beautiful little girl...
I believe it's like
divine intervention, you know?
Steffy has suffered so much in
her life -- so much loss and so
much disappointment.
She lost her twin.
She lost Liam.
She lost a baby of her own
before Kelly.
And she puts up a strong front,
but...
This gift you've provided
has truly given her a lot of
hope.
Thank you.
>> Liam: Well?
That couldn't have been easy.
>> Hope: I wanted to meet her.
>> Liam: Yeah.
Given all the hell you've been
through, the courage it must
have taken to put your pain
aside, to go over to that house,
to hold that baby, to welcome
her into the family...
I'm proud of you.
>> Hope: Well, Phoebe's gonna be
part of our lives for a very
long time.
>> Liam: Yeah.
She's my daughter's sister.
We're gonna be seeing
a lot of her.
>> Hope: She was beautiful.
>> Liam: Yeah, she was.
>> Hope: I-I can't stop thinking
about her.
You know, when I held her,
it was like...
I don't know. This...
energy just went throughout
my body, this warmth.
And -- and I know I don't --
It's hard to explain, but...
>> Liam: No, I -- I felt the
same thing.
I mean, I'm surprised you held
it together.
You've been dealing with
so much.
>> Hope: Yeah.
You know, that
precious little girl,
it was surreal, holding her.
It was like...
I wanted to close my eyes and
pretend like she was mine.
Pretend like it was our Beth.
And I know that's a terrible
thing to say.
I know it is Steffy's baby, and
our baby died.
But, you know, just for that
moment, I just wanted to know
what it would be like to hold my
own daughter.
What it would feel like
to be a mom.
Liam, I can't help but feel like
that that life should have been
ours.
That that little baby that I was
holding in our arms,
that it should have been Beth.
[ Crying ]
Our sweet little baby Beth.
>> Steffy: I'm here.
Mommy's here, sweetheart.
Mommy's here.
You always pay your
insurance on time.
Tap one little bumper
and up go your rates.
What good is having insurance if
you get punished for using it?
News flash: nobody's perfect.
For drivers with
Accident Forgiveness,
Liberty Mutual won't
raise your rates
due to your first accident.
Switch and you could save $782
on Home and Auto insurance.
Call for a free quote today.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
When you're confident
in your gut,
you feel confident to
take on anything.
With
Benefiber,
you'll feel the power of
gut health confidence
every day.
Benefiber is a
100% natural
prebiotic fiber.
Good morning
Mrs. Jonhson.
Benefiber.
Trust Your Gut.
(Thunderclap)
If your day doesn't
unfold as predicted.
Unfold this.
New Neutrogena®
Makeup Remover single.
And remove 99% of makeup.
100% rain or shine.
Neutrogena®.
Family: Happy birthday!
Let's blow out the
candles together!
Okay, let's huff
and puff.
Like you do
sometimes, Grandpa?
Well, when
you have COPD,
it can be hard to breathe.
So my doctor said...
SYMBICORT can help
you breathe better
starting within
5 minutes.
It doesn't replace
a rescue inhaler
for sudden symptoms.
SYMBICORT helps provide
significant improvement
of your lung function.
SYMBICORT is for COPD,
including chronic bronchitis
and emphysema.
It should not be taken
more than twice a day.
It may increase your risk
of lung infections,
osteoporosis, and
some eye problems.
Tell your doctor if
you have a heart condition
or high blood pressure
before taking it.
Grandpa :
SYMBICORT could mean a day
with better breathing.
Family:
Watch out, piggies!
(Blowing)
Ask your doctor
if SYMBICORT is right for you.
If you can't afford
your medication, AstraZeneca
may be able to help.
When was the last time
you felt...
Free.
It's time to uncover
that feeling again.
With the compassion and
strength of a name...
Most accepted by top doctors
and specialists.
And the power of a card...
that opens doors in
all fifty states.
Giving you the freedom to love
to dream to dance
Like no one is watching.
CareFirst
Blue Cross Blue Shield.
Live fearless.