TROOPS STILL SERVING AT THIS
MOMENT SO WE CAN LIVE FREE.
GOD BLESS TEXAS.
♪
♪ ♪
>> GOOD EVENING AND WELCOME TO
THE NEXT REVOLUTION.
I'M STEVE HILTON.
WORKER, PROFAMILY, PRO-
COMMUNITY AND ALWAYS BUT
ESPECIALLY ON THIS JULY 4
HOLIDAY WEEKEND, PRO-
AMERICA.
THAT'S WHERE WE START
TONIGHT.
THERE WAS A TIME WHEN BEING
PRO- AMERICAN.
[INAUDIBLE]
PRESIDENT REAGAN PUT IT
BEAUTIFULLY WHEN HE TALKED OF
A SHINING CITY ON THE HILL.
I ALSO LOVED BILL CLINTON'S
GREAT LINE, THERE'S NOTHING
WRONG WITH AMERICA THAT CAN'T
BE FIXED BY WHAT'S RIGHT WITH
AMERICA.
THIS WEEK WE STILL HAVE A
REPUBLICAN PRESIDENT WHO LIKE
RONALD REAGAN IS PROUD OF
AMERICA AND HAPPY TO SAY IT,
TO CELEBRATE IT BUT TODAY'S
DEMOCRATS, NO THEY'RE
EMBARRASSED BY AMERICA.
FAR FROM CELEBRATING, THEY
WANT TO TEAR DOWN AND TURN IT
INTO SOMETHING ELSE.
THAT'S THE BACKGROUND TO THE
SALUTE TO AMERICA ON
INDEPENDENCE DAY.
THE DEMOCRATS COULDN'T WAIT TO
ATTACK IT.
>> I DON'T THINK HE GETS IT.
>> HE DOESN'T GET IT.
OKAY LOOK, HERE'S SOME OF WHAT
THE PRESIDENT ACTUALLY SAID.
TOGETHER WE ARE PART OF ONE OF
THE GREATEST STORIES EVER
TOLD, THE STORY OF AMERICA.
IT IS THE SPIRIT DURING AND
DEFIANCE, EXCELLENCE AND
ADVENTURE, COURAGE AND
CONFIDENCE, LOYALTY AND LOVE
THAT BUILT THIS COUNTRY INTO
THE MOST EXCEPTIONAL NATION IN
THE HISTORY OF THE WORLD AND
OUR NATION IS STRONGER TODAY
THAN IT EVER WAS BEFORE.
>> I THINK YOU WILL FIND JOE
CHINA THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
GETS WHAT MAKES AMERICA GREAT
BETTER THAN A SWAMP CREATURE
WHO TOOK BILLIONS OF DOLLARS
IN BRIBES IN THE FORM OF
PAYMENT TO HIS FAMILY
BUSINESSES FROM AMERICA'S
NUMBER ONE ENEMY.
YOU ARE THE LAST PERSON TO
LECTURE ANYONE ON PATRIOTISM.
# JOE CHINA.
BUT IT WASN'T JUST HIM.
IT WAS ALL OF THEM.
HOW DARE YOU CELEBRATE AMERICA
TRIED THE LEFT, IT'S NOT WHO
WE ARE.
>> IT'S JUST NOT WHO WE ARE AS
AMERICANS BUT WE DON'T PUMP
OUR CHEST WITH TANKS IN THE
STREET, FLY JETS OVER TO PROVE
OUR STRENGTH.
>> I THINK REDUCING OUR NATION
TO TANKS AND SHOWS OF MUSCLE
JUST MAKES US LOOK LIKE THE
KIND OF LOUDMOUTH GUY AT THE
BAR.
>> ADVOCATES A WASTE OF
MONEY.
HE'S HAVING A PARADE OUT THERE
FOR HIMSELF, PUTTING TANKS OUT
THERE FOR HIMSELF AND IF HE
WAS SERVING OUR NATION HE'D BE
INVESTING IN HIGHER PAY,
BETTER HOUSING A BETTER
HEALTHCARE.
>> THAT IS EXACTLY WHAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS DONE
UNLIKE PRESIDENT OBAMA.
THE BIG POINT IS CAPTURED IN
THAT SMUG PLATITUDE PLOTTED
OUT BY THE RIDICULOUS ERIC'S
WALL WELL.
IT'S NOT WHO WE ARE.
FOR ONCE, THAT PHRASE TOLD US
SOMETHING USEFUL ABOUT THE
DEMOCRATS, JUST NOT THE WAY
THEY INTENDED.
THE PROUD AMERICANS WHO STOOD
IN THE POURING RAIN AND FROM
THE LINCOLN MEMORIAL TO
CELEBRATE THEIR COUNTRY,
THAT'S NOT WHO THE DEMOCRATS
ARE.
THE MILLIONS MORE WHO WATCHED
AT HOME AND THOUGHT FINALLY WE
HAVE A PRESIDENT WHO LOVES
AMERICA AS MUCH AS WE DO IN
ISN'T EMBARRASSED TO SAY SO,
NO, THAT IS NOT WHO THE
DEMOCRATS ARE.
THE DEMOCRATS WON'T CELEBRATE
AMERICA BECAUSE THEIR NEW
IDEOLOGY DEMANDS THAT THEY
DENIGRATE AMERICA, NOT LEAST
WITH THEIR RECKLESS DIVISIVE
LIES ABOUT CONCENTRATION CAMPS
AT THE BORDER, COLLUSION WITH
RUSSIA.
TODAY'S DEMOCRATS ARE ENGAGED
IN A CONCERTED EFFORT TO SMEAR
THIS COUNTRY AT HOME AND IN
THE EYES OF THE WORLD.
WHEN THEY TELL YOU THEY DON'T
WANT TO CELEBRATE AMERICA
BECAUSE IT'S NOT WHO WE ARE,
BELIEVE THEM.
PRESIDENT TRUMP BY CONTRAST
LAID OUT EXACTLY WHY WE SHOULD
CELEBRATE.
THE AMERICAN SPIRIT, HE TALKED
ABOUT ON INDEPENDENCE DAY HAD
DRIVEN SOME THE MOST PROFOUND
ACHIEVEMENTS IN HISTORY FOR
MEDICAL BREAKTHROUGHS TO
TECHNOLOGICAL MARVELS.
IT HAS CONTINUALLY CONFOUNDED
WHAT THE WORLD THANKS IS
POSSIBLE, BUT WHY, HOW, IT'S
NOT JUST CHANCE OR LUCK, THERE
ARE OTHER COUNTRIES JUST AS
TALENTED AND INGENIOUS.
HERE'S MIGHT SUSPECT AS A
RECENT ARRIVAL.
IT'S AMERICA'S GREATEST
ACHIEVEMENT THAT HAS MADE ALL
THE OTHERS POSSIBLE, AND THAT
IS THE GENIUS FRAMEWORK
CONSTRUCTED BY THE FOUNDERS
AND EXPRESSED IN THE FOUNDING
DOCUMENTS ALL IN-SERVICE WITH
THAT SIMPLE IDEA, IS LIBERTY
UNDER THE LAW.
IF THE GUARANTEE OF INDIVIDUAL
LIBERTY THAT GAVE THE PIONEERS
THE CONFIDENCE TO SET OUT INTO
THE UNKNOWN AND THE BELIEF
THEY COULD BUILD SOMETHING
BETTER.
THEY COULD GOVERN THEMSELVES.
POWER TO THE PEOPLE.
DECENTRALIZED AND LIMITED
GOVERNMENT.
THE RULE OF LAW.
THESE ARE THE FOUNDATION OF
THE AMERICAN SPIRIT THEY HAVE
PAVED THE WAY BUT ALSO OUR
ECONOMIC SYSTEM WHICH
INVESTMENT INNOVATION AND
SUCCESS IS REWARDED, NOT
PUNISHED.
LOOK AT THE DIFFERENCE IT
MAKES.
ANOTHER INCREDIBLE JOBS REPORT
LAST WEEK.
INCOMES RISING FASTEST, RECORD
LOW UNEMPLOYMENT AND A FAIR
ECONOMY.
FOR EXAMPLE THE GAP BETWEEN
WHITE AND AFRICAN-AMERICAN
UNEMPLOYMENT HAVE SHRUNK BY
NEARLY A HALF SINCE 2016.
THE OBAMA YEARS GAVE US LOW
GROWTH AND HIGHER INEQUALITY.
WITH OBAMA WE HAD THE EXACT
OPPOSITE LOWER IN A
INEQUALITY.
THEY BEEN CAPTURED BY AN
EXTREMIST IDEOLOGY THAT IS
FUNDAMENTALLY ANTI-AMERICAN.
YOU SOUGHT AT THE DEBATE.
IT CONNECTS EVERYTHING.
AND YES THEIR HYSTERICAL
REACTION TO PRESIDENT TRUMP
SALUTE TO AMERICA.
THEY'RE NOT CELEBRATING
AMERICA BUT DENIGRATING
AMERICA.
NOT POWER TO THE PEOPLE BUT
POWER FOR THEMSELVES ON THE
BUREAUCRATIC ELITE.
NOT DECENTRALIZED GOVERNMENT
BUT EVERYTHING CONTROLLED FROM
WASHINGTON D.C.
THE DEMOCRATS DON'T WANT
LIMITED GOVERNMENT.
THEY WANT ENDLESS, RELENTLESS
INTERVENTION BY AN
ALL-KNOWING, ALL SEEING
ALL-POWERFUL STATE.
HERE'S PERHAPS THE BIGGEST
CHANGE FROM THE DEMOCRATS OF
THE PAST.
TODAY'S DEMOCRATS DON'T EVEN
WANT THE MOST VITAL ELEMENTS
OF THE AMERICAN INHERITANCE,
THE RULE OF LAW.
AT THAT FIRST PRESIDENTIAL
DEBAOST ALL OF THE 2020
CANDIDATES BACK TO THE
DECRIMINALIZATION OF ILLEGAL
IMMIGRATION.
ON WEDNESDAY, CORY BOOKER
ASKED ESCORTED MIGRANTS TOWARD
THE BORDER HIMSELF, EVEN
PRESIDENT OBAMA'S FORMER
HOMELAND SECURITY SECRETARY
NOW SAYS THE DEMOCRATS ARE
EFFECTIVELY FOR OPEN BORDERS.
THE DEMOCRATS POINT TO THE
STATUE OF LIBERTY AND SAY
IMMIGRATION CONTROL IS
UN-AMERICAN.
THEY FORGET ONE VITAL THING,
IT'S NOT JUST LIBERTY, IT'S
LIBERTY UNDER THE LAW AND IT
IS THERE LATENT ASSAULT ON THE
RULE OF LAW THAT IS TRULY
UN-AMERICAN.
LET ME END ON A PERSONAL NOTE
ABOUT AMERICA.
I'M AN IMMIGRANT JUST AS MY
PARENTS WERE IN ENGLAND AFTER
THEY FLED COMMUNISM IN
HUNGARY.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN PRO-
IMMIGRATION.
HOW CAN I BE ANYTHING ELSE BUT
IT'S ESPECIALLY THOSE OF US
WHO BELIEVED IN THE VIRTUES
AND BENEFITS OF IMMIGRATION
WHO SHOULD WANT TO SEE IT
PROPERLY CONTROLLED.
PUBLIC CONSENT DEPENDS ON
GOVERNMENT CONTROL OF
IMMIGRATION.
THAT'S WHY IMMIGRATION HAS TO
BE DONE THE RIGHT WAY
ACCORDING TO THE RULES.
THAT CERTAINLY HOW I'VE DONE
IT SINCE I MOVED HERE WITH MY
FAMILY AND I THOUGHT THIS JULY
THE FOURTH WEEKEND WAS A GOOD
MOMENT LET YOU KNOW THAT I'M
NOW BEGUN THE PROCESS OF
APPLYING FOR U.S.
CITIZENSHIP.
I CAN'T TELL YOU HOW MUCH I
APPRECIATE THE OPPORTUNITY
THIS COUNTRY HAS GIVEN ME AND
THE WELCOME YOU ALL SHOWN ME
AND NOW I'M LOOKING FORWARD
ONE DAY TO CELEBRATING
INDEPENDENCE DAY AS AN
AMERICAN, IF YOU'LL HAVE ME
THAT IS.
LET ME KNOW.
AT STEVE HILTON X AND NEXT REV
FMC.
SENIOR ADVISOR KATRINA PEARSON
IS HERE AND FOX NEWS
CONTRIBUTOR AND AUTHOR OF THE
NEW BOOK POWER GRAB JASON
SHAPE US.
LOTS OF TOPICS IN THERE,
IMMIGRATION, THE DEMOCRATS
GOING NUTS, WHERE DO YOU WANT
TO START.
>> I THINK I'LL START BY
SAYING OF COURSE WE WELCOME
YOU.
I APPLAUD YOU.
WE NEED MORE AMERICANS THAT
FIGHT FOR THIS COUNTRY.
I THINK YOU HAVE IT EXACTLY
RIGHT.
THEY DIDN'T EVEN HAVE A FLAG
DURING THE DEBATE ON STAGE.
THEIR ANTI- AMERICAN ARE
DEPLORABLE AND THE OTHERS ARE
JUST AS EXPENDABLE BECAUSE
THEIR MAIN FOCUS AND PRIORITY
ARE ON THE FAMILY AND CHILDREN
OF ILLEGAL ALIENS IN FOREIGN
NATIONALS ON THE WAY.
I THINK YOUR ABSOLUTE RIGHT,
MOST AMERICANS SEE THAT.
THERE WERE DEMOCRATS AT THAT
EVENT IN WASHINGTON D.C. WHO
WATCHED THIS PRESIDENT AND WHO
WERE EXCITED TO BE THERE
BECAUSE THERE ARE SOME
DEMOCRATS LEFT IN THIS COUNTRY
WHO LOVE IT AND WHO SUPPORTED
BECAUSE IT IS THE UNITED
STATES OF AMERICA, IT'S THE
BEST COUNTRY IN THE WORLD AND
IT'S EXACTLY WHY EVERYONE IS
TRYING TO COME IN.
>> WHEN YOU SHOW CLIPS THAT
YOU SHOWED WHAT THESE
DEMOCRATS WERE SAYING, FRANKLY
IN MY OPINION, ANY
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE THAT IS
CRITICIZING SALUTING AMERICA
ON INDEPENDENCE DAY SHOULD BE
DISQUALIFIED.
>> WELL SAID.
JASON, THE DEMOCRATS WOULD SAY
IT'S OUTRAGEOUS, WERE NOT
ANTI-AMERICAN WE JUST HAVE A
DIFFERENT SET OF IDEAS.
WE LOOK AT THE WAY THEY ARE
RUNNING AROUND, DELIBERATELY
DISTORTING AND MAKING STUFF UP
TO MAKE AMERICA LOOK BAD, WHEN
YOU LOOK AT THE SHIFT TO THE
LEFT, IT CONTRADICTS SOMETHING
VERY IMPORTANT ABOUT THE
SPIRIT AND SOUL OF THIS
COUNTRY.
>> THE PRESIDENT BELIEVES IN
AMERICAN EXCEPTIONALISM.
I BELIEVE IN THAT AND YET
DEMOCRATS ARE EMBARRASSED
ABOUT THE COUNTRY, THERE
EMBARRASSED OF THE FLAG, THERE
EMBARRASSED THIS PRESIDENT HAS
WRAPPED HIMSELF IN THE FLAG.
I THINK THAT'S WHY THE
OVERWHELMING MAJORITY OF
AMERICANS LOVE THIS PRESIDENT
BECAUSE IT'S THE ONE THING
THAT SUPPOSED TO DRAW
TOGETHER, A FLAG OF THE UNITED
STATES OF AMERICA.
IT SHOULDN'T BE A PARTISAN
ISSUE BUT THERE CHOOSING TO
MAKE IT A PARTISAN ISSUE.
I THINK THEY DO SO WITH THEIR
OWN POLITICAL PERIL.
I LIKE THE SUM OF WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING.
THE RULE OF LAW DOES GIVE US
THE LIBERTY AND WE DO BELIEVE
IN LIMITED GOVERNMENT AND
THERE IS A FUNDAMENTAL
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN WHAT THE
DEMOCRATS BELIEVE IN WHICH IS
MORE EAGER GOVERNMENT AND WHAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS FIGHTING
FOR TO INCREASE OUR LIBERTY BY
GIVING MORE CHANCES, MORE
OPPORTUNITY.
>> YOU COULD SAY THAT DEBATE
WHICH IS A FRAMEWORK WHICH IS
DIFFERENT THAN ANYWHERE IN THE
WORLD.
ANYWHERE ELSE IN THE WORLD
THAT WOULD BE A REALLY WEIRD
THING TO SAY.
[INAUDIBLE]
IT'S JUST FUNDAMENTALLY
ANTI-AMERICAN.
>> IT IS.
THE PEOPLE WON'T ALLOW IT.
IT'S NOT ABOUT BIG
GOVERNMENT.
IT'S ABOUT POWER AND THEY
WON'T SAY THAT.
IN ORDER TO HAVE ALL THE POWER
THEY HAVE TO HAVE THE
GOVERNMENT AS BIG AS POSSIBLE
SO THEY CAN CONTROL EVERYONE.
THEY WILL EXEMPT THEMSELVES
JUST LIKE THEY ALWAYS HAVE IN
THE PAST BUT IT IS ABOUT
POWER.
THIS ERRATIC DERANGEMENT THAT
WE SEE AMONG THE DEMOCRATS AND
IN THE MEDIA, ALTHOUGH I
REPEAT MYSELF WAS REALLY
COMING FROM THIS TRAUMA OF
THIS ELECTION AND THEY GRASP
ONTO THIS AND YOU SEE THIS
CONSTANTLY ATTACKING INNOCENT
PEOPLE AS DEPLORABLE AND
ATTACKING IN ADAMANT OBJECTS
BECAUSE NOW THEY'RE UNHINGED.
YOU SAW THIS DEBATE.
WE HAVE THIS PLETHORA OF
CANDIDATES WHO WERE SAYING
OUTRAGEOUS THINGS WITH READ
DICK ILLICITLY STUPID POLICY
AND WHAT WE HAVE TODAY,
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S APPROVAL IS
NOW THE HIGHEST IT'S EVER BEEN
AND THAT GIVES YOU A CLUE ON
WHERE AMERICANS STAND ON THESE
ISSUES TODAY.
>> WERE GOING TO LOOK, I'M
SORRY WERE OUT OF TIME FORWARD
AND A LOOK AT THE POLICY SHIFT
A LITTLE BIT LATER IN THE
SHOW.
IT WAS SO DEEPLY REVEALING OF
WHERE THEY ARE.
EVEN THOUGH THEY SAY WE MUST
UNDERSTAND WE CAN'T MAKE THAT
MISTAKE AGAIN YOU KNOW THE WAY
THEY TALK THEY REALLY LOOK
DOWN THEIR NOSE FROM A
CULTURAL PERSPECTIVE EVEN THE
FOOD THEY EAT.
THAT'S WHY THEY CAN'T STAND
TRUMP BECAUSE HE CONNECTS W
THAT AND RS THAT
GIVES VOICE TO THAT.BEFORE WE TS
SOCCER TEAM WNG<I THE WORLD
CUP EARLIER TODAY.
WHAT A GREAT WAY TO CLOSE OUT
THE WEEKEND.
MANY CONGRATULATIONS FOR
FANTASTIC AND INSPIRING
ACHIEVEMENT.
AFTER THE BREAK, THE PEOPLE
VERSUS CHIEF JUSTICE JOHN
ROBERTS.
IT'S GOING TO BE A
Fact is, every insurance company
hopes you drive safely.■=■=÷
IT'S GOING TO BE A
CO■=
But Allsta???■■■ly...
with Drivewise.
It lets you know when you go too
fast...
...and bññd.
With feedback to help you drive
safer.
Giving you the power to actually
lower your cost.
Unfortunateln't do
anything about that.
Now that you know the truth...
are you in Good Hands?
It's time for our Lowest
Prices of the Season on
the Sleep Number 360 smart bed.
It senses your movement
and automatically adjusts
to keep you both comfortable.
The queen Sleep Number 360
c4 smart bed, now $1299.
Plus, free premium delivery
when you add a base.
Ends Sunday.
THIS WEEK THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION ANNOUNCED IT
INTENDS TO PUT A CONSENSUS
QUESTION ON THE ELECTION.
WHATEVER THE ARGUMENT ABOUT
THE CENSUS QUESTION THERE WAS
AN ASPECT OF THE RULING AND
ESPECIALLY THE MAJORITY
ACHIEVE OPINION FROM THE CHIEF
JUSTICE THAT WILL HAVE
LONG-LASTING AND DISASTROUS
CONSEQUENCES FOR THE COUNTRY
WAY BEYOND THE CENSUS.■■■1T IT'S
CHIEF JUSTICE JOHN ROBERTS.
THE ARGUMENT USED BY THE CHIEF
JUSTICE TO BLOCK THE
CITIZENSHIP QUESTION WAS THAT
THE RATIONALE FOR THE CHANGE
GIVEN BY WILBUR ROSS WAS THAT
HE WAS RESPONDING TO A REQUEST
FROM THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
AND WASN'T WRITTEN THE REAL
REASON.
HE WAS PLANNING TO PUT THIS
CITIZEN QUESTION ON THE CENSUS
BEFORE IT CAME IN.
SO WHAT.
UNDER THE CONSTITUTION IT'S AN
EXECUTIVE BRANCH DECISION THAT
HAS LONG BEEN A LEGAL
PRECEDENT THAT THE COURT CAN'T
OBJECT TO ACTION JUST BECAUSE
THERE ARE OTHER REASONS FOR
THE DECISION THAN THOSE
STATED.
JOHN ROBERTS HAS JUST
OVERTURNED THAT PRESIDENT AND
THIS WILL HAVE MASSIVE AND
DEEPLY DAMAGING IMPLICATIONS
FOR THE WAY THINGS WORK OR
RATHER DON'T WORK IN AMERICA.
IN THE DEFENSE OF THE CASE
WRITTEN BY JUSTICE CLARENCE
THOMAS AND JOINED BY GORSUCH
AND KAVANAUGH, HE WROTE THE
COURT HAS OPENED A PANDORA'S
BOX AND CHALLENGES IN
ADMINISTRATIVE LAW.
WHAT DOES ALL THIS MEAN IN
PLAIN ENGLISH AND WHAT DOES IT
MEAN FOR YOU.
[INAUDIBLE]
IS HAD NO ON T ACA, ASYLUM,
EVEN BLOCKING IMMIGRATION.
THE COURT SAID NO TO POLICIES
YOU VOTED FOR.
ALL IN ALL, UNELECTED JUDGES
HAVE RULED AGAINST THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION MORE THAN 70
TIMES, WAY MORE THAN THE RATES.
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
VOTE FOR THIS TYPE OF
PRESIDENT.
NOW THIS RULING WILL MAKE IT
TEN TIMES WORSE.
ANY PART OF THAT GROUP WILL BE
ABLE TO TAKE LEGAL ACTION
AGAINST THE ADMINISTRATION AND
HELPING AS JUSTICE THOMAS SAID
THROUGH DEPOSITION, DELAY AND
DISTRACTION.
GREAT.
THAT'S JUST WHAT WE NEED AND
EVEN MORE POLITICIZED
JUDICIARY.
EVEN MORE ROADBLOCKS IN THE
WAY OF ACTUALLY GETTING THINGS
DONE THAT HELP YOUR LIFE.
THE WORST OF IT ALL IS JOHN
ROBERTS OWN MOTIVE.
FOR THE HIM IT IS ALL ABOUT
THE IMAGE OF THE COURT.
NOW THAT HE'S THE SWING VOTE.
HE DOESN'T WANT TO MAKE HIS
COURT LOOK PARTISAN.
THE OTHER WEEK HE BALANCED HIS
RULING ON GERRYMANDERING WITH
THIS DAMAGING ON THE REVIEW OF
EXECUTIVE DECISIONS.
HE SUPPOSED TO BE THE CHIEF
JUSTICE, NOT THE CHEAP PR.