>> TO BE STANDING HERE,
REPRESENTING ONE OF THE GREATEST
ARTISTS OF OUR TIME, JAMES
BALDWIN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IT'S A LITTLE SURREAL.
JAMES BALDWIN BIRTHED THIS BABY.
AND BARRY, YOU NURTURED HER,
SURROUNDED HER WITH SO MUCH LOVE
AND SUPPORT.
SO, IT'S APPROPRIATE FOR ME TO
BE STANDING HERE, BECAUSE I'M AN
EXAMPLE OF WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE
WHEN SUPPORT AND LOVE IS POURED
INTO SOMEONE.
MOM, I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU FOR TEACHING ME THAT
GOD IS ALWAYS LEANING, ALWAYS
HAS BEEN LEANING IN MY
DIRECTION.
GOMOSIS, ASK ME ABOUT THAT
LATER.
SO MANY PEOPLE TO THANK, CHELSEA
BARNARD, MEGAN ELLENSON, PLAN B,
THIS AMAZING CAST.
MY SISTERS IN ART.
MARINA, AMY.
EMMA, RACHEL, IT'S AN HONOR TO
HAVE MY NAME TO BE SAID WITH
YOURS.
THIS WHOLE STEP OF THE WAY HAS
BEEN PRETTY AMAZING.
THE RIVERS FAMILY, KIKI,
COLEMAN, KIANA, STEFON.
GOD IS GOOD, ALL THE TIME.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> PLEASE WELCOME JASON MOMOA
AND ACADEMY AWARD-WINNING
ACTRESS, HELEN MIRREN.
>> YOU KNOW, HONESTLY, I SWEAR
TO GOD, JASON AND I CAN'T
COORDINATE OUR OUTFITS TONIGHT.
THIS IS PURELY ACCIDENTAL.
BUT IT JUST GOES TO SHOW, THESE
DAYS, A HAWAIIAN GOD, AND A VERY
MATURE ENGLISH WOMAN CAN BOTH
WEAR PINK.
>> FINALLY.
THE TIMES ARE CHANGING.
>> YES.
>> BOOM.
DOCUMENTARY FILMMAKERS BRING US
STORIES OF REAL PEOPLE, DOING
REAL THINGS, AND IN DOING SO,
THEY CAN OFTEN OPEN OUR EYES TO
THE MOST IMPORTANT ISSUES OF
YESTERDAY, TODAY, AND TOMORROW.
>> THEY ARE INSIGHTFUL AND
ILLUMINATING, SOMETIMES
ASTONISHING, AND ALWAYS
AUTHENTIC.
AND REVELATORY.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR BEST
DOCUMENTARY FEATURE.
"FREE SOLO."
>> THE CHANCE OF ME FALLING OFF
IS QUITE LOW, EVEN THOUGH THE
CONSEQUENCES WITH EXTREMELY
HIGH.
>> "HALE COUNTY THIS MORNING,
THIS EVENING."
>> I WANT MY SON TO KNOW, I JUST
WANT TO MAKE LIFE BETTER FOR
HIM.
>> "MINDING THE GAP."
>> I'M MAKING THIS FILM BECAUSE
I WAS PHYSICALLY DISCIPLINED BY
MY STEPFATHER, IT DIDN'T MAKE
SENSE TO ME.
AND I SAW MYSELF IN YOUR OWN
STORY.
>> "OF FATHERS AND SONS."
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
>> "RBG."
>> I ASKED NO FAVOR FOR MY SEX.
ALL I ASK OF OUR BRETHREN IS
THAT THEY TAKE THEIR FEET OFF
OUR NECKS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO "FREE
SOLO."
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR
NOMINATION FOR THE TEAM.
♪
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> OH -- WOW.
BREATHE.
>> WOW.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, "NATIONAL GEOGRAPHIC"
FOR BELIEVING IN US, AND HIRING
WOMEN AND PEOPLE OF COLOR,
BECAUSE WE ONLY HELP MAKE THE
FILMS BETTER.
THANK YOU TO ALL THE AMAZING
PEOPLE WHO WORKED ON THIS FILM.
EVAN, SHANNON.
>> OUR HIGH ANGLE TEAM.
>> I MEAN, IT WAS A WORK OF AN
ARMY, AND WE APPRECIATE YOU IN
EVERY WAY.
THANK YOU TO OUR FAMILIES.
ESPECIALLY OUR TWO KIDS.
MARINA, I KNOW YOU'RE HERE.
>> JAMES.
>> AND THEN THANK YOU TO SONNY
McCANDLESS.
YOU CLIMBED YOUR OWN MOUNTAIN
THAT DAY.
THANK YOU.
THIS FILM WOULD BE SO BORING
WITHOUT YOU.
I'M JUST SAYING, OKAY?
ANYWAY, THANK YOU, ALEX, FOR
GIVING US COURAGE AND TEACHING
US HOW TO BELIEVE IN THE
IMPOSSIBLE, AND INSPIRING US.
THIS FILM IS FOR EVERYONE WHO
BELIEVES IN THE IMPOSSIBLE.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> COMING UP, A LOOK AT "VICE."
AND THE AWARDS FOR MAKEUP AND
HAIRSTYLING AND COSTUME DESIGN.
AND LATER, MELISSA McCARTHY,
TYLER PERRY, EMILIA CLARKE AND A
PERFORMANCE BY JENNIFER HUDSON.
I go to a lot
of different music festivals,
a lot of different
concerts,
and when I'm
in these large crowds,
even when I'm with tens
of thousands of people,
and I just love being
the friend with service.
It's really cool
to be able to take a photo,
take a video,
be immediately able to post it
on my social media.
Because I am tall,
I get that good
kind of view of the stage.
(camera clicks)
Amazing.
(VO)
There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best network
now always includes
Apple Music on us.
Starting at only $40.
Only on Verizon.
Open the pod bay doors Hal.
Hello Hal, do you read me?
Hey Google,
open the pod bay doors.
♪♪
Show me photos from last night.
(Google Assistant)
Showing your photos.
Oh no...
no no no no no no no.
You should just go
to city college.
You know with your work ethic...
just go to city college
and then to jail...
and then back to city college...
and learn to pull yourself up...
(Google Assistant)
Your Lyft has arrived.
...everybody to do...
ah! ahhhh!
Hello?
Hello, are you ready?
Yes.
What door am I at?
Patio door, police
are on their way!
See ya!
♪♪
Show me the money!
(Google Assistant)
Here you go.
Ahh hah hah!
Show!
Me!
The!
Money!
Hey Google,
what's on my calender today?
(Google Assistant)
At 5:30 PM you have:
"Appear in Google Commercial"
Hah, that's never going to
happen. Mm mm.
♪♪
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>>> FROM RAGE AGAINST THE
MACHINE, HERE IS TOM MORELLO.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> MOVIES, LIKE MUSIC, CAN DO
MORE THAN ENTERTAIN.
A GREAT MOVIE CAN BECOME A PART
OF THE CONVERSATION OF HISTORY.
AND, LIKE OUR NEXT MOVIE, AND
THE KIND OF SONGS I LIKE TO
MAKE, IT CAN DO IT WITH
FEEDBACK, NOISE, AND, YES,
ANGER.
ADAM McKAY'S "VICE" IS SUCH A
FILM.
SHREDDING THE TRADITIONAL
BIOPIC STRUCTURE WITH PASSION
AND HUMOR, "VICE" SEEKS TO PUT A
SPOTLIGHT ON A MAN WHO AVOIDED
IT HIS WHOLE CAREER --
DICK CHENEY.
BRILLIANTLY ACTED, THE FILM IS A
LESSON ABOUT THE PAST THAT
SERVES AS A WARNING ABOUT THE
PRESENT AND THE FUTURE.
WAR, GREED, TRUTH, LIES,
FATHERHOOD, LOVE, TORTURE, AND
BETRAYAL ALL SWIRL AROUND IN
"VICE" WITH A HARD BACKBEAT AND
A KILLER BASSLINE.
SOME WILL DIG IT.
SOME WILL COVER THEIR EARS.
BUT EVERYONE WILL DO THE ONE
THING THE MOVIE BEGS US TO DO,
REACT.
THIS IS "VICE."
>> SO, WHAT'S THE PLAN?
>> THE PLAN IS TO TAKE OVER THE
DAMN PLACE.
>> GEORGE, YOU MAKE DECISIONS
BASED ON INSTINCT.
>> NO ONE HAS SHOWN THE WORLD
THE TRUE POWER OF THE AMERICAN
PRESIDENCY.
>> THAT'S NOT SOMETHING THE VICE
PRESIDENT REALLY DOES.
>> IT IS NOW.
>> YOU NEED TO REMEMBER THAT IF
YOU HAVE POWER, PEOPLE WILL
ALWAYS TRY TO TAKE IT FROM YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> PLEASE WELCOME ELSIE FISHER
AND STEPHAN JAMES.
>> IT DOESN'T TAKE A MAGIC WAND
TO TRANSFORM AN ACTOR INTO A
CHARACTER WHOSE LOOK IS
MEMORABLE AND MEANINGFUL TO THE
STORY.
>> ALL IT TAKES ARE THIS YEAR'S
NOMINEES FOR ACHIEVEMENT IN
MAKEUP AND HAIRSTYLING.
>> "BORDER."
"MARY QUEEN OF SCOTS."
"VICE."
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO "VICE."
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR KIT AND PATRICIA,
THE FOURTH OSCAR AND TENTH
NOMINATION FOR GREG.
OSCARS IN THIS CATEGORY HAVE
BEEN AWARDED SINCE 1981.
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> THANK YOU, ADAM, OUR GREAT
DIRECTOR, CHRISTIAN BALE.
OH, YOU'RE HERE.
GO AHEAD.
>> CAN YOU READ THAT?
>> I ALREADY DID.
GO AHEAD.
>> PLAN B, GARY SANCHEZ.
>> THE VOTING ACADEMY MEMBERS,
AND OUR FELLOW NOMINEES FROM THE
UK AND SWEDEN, THANK YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> CHRISTIAN BALE, YOU'RE
FANTASTIC.
SO GREAT TO WORK WITH, AND
CREATE WITH, AND EVERYTHING.
THANK YOU.
>> AMY ADAMS, THANK YOU FOR
BRINGING US UP TO YOUR LEVEL OF
COMMITMENT.
>> SAM ROCKWELL, AND THE 150
OTHER S.A.G. MEMBERS, GREAT JOB.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> SUSAN MATHESON.
>> JEFF WAXMAN.
>> AND JENNIFER MADELOFF.
>> PAULA WILLIAMS, LESLIE
WOFFORD.
>> CHRIS GALLAHER.
>> KENNY MYERS.
GO AHEAD.
>> ERIC, BRIAN WADE.
♪
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> PLEASE WELCOME BRIAN TYREE
HENRY, AND A NOMINEE TONIGHT FOR
ACTRESS IN A LEADING ROLE,
MELISSA McCARTHY.
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> A RAKISH TILT TO A HAT.
THE DRAPE OF FABRIC, JUST SO.
NUANCE AND SOPHISTICATION ARE
JUST TWO QUALITIES OF THE MOST
EFFECTIVE COSTUME DESIGN.
>> THESE ARTISTS CREATE A
PASTICHE OF TEXTILES WITH
AUTHENTICITY, YET NEVER DISTRACT
FROM THE STORY.
COSTUME DESIGNERS CONSTRUCT THE
LOOKS THAT GROUND A CHARACTER TO
A PARTICULAR TIME AND PLACE IN
THE SUBTLEST OF WAYS.
>> SO TRUE.
SO TRUE.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
ACHIEVEMENT IN COSTUME DESIGN.
>> "THE BALLAD OF BUSTER
SCRUGGS."
"BLACK PANTHER."
"THE FAVOURITE."
"MARY POPPINS RETURNS."
"MARY QUEEN OF SCOTS."
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO -- GET
IT.
>> I GOT IT.
OKAY.
>> OKAY.
"BLACK PANTHER," RUTH CARTER!
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
THIRD NOMINATION FOR RUTH
CARTER.
SHE WAS PREVIOUSLY NOMINATED
FOR "MALCOLM X" AND "AMISTAD."
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> WOW.
WOW.
I GOT IT.
THIS HAS BEEN A LONG TIME
COMING.
SPIKE LEE, THANK YOU FOR MY
START.
I HOPE THIS MAKES YOU PROUD.
[ APPLAUSE ]
MARVEL MAY HAVE CREATED THE
FIRST BLACK SUPERHERO, BUT
THROUGH COSTUME DESIGN, WE
TURNED HIM INTO AN AFRICAN KING.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
IT'S BEEN MY LIFE'S HONOR TO
CREATE COSTUMES.
THANK YOU TO THE ACADEMY, THANK
YOU FOR HONORING AFRICAN
ROYALTY, AND THE EMPOWERED WAY
WOMEN CAN LOOK AND LEAD
ONSCREEN.
THANK YOU TO MY CREWS AROUND THE
WORLD WHO HELPED BRING WIAKANDA
TO LIFE, OUR GENIUS DIRECTOR,
RYAN COOGLER.
YOU ARE A GUIDING FORCE.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR TRUST AND
UNDERSTANDING MY ROLE IN TELLING
THE AFRICAN-AMERICAN STORY.
ADDING VIBRANIUM TO COSTUMES IS
VERY EXPENSIVE, SO THANK YOU.
MY CAREER IS BUILT WITH PASSION
TO TELL STORIES THAT ALLOW US TO
KNOW OURSELVES BETTER.
THIS IS FOR MY 97-YEAR-OLD
MOTHER, WATCHING IN
MASSACHUSETTS.
MOM, THANK YOU FOR TEACHING ME
ABOUT PEOPLE AND THEIR STORIES.
YOU ARE THE ORIGINAL SUPERHERO.
THANK YOU!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> COMING UP, JENNIFER LOPEZ,
CHRIS EVANS, AND TYLER PERRY,
THE AWARD FOR CINEMATOGRAPHY,
AND A LOOK AT BEST PICTURE
NOMINEE "A STAR IS BORN."
THEN LATER, ANGELA BASSETT AND
JAVIER BARDEM.
PLUS, A PERFORMANCE FROM
JENNIFER HUDSON.
ALL HERE ON THE OSCARS AT THE
DOLBY THEATER.
♪
We style the stars behind the
scenes in Walmart Fashion.
Perfect let's try it again.
♪(oh oh oh oh)
It's taking over.♪
♪There's no escape...♪
♪...You better get moving. Ready
or not♪
♪...It's about to go down here
it comes now♪
♪...Get ready (oh oh oh oh), Get
ready♪
♪...Moving. Ready or not♪
♪...Get ready (oh oh oh oh)♪
Free!
Free, free free.
♪
[explosion]
That's right. TurboTax Free
is free. Free, free free free.
Wow,
Right?
these Cheesy Bacon
Fries are tremendous.
I know.
Crispy bacon is the best thing
to ever happen to the fries.
WHAT!?!
This is the fries' show!
McDonald's World
Famous Fries...
Featuring Bacon.
Or is the crispy bacon
giving the fries
some street cred with
a whole new audience?
I'm gonna let
bacon think that.
What's that?
Couldn't hear you over
the bacon-ovation.
BACON, BACON,
BACON, BACON, BACON!
McDonald's Classics with
Bacon, only for a limited time.
Is it the best thing to
happen to our Classics?
Or to bacon?
Try for yourself
and decide.
DEAREST BRITAIN.
WE LOVE YOU.
MAYBE IT'S YOUR BIG HEARTS.
YOUR SENSE OF STYLE.
WELCOME TO BA100.
(BA100,
YOU'RE CLEAR FOR TAKE-OFF).
HOW YOU FOLLOW YOUR OWN PATH.
YOU'VE LED REVOLUTIONS...
OF ALL KINDS.
YET YOU WON'T SHOUT ABOUT IT.
IT'S JUST NOT IN YOUR NATURE.
INSTEAD, YOU'LL
QUIETLY MAKE HISTORY.
CAKE.
BEDS.
POETRY.
TROUBLE.
LOVE! HOPE!
AND RATHER A LOT OF TEA.
THE BEST OF BRITAIN,
FROM THE MOMENT
YOU STEP ON BOARD.
♪
>>> PLEASE WELCOME JENNIFER
LOPEZ AND CHRIS EVANS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> TONIGHT IS NOT ONLY ABOUT
CELEBRATING THE PEOPLE IN FRONT
OF THE CAMERA, IT'S ALSO ABOUT
RECOGNIZING THE ARTISTS WHO
DESIGN THE BEAUTIFUL WORLDS OUR
CHARACTERS INHABIT.
>> LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT THE
INCREDIBLE WORK THEY DO,
CREATING THE OVERALL APPEARANCE
OF THEIR FILMS.
HERE ARE TONIGHT'S NOMINEES FOR
ACHIEVEMENT IN PRODUCTION
DESIGN.
>> "BLACK PANTHER."
"THE FAVOURITE."
"FIRST MAN."
"MARY POPPINS RETURNS ♪
"ROMA."
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO "BLACK
PANTHER."
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR HANNAH, SHE'S THE
FIRST AFRICAN-AMERICAN TO BE NOM
T
NOMINATED IN THIS CATEGORY.
JAY HART WAS PREVIOUSLY
NOMINATED TWO TIMES.
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> THANK YOU.
THANKS.
THANK YOU.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
CAN YOU HOLD THIS FOR ME?
I DIDN'T EVEN -- OKAY, YOU'RE ON
MY DRESS.
ALL RIGHT, I GOT TO PUT THESE
ON.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE I PUT MY
SPEECH, I'M REALLY SHAKING HARD.
I PUT IT IN MY PHONE, I CAN'T
FIND IT.
I LOVE YOU GUYS.
I WANT TO THANK ALL OF THE
NOMINEES IN THIS CATEGORY FOR
THE EXTRAORDINARY WORLDS THEY
BUILT.
I WANT TO THANK THE ACADEMY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
RYAN COOGLER.
I STAND HERE STRONGER THAN I WAS
YESTERDAY.
I STAND HERE WITH AGENCY AND
SELF-WORTH BECAUSE OF RYAN
COOGLER, WHO NOT ONLY MADE ME A
BETTER DESIGNER, STORYTELLER, A
BETTER PERSON.
THIS MAN OFFERED ME A DIFFERENT
PERSPECTIVE OF LIFE, WHO OFFERED
ME A SAFE SPACE, WAS PATIENT,
AND GAVE ME AIR, HUMANITY, AND
BROTHERHOOD.
THANK YOU, RYAN, I LOVE YOU.
I'M STRONGER BECAUSE OF MARVEL,
WHO GAVE ME THE OPPORTUNITY TO
DO MY BEST.
WHO SUPPORTED THE VISION OF THIS
FILM, AND LIFTED US OF UP DAY.
VICTORIA, KEVIN, LOU, AND NATE
MOORE, THANK YOU.
AND I'M STRONGER BECAUSE OF THE
HART DEPARTMENT CREW, WHO
BROUGHT THEIR COURAGE AND
HUMILITY TO THE TABLE.
AND THANK YOU TO THE WONDERFUL
CAST, WHO BREATHED LIFE INTO
THIS WORLD.
BECAUSE OF RUTH CARTER AND
RACHEL MORRISON, AND EVERYTHING
THEY DID BEHIND THE CAMERA WITH
ME.
I'M STRONGER BECAUSE OF A WOMAN
WHO SUPPORTED ME EVERY DAY,
CAROL TREVINO, REST IN POWER.
I'M STRONGER BECAUSE OF MY
FAMILY, I GIVE THE STRENGTH TO
ALL OF THOSE WHO COME NEXT, TO
KEEP GOING, TO NEVER GIVE UP.
WHEN YOU THINK IT'S IMPOSSIBLE,
JUST REMEMBER TO SAY THIS PIECE
OF ADVICE, I DID MY BEST, AND MY
BEST IS GOOD ENOUGH.
THANK YOU.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> I JUST WANT TO THANK MY CREW!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> PLEASE WELCOME TYLER PERRY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> COMMUNITY.
WE OFTEN USE THAT WORD TO
DESCRIBE WHO WE ARE AND WHAT
CONNECTS ALL OF US INVOLVED IN
THE DIFFERENT ELEMENTS THAT
BRING A FILM FROM AN IDEA IN THE
WRITER'S MIND TO ITS PREMIERE ON
THE BIG SCREEN.
EACH PERSON, EACH CRAFT, EACH
DISCIPLINE IS ESSENTIAL TO THE
PROCESS.
DEEP DOWN, WE KNOW THAT.
WE ALWAYS HAVE.
IN THE END, THIS TRULY
COLLABORATIVE COMMUNITY COMES
TOGETHER ON A NIGHT LIKE THIS TO
CELEBRATE THIS PAST YEAR AND TO
LOOK FORWARD TO THE NEXT.
IT IS A TRUE HONOR FOR ME TO
PRESENT THIS NEXT AWARD.
LIVE ON CAMERA, NOT DURING THE
COMMERCIAL BREAK.
THANK YOU, ACADEMY.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
ACHIEVEMENT IN CINEMATOGRAPHY.
>> "COLD WAR," LUKASZ ZAL.
"THE FAVOURITE," ROBBIE RYAN.
"NEVER LOOK AWAY," CALEB
DESCHANEL.
"ROMA," ALFONSO CUARON.
"A STAR IS BORN," MATTHEW
LIBATIQUE.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO ALFONSO
CUARON, "ROMA."
>> ALFONSO CUARON IS THE FOURTH
PERSON TO RECEIVE NOMINATIONS IN
FOUR DIFFERENT CATEGORIES FOR
THE SAME FILM.
THIS IS HIS FOURTH OSCAR AND
TENTH NOMINATION.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
IT'S AN AMAZING HONOR.
THANK YOU, ACADEMY.
TO CREATE A SINGLE FRAME OF
FILM, AS YOU KNOW, REQUIRES THE
HARD WORK OF A LOT OF PEOPLE.
I WANT TO THANK THE AMAZING CAST
AND CREW.
THE PRODUCERS, NETFLIX.
AND IF THIS FILM WAS CREATED BY
MY OWN MEMORIES, THE FILM WAS
CRAFTED THROUGH THE MEMORIES OF
WHAT THIS GREAT MASTER OF
CINEMATOGRAPHY HAS GIVEN TO US.
IT'S WELL KNOWN THAT IN BILLY
WILDER'S OFFICE, THERE WAS A
SIGN THAT SAID, WHAT WOULD
LUBISCH HAVE DONE?
AND THIS IS FOR YOU, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH, MEXICO.
MY FAMILY.
A
I LOVE YOU GUYS.
THANK YOU.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, PLEASE
WELCOME EMILIA CLARKE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> THE FIRST NOMINEE FOR
ORIGINAL SONG WAS COMPOSED FOR
THE DOCUMENTARY FEATURE, "RBG".
SUNG AS A RALLYING CRY, AN
ANTHEM AND A PERSONAL PROMISE,
THE SONG EMBODIES THE SEEMINGLY
ENDLESS STRENGTH AND COMMITMENT
OF ITS SUBJECT, SUPREME COURT
JUSTICE RUTH BADER GINSBURG, A
WOMAN WHO HAS SPENT HER CAREER
AT THE FOREFRONT OF THE FIGHT
AGAINST GENDER DISCRIMINATION.
KHALEESI HAS NOTHING ON HER.
JUSTICE GINSBURG, IF YOU'D EVER
LIKE TO BORROW THE DRAGONS,
RING ME.
ALTHOUGH THE SONG'S SUBJECT IS
SOFT-SPOKEN, ITS SINGER IS A
VOCAL POWERHOUSE, PRESENTING ITS
MESSAGE WITH THE PASSION IT
DESERVES.
AND NOW, PERFORMING "I'LL FIGHT"
BY SONGWRITER DIANE WARREN,
PLEASE WELCOME ACADEMY AWARD
WINNER JENNIFER HUDSON.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
♪ WHEN YOU FEEL YOU'RE TAKING
ALL THAT YOU CAN TAKE
AND YOU'RE SURE YOU'RE NEVER
GONNA CATCH A BREAK ♪
♪ AND THE TEARS ARE RIVERS
RUNNING DOWN YOUR FACE
YEAH ♪
♪ WHEN YOUR FAITH IS LOW
AND YOU'VE GOT NO STRENGTH LEFT
WHEN YOU THINK YOU'VE GONE ♪
♪ AS FAR AS YOU CAN GET
AND YOU'RE TOO UNDONE
TO TAKE ANOTHER STEP ♪
♪ OH I WILL TAKE UP
THE STRUGGLE
OH, I KNOW IT'S A FIGHT ♪
♪ SO I'LL FIGHT
FIGHT THAT WAR FOR YOU
I'LL FIGHT
STAND AND DEFEND YOU ♪
♪ TAKE YOUR SIDE
THAT'S WHAT I'M HERE TO DO ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE TO BE STRONG
OH, I'LL KEEP ON
KEEP ON
♪ I'LL HAVE YOUR BACK WHEN
YOUR BACK'S TO THE WALL
AND I'LL CATCH THE TEARS WHEN
YOUR TEARS FALL ♪
♪ I'LL GIVE IT ALL
I WON'T GIVE UP ♪
♪ I'LL FIGHT
YEAH I'LL FIGHT ♪
♪ THAT'S WHAT I'M HERE TO DO ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE TO BE STRONG
OH, I'LL KEEP ON
KEEP ON
I'LL FIGHT ♪
♪ I'LL FIGHT ♪
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> KEEP WATCHING FOR MORE
HIGHLIGHTS OF THIS YEAR'S BEST
PICTURE NOMINEES.
AND A PERFORMANCE BY BETTE
MIDLER.
AND NEXT, JAMES McAVOY AND DANAI
GURIRA.
THEN LATER, ANGELA BASSETT,
AND KEEGAN-MICHAEL KEY.
It's hard sometimes to be away.
Tengo familia esparcida
por todas partes--
¿Dónde estás ahorita?
My parents live in Mexico,
and cannot travel anymore.
They're older now.
¡Háblale a la abuela, enséñale!
It's important for me to feel
like I'm there
and they can
see my children grow.
¡Kelly acaba de ganar una
competencia de baile!
Despite the-- the distance,
we can communicate easily
and share special moments.
(VO)
There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best network
now always includes
Apple Music on us.
Starting at only $40.
Only on Verizon.
♪♪
Get out of there now!
This is a stunt test.
Still rolling?
We style the stars behind the
scenes in Walmart Fashion.
♪♪
Hey Google,
are there any hotels nearby?
(Google Assistant)
Bates motel has a rating
of 1 out of 5.
Are you looking
for a room tonight?
I'd rather not.
(Google Assistant)
Okay.
♪♪
♪
>>> PLEASE WELCOME SERENA
WILLIAMS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WHEN WE'RE YOUNG, WE ALL HAVE
DREAMS OF WHAT WE CAN ACCOMPLISH
IN LIFE.
HAVING THE DREAM IS EASY.
MAKING IT COME TRUE IS HARD.
WHETHER THAT DREAM IS BECOMING
AN ACTOR, A TENNIS PLAYER, OR A
SINGER LIKE ALLIE IN "A STAR IS
BORN."
IN TONIGHT'S NEXT NOMINEE FOR
BEST PICTURE, WE SEE, THROUGH
ALLIE'S EYES, THE HIGHS AND LOWS
ON THE JOURNEY TO STARDOM.
THE RUSH OF FAME, THE PRESSURE
OF SUCCESS, AND THE HEARTACHE
THAT COMES WITH SACRIFICING LOVE
FOR CAREER, OR CAREER FOR LOVE.
THIS IS "A STAR IS BORN."
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
McAVOY AND DANAI GURIRA.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THE NOMINEES FOR SOUND
EDITING THIS YEAR RUN THE GAMUT.
>> FROM THE CACOPHONY OF BATTLE
IN "BLACK PANTHER."
>> AND THE ARENA ROCK OF
"BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY."
>> TO THE QUIET TENSIONS OF HOME
IN "ROMA."
>> AND THE SUSPENSEFUL SILENCE
OF "A QUIET PLACE."
>> AND THE UTTER SILENCE OF
SPACE IN "FIRST MAN."
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
ACHIEVEMENT IN SOUND EDITING.
>> "BLACK PANTHER."
"BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY."
"FIRST MAN."
"A QUIET PLACE."
"ROMA."
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO
"BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY"!
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR JOHN AND NINA.
"BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY" IS NOMINATED
IN FIVE CATEGORIES TONIGHT,
INCLUDING BEST PICTURE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> WOW.
THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
WE'D LIKE TO THANK THE ACADEMY.
THIS TRULY IS AN HONOR,
ESPECIALLY IN A CATEGORY WITH SO
MANY AMAZING-SOUNDING FILMS.
WORKING ON "BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY"
REALLY WAS AN HONOR.
WE GOT TO WORK WITH QUEEN FOR
OUR DAY JOB, WHICH WAS
WONDERFUL.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WE'D LIKE TO THANK ALL OF QUEEN,
AND THE FULL TEAM.
FOR THE, JUST FOR THE GREAT
MUSIC, FOR THE SUPPORT.
AND, YEAH, A SPECIAL NOD TO
FREDDIE AS WELL.
[ APPLAUSE ]
AND QUICK SHOUT-OUT, SO MANY
THANKS, STEPH, MY KIDS.
NINA?
>> I WOULD LIKE TO THANK OUR
FULL TEAM.
ALL THE PEOPLE WHO ARE HERE, AND
ALSO EVERYONE IN LONDON, WHO ARE
WATCHING RIGHT NOW.
AND OBVIOUSLY, MY HUSBAND KEVIN
IS UP THERE.
MY FAMILY, MY KIDS, MY MOM AND
DAD, WHO ARE LOOKING AFTER THEM.
MOM, WE'LL BE HOME SOON.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND NOW, IT'S TIME FOR THE
NEXT AWARD.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
ACHIEVEMENT IN SOUND MIXING.
>> "BLACK PANTHER."
"BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY."
"FIRST MAN."
"ROMA."
"A STAR IS BORN."
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO
"BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY"!
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR WIN
FOR THIS SOUND MIXING TEAM.
PAUL HAS EIGHT PREVIOUS
NOMINATIONS, RECEIVING HIS FIRST
FOR HIS WORK ON "LEGENDS OF THE
FALL."
TIM WAS PREVIOUSLY NOMINATED IN
THIS CATEGORY FOR "BABY DRIVER."
THIS IS THE FIRST NOMINATION FOR
JOHN.
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, ACADEMY.
HUGE HONOR.
I'D LIKE TO THANK OUR PRODUCERS,
GRAHAM, DENNIS, TED FROM FOX,
AND OUR WHOLE SOUND CREW, THANK
YOU.
MASSIVE SHOUT-OUT TO BRIAN AND
ROGER.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR YOUR
MUSIC, COLLABORATION, AND
SUPPORT.
AND I WOULD LIKE TO DEDICATE
THIS TO MY KIDS, SHAWN, ANDREW,
SOPHIE, TAYLOR, I LOVE YOU ALL.
THANK YOU.
>> I WANT TO THANK MY WIFE.
MY KIDS, AND HONOR MY TEAM.
FOR CHRIS, THANKS, MATE.
THANK YOU.
>> I'D LIKE TO THANK MY TEAM,
OUR CIRCUIT, EVERYONE ELSE WHO
WORKED ON THE SOUND, MY MOM AND
DAD, MY AMAZING BROTHERS, AND MY
FRIENDS WATCHING TONIGHT.
THANK YOU.
>> COMING UP, THE AWARD FOR
FOREIGN LANGUAGE FILM.
AND A PERFORMANCE BY BETTE
MIDLER.
THEN WE FIND OUT WHO WINS FOR
SUPPORTING ACTOR.
WILL IT BE MAHERSHALA ALI, ADAM
DRIVER, SAM ELLIOTT, RICHARD E.
GRANT, OR SAM ROCKWELL?
PLUS, LADY GAGA AND BRADLEY
COOPER TAKE THE STAGE.
♪
Heeey!
Hey. Famished!
We style the stars behind the
scenes in Walmart Fashion.
You have brie?
[Woman 1]
So cute.
[Woman 2]
Best buds.
Wait-who's that blurred out
there in the background?
[Woman 1]
Did you bokeh my child?
Um, uh, that was totally
unintentional.
[Woman 1]
Why do you hate Jacob?
[LAUGHS]
What?
No-look.
I can un-bokeh. See?
[Woman 2]
Bokeh, un-bokeh.
[Woman 1]
Wow.
What kind of person
bokehs a child?
[Woman 1]
I would never bokeh your child.
Just so you know.
>>> PLEASE WELCOME
OSCAR-NOMINATED ACTRESS QUEEN
LATIFAH.
>> IT'S AN HONOR TO BE HERE TO
INTRODUCE ONE OF TONIGHT'S
NOMINEES FOR BEST PICTURE, "THE
FAVOURITE."
THE FILM TAKES US TO
18th CENTURY BRITAIN WITH A
MONARCH LACKING THE INTEREST,
AND MAYBE THE ABILITY, TO LEAD.
DECISION MAKING IS TAKEN OVER BY
AN INNER CIRCLE.
THERE IS INFIGHTING FOR THE
RULER'S AFFECTION.
AS THE STAKES GET HIGHER, WE SEE
CORRUPTION LEAD TO THE DOWNFALL
OF ONE UNDERLING AFTER ANOTHER.
IT'S NOT EASY BEING QUEEN.
THIS IS "THE FAVOURITE."
>> I HOPE YOU HAVEN'T FOUND YOUR
TIME WITH THE QUEEN TOO TEDIOUS.
>> YES, I'M BEAUTIFUL.
IF I WERE A MAN, I WOULD RAVISH
YOU.
>> YOU'RE JEALOUS.
>> SHE'S A VIPER.
>> I'M ON MY SIDE, ALWAYS.
>> STOP IT.
STOP!
>> IT IS FUN TO BE QUEEN,
SOMETIMES.
>> YOU HAVE WON.
>> HAVEN'T I?
>> TAKE YOUR SHOT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> PLEASE WELCOME ACADEMY
AWARD-NOMINATED ACTRESS ANGELA
BASSETT AND ACADEMY
AWARD-WINNING ACTOR JAVIER
BARDEM.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> MEMBERS OF THE MOVIE ACADEMY
COME FROM ACROSS THE GLOBE, SO
IT IS TRULY FITTING THAT THIS
YEAR, FOREIGN LANGUAGE FILMS ARE
NOT JUST RECOGNIZED IN THIS
CATEGORY, BUT IN ALMOST EVERY
CATEGORY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR BEST
FOREIGN LANGUAGE FILM.
>> FROM LEBANON, "CAPERNAUM."
FROM POLAND, "COLD WAR."
FROM GERMANY, "NEVER LOOK AWAY."
"ROMA," FROM MEXICO.
"SHOPLIFTERS," FROM JAPAN.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO "ROMA"!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> THIS IS THE NINTH MOVIE FROM
MEXICO TO BE NOMINATED, AND THE
FIRST TO WIN THE OSCAR FOR
FOREIGN LANGUAGE FILM.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> THANK YOU.
AM I GOING TO GET SUBTITLED AS
WELL?
THANK YOU, YALITZA, MARINA,
GABRIELA, NICO, ALL THE CAST AND
CREW.
I GREW UP WATCHING FOREIGN
LANGUAGE FILMS, LEARNING SO MUCH
FROM THEM, BEING INSPIRED.
FILMS LIKE "CITIZEN
KANE," "JAWS."
AND THERE ARE NO WAVES, THERE'S
ONLY THE OCEAN.
I THINK THE NOMINEES TONIGHT
HAVE PROVEN THAT WE ARE PART OF
THE SAME OCEAN.
I WANT TO THANK MY FAMILY,
MEXICO, FOR THE BEACH WHERE THIS
FILM COMES FROM.
AND ALSO TO OLMO, BOO, FOR BEING
THE CURRENT THAT PUSHES MY
DRIFT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> AND NOW, DROPPING INTO THE
OSCARS FROM ABOVE, PLEASE
WELCOME KEEGAN-MICHAEL KEY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> THIS THING.
THIS EVENING'S NEXT NOMINEE FOR
BEST ORIGINAL SONG WAS WRITTEN
BY MARC SHAIMAN AND SCOTT
WITTMAN FOR THE FILM "MARY
POPPINS RETURNS."
[ APPLAUSE ]
IN ADDITION TO LIFTING THE BANKS
CHILDREN'S SPIRITS THROUGH A
SERIES OF MAGICAL ADVENTURES,
MARY POPPINS OFFERS COMFORT AND
COMPASSION WITH THIS TENDER
LULLABY, UNDERSCORING THE NOTION
THAT A LOVED ONE WHO IS
LOST CAN STILL BE VERY MUCH
PRESENT.
PERFORMING "THE PLACE WHERE LOST
THINGS GO" WITH MARC SHAIMAN ON
PI
PIANO, PLEASE WELCOME THE DIVINE
MISS "M."
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
♪ DO YOU EVER LIE
AWAKE AT NIGHT
JUST BETWEEN THE DARK
AND THE MORNING LIGHT ♪
♪ SEARCHING FOR THE THINGS
YOU USED TO KNOW
LOOKING FOR THE PLACE
WHERE THE LOST THINGS GO ♪
♪ DO YOU EVER DREAM
OR REMINISCE
WONDERING WHERE TO FIND
WHAT YOU TRULY MISS ♪
♪ WELL MAYBE ALL THOSE THINGS
THAT YOU LOVE SO
ARE WAITING IN THE PLACE
WHERE THE LOST THINGS GO ♪
♪ MEMORIES YOU'VE SHARED
GONE FOR GOOD YOU FEARED
THEY'RE ALL AROUND YOU STILL
THOUGH THEY'VE DISAPPEARED ♪
♪ MAYBE TO THE MOON
OR MAYBE SOMEWHERE NEW
MAYBE ALL YOU'RE MISSING
LIVES INSIDE OF YOU ♪
♪ SO WHEN YOU NEED HER TOUCH
AND LOVING GAZE
GONE BUT NOT FORGOTTEN
IS THE PERFECT PHRASE ♪
♪ SMILING FROM A STAR
THAT SHE MAKES GLOW TRUST
SHE'S ALWAYS THERE ♪
♪ WATCHING AS YOU GROW
FIND HER IN THE PLACE
WHERE THE LOST THINGS GO ♪
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> COMING UP, A LOOK AT BEST
PICTURE NOMINEE "BLACK PANTHER,"
THE OSCARS FOR FILM EDITING AND
BEST SUPPORTING ACTOR, MICHAEL
KEATON, AND A PERFORMANCE OF
"SHALLOW" BY OSCAR NOMINEES LADY
GAGA AND BRADLEY COOPER.
AND LATER, CHARLIZE THERON,
KACEY MUSGRAVES, AND LAURA DERN,
HERE AT THE DOLBY THEATRE.
♪ Will I be pretty. ♪
♪ Will I be rich. ♪
♪ Here's what she said to me. ♪
♪ Que será, será. ♪
♪ Whatever will be, will be. ♪
♪ The future's not ours
to see. ♪
♪ Que será, será. ♪
♪ What will be, will be. ♪
♪ Whatever will be, will be. ♪
♪ Que será, será. ♪
♪ What will be, will be. ♪
♪ Que será, seráaaaaa... ♪
♪ ...aaa. ♪
♪ ♪
♪
Ray...we need an assist.
We style the stars behind the
scenes in Walmart Fashion.
Hey when's lunch?
You.
All of you.
How you live,
what you love.
That's what inspired
us to create
America's most
advanced internet.
Internet that puts
you in charge.
That protects
what's important.
It handles everything,
and reaches everywhere.
This is beyond WiFi,
this is xFi.
Simple. Easy. Awesome.
Xfinity, the
future of awesome.
>>> PLEASE WELCOME TREVOR NOAH.
♪
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> "BLACK PANTHER" MAY BE AN
AFRICAN HERO, BUT HIS STORY AND
HIS APPEAL ARE UNIVERSAL.
I KNOW THIS PERSONALLY, BECAUSE
OF ALL THE PEOPLE WHO CONSTANTLY
COME UP TO ME AND SAY,
"WAKANDA FOREVER."
EVERYWHERE IN THE WORLD.
MY AFRICAN FRIENDS ARE LIKE,
"WANKANDA FOREVER."
IN FRANCE, PEOPLE SAY, "HELLO,
TREVOR NOAH, HOW YOU SAY,
WAKANDA FOREVER?"
EVEN BACKSTAGE, MEL GIBSON CAME
UP TO ME, LIKE, "WAKANDA
FOREVER."
HE SAID ANOTHER WORD TO ME AFTER
THAT, BUT THE WAKANDA PART WAS
NICE.
GROWING UP AS A YOUNG BOY IN
WAKANDA, I WOULD SEE KING
T'CHALLA FLYING OVER OUR VILLAGE
AND HE WOULD REMIND ME OF A
GREAT XHOSA PHRASE.
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
WHICH MEANS, "IN TIMES LIKE
THESE, WE ARE STRONGER WHEN WE
FIGHT TOGETHER THAN WHEN WE TRY
TO FIGHT APART."
THIS IS BEST PICTURE NOMINEE,
"BLACK PANTHER."
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> I WANT TO BE A GREAT KING,
JUST LIKE YOU.
.
>> YOU'RE A GOOD MAN WITH A GOOD
HEART.
AND IT'S HARD FOR A GOOD MAN TO
BE KING.
>> THE BLACK PANTHER LIVES.
YOU GET TO DECIDE WHAT KIND OF
KING YOU ARE GOING TO BE.
>> WAKANDA FOREVER!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> PLEASE WELCOME OSCAR
NOMINATED ACTOR MICHAEL KEATON.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> IF YOU THINK OF SHOOTING A
MOVIE AND MAKING A MOVIE AS THE
SAME THING, YOU'VE OVERLOOKED
ONE OF THE MOST IMPORTANT
ELEMENTS OF FILMMAKING --
THE EDITING.
EDITORS INFUSE A FILM WITH
RHYTHM.
THEY BUILD SUSPENSE.
AND THEY CREATE MOMENTS THAT
WOULD OTHERWISE NOT HAVE
EXISTED.
AND AS AN ACTOR, THEY CAN MAKE
THINGS LIKE YOUR PERFORMANCE A
WHOLE LOT BETTER.
TRUST ME.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
ACHIEVEMENT IN FILM EDITING.
>> "BLACKKKLANSMAN,"
BARRY ALEXANDER BROWN.
"BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY,"
JOHN OTTMAN.
"THE FAVOURITE,"
YORGOS MAVROPSARIDIS.
"GREEN BOOK,"
PATRICK J. DON VITO.
"VICE," HANK CORWIN.
AND THE OSCAR GOES TO
"BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY,"
JOHN OTTMAN.
♪
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR JOHN OTTMAN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> THANK YOU.
>> HE ASKED IF I WOULD LIKE
THIS, I SAID, SURE, MY MOM WOULD
LIKE IT.
OVER HERE, SHE'S 85 YEARS OLD.
WOW, YOU GET UP HERE, AND YOU
COMPLETELY BLANK.
THIS FILM, I LIKE TO SAY, THE
CAST AND CREW LIKES TO SAY, WAS
A LABOR OF LOVE.
I THINK FREDDIE MERCURY BROUGHT
US TOGETHER, FROM WHEREVER HE
IS, JUST LIKE HE DID HIS
AUDIENCE.
I'M SO THANKFUL FOR EVERYBODY
BONDING TOGETHER, AND TRUSTING
ME, AND THERE'S TOO MANY PEOPLE
TO THANK.
RAMI, LOOKING AT ME, YOU HAD
BETTER THANK ME.
I GOT THE BAND OVER HERE, THANK
YOU SO MUCH, BRIAN AND ROGER.
AND I HAVE TO MENTION, OF
COURSE, GRAHAM KING AND DENNIS
O'SULLIVAN, TWO OF THE
HARDEST-WORKING PRODUCERS.
AND MY PARENTS, THIS GOES TO
THEM ON THEIR MANTEL, THEY
ENCOURAGED ME TO DO WHATEVER I
WANTED AS A KID, WRITING MUSIC,
OR WRITING FILMS IN THEIR GARAGE
IN CALIFORNIA.
SO, AS FREDDIE'S FATHER WOULD
SAY, GOOD THOUGHTS, GOOD WORDS,
GOOD DEEDS.
THANK YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> PLEASE WELCOME DANIEL CRAIG
AND ACADEMY AWARD WINNER
CHARLIZE THERON.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> AS ACTORS, WE SHOW UP, WE
WORK HARD, AND HOPEFULLY WE TAKE
OUR JOBS SERIOUSLY WITHOUT
TAKING OURSELVES TOO SERIOUSLY.
SERIOUSLY, CHARLIZE COULD KICK
MY --
WE ASPIRE TO TRANSFORM OURSELVES
INTO THE CHARACTERS WE PLAY, AND
TO TRANSPORT THE MOVIEGOER IN
THE PROCESS.
>> AMONG A SEA OF BRILLIANT
PERFORMANCES EACH YEAR, CERTAIN
OF THEM STAND OUT FOR THEIR
ARTISTRY, THEIR HONESTY, AND THE
MASTERFUL CHOICES MADE IN
INTERPRETING THE ROLE.
WE HONOR THOSE INDIVIDUALS
TONIGHT.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
PERFORMANCE BY AN ACTOR IN A
SUPPORTING ROLE.
>> MAHERSHALA ALI, "GREEN BOOK."
>> I JUST PUT THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL OF THE UNITED STATES IN
AN INCREDIBLY AWKWARD POSITION.
>> SO WHAT?
THAT'S WHAT HE GETS PAID FOR.
>> THAT MAN AND HIS BROTHER ARE
TRYING TO CHANGE THIS COUNTRY.
THAT'S WHAT ELSE HE HAS GOT TO
DO.
>> NOW HE THINKS I'M SOME KIND
OF -- CRAWLING FROM SOME
BACKWOODS SWAMP JAIL.
WHO DOES THAT?
GARBAGE, THAT'S WHO.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> ADAM DRIVER,
"BLACKKKLANSMAN."
>> I'M JEWISH, YES, BUT I WASN'T
RAISED TO BE.
IT WASN'T PART OF MY LIFE.
I NEVER THOUGHT MUCH ABOUT BEING
JEWISH, NOBODY AROUND ME WAS
JEWISH.
I WASN'T GOING TO A BUNCH OF BAR
MITZVAHS.
NOW I'M IN SOME BASEMENT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> SAM ELLIOTT, "A STAR IS
BORN."
>> IT ISN'T YOUR FAULT.
IT JUST ISN'T.
YOU KNOW WHOSE FAULT IT WAS?
JACK.
THAT'S IT.
NO ONE ELSE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> RICHARD E. GRANT, "CAN YOU
EVER FORGIVE ME?"
>> SHE DIED.
>> SHE DID?
THAT'S YOUNG.
>> MAYBE SHE DIDN'T DIE.
MAYBE SHE JUST MOVED BACK TO THE
SUBURBS.
I WAS CONFUSED.
THAT'S RIGHT, SHE GOT MARRIED
AND HAD TWINS.
>> BETTER TO HAVE DIED.
>> INDEED.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> SAM ROCKWELL, "VICE."
>> YOU'RE ONE OF THE MOST
EXPERIENCED GUYS AROUND.
WILL YOU JUMP ONBOARD, BE MY
VICE?
>> I'M HONORED.
>> SAY YES.
>> I HAVE TO SAY NO.
>> DICK, COME ON, WE'LL HAVE A
LOT OF FUN.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING RIGHT NOW?
IN THE PRIVATE SECTOR?
>> YEAH.
>> COME ON.
I KNOW YOU LOVE POLITICS.
>> GEORGE, L.
>> LET'S GO.
>> NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> COME ON, NOW.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO
MAHERSHALA ALI.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> THIS IS THE SECOND OSCAR AND
SECOND NOMINATION FOR MAHERSHALA
ALI.
HE TOOK HOME HIS FIRST OSCAR IN
THIS CATEGORY FOR "MOONLIGHT."
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> THE ACADEMY, THANK YOU.
I WANT TO THANK DR. SHIRLEY FOR
JUST TRYING TO CAPTURE HIS
ESSENCE.
JUST TRYING TO CAPTURE DR.
SHIRLEY'S ESSENCE, PUSHED ME TO
MY ENDS.
WHICH IS A REFLECTION OF THE
PERSON HE WAS AND THE LIFE THAT
HE LIVED.
AND I THANK HIM.
I THANK MY PARTNER, VIGGO.
IT WAS EXTRAORDINARY WORKING
WITH YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
PETER FAIRLEY, THANK YOU FOR
YOUR LEADERSHIP AND GUIDANCE.
AND ALSO FOR GIVING US SPACE,
LIKE, REALLY GIVING US SPACE TO
WORK IT OUT, AND COMING IN AND
TWEAKING.
REALLY APPRECIATE AND LOVE YOU.
OCTAVIA SPENCER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
CHRIS BOWERS, MY DOUBLE.
I WANT TO DEDICATE THIS TO MY
GRANDMOTHER, WHO HAS BEEN IN MY
EAR MY ENTIRE LIFE.
TELLING ME THAT IF I FIRST I
DON'T SUCCEED, TRY, TRY AGAIN.
THAT I CAN DO ANYTHING I PUT MY
MIND TO.
ALWAYS, ALWAYS PUSHING ME TO
THINK POSITIVELY AND I KNOW THAT
I WOULD NOT BE HERE WITHOUT HER,
THAT SHE'S GOTTEN ME OVER THE
HUMP IN A LOT OF WAYS.
MY WIFE, MY DAUGHTER, EVERYONE
WHO CONTRIBUTED WITH THE MOVIE.
AGAIN, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> COMING UP NEXT, THE AWARD FOR
ANIMATED FEATURE.
THEN LATER, A LOOK AT
"BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY" AND "ROMA."
AND A PERFORMANCE OF "SHALLOW"
FROM "A STAR IS BORN."
>> LAST YEAR, MOVIES TOOK US
ACROSS THE GLOBE, FROM THE MAGIC
OF SINGAPORE, TO THE MYSTERIES
OF AFRICA, ENCHANTING US WITH
THE JOY OF TRAVEL.
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, PLEASE
WELCOME LAURA DERN.
>> GROWING UP IN LOS ANGELES,
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT WAS ONLY A
DREAM THAT THERE WOULD EVER BE A
PLACE WHERE PEOPLE COULD GO TO
IMMERSE THEMSELVES IN THE
PASSION AND MAGIC OF MOVIES.
EVEN AS A CHILD OF ACTORS, THERE
WAS NOTHING.
TRUST ME.
BUT, GUESS WHAT, THE DREAM IS
HAPPENING.
WHEN WE ENTER THE NEW ACADEMY
MUSEUM OF MOTION PICTURES, WE
WILL OPEN A DOOR AND WALK INTO
THE TECHNICOLOR LAND OF OZ.
WE WILL TRAVEL THROUGH THE
ANIMATED WORLD OF MIYAZAKI,
PERHAPS ENCOUNTER THE SHARK FROM
"JAWS," AND SEE THE RUBY RED
SLIPPERS.
THE DREAM IS A REALITY, NOT JUST
FOR THE CHILD IN ME, BUT FOR ALL
OF US, FROM ALL AROUND THE
WORLD.
COMING SOON.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> PLEASE WELCOME MICHELLE YEOH
AND OSCAR-NOMINATED COMPOSER AND
PRODUCER, PHARRELL WILLIAMS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> THE BIBLE SAYS, "WHEN I WAS A
CHILD, I SPOKE AS A CHILD, I
UNDERSTOOD AS A CHILD, I THOUGHT
AS A CHILD.
AND WHEN I BECAME A MAN, I PUT
AWAY CHILDISH THINGS."
>> WHEN WE MOVE THROUGH
ADULTHOOD WE LOOK BACK FONDLY ON
THOSE SIMPLER TIMES.
THE CREATIVITY WE EXHIBITED, OUR
FEARLESSNESS, HOW WE APPROACHED
NEW THINGS WITH WONDER.
>> THE FILMS NOMINATED FOR BEST
ANIMATED FEATURE POSSESS THE
ABILITY TO MOVE US ALL.
NO NEED TO PUT THINGS AWAY, BUT
INSTEAD EMBRACE AND ENJOY A
SHARED EXPERIENCE.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
BEST ANIMATED FEATURE FILM.
>> "INCREDIBLES 2," BRAD BIRD,
JOHN WALKER, AND
NICOLE PARADIS GRINDLE.
"ISLE OF DOGS," WES ANDERSON,
SCOTT RUDIN, STEVEN RALES, AND
JEREMY DAWSON.
"MIRAI," MAMORU HOSODA AND
YUICHIRO SAITO.
"RALPH BREAKS THE INTERNET,"
RICH MOORE, PHIL JOHNSTON, AND
CLARK SPENCER.
"SPIDER-MAN: INTO THE
SPIDER-VERSE," BOB PERSICHETTI,
PETER RAMSEY, RODNEY ROTHMAN,
PHIL LORD, AND
CHRISTOPHER MILLER.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO, YOU
WERE RIGHT.
"SPIDER-MAN: INTO THE
SPIDER-VERSE."
>> I WANTED TO DO THE NAMES.
>> BOB PERSICHETTI,
PETER RAMSEY, RODNEY ROTHMAN,
PHIL LORD, AND
CHRISTOPHER MILLER.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR
NOMINATION FOR BOB, PHIL,
RODNEY, PETER, AND CHRISTOPHER.
>> THERE'S A LOT OF US.
>> WOW.
>> HEY, WOW.
THANK YOU, ACADEMY.
>> THANK YOU, SONY.
WE SHARE THIS WITH OUR FELLOW
PRODUCERS, CAST, CREW, THERE'S
800 FILMMAKERS WHO TOOK RISKS TO
MAKE PEOPLE FEEL POWERFUL AND
SEEN.
>> SO, WHEN WE HEAR THAT
SOMEBODY'S KID WAS WATCHING THE
MOVIE AND TURNED TO THEM AND
SAID, HE LOOKS LIKE ME, OR THEY
SPEAK SPANISH LIKE US, WE FEEL
LIKE WE ALREADY WON.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> TO OUR AUDIENCE, THANK YOU SO
MUCH.
WE LOVE YOU, AND WE JUST WANT
YOU ALL TO KNOW, WE SEE YOU,
YOU'RE POWERFUL.
THIS WORLD NEEDS YOU.
OKAY?
SO, PLEASE, WE'RE ALL COUNTING
ON YOU.
THANK YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> ON BEHALF OF EVERYONE, WE
WANT TO THANK OUR FAMILIES, WHO
STAYED WITH US FOR FOUR YEARS ON
THIS.
THIS IS FOR YOU.
WE LOVE YOU ALL.
>> AND FINALLY --
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> PLEASE WELCOME KACEY
MUSGRAVES.
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> "THE BALLAD OF
BUSTER SCRUGGS" BROUGHT NEW LIFE
INTO WESTERNS WITH ITS MIX OF
SATIRE, SENTIMENT, REALISM, AND
ROMANCE.
ALL OF THESE QUALITIES ARE ON
DISPLAY IN THIS HAUNTING SONG.
IT'S FRESH AND YET YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU'VE HEARD IT YOUR WHOLE LIFE.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN AN ABSURD AND
COMICAL MOMENT IN THE FILM, BUT
THE SONG ELEVATES IT INTO
SOMETHING AUTHENTIC AND
BEAUTIFUL.
HERE ARE THE WONDERFUL
GILLIAN WELCH AND DAVID RAWLINGS
WITH THE OSCAR NOMINATED SONG,
"WHEN A COWBOY TRADES HIS SPURS
FOR WINGS."
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
♪ LET ME TELL YOU BUDDY
THERE'S A FASTER GUN
COMING OVER YONDER
WHEN TOMORROW COMES ♪
♪ LET ME TELL YOU BUDDY
AND IT WON'T BE LONG TILL
YOU FIND YOURSELF SINGING
YOUR LAST COWBOY SONG ♪
♪ YIPPEE KI-YI-YAY
WHEN THE ROUNDUP ENDS
YIPPEE KI-YI-YAY
AND THE CAMPFIRE DIMS ♪
♪ YIPPEE KI-YI-YAY
HE SHOUTS AND HE SINGS
WHEN A COWBOY TRADES
HIS SPURS FOR WINGS ♪
♪ YIPPEE KI-YI-YAY
I'M GLORY BOUND
NO MORE JINGLE JANGLE
I'LL LAY MY GUNS DOWN ♪
♪ YIPPEE KI-YI-YAY
HE SHOUTS AND HE SINGS
WHEN A COWBOY TRADES
HIS SPURS FOR WINGS ♪
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> COMING UP, HIGHLIGHTS FROM
BEST PICTURE NOMINEES
"BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY," "ROMA,"
"BLACKKKLANSMAN," AND "GREEN
BOOK."
PLUS, MIKE MYERS AND DANA CARVEY
TOGETHER ONSTAGE,
CHADWICK BOSEMAN, CONSTANCE WU,
BRIE LARSON, SAMUEL L. JACKSON,
LADY GAGA, AND BRADLEY COOPER.
Hello?
Hello, are you ready?
Yes.
What door am I at?
Patio door, police
are on their way!
See ya!
♪♪
That's a cut.
(Bell rings)
Copy that.
We style the stars behind the
scenes in Walmart Fashion.
I've talked on this phone
through the happiest times
of my life,
and through the saddest
times of my life.
But I never dreamed
in a thousand years
that it would save my life.
Boom!
I fell 22 feet,
completely shattered my pelvis,
in the middle of the woods.
I called my wife,
she thought I was jokin'.
I said, "Man, I'm not...
I'm not."
I was so lucky that day...
saved my life.
(VO)
There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best network
now always includes
Apple Music on us.
Starting at only $40.
Only on Verizon.
>>> I THINK WE'LL GO WITH A
LITTLE "BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY,"
GENTLEMEN.
>> GOOD CALL.
♪ MAMA MIA MAMA MIA LET ME GO
THE DEVIL HAS A SITE SET ASIDE
FOR ME ♪
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, PLEASE
WELCOME MIKE MYERS AND DANA
CARVEY!
[ SCREAMING ]
>> WE'RE NOT WORTHY!
>> I THINK I'M GONNA HURL.
>> DON'T HURL.
'CAUSE IF YOU HONK, I'LL SPEW.
>> IF YOU SPEW, I'LL BLOW
CHUNKS.
SO I SHALL NOT HURL.
>> GOOD CALL.
GOOD CALL.
BUT SERIOUSLY, "BOHEMIAN
RHAPSODY" PLAYED A LARGE PART IN
THE SUCCESS OF "WAYNE'S WORLD."
WE ARE HUMBLED TO BE ASSOCIATED
WITH THAT BRILLIANT SONG.
>> IT IS OUR PLEASURE TO
INTRODUCE A BEST PICTURE NOMINEE
THAT CELEBRATES THE LIFE OF
FREDDIE MERCURY THROUGH THE
GENIUS OF QUEEN'S MUSIC.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN --
>> Both: "BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY!"
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> I KNOW THEY'RE LISTENING.
I'M NOT AFRAID OF ANYTHING.
NO ONE WILL PLAY QUEEN.
FORTUNE FAVORS THE BOLD.
>> THOUGHTS, GOOD WORDS, GOOD
DEEDS.
THAT'S WHAT YOU SHOULD ASPIRE
TO.
>> I NEED SOME TIME.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TIME.
♪
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> PLEASE WELCOME AWKWAFINA AND
JOHN MULANEY.
♪
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> OKAY.
>> OH, YEAH, JOHN.
YOU'RE HERE, TOO?
THAT'S GOOD.
>> THEY TOLD ME BACKSTAGE YOU'RE
DOING THIS WITH AWKWAFINA AND I
WAS LIKE, THANK GOD I'M NOT
PRESENTING ALONE.
>> THIS IS MY FIRST TIME EVER AT
THE OSCARS, LIKE, EVER.
>> THIS IS MY FIRST TIME AT THE
OSCARS, TOO.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> YES!
>> YES.
I'M HAVING A PANIC ATTACK.
>> I'M SO SCARED.
WHY AM I SO SCARED?
YOU SEE THE COMMERCIALS LIKE,
THE OSCARS, IT'S HOLLYWOOD'S
BIGGEST NIGHT, AND I'M ALWAYS
LIKE, "WHATEVER, SHUT UP."
AND I'M HERE, AND I'M LIKE, THIS
IS HOLLYWOOD'S BIGGEST NIGHT.
I WANT THEM TO LIKE ME TO A
DEGREE THAT I FIND EMBARRASSING.
>> WHO WERE YOU MOST NERVOUS TO
SEE?
BECAUSE WHEN I WALKED OUT, I SAW
SPIKE LEE, AND I WAS LIKE,
"WHAT?"
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU SAID?
>> I WAS LIKE --
>> THAT'S GREAT.
DO YOU KNOW WHO I SAW AND I
LEGIT FREAKED OUT?
JORDAN PEELE.
>> DON'T YOU KNOW HIM?
>> YEAH, THAT'S WHY IT'S WEIRD.
>> ALL RIGHT, THIS IS AWESOME.
LET'S DO THIS.
WE ARE HERE TO PRESENT THE AWARD
FOR BEST ANIMATED SHORT.
>> DUDE, THEY GAVE US ONE OF THE
BIG ONES.
>> IT'S A BIG ONE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR BEST
ANIMATED SHORT FILM.
>> "ANIMAL BEHAVIOUR,"
ALISON SNOWDEN AND DAVID FINE.
"BAO," DOMEE SHI AND
BECKY NEIMAN-COBB.
"LATE AFTERNOON," LOUISE BAGNALL
AND NURIA GONZÁLEZ BLANCO.
"ONE SMALL STEP,"
ANDREW CHESWORTH AND
BOBBY PONTILLAS.
"WEEKENDS," TREVOR JIMENEZ.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO "BAO."
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR DOMEE AND BECKY.
ACADEMY AWARDS IN THIS CATEGORY
HAVE BEEN PRESENTED SINCE 1932.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> OKAY, HOLY -- IT'S OUR FIRST
TIME, TOO.
THANK YOU TO THE ACADEMY, THANK
YOU TO MY FELLOW NOMINEES, THANK
YOU FOR SUPPORTING SHORTS.
TO ALL OF THE NERDY GIRLS WHO
HIDE BEHIND THEIR SKETCHBOOKS,
DON'T BE AFRAID TO TELL YOUR
STORIES TO THE WORLD.
YOU'RE GOING TO FREAK PEOPLE
OUT, BUT YOU'LL PROBABLY CONNECT
WITH THEM, TOO, AND THAT'S AN
AMAZING FEELING TO HAVE.
THANK YOU TO PETE FOR BELIEVING
IN MY WEIRDNESS, AND GIVING ME A
VOICE AT THE STUDIO.
AND THANK YOU TO MY MOM AND MY
DAD, MY MUSES, AND MY PARTNER
DARREN FOR BEING THERE WITH ME.
>> WE WANT TO THANK THE
ENTIRE "BAO" CREW, THEY BROUGHT
THEIR HEART TO THE SHORT.
AND EVERYONE AT PIXAR, DISNEY,
TO MY FRIENDS AND FAMILY,
PARENTS AND SISTER.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
I GOT TO HELP MAKE A SHORT THAT
WAS ABOUT A MOTHER JUST AS I WAS
BECOMING ONE.
TO MY LITTLE BAO LUCY AND TO
DEANNE, I LOVE YOU.
WITHOUT YOU, NONE OF THIS WOULD
BE POSSIBLE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WHY ARE WE STILL HERE?
WHY ARE WE STILL HERE?
WE'RE DOING ANOTHER ONE.
>> YES, DOCUMENTARY SHORT
SUBJECT.
>> THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES.
>> "BLACK SHEEP," ED PERKINS AND
JONATHAN CHINN.
"END GAME," ROB EPSTEIN AND
JEFFREY FRIEDMAN.
"LIFEBOAT," SKYE FITZGERALD AND
BRYN MOOSER.
"A NIGHT AT THE GARDEN,"
MARSHALL CURRY.
"PERIOD. END OF SENTENCE."
RAYKA ZEHTABCHI AND
MELISSA BERTON.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES
TO "PERIOD.
END OF SENTENCE."
>> THIS IS THEIR FIRST OSCAR
NOMINATION.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> OH, MY GOD.
I'M NOT CRYING BECAUSE I'M ON MY
PERIOD OR ANYTHING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE A FILM ABOUT
MENSTRUATION JUST WON AN OSCAR.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, NETFLIX, FOR GIVING
US A PLATFORM, THANK YOU TO MY
CREATIVE PARTNER, SAM, I SHARE
THIS WITH YOU.
THANK YOU TO MY MOM AND SISTER,
I LOVE YOU.
TO LISA AND GARRETT.
TO THE WOMEN, KNOW THAT YOU ARE
EMPOWERING WOMEN ALL OVER THE
WORLD TO FIGHT FOR MENSTRUAL
EQUALITY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THIS FILM BEGAN BECAUSE HIGH
SCHOOL STUDENTS HERE AND OUR
GREAT PARTNERS AT ACTION INDIA
WANTED TO MAKE A HUMAN RIGHTS
DIFFERENCE.
I SHARE THIS AWARD WITH THE
FEMINIST MAJORITY FOUNDATION.
WITH THE ENTIRE PAD PROJECT
TEAM.
WITH THE OAKWOOD SCHOOL.
I SHARE THIS -- I SHARE THIS
WITH TEACHERS AND WITH STUDENTS
AROUND THE WORLD.
A PERIOD SHOULD END A SENTENCE,
NOT A GIRL'S EDUCATION.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> SOME OF THE BIGGEST AWARDS OF
THE NIGHT ARE AHEAD.
AND RIGHT NOW, WE'RE HEADING TO
THE BACKSTAGE GREEN ROOM TO SEE
THE STARS AS THEY GET READY TO
GO ONSTAGE, AND WHERE THE
WINNERS COME TO CELEBRATE AFTER
THEIR BIG MOMENT.
COMING UP NEXT, DIEGO LUNA,
JOSE ANDRES, PAUL RUDD, AND
SARAH PAULSON.
PLUS, A PERFORMANCE OF "SHALLOW"
BY LADY GAGA AND BRADLEY COOPER.
♪(oh oh oh oh)
It's taking over.♪
♪There's no escape...♪
♪...You better get moving. Ready
or not♪
♪...It's about to go down here
it comes now♪
♪...Get ready (oh oh oh oh), Get
ready♪
♪...Moving. Ready or not♪
♪...Get ready (oh oh oh oh)♪
♪♪
This is why you do it.
Why you squeeze one more task
into your morning routine.
Why you make bedtime just as
memorable as playtime.
For this: the big smiles those
little surprises can bring.
Kinder Joy is a
two-in-one treat.
Half smooth cocoa,
sweet cream and crispy wafers.
Half mystery toy,
now with over 50 new surprises
to build.
Kinder Joy.
A Little Surprise Goes
a Long Way.
♪♪
We style the stars behind the
scenes in Walmart Fashion.
>>> PLEASE WELCOME DIEGO LUNA
AND CHEF JOSE ANDRES.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
>> I'M A CHEF.
I FOLLOW THE RECIPE.
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
>> SO, PEOPLE OF THE WORLD, EACH
PERSON'S LIFE IS A RECIPE ALL ON
ITS OWN.
WITH DIFFERENT MEASURES OF JOY
AND SADNESS, STRUGGLE AND
SUCCESS, LOVE AND LOSS.
THE RESULTS ARE UNIQUE EVERY
TIME, EVEN THOUGH ALL OF THE
INGREDIENTS ARE UNIVERSAL.
>> IN "ROMA," ALFONSO CUARON
PRESENTS AN HONEST AND VITAL
PORTRAIT OF THE MEXICO CITY OF
HIS CHILDHOOD.
A PLACE FULL OF CONTRASTS AND
CONTRADICTIONS.
THIS IS A STORY OF LONELY WOMEN
AND ABSENT MEN, OF PAINFUL CLASS
DIVISIONS AND RACIAL DYNAMICS,
BUT LOVE IS WHERE EVERYONE
MEETS.
>> AND THIS BEAUTIFUL, INTIMATE
FILM, ONE THAT GIVES A VOICE TO
THE VOICELESS, REMINDS US OF THE
UNDERSTANDING AND COMPASSION
THAT WE ALL OWE TO THE INVISIBLE
PEOPLE IN OUR LIVES WHO MOVE
HUMANITY FORWARD.
IMMIGRANTS AND WOMEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> PLEASE WELCOME PAUL RUDD AND
SARAH PAULSON.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> IN "DUCK SOUP," CHICO MARX
ASKS, "WHO ARE YOU GOING TO
BELIEVE?
ME OR YOUR OWN EYES?"
WHEN IT COMES TO VISUAL EFFECTS,
THE ANSWER'S NOT SO SIMPLE.
>> TODAY'S EFFECTS ARTISTS
COLLABORATE WITH EVERY OTHER
DEPARTMENT TO CONVINCE AUDIENCES
OF EVEN THE MOST IMPLAUSIBLE
REALITIES.
THIS IS THE KIND OF MAGIC THAT
ALLOWS THE AUDIENCE TO BELIEVE I
WAS ACTUALLY OBLITERATED BY A
TRUCK IN "BIRD BOX."
>> AND THE SAME KIND OF MAGIC
THAT ALLOWS THE AUDIENCE TO
BELIEVE THAT I'M AN ACTOR.
>> HERE ARE THIS YEAR'S NOMINEES
FOR ACHIEVEMENT IN VISUAL
EFFECTS.
>> "AVENGERS: INFINITY WAR,"
DAN DELEEUW, KELLY PORT,
RUSSELL EARL, AND DAN SUDICK.
"CHRISTOPHER ROBIN,"
CHRISTOPHER LAWRENCE,
MICHAEL EAMES, THEO JONES, AND
CHRIS CORBOULD.
"FIRST MAN," PAUL LAMBERT,
IAN HUNTER, TRISTAN MYLES, AND
J.D. SCHWALM.
"READY PLAYER ONE,"
ROGER GUYETT, GRADY COFER,
MATTHEW E. BUTLER, AND DAVID
SHIRK.
"SOLO: A STAR WARS STORY,"
ROB BREDOW, PATRICK TUBACH,
NEAL SCANLAN, AND DOMINIC TUOHY.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO "FIRST
MAN."
PAUL LAMBERT, IAN HUNTER,
TRISTAN MYLES, AND J.D. SCHWALM.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR
NOMINATION FOR TRISTAN AND J.D.
THE SECOND TIME FOR PAUL AND
IAN.
♪
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
A TRULY MAGNIFICENT MOMENT, AND
TO BE RECOGNIZED BY THE ACADEMY
IS THAT MUCH MORE SPECIAL.
THANKS TO KEVIN AND JENNIFER,
THANK YOU TO DAMIAN, WHO IS AN
INSPIRATION.
AND OUR AMAZING CAST, AND LINUS,
TOM, JUSTIN, MILDRED, WHO MADE
THIS FILM SO MEMORABLE.
AND A BIG SHOUT-OUT TO THE TEAM
IN VANCOUVER.
>> THANK YOU TO DAMIAN, MY WIFE,
MY TWO BOYS, AND MY DAD, WHO
TAUGHT ME HOW TO PUT THE MAGIC
IN MOVIES.
>> THANKS TO THE CREW, WITHOUT
WHOSE HARD WORK WE WOULDN'T BE
HERE TONIGHT.
THANKS TO MY WIFE AND OUR
CHILDREN FOR ALL THEIR SUPPORT
OVER THE YEARS.
>> AND IT'S AN HONOR, IT'S
HUMBLING TO HONOR NEAL ARMSTRONG
AND ALL THE MEN AND WOMEN AT
NASA.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪ TELL ME SOMETHIN' GIRL
ARE YOU HAPPY
IN THIS MODERN WORLD ♪
♪ OR DO YOU NEED MORE
IS THERE SOMETHIN' ELSE
YOU'RE SEARCHIN' FOR
I'M FALLING ♪
♪ IN ALL THE GOOD TIMES
I FIND MYSELF LONGIN'
FOR CHANGE ♪
♪ AND IN THE BAD TIMES
I FEAR MYSELF ♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
♪ TELL ME SOMETHING BOY
AREN'T YOU TIRED
TRYIN' TO FILL THAT VOID
OR DO YOU NEED MORE ♪
♪ AIN'T IT HARD
KEEPING IT SO HARDCORE I'M
FALLING ♪
♪ IN ALL THE GOOD TIMES
I FIND MYSELF LONGING
FOR CHANGE ♪
♪ AND IN THE BAD TIMES
I FEAR MYSELF ♪
♪ I'M OFF THE DEEP END
WATCH AS I DIVE IN
I'LL NEVER MEET THE GROUND ♪
♪ CRASH THROUGH THE SURFACE
WHERE THEY CAN'T HURT US
WE'RE FAR FROM
THE SHALLOW NOW ♪
♪ IN THE SHA-HA
SHA-HA-LOW
IN THE SHA-HA
SHA-LA-LA-LA-LOW ♪
♪ IN THE SHA-HA
SHA-HA-LOW
WE'RE FAR FROM
THE SHALLOW NOW ♪
♪
♪ OH OH OH OH OH OH ♪
♪ OH OH OH ♪
♪ I'M OFF THE DEEP END
WATCH AS I DIVE IN
I'LL NEVER MEET THE GROUND ♪
♪ CRASH THROUGH THE SURFACE
WHERE THEY CAN'T HURT US
WE'RE FAR FROM THE SHALLOW NOW ♪
♪ IN THE SHA-HA
SHA-HA-LOW
IN THE SHA-SHA-LA-LA-LA-LOW ♪
♪ IN THE SHA-HA
SHA-HA-LOW
WE'RE FAR FROM
THE SHALLOW NOW ♪
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> COMING UP, THE OSCARS FOR
ORIGINAL AND ADAPTED
SCREENPLAYS.
THEN LATER, WE'LL FIND OUT WHO
BRINGS HOME THE OSCARS FOR BEST
ACTOR AND ACTRESS.
PLUS, BRIE LARSON,
SAMUEL L. JACKSON,
TESSA THOMPSON,
CHADWICK BOSEMAN, AND
CONSTANCE WU.
HERE ON THE OSCARS.
I love my babies,
love my boys.
Since I'm a truck driver,
you know there's times
that I'm gone for,
like, three weeks at a time.
Even if I'm 3,000 miles away,
I'm connected with my boys.
Every day I can
video chat with them.
I could be in the middle
of Wyoming,
even if I'm like waaay...
out here,
I can still reach my kids.
Baby, you-- you see me?
(sons)
Hey, Daddy!
(VO)
There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best network
now always includes
Apple Music on us.
Starting at only $40.
Only on Verizon.
♪♪
Get out of there now!
This is a stunt test.
Still rolling?
We style the stars behind the
scenes in Walmart Fashion.
[music]
Bonvoy.
Discover the new language
of travel.
Marriott Bonvoy.
30 hotel brands.
Endless experiences.
Rewards reimagined.
>>> PLEASE WELCOME
KRYSTEN RITTER AND KIKI LAYNE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> THIS YEAR'S SHORT FILMS ARE
INNOVATIVE, PROFOUNDLY MOVING,
AND WORTHY OF NOMINATIONS IN
EVERY CATEGORY.
>> SET IN LOCATIONS AROUND THE
WORLD, THEY SHOW US THE BEST AND
WORST IN OURSELVES.
IF YOU LOVE MOVIES, YOU NEED TO
SEE THEM.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
BEST LIVE ACTION SHORT FILM.
>> "DETAINMENT," VINCENT LAMBE
AND DARREN MAHON.
"FAUVE," JEREMY COMTE AND
MARIA GRACIA TURGEON.
"MARGUERITE," MARIANNE FARLEY
AND MARIE-HELENE PANISSET.
"MOTHER," RODRIGO SOROGOYEN AND
MARIA DEL PUY ALVARADO.
"SKIN," GUY NATTIV AND
JAIME RAY NEWMAN.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO -- YES!
"SKIN," GUY NATTIV AND
JAIME RAY NEWMAN.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR GUY AND JAIME
RAY.
ACADEMY AWARDS FOR LIVE ACTION
SHORT FILMS HAVE BEEN PRESENTED
FOR OVER 80 YEARS.
♪
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> YES!
OH, MY GOD!
>> OH, MY GOD.
I MOVED HERE FIVE YEARS AGO FROM
ISRAEL.
AND MY GRANDPARENTS ARE
HOLOCAUST SURVIVORS.
WE SEE BIGOTRY EVERY DAY IN
AMERICA AND EUROPE, AND THIS
FILM IS ABOUT EDUCATION, IT'S
ABOUT TEACHING YOUR KIDS A
BETTER WAY.
>> WE DEDICATE THIS TO OUR --
OH, MY GOD, OUR 5-MONTH-OLD
BABY, AT HOME WITH MY PARENTS.
WE HOPE YOU GROW UP IN A WORLD
WHERE THESE THINGS DON'T HAPPEN,
BECAUSE PEOPLE LEARN TO LOVE
EACH OTHER.
I WANT THIS THANK OUR TEAM,
EVERYONE AT FOX SEARCHLIGHT.
WE LOVE YOU.
YES!
>> WHOO!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> PLEASE WELCOME
ACADEMY AWARD-NOMINATED ACTOR,
SAMUEL L. JACKSON, AND
ACADEMY AWARD WINNER,
BRIE LARSON.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> FIRST OF ALL, SPIKE, SO GLAD
YOU'RE SITTING DOWN.
AFTER 18 CONSECUTIVE HOME
LOSSES, THE KNICKS WON TONIGHT.
I REPEAT, THE KNICKS WON
TONIGHT.
DEFEATING SAN ANTONIO, 130-118.
>> AND NOW, TO GET BACK
ON-SCRIPT.
THE LEGENDARY FILMMAKER
FRANK CAPRA SAID, SCRIPTWRITING
IS THE TOUGHEST PART OF THE
WHOLE RACKET, THE LEAST
UNDERSTOOD, AND THE LEAST
NOTICED.
>> OH, WE NOTICE.
>> OF COURSE.
>> WE NOTICE.
>> BRIE AND I DON'T SHOW UP ON A
MOVIE SET AND AD LIB FOR
12 HOURS.
WE'RE NOT WINGING IT.
WE NEED WORDS.
WHICH IS WHY WE TRULY APPRECIATE
WHAT THE LATE, GREAT
WILLIAM GOLDMAN SAID ABOUT HIS
CRAFT.
THE LATEST -- THE EASIEST THING
TO DO ON EARTH IS NOT TO WRITE.
>> TRUTH.
LUCKILY, THESE WRITERS TOOK THE
HARD PATH.
THEY ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
ORIGINAL SCREENPLAY.
>> "THE FAVOURITE," WRITTEN BY
DEBORAH DAVIS AND TONY McNAMARA.
"FIRST REFORMED," WRITTEN BY
PAUL SCHRADER.
"GREEN BOOK," WRITTEN BY
NICK VALLELONGA, BRIAN CURRIE,
PETER FARRELLY.
"ROMA," WRITTEN BY
ALFONSO CUARON.
"VICE," WRITTEN BY ADAM McKAY.
>> YEAH, I DID IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
AND THE OSCAR GOES TO --
NICK VALLELONGA, BRIAN CURRIE,
PETER FARRELLY FOR "GREEN BOOK."
.
>> THEY ARE ALSO NOMINATED IN
THE BEST PICTURE CATEGORY.
>> I'D LIKE TO THANK UNIVERSAL
STUDIOS, DREAMWORKS.
AS WRITERS, WHEN YOU HAVE
MAHERSHALA ALI, VIGGO MORTENSEN,
AND LINDA CARDELLINI SAYING YOUR
WORDS, YOU PINCH YOURSELF.
I WANT TO THANK MY FAMILY, AND
PARTICULARLY GEORGE AND IRENE,
THE BEST PARENTS ANYBODY COULD
HAVE.
>> THEY SAY IF YOU WANT TO GO
SOMEWHERE FAST, GO ALONE.
IF YOU WANT TO GO FAR, GO
TOGETHER.
I HAVE A LOT OF PEOPLE TO THANK.
STARTING WITH THE ENTIRE STATE
OF RHODE ISLAND.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I WANT TO THANK VIGGO,
MAHERSHALA, AND LINDA.
I WANT TO THANK MY WIFE, KIDS,
BOB, RICHARD, JOE, PETER,
AMANDA, STACEY, JONATHAN,
ROBERT, J.B., CHARLIE, JIM, TED,
SHAWN, TOM, AND SHINOLA WATCHES,
UNBELIEVABLE, THEY'RE SAVING
DETROIT.
AND I WANT TO THANK MY BROTHER,
AND BENNETT, I'M NOTHING WITHOUT
YOU.
>> THANK YOU FOR VOTING FOR US,
THANK YOU TO THE OTHER AMAZING
NOMINEES.
THIS IS AN AMAZING ROOM OF
FILMMAKERS.
EMBRACE OURSELVES AND LOVE EACH
OTHER.
THANK YOU ALL.
MY MOTHER AND FATHER, I LOVE
YOU, WE DID IT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> OKAY.
>> AND NOW, HERE ARE THE
NOMINEES FOR BEST ADAPTED
SCREENPLAY.
>> CORRECT.
>> "THE BALLAD OF
BUSTER SCRUGGS," WRITTEN BY
JOEL COEN AND ETHAN COEN.
"ALL GOLD CANYON" IS BASED ON A
STORY BY JACK LONDON.
"THE GAL WHO GOT RATTLED" IS
INSPIRED BY A STORY BY
STEWART EDWARD WHITE.
"BLACKKKLANSMAN," WRITTEN BY
CHARLIE WACHTEL AND
DAVID RABINOWITZ AND KEVIN
WILLMOTT AND SPIKE LEE.
BASED ON THE BOOK BY
RON STALLWORTH.
"CAN YOU EVER FORGIVE ME?"
SCREENPLAY BY NICOLE HOLOFCENER
AND JEFF WHITTY.
BASED ON THE BOOK BY LEE ISRAEL.
"IF BEALE STREET COULD TALK,"
WRITTEN FOR THE SCREEN BY
BARRY JENKINS.
BASED ON THE BOOK BY
JAMES BALDWIN.
"A STAR IS BORN," SCREENPLAY BY
ERIC ROTH AND BRADLEY COOPER AND
WILL FETTERS.
BASED ON THE 1954 SCREENPLAY BY
MOSS HART AND THE
1976 SCREENPLAY BY
JOHN GREGORY DUNNE AND
JOAN DIDION AND FRANK PIERSON.
BASED ON A STORY BY
WILLIAM WELLMAN AND
ROBERT CARSON.
>> OKAY.
AND THE OSCAR GOES TO --
>> OH!
CHARLIE WACHTEL,
DAVID RABINOWITZ, KEVIN WILLMOTT
AND SPIKE LEE.
>> IT'S THE FIRST NOMINATION FOR
CHARLIE, DAVID, AND KEVIN.
IT'S THE FIRST WIN FOR SPIKE
LEE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT.
I WANT TO THANK TANYA, THE WORD
TODAY IS IRONY.
THE DATE, THE 24th.
THE MONTH, FEBRUARY, WHICH ALSO
HAPPENS TO BE THE SHORTEST MONTH
OF THE YEAR.
WHICH ALSO HAPPENS TO BE BLACK
HISTORY MONTH.
THE YEAR, 2019.
THE YEAR, 1619.
HISTORY, HERSTORY.
1619, 2019.
400 YEARS, OUR ANCESTORS WERE
STOLEN FROM AFRICA AND ENSLAVED.
THEY WORKED THE LAND FROM
MORNING TO NIGHT.
MY GRANDMOTHERS, WHO LIVED 100
YEARS YOUNG, A COLLEGE GRADUATE
EVEN THOUGH HER MOTHER WAS A
SLAVE.
MY GRANDMOTHER, WHO SAVED 50
YEARS OF SOCIAL SECURITY CHECKS
TO PUT ME THROUGH COLLEGE.
SHE CALLED ME SPIKY POO.
SHE PUT ME THROUGH FILM SCHOOL.
NYU!
BEFORE THE WORLD TONIGHTS I GIVE
PRAISE TO MY ANCESTORS WHO BUILT
OUR COUNTRY, ALONG WITH THE
GENOCIDE OF OUR NATIVE PEOPLE.
WE ALL CONNECT WITH ANCESTORS,
TO REGAIN OUR HUMANITY.
IT WILL BE A POWERFUL MOMENT.
THE 2020 PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION
IS AROUND THE CORNER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
LET'S ALL MOBILIZE, LET'S ALL BE
ON THE RIGHT SIDE OF HISTORY.
MAKE THE MORAL CHOICE BETWEEN
LOVE VERSUS HATE.
LET'S DO THE RIGHT THING!
YOU KNOW I HAD TO GET THAT IN
THERE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> COMING UP, BARBRA STREISAND,
AND A LOOK AT THE FINAL TWO BEST
PICTURE NOMINEES,
"BLACKKKLANSMAN" AND
"GREEN BOOK."
THEN LATER, THE OSCARS FOR BEST
ACTOR AND ACTRESS.
AND JULIA ROBERTS PRESENTS BEST
PICTURE.
PLUS, CHADWICK BOSEMAN,
CONSTANCE WU, AND OSCAR WINNERS
SAM ROCKWELL AND ALLISON JANNEY.
e
and then to jail...
and then back to city college...
and then maybe
you'd pull yourself up...
(Google Assistant)
Your Lyft has arrived.
...everybody to do...
ah! ahhhh!
♪♪
I can't believe it.
That there's a lobster
in our hot tub?
Lobster: Oh, you guys.
There's a jet!
Oh...I needed this.
No, I can't believe how
easy it was
to save hundreds of dollars on
our car insurance with GEICO.
We could have been doing
this a long time ago.
So, you guys staying
at the hotel?
Yeah, we just got married.
Oh ho-ho! Congratulations!
Thank you.
Yeah, I'm afraid of
commitment...
and being boiled alive.
Oh, shoot.
Believe it.
GEICO could save you 15% or more
on car insurance.
That guy's the worst.
♪
Ray...we need an assist.
We style the stars behind the
scenes in Walmart Fashion.
Hey when's lunch?
Here it is...
♪♪
Show me the money!
(Google Assistant)
Here you go.
Ahh hah hah!
Show!
Does it make you feel good
just to say that?
Say it with me one time!
>>> TH
Everyone's got to listen to mom.
When it comes to reducing the
sugar in your family's diet,
Coke, Dr Pepper and Pepsi hear
you.
We're working together to do
just that.
Bringing you more great tasting
beverages with less sugar
or no sugar at all.
Smaller portion sizes,
clear calorie labels and
reminders to think balance.
Because we know mom wants what's
best.
More beverage choices, smaller
portions, less sugar.
BalanceUS.org
[ music playing ]
♪ Here Comes the Sun ♪
You, all of you.
How you live. What you love.
[ laughter ]
That's what inspired us
to create America's
most advanced Internet.
Internet that
puts you in charge.
[ chattering ]
That protects what's important.
That handles everything
[ group cheering ]
and reaches everywhere.
This is beyond WiFi.
This is xFi.
Simple. Easy. Awesome.
Xfinity.
The future of awesome.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO THE OSCARS
AT THE DOLBY THEATRE.
TONIGHT'S BAND IS LED BY MUSIC
DIRECTOR RICKEY MINOR.
AND NOW, PLEASE WELCOME TESSA
THOMPSON AND MICHAEL B. JORDAN.
♪
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THE SCORE SERVES AS A MUSICAL
THROUGHLINE THAT IMPACTS OUR
FEELINGS IN ANY GIVEN SCENE.
>> LIKE WHEN WE HEAR THIS OSCAR
WINNING SCORE --
♪
>> IT'S TIME TO TAKE MY -- OUT
OF THE WATER, BECAUSE SOMETHING
BAD IS PROBABLY GOING TO HAPPEN
IN THE OCEAN.
>> BUT YOU CAN SWIM, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, WHY WOULD YOU ASK THAT?
>> BECAUSE A LOT OF PEOPLE DON'T
KNOW THAT ABOUT US.
>> TOUCHE, TOUCHE.
HOW ABOUT THIS?
♪
>> WE KNOW PEOPLE ARE GOING TO
FALL IN LOVE BEFORE SOMETHING
ELSE BAD HAPPENS IN THE OCEAN.
A GREAT SCORE MOVES US AS AN
AUDIENCE.
>> WHILE REMINDING US THAT
REALLY BAD THINGS CAN HAPPEN IN
THE OCEAN.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
BEST ORIGINAL SCORE.
"BLACK PANTHER."
"BLACKKKLANSMAN."
"IF BEALE STREET COULD TALK."
"ISLE OF DOGS."
"MARY POPPINS RETURNS."
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO LUDWIG
GORANSSON AND "BLACK PANTHER."
>> THIS IS HIS FIRST OSCAR
NOMINATION.
>> THANK YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WOW.
THANK YOU, RYAN COOGLER.
RYAN, RYAN, WORKING WITH YOU HAS
BEEN AN INCREDIBLE HONOR.
I REMEMBER 12 YEARS AGO, WE WERE
SITTING IN OUR DORM AT UC,
WRITING YOUR FIRST, THE SCORE
FOR YOUR FIRST SHORT FILM.
12 YEARS LATER, WE'RE HERE, YOU
KNOW, CELEBRATING ONE OF THE
MOST IMPORTANT CINEMATIC MOMENTS
IN HISTORY.
I WANT TO SHARE THIS AWARD WITH
ALL OF THE INCREDIBLE AFRICAN
ARTISTS THAT I WORKED WITH ON
THE SCORE.
AND ALL THE CLASSICAL MUSICIANS
IN LONDON THAT RECORDED ON THE
SCORE.
AND EVERYONE ELSE, I WANT TO
SHARE THIS WITH MY MOM, DAD, AND
SISTER, THAT INSISTED I PLAY
GUITAR.
AND MY WIFE, I LOVE YOU SO MUCH,
THANK YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> PLEASE WELCOME CONSTANCE WU
AND CHADWICK BOSEMAN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> "OVER THE RAINBOW" AND THE
THEME FROM "SHAFT."
>> "MONA LISA" AND "LOSE
YOURSELF."
>> "THE WAY WE WERE" AND "MAN OR
MUPPET."
>> "STREETS OF PHILADELPHIA" AND
"REMEMBER ME."
THE ONLY THING THESE SONGS COULD
POSSIBLY HAVE IN COMMON IS THE
PLACE THEY'VE EARNED IN HISTORY
AS ACADEMY AWARD WINNERS.
TONIGHT, ANOTHER WILL JOIN THEIR
RANKS.
>> THIS YEAR'S NOMINATED SONGS
ARE AS ECLECTIC AND
STYLISTICALLY DISTINCTIVE AS THE
STORIES THEY TELL.
>> ONCE AGAIN, HERE ARE THIS
YEAR'S NOMINEES FOR BEST
ORIGINAL SONG.
>> "ALL THE STARS," FROM "BLACK
PANTHER."
"I'LL FIGHT," FROM "RBG."
"THE PLACE WHERE LOST THINGS
GO," FROM "MARY POPPINS
RETURNS."
"SHALLOW," FROM "A STAR IS
BORN."
"WHEN A COWBOY TRADES HIS SPURS
FOR WINGS," FROM "THE BALLAD OF
BUSTER SCRUGGS."
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES
TO "SHALLOW".
>> THIS IS THEIR FIRST OSCAR
NOMINATION, THE FIRST WIN AND
THIRD NOMINATION FOR LADY GAGA,
WHO IS ALSO NOMINATED IN THE
LEADING ACTRESS CATEGORY.
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
TO THE ACADEMY FOR THIS
WONDERFUL HONOR, THANK YOU TO
EVERY PERSON IN THE ROOM, TO
MARC, ANTHONY, ANDREW, MY
CO-WRITERS, I LOVE THEM SO MUCH.
TO MY SISTER, MY SOUL MATE, I
LOVE YOU.
MY FAMILY'S HERE.
I LOVE YOU, MOM AND DAD.
BRADLEY.
THERE'S NOT A SINGLE PERSON ON
THE PLANET THAT COULD HAVE SANG
THIS SONG WITH ME BUT YOU.
THANK YOU FOR BELIEVING IN US.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
AND IF YOU ARE AT HOME AND
YOU'RE SITTING ON YOUR COUCH,
AND YOU ARE WATCHING THIS RIGHT
NOW, ALL I HAVE TO SAY IS THAT
THIS IS HARD WORK.
I'VE WORKED HARD FOR A LONG
TIME, AND IT'S NOT ABOUT, YOU
KNOW, IT'S NOT ABOUT WINNING.
BUT WHAT IT'S ABOUT IS NOT
GIVING UP.
IF YOU HAVE A DREAM, FIGHT FOR
IT.
THERE'S A DISCIPLINE FOR
PASSION, AND IT'S NOT ABOUT HOW
MANY TIMES YOU GET REJECTED OR
YOU FALL DOWN, OR YOU'RE BEATEN
UP.
IT'S ABOUT HOW MANY TIMES YOU
STAND UP, AND ARE BRAVE, AND YOU
KEEP GOING.
THANK YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> ONLY BECAUSE YOU CAN'T REALLY
THANK YOURSELF, I THINK WHEN
YOU'RE IN THE ROOM WITH THIS
PERSON, YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO TOO
MUCH.
SHE ACTS, WRITES, SINGS THE
SONG.
LADY GAGA, WE SALUTE YOU FOR
THIS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> PLEASE WELCOME THE PRESIDENT
OF THE ACADEMY OF MOTION PICTURE
ARTS AND SCIENCES, JOHN BAILEY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THIS EVENING, WE CELEBRATE
THE ACHIEVEMENTS NOT ONLY OF OUR
AWARD WINNERS, BUT ALL
212 NOMINEES OF THE ACADEMY'S
CLASS OF 2018.
WE ALSO PAUSE TO HONOR ALL THOSE
ARTISTS WHO HAVE LEFT US SINCE
OUR LAST AWARDS CEREMONY, THE
MEN AND WOMEN WHOSE MOVIES HAVE
SO ENTERTAINED AND INSPIRED US.
ONLY A FEW OF THEM CAN BE
HIGHLIGHTED HERE.
BUT LET'S NOW GIVE TRIBUTE TO
ALL THEIR EXTRAORDINARY LIVES
AND WORKS IN THIS MUSIC OF JOHN
WILLIAMS, WITH THE LOS ANGELES
PHILHARMONIC CELEBRATING ITS
CENTENNIAL YEAR UNDER THE
DIRECTION OF MAESTRO GUSTAVO
DUDAMEL.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
[ APPLAUSE ]
DEAR TECH...
♪ ♪ ♪
LET'S TALK.
WE HAVE A PRETTY
GOOD RELATIONSHIP.
YOU'VE DONE A LOT OF
GOOD FOR THE WORLD.
BUT I FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE THE
POTENTIAL TO DO SO MUCH MORE.
ARE YOU WORKING FOR ALL OF US,
OR JUST A FEW OF US?
CAN WE BUILD AI WITHOUT BIAS?
AI THAT FIGHTS BIAS?
AI THAT HELPS US SEE
THE BIAS IN OURSELVES?
WE NEED TECH THAT HELPS
PEOPLE UNDERSTAND EACH OTHER.
THAT UNDERSTANDS MY BUSINESS.
♪ ♪ ♪
DEAR TECH...
LET'S CHAMPION DATA
RIGHTS AS HUMAN RIGHTS.
LET'S USE BLOCKCHAIN
TO HELP REDUCE POVERTY.
LET'S DEVELOP NEW SOLUTIONS WITH
THE HELP OF QUANTUM TECHNOLOGY.
LET'S SHOW GIRLS THAT STEM
ISN'T JUST A BOY'S CLUB.
LET'S MAKE A DIFFERENCE
IN PEOPLE'S LIVES.
LET'S DO IT ALL.
TOGETHER.
LET'S EXPECT MORE
FROM TECHNOLOGY.
LET'S PUT SMART TO WORK.
♪ ♪ ♪
♪♪
♪
Heeey!
Hey. Famished!
We style the stars behind the
scenes in Walmart Fashion.
You have brie?
I've talked on this phone
through the happiest times
of my life,
and through the saddest
times of my life.
But I never dreamed
in a thousand years
that it would save my life.
Boom!
I fell 22 feet,
completely shattered my pelvis,
in the middle of the woods.
I called my wife,
she thought I was jokin'.
I said, "Man, I'm not...
I'm not."
I was so lucky that day...
saved my life.
(VO)
There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best network
now always includes
Apple Music on us.
Starting at only $40.
Only on Verizon.
>>> IN NOVEMBER, THE ACADEMY
HELD THE GOVERNOR'S AWARDS.
HONORARY OSCARS WERE PRESENTED
TO ACTRESS CICELY TYSON,
COMPOSER LALO SCHIFRIN AND
PUBLICIST MARVIN LEVY.
THE THALBERG AWARD WENT TO
PRODUCERS KATHLEEN KENNEDY AND
FRANK MARSHALL.
KENNEDY IS THE FIRST WOMAN TO
RECEIVE THE THALBERG.
AND ON FEBRUARY 9th, DAVID
OYELOWO HOSTED THE ACADEMY'S
ANNUAL SCI-TECH AWARDS.
NINE SCIENTIFIC AND TECHNICAL
ACHIEVEMENTS REPRESENTED BY
27 INDIVIDUAL AWARD RECIPIENTS
WERE HONORED THAT NIGHT.
AND NOW, PLEASE WELCOME TWO-TIME
ACADEMY AWARD WINNER, BARBRA
STREISAND.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU.
WHEN I FIRST SAW
"BLACKKKLANSMAN," I WAS STUNNED
AND WAS VERY EXCITED, AND WAS
VERY MOVED.
IT HAD EVERYTHING A GREAT FILM
SHOULD HAVE.
IT WAS SO REAL, SO FUNNY, AND
YET SO HORRIFYING, BECAUSE IT
WAS BASED ON THE TRUTH.
AND TRUTH IS ESPECIALLY PRECIOUS
THESE DAYS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I HAD TO -- THANK YOU.
SO, I HAD TO TWEET ABOUT IT, YOU
KNOW, ABOUT HOW GOOD IT WAS.
AND THEN I GOT A LOVELY THANK
YOU FROM SPIKE HIMSELF.
THE CONVERSATION AFTER THAT WAS
VERY EASY, BECAUSE WE WERE BOTH
RAISED IN BROOKLYN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
AND, SPIKE, WE BOTH LOVE HATS.
SO, AFTER A LIFETIME OF BOLD,
GAMECHANGING WORK, HERE IS
SPIKE LEE'S MASTERPIECE, THE
STORY OF THE FIRST
AFRICAN-AMERICAN DETECTIVE IN
THE COLORADO SPRINGS POLICE
DEPARTMENT WHO JOINS FORCES WITH
HIS JEWISH COLLEAGUE TO
INFILTRATE THE KU KLUX KLAN.
NOW, THAT IS FUNNY ALREADY.
BUT IT'S AN UNFLINCHING LOOK AT
RACE RELATIONS IN AMERICA BACK
IN THE 1970s.
THAT WAS THEN, BUT IT'S JUST AS
RELEVANT TODAY.
>> THIS IS RON STALLWORTH.
I'M ANXIOUS TO MEET YOU.
>> I'M JUST HAPPY TO MEET A TRUE
WHITE AMERICAN.
>> THEY WANT TO MEET ME FIRST.
>> YOU PROBABLY SHOULDN'T GO TO
THAT MEETING.
>> YOU NEED TO WAKE UP.
>> DON'T THINK THAT I DON'T CARE
ABOUT MY PEOPLE!
♪
>> BLACK POWER!
>> WHITE POWER!
>> YOU'RE JEWISH, BROTHER.
>> WHY ARE YOU ACTING LIKE YOU
DON'T HAVE SKIN IN THE GAME?
>> THAT'S MY BUSINESS.
>> IT'S OUR BUSINESS.
♪
>> PLEASE WELCOME LAST YEAR'S
WINNERS FOR ACTRESS IN A
SUPPORTING ROLE AND ACTOR IN A
LEADING ROLE, ALLISON JANNEY AND
GARY OLDMAN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> YOU KNOW, YOU AND I COULDN'T
HAVE WON OSCARS FOR PORTRAYING
TWO MORE DIFFERENT PEOPLE.
>> THAT'S SO TRUE.
ONE OF US PLAYING A BRASH AND
CONTROVERSIAL LEADER, KNOWN FOR
LOVING WHISKY AND ALWAYS BEING
ENSHROUDED IN THAT TRADEMARK
CLOUD OF SMOKE.
>> YES.
AND THEN, OF COURSE, YOU PLAYED
CHURCHILL.
>> YES.
>> AND HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
PERFORMANCE BY AN ACTOR IN A
LEADING ROLE.
>> CHRISTIAN BALE, "VICE."
>> 3,000 INNOCENT PEOPLE BURNED
TO DEATH BY THOSE MONSTERS.
AND YET YOU OBJECT WHEN I REFUSE
TO KISS THOSE MONSTERS ON THE
CHEEK AND SAY PRETTY PLEASE.
YOU ANSWER ME THIS.
WHAT TERRORIST ATTACK WOULD YOU
HAVE LET GO FORWARD SO YOU
WOULDN'T SEEM LIKE A MEAN AND
NASTY FELLA?
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> BRADLEY COOPER, "A STAR IS
BORN."
>> CAN I TELL YOU A SECRET?
I THINK YOU MIGHT BE A
SONGWRITER.
DON'T WORRY, I WON'T TELL
ANYBODY.
BUT I'M NOT VERY GOOD AT KEEPING
SECRETS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WILLEM DAFOE, "AT ETERNITY'S
GATE."
>> I BELIEVE I HAVE A MENACING
SPIRIT AROUND ME.
AN INVISIBLE BEING.
I FEEL IT, I DON'T SEE IT.
HE SPEAKS TO ME, AND THREATENS
ME, AND ALL HE WANTS TO DO IS
PLUNGE A KNIFE INTO MY HEART.
I SAW HIM, AND I TRIED TO CUT
HIM OUT OF MYSELF.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> RAMI MALEK, "BOHEMIAN
RHAPSODY."
♪
♪ COME ON I DON'T WANT TO DIE
SOMETIMES WISH I NEVER HAD BEEN
BORN AT ALL ♪
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> VIGGO MORTENSEN, "GREEN
BOOK."
>> YOU SPEAK GERMAN, HUH?
>> THAT WAS RUSSIAN.
>> I WAS STATIONED IN GERMANY,
IN THE ARMY.
I COULD PICK UP A LITTLE BIT OF
WHAT YOU SAID.
WATCH OUT FOR THEM KRAUTS,
THEY'RE ALL SNEAKS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO RAMI
MALEK!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR RAMI MALEK.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> OH, MY GOD.
MY MOM IS IN HERE SOMEWHERE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
OH, I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, LADY.
MY FAMILY, THANK YOU FOR ALL OF
THIS.
YOU KNOW, MY DAD DIDN'T GET TO
SEE ME DO ANY OF THIS.
BUT I THINK HE'S LOOKING DOWN ON
ME RIGHT NOW.
SO, THIS IS A MONUMENTAL MOMENT.
ONE I'M SO APPRECIATIVE OF ALL
OF YOU, TO EVERYONE WHO HAS HAD
A HAND IN GETTING ME HERE.
TO THE ACADEMY, TO PEOPLE WHO
TOOK A CHANCE ON ME.
EVERY STEP OF THE WAY.
GRAHAM KING.
DENNIS O'SULLIVAN, EVERYONE AT
FOX.
AND NEW REGENCY.
I KNOW I WASN'T THE OBVIOUS
CHOICE, BUT I GUESS IT WORKED
OUT.
THANK YOU, QUEEN.
THANK YOU GUYS FOR BEING, FOR
ALLOWING ME TO BE THE TINIEST
PART OF YOUR PHENOMENAL,
EXTRAORDINARY LEGACY.
I AM FOREVER IN YOUR DEBT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
MY CREW, AND MY CAST.
I LOVE YOU.
YOU ARE MY EQUALS, MY BETTERS.
I COULD HAVE NEVER BEEN HERE
WITHOUT YOU.
I THINK ABOUT WHAT IT WOULD HAVE
BEEN LIKE TO TELL LITTLE BUBBA
RAMI THAT ONE DAY THIS MIGHT
HAPPEN TO HIM.
AND I THINK HIS CURLY-HAIRED
LITTLE MIND WOULD BE BLOWN.
HE WAS STRUGGLING WITH HIS
IDENTITY, TRYING TO FIGURE
HIMSELF OUT.
AND I THINK TO ANYONE STRUGGLING
WITH THEIRS, AND TRYING TO
DISCOVER THEIR VOICE, LISTEN, WE
MADE A FILM ABOUT A GAY MAN, AN
IMMIGRANT, WHO LIVED HIS LIFE
JUST UNAPOLOGETICALLY HIMSELF.
THE FACT THAT I'M CELEBRATING
HIM AND THIS STORY WITH YOU
TONIGHT IS PROOF THAT WE'RE
LONGING FOR STORIES LIKE THIS.
I AM THE SON OF IMMIGRANTS FROM
EGYPT, A FIRST-GENERATION
AMERICAN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
AND PART OF MY STORY IS BEING
WRITTEN RIGHT NOW.
AND I COULD NOT BE MORE GRATEFUL
TO EACH AND EVERY ONE OF YOU,
AND EVERYONE WHO BELIEVED IN ME
FOR THIS MOMENT.
IT'S SOMETHING I WILL TREASURE
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
LUCY, YOU'RE THE HEART OF THIS
FILM.
YOU ARE BEYOND IMMENSELY
TALENTED.
YOU HAVE CAPTURED MY HEART.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> COMING UP NEXT, A LOOK AT
BEST PICTURE NOMINEE "GREEN
BOOK," AND THE AWARD FOR BEST
ACTRESS.
WILL THE OSCAR GO TO YALITZA
APARACIO, GLENN CLOSE, OLIVIA
COLMAN, LADY GAGA, OR MELISSA
McCARTHY?
KEEP WATCHING TO FIND OUT.
[Background music]
"If we show emotwe're
called dramatic."
"If we want to play against
men, we're nuts."
"And if we dream of equal
opportunity, delusional."
"When we stand for something,
we're unhinged."
"When we're too good there's
something wrong with us."
"And if we get angry...
we're hysterical, irrational
or just being crazy."
"But, a women running a
marathon is crazy."
[ANNOUNCER]
"Officials tried to pull her
off the course"
"A woman boxing was crazy."
"A woman dunking, crazy."
"Coaching an NBA team, crazy."
"A woman competing in a hijab."
"Changing her sport."
"Landing a double cork 1080."
"Or winning 23 grand slams,
having a baby and then coming
back for more.
Crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy
and crazy."
[SFX]
Crowd cheering
"So if they want to call
you crazy, fine.
Show them what crazy can do."
[Background music]
It's only crazy until you do it.
Just do it.
[Background music]
Today, faster than ever,
the world is changing,
because opportunity is raging.
Mixed Reality changing
the world we see,
intelligence to build it like
we'd always hoped it would be.
But it's not really about
what technology can do,
it's about how it's used by you.
In the end, its just
a tool so bring it,
what's a hammer without
a person to swing it.
Your possibility is endless,
your limits are few.
So, here's the real question,
What will you do?
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, PLEASE
WELCOME AMANDLA STENBERG AND
CONGRESSMAN JOHN LEWIS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> THANK YOU.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> OUR FINAL NOMINEE FOR BEST
PICTURE IS A FILM ABOUT BIGOTRY,
FRIENDSHIP, AND GROWTH, BASED ON
THE STORY OF A WHITE MAN AND AN
AFRICAN-AMERICAN MAN ON A
JOURNEY THROUGH THE SEGREGATED
SOUTH.
>> I CAN BEAR WITNESS THAT THE
PORTRAIT PAINTED OF THAT TIME
AND PLACE IN OUR HISTORY IS VERY
REAL.
IT'S SEARED IN MY MEMORY, BLACK
MEN AND WOMEN, OUR BROTHERS AND
SISTERS, TREATED AS SECOND CLASS
CITIZENS, THREATENED FOR RAISING
THEIR FAMILIES OR EARNING A
LIVING, BEATEN AND SOMETIMES
KILLED FOR THE CRIME OF TRYING
TO LIVE A LIFE WITH DIGNITY.
OUR NATION BEARS THE SCARS OF
THAT TIME, AS DO I.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THE CHARACTERS IN "GREEN
BOOK" GRADUALLY TORE DOWN THE
WALLS BETWEEN THEM, TRANSFORMING
EACH OTHER IN THE PROCESS.
AS THIS FILM DEMONSTRATES, ANY
JOURNEY THAT OPENS SOMEONE'S
EYES AND SOFTENS THEIR HEART IS
ONE THAT IS WORTH TAKING.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> YOUNG OR OLD, I ENCOURAGE YOU
TO BE AN ACTIVE PARTICIPANT IN
THE JOURNEY.
THIS IS "GREEN BOOK."
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> HAVE YOU EVER DRIVEN
PROFESSIONALLY BEFORE?
>> I CAN DRIVE ANYTHING.
>> WHAT OTHER EXPERIENCE DO YOU
HAVE?
>> PUBLIC RELATIONS.
>> I'M ABOUT TO EMBARK ON A
CONCERT TOUR IN THE DEEP SOUTH.
>> YOU, IN THE DEEP SOUTH?
THERE WILL BE PROBLEMS.
GET YOUR HANDS OFF OF HIM, NOW!
>> DEAR DELORES, THE DISTANCE
BETWEEN US IS SO DIFFICULT.
>> IT TAKES COURAGE TO CHANGE
PEOPLE'S HEARTS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> PLEASE WELCOME ACADEMY AWARD
WINNERS FRANCES McDORMAND AND
SAM ROCKWELL.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> IT'S AN HONOR FOR US TO BE
BACK ONSTAGE.
FRANCES, DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING TO
ADD?
>> NO.
NO, NO, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
PERFORMANCE BY AN ACTRESS IN A
LEADING ROLE.
>> YALITZA APARICIO, "ROMA."
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> GLENN CLOSE, "THE WIFE."
>> WHAT WE WERE TALKING ABOUT
THE OTHER DAY?
>> YES?
>> I WANT TO SAY THAT WHAT YOU
IMPLIED ISN'T TRUE.
AND IF YOU MALIGN JOE'S TALENT
IN ANY WAY, I'LL TAKE YOU TO
COURT.
GOOD LUCK, NATHANIEL, I'M SURE
YOU'LL WRITE A FINE BOOK.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> OLIVIA COLMAN, "THE
FAVOURITE."
>> I HAVE BEEN WANTING TO GIVE
YOU SOMETHING FOR QUITE SOME
TIME NOW.
THE PERFECT OPPORTUNITY.
>> IT'S A MONSTROUS
EXTRAVAGANCE.
>> OH, I DID NOT KNOW THAT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> LADY GAGA, "A STAR IS BORN."
>> I WON'T DO THAT AGAIN.
I WON'T COME AND FIND YOU.
NEXT TIME, YOU CAN CLEAN UP YOUR
OWN MESS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> MELISSA McCARTHY, "CAN YOU
EVER FORGIVE ME?"
>> IT WASN'T MY WORK, WAS IT?
IF I HAD PUT IN MY WORK, I WOULD
HAVE BEEN OPENING MYSELF UP.
AND I'M TOO MUCH OF A COWARD TO
DO THAT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO OLIVIA
COLMAN.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR OLIVIA COLMAN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> I'M -- OH.
IT'S GENUINELY QUITE STRESSFUL.
THIS IS HILARIOUS.
I GOT AN OSCAR.
OKAY.