MANY YEARS.
DR. OZ: WHY DID YOU NOT LOSE
YOUR LEG?
>> IT HAD GANGRENE.
I WAS TAKEN TO THE BALTIMORE
SHOCK TRAUMA CENTER WHERE I HAD
HYPERBARIC TREATMENTS.
DR. OZ: CUTTING-EDGE BUT THEN.
>> IT WAS CUTTING-EDGE.
IT WAS ALSO PAINFUL.
BUT IT HELPED TO SAVE ME.
DR. OZ: YOU STILL HAVE BULLETS
IN YOUR BODY.
>> I STILL CARRY TWO BULLETS.
DR. OZ: GOING THROUGH ALL OF
THAT AND REALIZING THE MAGNITUDE
OF THE TRAGEDY AT JONESTOWN MUST
HAVE BEEN VERY CHALLENGING.
>> IT WAS.
I LOST MY MENTOR, THE MAN I
WORKED FOR WHO I BELIEVED WAS
DOING THE RIGHT THING TRYING TO
SAVE HIS CONSTITUENTS.
900 PEOPLE'S LIVES WERE LOST,
MANY OF WHOM I INTERACTED WITH
OVER THE COURSE OF TWO DAYS.
THERE WERE SOME PEOPLE'S LIVES
WE WERE ABLE TO SAVE.
BUT IT WAS HORRIFIC ON SO MANY
LEVELS BECAUSE OUR LOCAL
GOVERNMENTS DID NOT RESPOND
PROPERLY TO CAUSE THERE WAS ALL
THIS ABUSE GOING ON.
OUR STATE DEPARTMENT DID NOT
OPERATE AS IT SHOULD IN TERMS OF
PROTECTING AMERICAN CITIZENS
ABROAD.
IT WAS A VERY SAD TALE ALL THE
WAY AROUND.
DR. OZ: WHAT MAKES ME ADMIRE YOU
SO MUCH.
YOU GET THROUGH THAT.
SHE HAS A WONDERFUL BOOK WHERE
SHE TALKS ABOUT THESE THINGS
VERY OPENLY.
TWO MISCARRIAGES.
YOU LOST A WONDERFUL HUSBAND
WHILE YOU WERE PREGNANT WITH HER
SECOND CHILD.
YOU CANNOT PUT THE STORIES
TOGETHER.
HOW DO YOU BEGIN TO STAY STRONG
THROUGH THAT?
HOW DO YOU FIND MEANING INSTEAD
OF ALL OF THIS LOSS?
>> THE BOOK IS REALLY ABOUT
RESILIENCE.
WE DON'T KNOW HOW RESILIENT WE
REALLY ARE.
BUT IF WE SURROUND OURSELVES
WITH FAMILY, FRIENDS, AND FAITH,
WE CAN OVERCOME VIRTUALLY
ANYTHING.
[APPLAUSE]
>> THERE WERE DAYS I DID NOT
WANT TO GET UP.
[APPLAUSE]
>> WHEN I DID NOT WANT TO GET UP
ON THOSE DAYS, I WOULD GIVE
MYSELF PERMISSION TO STAY IN
BED.
BUT THEN I ALSO DEMANDED I GET
UP THE NEXT DAY.
AND SO, IT IS A COMBINATION OF
BEING KIND TO YOURSELF BUT ALSO
BEING SOMEWHAT RESOLUTE AND
DEMANDING OF YOURSELF, TOO.
DR. OZ: FAMILY, FAITH, AND
FRIENDS.
I WOULD ADD FOOD AND FUN.
>> THAT IS GOOD, TOO.
DR. OZ: THANK YOU FOR DEDICATING
YOUR LIFE TO SERVICE.
HER BOOK IS AVAILABLE NOW.
ENJOY IT.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
When you feed yourself
some oats,
the oats feed your body fiber.
Fiber helps keep things
moving through your system.
Which is great.
Because when you're good
to your system,
it'll be good to you.
>> I WOULD LIKE TO RETURN THIS.
>> IN PAST INVESTIGATIONS, WE
REVEALED MAJOR RETAILERS
RESTOCKING USED UNDERWEAR AS IF
NEW.
WE BOUGHT THEM, REMOVED THE TAX,
SECRETLY MARKED THEM, AND
RETURNED THEM.
SURE ENOUGH, RIGHT BACK ON THE
SALES FLOOR THEY WENT.
IN ANOTHER INVESTIGATION, WE
DETECTED FECAL MATTER AND
BACTERIA, EVEN BLOOD, ON
STORE-BOUGHT UNDERWEAR.
NOW I AM GOING UNDERCOVER WITH
HIDDEN CAMERAS TO BUY A VARIETY
OF UNDERWEAR TO FIND OUT IF
CONTAMINATED PRODUCTS ARE STILL
BEING SOLD.
I AM VISITING A NUMBER OF
NATIONAL RETAIL CHAINS, BOTH
UPSCALE MERCHANTS AND DISCOUNT
VENDORS.
CONSIDERING WHAT WE FOUND ON
PREVIOUS INVESTIGATIONS, I WAS
CURIOUS ABOUT THE RETURN POLICY
FOR UNDERWEAR.
>> YOU CANNOT BRING THEM BACK?
>> PUT IN THE SAME STORE, I GOT
A DIFFERENT ANSWER AT THE
REGISTER.
>> YOU CAN BRING IT BACK.
>> AT ANOTHER RETAILER, THE SAME
CONFLICTING RETURN POLICY.
>> NO RETURNS?
>> STILL, EVERYONE ASSURED ME IF
UNDERWEAR WERE RETURNED, IT
WOULD NOT GO BACK OUT ON THE
STORE SHELVES.
>> IF THE UNDERWEAR COMES BACK
--
>> YOU DO WHAT?
>> DAMAGE IT.
>> YOU DON'T PUT IT BACK OUT?
>> BUT THE EVIDENCE WILL SPEAK
FOR ITSELF.
I'M ASKING OUR TEAM TO CATALOG
AND SHIP A NUMBER OF SAMPLES TO
THE LABORATORY FOR TESTING.
COULD THE UNDERWEAR YOU ARE
BUYING AS NEW BE DIRTY?
DR. OZ: THE RESULTS OF OUR
UNDERCOVER INVESTIGATION INTO
DIRTY DRAWERS IS IN.
WE ARE ABOUT TO FIND OUT IF
RETAILERS ARE STILL FILLING --
SELLING FILTHY UNDERWEAR.
ARE YOU SHAKING YOUR HEAD
WONDERING, REALLY?
EVERYONE IS MOANING.
LOOK AT THE SURPRISING STATS
FROM MY ONLINE POLL.
ALMOST 20% SAY THEY HAVE
RETURNED UNDERWEAR BEFORE.
THAT IS A LOT OF PEOPLE.
MORE THAN HALF SAY THEY EVEN
WORE UNDERWEAR BEFORE WASHING
THEM.
WE LOOKED AT THE STORE POLICIES
AND FOUNDER IS NO GUARANTEE THAT
THE UNDERWEAR YOU ARE BUYING IS
CLEAN.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN RETURNED AND
PUT BACK.
MY TEAM TESTED UNDERWEAR FOR
MULTIPLE RETAILERS.
WE ASKED IN VIEWERS TO BRING IN
SHOPPING SAMPLES.
WHAT WE FOUND IS PROBABLY NOT
WHAT YOU WERE EXPECTING.
NINE OUT OF THE 11 SAMPLES WE
TESTED HAD SOME SORT OF
CONTAMINATION.
NINE OUT OF 11.
ACCORDING TO OUR SAMPLES, WE
WERE SURPRISED TO FIND THEY HAVE
NOT BEEN WORN.
THAT IS GOOD NEWS.
SOMEHOW, THEY GOT CONTAMINATED
ALONG THE WAY WITHOUT HAVING
BEEN WORN.
SHE IS HERE TO HELP US ANALYZE
THE RESULTS.
HOW DO YOU THINK THEY GOT
CONTAMINATED IF NOT FROM PEOPLE
WEARING THEM?
>> IF NOT FROM PEOPLE WEARING
THEM, IT CAN BE THAT PEOPLE
TOUCH IT.
THESE THINGS COME IN BINS.
THOSE ARE PROBABLY NOT CLEANED.
THEY ARE SHIPPED FROM OTHER
COUNTRIES.
PLACES.
SOME OF US DO NOT WASH OUR
HANDS.
I SAW A WOMAN THE OTHER DAY WHO
PICKED UP A BINKY AND PUT IT
BACK IN HER KID'S MATH.
IN SOME RETAIL STORES, THERE ARE
BINS AND BINS OF UNDERWEAR.
YOU SEE EVERYBODY GOING THROUGH
IT.
DR. OZ: WERE YOU TOLD BY YOUR
MOM TO WASH YOUR UNDERWEAR
BEFORE YOU WORE IT?
>> OH, YES.
DR. OZ: HOW MANY OF YOU WERE
TOLD THAT?
THANKFULLY, ALMOST ALL OF THE
WOMEN HEARD THIS.
THROUGH THE SURVEY, I LEARNED
ONLY HALF OF US ARE DOING IT.
KIMBERLY IS TAKING A DEEP DIVE
INTO WHAT WE FOUND.
DID YOUR MOM TELL YOU TO WASH
HER UNDERWEAR?
>> YES.
DR. OZ: WE WANT TO SEE IF IT IS
CLEAN.
THERE WE ARE.
THERE IS SOME UNDERWEAR.
YOU BROUGHT YOUR UNDERWEAR.
THIS IS WHAT WE FOUND.
ARE YOU READY TO HEAR THIS?
>> NO.
[LAUGHTER]
DR. OZ: WE ACTUALLY FOUND
COLIFORM IN THE UNDERWEAR.
I WILL SHOW YOU A PICTURE.
ALMOST ALL OF THE SAMPLES TESTED
POSITIVE FOR THE MAXIMUM LEVELS
OF THIS BACTERIA, WHICH IS
SURPRISING TO ME.
WHAT CAN IT DO TO YOU?
>> IT INCLUDES BACTERIA LIKE E.
COLI.
BY THE WAY, ALL OF THOSE
BACTERIA COME FROM THE BOWEL.
HE COMES FROM FECES, HUMAN
FECES.
IF YOU GET CONTAMINATED WITH IT,
NOT ONLY CAN YOU GET FRAGILE --
VAGINAL DISCHARGE.
YOU CAN GET DIARRHEA, A URINARY
TRACT INFECTION.
DR. OZ: HOW DOES THAT MAKE YOU
FEEL?
>> NOT GOOD.
>> YOU REALLY HAVE TO WASH
EVERYTHING BEFORE YOU WEAR IT.
DR. OZ: IT SORT OF MAKES SENSE.
PEOPLE DON'T CLEAN THEMSELVES
BEFORE THEY PICK IT UP AND PUT
IT DOWN.
THESE ARE BACTERIA UBIQUITOUSLY
AROUND.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BUY PRODUCTS
THAT HAVE IT AND CAN GIVE IT TO
YOU.
I DON'T WANT TO MESS UP THE
STAGE.
NEXT IS KENNEDY.
KENNEDY BROUGHT AS AN UNDERWEAR
SAMPLE AS WELL.
I DON'T WANT TO CONTAMINATE
THIS.
IT IS A NICE COLOR, BY THE WAY.
>> I LIKE THAT.
>> THANK YOU.
DR. OZ: MOST PEOPLE WOULD NOT BE
ABLE TO TELL THEY ARE
COLOR-COORDINATED, BUT YOU KNOW.
IN YOUR SAMPLE, WE DETECTED A
SMALL AMOUNT OF FUNGUS.
>> WHAT?
DR. OZ: FUNGUS IS DIFFERENT FROM
BACTERIA.
THIS IS A CONCERN EVEN THOUGH IT
IS A SMALL AMOUNT.
>> IT IS A CONCERN.
THERE IS FUNGUS AMONG US, AS I
ALWAYS SAY.
YOU CAN GET A USED INFECTION.
YOU CAN BE ON YOUR SKIN.
ON THE VULVA.
I'M CONCERNED THAT HIS BODILY
FLUID.
THINK ABOUT SOMEBODY THAT HAS A
TAMPON.
SOMETIMES ON THE STRING, YOU CAN
SEE A LITTLE BIT OF BLOOD.
THAT IS ALSO ON THE PANTY.
EAST AND FUNGUS?
NO.
WE ARE TALKING ABOUT HIV AND
HEPATITIS.
DR. OZ: I AM NOT TRYING TO PANIC
YOU.
HIGHLY UNLIKELY YOU WILL GET HIV
.
>> YOU ARE NOT SAFE FROM
ANYTHING.
YOU HAVE TO BE CAUTIOUS IN
EVERYTHING YOU DO, BUY, SAY.
IT IS CRAZY.
DR. OZ: YOU ARE SAFE IF YOU WASH
IT.
>> IF YOU WASH IT.
DR. OZ: OR SO IT SEEMS.
FIND OUT HOW THESE UNDERWEAR CAN
MAKE YOU SICK EVEN IF YOU WASH
THEM BEFORE WEARING THEM.
STICK AROUND.
[APPLAUSE]
Never ending is now even better
at Olive Garden.
All new Never Ending Stuffed
Pastas starting at $12.99.
Pick your favorite stuffed
pasta, sauce and topping.
It's all never ending.
All new
Never Ending Stuffed Pastas.
Only for a limited time,
at Olive Garden.
New Year's resolutions are hard.
But a New Year's deal
on the best entertainment
and the quickest
way to find it?
The Crown.
Easy.
Getting the kids to
school on time? Hard.
But getting the
most reliable Internet
so you can stream
while you frost?
Easy.
It's the Xfinity
New Year New Deal.
And it's simple,
easy, awesome.
Get this deal on
TV, Internet and Voice
for $79.99 a
month for 2 years
with DVR free for a year.
And ask about Netflix,
Prime Video and Youtube
in 4K ultra HD.
Click, call or visit us today.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE ARE BACK WITH OUR
UNDERCOVER UNDERWEAR
INVESTIGATION.
DR. MINAYA IS BACK.
NINE OUT OF 11 SAMPLES WERE
CONTAMINATED WITH BACTERIA.
ACCORDING TO THE SURVEY, LESS
THAN HALF OF US WASH THEM BEFORE
WE WEAR THEM.
EVEN IF YOU WASH THEM, WE
UNCOVERED A SURPRISING WAY THAT
YOUR SHOPPING STYLE STILL MAKE
YOU SICK.
LOOK AT WHAT HOUR UNDER CAMERA
--UNDERCOVER CAMERAS CAUGHT.
>> AS WE ARE WATCHING THIS
VIDEO, THE WOMAN IS PUTTING ALL
OF THE GARMENTS TOGETHER.
EVEN IF YOU HAD A CONTAMINATED
UNDERWEAR OF ANY SORT, NOW YOUR
SWEATER IS IN THERE.
A SWEATER YOU MIGHT NOT WASH
BECAUSE YOU HAVE DINNER PLANS
LATER ON.
THAT MEANS IT WILL GO ON YOUR
LIPS.
YOU WILL LIFT YOUR LIPS, RIGHT?
THINK ABOUT ALL OF THOSE THINGS.
SOMETIMES IT IS SO SCARY.
WATCHING THAT VIDEO DEMONSTRATES
WHAT WE WERE TALKING ABOUT.
DR. OZ: LET'S SAY YOU ARE
SHOPPING.
THIS IS THE UNDERWEAR.
THIS IS THE COLIFORM OR FUNGUS.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO HAVE MUCH.
YOU TAKE IT OUT AND PUT IT IN
THE BACK.
EVEN IF THERE WAS NO BACTERIA,
YOU PUT IT ON THE SURFACE.
THE SURFACE, YOU MAY HAVE BOUGHT
-- SOMEONE MAY HAVE BOUGHT WHOLE
TREAT THE LASH POULTRY OR
SOMETHING YOU DON'T KNOW ABOUT.
THAT GETS PUT IN YOUR REGULAR
BAG THAT YOU ARE CARRYING
AROUND.
YOU HAVE YOUR BEAUTIFUL SHIRT OR
SWEATER YOU SPOKE ABOUT.
SEE THE LITTLE SPECKS?
YOUR UNDERWEAR CONTAMINATED
EVERYTHING ELSE IN THE BAG.
AND MADE IT BAD FOR THE NEXT
PERSON.
THIS IS WHAT WE ARE TALKING
ABOUT.
YOU HAVE TO BE HYPER CAREFUL
ABOUT HOW YOU TREAT THE
UNDERWEAR.
WE REACHED OUT TO THE AMERICAN
APPAREL AND FOOTWEAR
ASSOCIATION.
THEY DID NOT RESPOND WITH
COMMENT BEFORE THE TAPING OF THE
SHOW.
I HAVE SOME RECOMMENDATIONS.
WHEN YOU BUY IT, TRY TO WRAP IT
SEPARATELY SO YOU WILL NOT PUT
IT NEXT TO SOMETHING YOU WILL BE
ROLLING YOUR MOUTH THROUGH.
YOU HAVE TIPS ON HOW TO WASH
THAT WILL COME IN HANDY.
>> THE FIRST THING IS WASHING
MACHINE AND HOT WATER.
REMEMBER THAT THESE THINGS COME
FROM DIFFERENT PLACES.
THEY CAN BE IN FORMALDEHYDE THAT
CAN GIVE YOU A RASH.
I WAS A WASH THEM RIGHT AWAY.
THAT INCLUDES ALL OF YOUR
GARMENTS.
PLEASE USE HOT WATER.
ADD A LITTLE VINEGAR.
IT DOES KILL BACTERIA.
DO NOT USE BLEACH.
THAT IS AN IRRITANT TO THE VULVA
SO PLEASE DON'T USE THAT.
DR. OZ: YOU CONTROL YOUR
DESTINY.
DON'T BE WORRIED ABOUT IT.
FIX THE PROBLEM.
TELL YOUR FRIENDS ABOUT IT.
IT MAKES US ALL HEALTHIER.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: NEXT, A CUTTING-EDGE
EXPERIMENT TO FIND OUT IF THESE
WORK.
ARE THEY REALLY MOISTURIZING?
The best internet meets the best
things to do on the internet
when you switch to Fios, the
100% fiber-optic network.
And right now is your last
chance to get a year
of Amazon Prime and an Amazon
Echo on us when you switch.
Already have Prime? We'll
cover another year.
It's all yours when you sign up
for Fios Gigabit Connection,
plus TV, plus phone, all with a
2-year price guarantee,
all for just $79.99 per month
with a 2-year agreement.
With Fios and Prime, you can
stream Prime Originals in 4K,
get free games with
Twitch Prime,
and get fast, free shipping on
over one hundred million items.
Now is your last chance
to get a year
of Prime and an
Amazon Echo on us,
plus the fastest internet
available, TV, and phone
for just $79.99 per month
with a 2-year price guarantee
and a 2-year agreement.
Only need internet?
This is also your last chance
to get a $50 Amazon gift card
when you switch to Fios internet
for $39.99 per month.
Hurry, these offers
end January 30th.
100% fiber-optic network.
100% phenomenal.
Go to getfios.com today.
Never ending is now even better
at Olive Garden.
All new Never Ending Stuffed
Pastas starting at $12.99.
Pick your favorite stuffed
pasta, sauce and topping.
It's all never ending.
All new
Never Ending Stuffed Pastas.
Only for a limited time,
at Olive Garden.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE ARE INVESTIGATING THE
SKINCARE ITEM WE HAVE BEEN
FOLLOWING SINCE BEFORE IT BECAME
A TREND.
MY DAUGHTER TURNED ME ON TO
THEM.
SHE IS A DEVOTED FAN.
THERE ARE THOUSANDS OF THEM.
SOME WITH FUNNY FACES.
SOME A LITTLE SCARY.
LOOK AT THAT ONE.
THEY PROMISE TO CLEAN AND
TIGHTEN THE PORES, TO LOCK IN
ALL OF THAT MOISTURE SO IT
CANNOT GO ANYWHERE.
YOU WANT THAT MOISTURE.
IT IS GOOD, IDEALLY.
AND IT PROMISES TO MAKE YOU
GLOW, LIGHT UP, WHICH IS WHAT
MANY FOLKS WANT.
FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER, WE TEST
THESE SHEET MASKS WITH
CUTTING-EDGE TECHNOLOGY TO FIND
OUT WHAT THEY ARE DOING TO YOUR
SKIN.
ARE THEY DOING ANYTHING AT ALL?
HERE TO BREAK IT DOWN FOR US IS
DERMATOLOGIST DR. JEANINE
DOWNIE.
WHY ARE THERE SO MANY ON THE
MARKET?
>> IT IS A LITTLE BIT OF LUXURY.
YOU LAY DOWN AND PUT IT ON YOUR
FACE.
YOU SOAK ALL THE GOOD STUFF IN.
YOU CAN DESTRESS YOU SO PEOPLE
LOVE IT.
THEY ARE FOUND EVERYWHERE.
THEY CAN ANTI-AGE YOU AND
REHYDRATE YOU.
IT IS A SIMPLE THING.
YOU TAKE IT AND TOSS IT WHEN YOU
ARE DONE.
DR. OZ: LET'S TALK ABOUT WHAT IS
IN THESE.
THE INGREDIENTS MAKE A BIG
DIFFERENCE.
THEY FEEL GOOD TO ME.
I DO USE MASKS.
I'M NOT SURE WHAT IS IN THEM.
YOU LOOKED INTO THIS.
>> THEY HAVE GLYCOL.
THAT IS A HUMECTANT.
THAT DRAWS MOISTURE INTO YOUR
SKIN.
THEY HAVE HIGHER LAW ON IT --
HYOLURONIC ACID.
THEY ARE POPULAR BECAUSE THEY
HAVE ACTIVE INGREDIENTS THAT
THEORETICALLY SHOULD WORK WELL
DEPENDING ON WHAT LEVELS AND
QUANTITIES THEY ARE IN.
DR. OZ: I HAVE SEEN THAT BUT I
HAVE SEEN UGLY REPORTS ABOUT A
DIFFERENT REALITY WITH THESE.
THESE MASKS ARE BEING PACKAGED
WITH BARE HANDS.
WHATEVER IS ON YOUR HANDS IS ON
THAT MASK.
THAT IS WHAT PEOPLE ARE PUTTING
ON THEIR FACE.
THAT IS IN A PRIVATE HOME.
NOT ANY KIND OF HYGIENE RULES.
SOMEONE EVEN GOT A HAIR STUCK
INSIDE THE PLASTIC.
A LOT OF THESE ARE PACKAGED
OVERSEAS.
IS ANYONE TESTING TO MAKE SURE
THEY ARE SAFE?
>> BASICALLY, THEY ARE A
COSMETIC THAT HAS A
PHARMACEUTICAL GRADE OF
ACTIVITY.
THEY ARE NOT REGULATED BY THE
FDA.