SEASON 10?
>> YEAH!
>> I LOVE YOU, DR. OZ.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: TODAY, WE ARE
INVESTIGATING ALL DAY FAST FOOD
BREAKFASTS BECAUSE YOUR FAVORITE
CHOICE IS NOW AVAILABLE ANYTIME
AND MAY BE THE START OF THE NEW
BREAKFAST WARS AMONGST THE FAST
FOOD BRANDS WITH ONE EVEN
QUESTIONING IF IT'S COMPETITORS
ARE SERVING REAL EGGS AT ALL.
BACK IN THE DAY, IF YOU TRIED TO
ORDER BREAKFAST AT 10:31 A.M.,
YOU WERE OUT OF LUCK.
BUT TODAY, MORE CHAINS ARE
OFFERING EGG SANDWICHES,
HASHBROWNS, AND COFFEE ALL DAY
LONG.
WE ARE IN A FAST FOOD BREAKFAST
BOOM.
>> IT IS JUST A CHOICE.
YOU CAN HAVE IT WHENEVER YOU
WANT.
>> EVEN THOUGH IT IS 5:30 P.M.,
I STILL WANT AND AND FAMILY --AN
EGG SANDWICH.
DR. OZ: IT IS NOT JUST BURGER
JOINTS.
TACO AND COFFEE CHAINS ARE ALSO
WAKING UP TO THE IDEA OF CASHING
IN ON BREAKFAST SANDWICHES AND
WRAPS.
BUT RECENT HEADLINES ARE RAISING
QUESTIONS.
OUR THE EGGS IN YOUR FAST FOOD
SANDWICH REAL?
PANERA, WHICH ONLY USES 100%
REAL EGGS, IS PETITIONING THE
FDA TO ESTABLISH A CLEAR
DEFINITION OF THE TERM "EGG."
A QUICK LOOK AT OTHER CHAIN
RESTAURANT WEBSITES, AND YOU
WILL SEE A LOT OF VERY
PROCESSED-SOUNDING INGREDIENTS
IN EGG SANDWICHES.
MODIFIED FOOD STARCH, SODIUM
PHOSPHATE, POWDERED CELLULOSE,
AND XANTHAN GUM.
WHAT IS GUM DOING IN YOUR
EGGS?
TODAY, WE ARE SERVING UP THE
TRUTH ABOUT YOUR ALL-DAY
BREAKFAST FOODS.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: INVESTIGATOR IS HERE TO
HELP US INVESTIGATE.
WHY IS IT FAST FOOD MEALS HAVE
BECOME SO POPULAR?
>> AMERICANS WANT WHAT THEY
WANT, AND THIS FOOD IS PRETTY
GOOD.
THE PERFECT TRIFECTA OF SALT,
SUGAR FAT.
THERE ARE SO MANY MORE OPTIONS
NOW.
BEFORE, THERE WERE ONLY A
HANDFUL OF PLACES THAT OFFERED
BREAKFAST.
NOW THERE ARE SOME THE THINGS
YOU CAN GET.
THERE IS ONE THING.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT IS IN YOUR
BREAKFAST WHEN YOU GRAB AND GO.
DR. OZ: LET'S START WITH THE
MOST POPULAR ITEM ON THE MENU,
THE BREAKFAST SANDWICH.
LET'S START WITH THE EGGS.
ONE OF THE BIG BRANDS WENT TO
THE FDA INSISTING THEY DEFINE
WHAT AN EGG IS.
WHAT GIVES?
>> THIS IS ALL THAT BRAND
INTEGRITY.
THEY SAY WE USE 100% REAL EGGS
AND LOOK TO THE FDA FOR
GUIDELINES.
THERE IS NO CLEAR GUIDELINE ON
WHAT AN EGG IS.
SOME OF THEIR COMPETITORS ARE
USING EGGS WITH ADDITIVES.
THEY ARE SAYING WE NEED YOU TO
SET THE STANDARD.
DR. OZ: EGGS ARE READY-MADE.
YOU BREAK THE SHOW AND YOU HAVE
THE EGG.
>> THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
THIS IS REALLY ABOUT SHELFLIFE.
WHEN YOU GO TO A FAST FOOD
RESTAURANT, YOU WANT YOUR FOOD
BEFORE YOU FINISH PAYING.
TO DO THAT, THEY ADD TONS OF
ADDITIVES TO MAKE SURE IT CAN
LAST LONGER.
THEY COOK IT UP AND REHEAT IT
WHEN IT IS READY TO GO.
DR. OZ: THE FAST FOOD BREAKFAST
MAY NOT BE AS FRESH AS YOU
THINK.
WHEN FAST FOOD MOVED TO THE ALL
DAY PLAN, IT MAKES US WONDER, IS
IT ALWAYS FRESH MADE, READY TO
ORDER, OR IS IT SITTING AROUND
FOR A WHILE?
>> THE TRUTH IS YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE GETTING.
DR. OZ: WE FOUND UP BREAKFAST
SANDWICHES ARE SOMETIMES MADE
FROM LIQUID EGGS.
I GET THAT THE INSIDE OF AN EGG
IS LIQUIDY, BUT WHAT IS THIS?
>> STARTING IN 2009, PEOPLE
CONSUME 76 BILLION EGGS.
30% OF THIS WAS EGG PRODUCTS.
IT CAN BE LIQUID EGGS, FROZEN,
OR DRIED.
EGG PRODUCT IS ACTUALLY AN EGG
THAT IS CRACKED AND MIXED WITH
SOMETHING ELSE.
THEY DO THIS FOR SHELFLIFE.
IT ALLOWS IT TO LAST LONGER.
DR. OZ: IF I GO TO A FAST FOOD
RESTAURANT AND BY AN EGG, HOW DO
I KNOW IF IT IS IN A PRODUCT OR
IF THEY BROKEN EGG?
>> IF IT IS FOLDED LIKE THIS,
THAT MEANS IT HAS STARCH AND
LIKELY OTHER ADDITIVES IN IT.
DR. OZ: LOOK HOW IT IS FOLDED?
>> IT IS CUTE, BUT HAS OTHER
STUFF IN IT.
DR. OZ: LIKE A PIECE OF PAPER.
>> A DELICIOUS PIECE OF PAPER.
DR. OZ: YOU HAVE A HACK TO
GUARANTEE WE CAN GET A FRESH
EGG.
WHAT DO YOU ORDER?
>> YOU HAVE TO ASKED TO SUB
OUT FOR A ROUND EGG.
THEY WILL TAKE A FRESH EGG,
CRACK IT OPEN, PUT IT IN A
CIRCULAR RING, AND COOK IT RIGHT
THERE FOR YOU.
DR. OZ: IT SEEMS EFFICIENT.
>> YOU HAVE TO MAKE SURE YOU ARE
INVESTING IN GETTING THE
HEALTHIEST THING YOU CAN FOR
YOUR BODY.
DR. OZ: SUBBED ROUND EGG.
THAT IS HOW YOU KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
GETTING.
NEXT, WE INVESTIGATED THE MEAT
OF THE BREAKFAST SANDWICH.
WE INVITED THIS BUTCHER.
HE KNOWS GOOD MEAT.
ALL BREAKFAST SANDWICHES CAN BE
ORDERED WITH OR WITHOUT MEAT.
>> NOTHING SAYS NEW YORK
BREAKFAST LIKE A BACON, EGG, AND
CHEESE IN MY OPINION.
TO BRING ALL THOSE FLAVORS FROM
THE RUNNY EGG AND CHEESE, YOU
HAVE TO ADD MEAT.
TYPICALLY BACON OR SAUSAGE.
DR. OZ: WE HAVE BACON, SAUSAGE
PATTIES.
CANADIAN BACON AS WELL.
YOU HAVE TASTED THEM ALL.
YOU HAVE THE DISCRIMINATING
PALATE OF A BUTCHER.
HOW WE UNDERSTAND HOW YOU CREATE
THESE.
>> WHERE STARTING WITH THE
SAUSAGE PATTY.
FROM A BUTCHER'S PERSPECTIVE,
THIS IS A COMBINATION OF GROUND
PORK.
DR. OZ: HOW ABOUT BACON?
>> BACON I AM A FAN OF.
IT TENDS TO BE ELASTIC AND NOT
VERY HAPPY.
KIND OF SAD.
IF THIS WAS COMING OUT OF MY
SHOP, I WOULD HAVE A THICKER CUT
AND NICER QUALITY.
DR. OZ: IT WOULD NOT BEND.
>> IT WOULD NOT BEND AND IT
WOULD SMELL NICER.
DR. OZ: BUTCHER SNOB.
HOW ABOUT CANADIAN BACON?
>> CANADIAN BACON IS THE LEANEST
CUTS.
IT ALSO HAS A RUBBERY
CONSISTENCY.
TYPICALLY PORK LOIN IS WHERE
THIS IS COMING FROM.
DR. OZ: SAUSAGE, WE DON'T KNOW
WHERE THAT CAME FROM ON THE PIG.
BACON COMES FROM THE PORK BELLY.
THE LOIN IS THIS AREA HERE,
WHERE THE CANADIAN BACON COMES
FROM.
HAM IS FROM HERE AND HERE.
>> SAUSAGE CAN BE A COMBINATION
OF ALL OF THESE CUTS.
DR. OZ: IT COULD BE ANYTHING.
>> CORRECT.
NOT FROM ME.
>> DISCLAIMER.
DR. OZ: THANK YOU FOR YOUR
EXPERTISE.
THE NEXT THING WE LOOKED AT WAS
WHETHER ORDERING A BREAKFAST
SANDWICHES A HEALTHY CHOICE TO
MAKE LATER IN THE DAY OR NIGHT.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: YOU ARE A MEMBER OF THE
AUDIENCE.
WE PICKED YOU RANDOMLY.
YOU HAVE DECIDED TO GO WITH THE
EGG SANDWICH.
YOU BELIEVE IT IS HEALTHIER THAN
THE HAMBURGER.
THE BIG BATTLE RIGHT NOW IS
BETWEEN HAMBURGERS AND EGG
SANDWICHES.
WHY DO YOU BELIEVE THE EGG
SANDWICHES ARE BETTER?
>> I THINK IT IS BETTER BECAUSE
IT DOES NOT LEAVE ME SLUGGISH.
IT IS ALSO A HEALTHIER OPTION
THAN THE BURGER.
DR. OZ: IS IT?
THAT IS THE QUESTION.
LOOK AT WHAT HAPPENED WHEN WE
COMPARED ONE OF THE MOST POPULAR
BREAKFAST SANDWICHES WITH ONE OF
THE MOST POPULAR DELUXE BURGERS.
WHAT DID WE FIND?
>> YOU ARE A LITTLE WRONG.
YOU ARE RIGHT IN TERMS OF.
IT IS LOWER IN CALORIES AND FAT.
BUT THE BURGER HAS THE BREAKFAST
SANDWICH BEAT WHEN IT COMES TO
PRINTING.
DR. OZ: IT WINS WITH PROTEIN.
>> BUT WHEN IT COMES TO FAT AND
CALORIES, YOU ARE RIGHT, THIS IS
LEANER, YOU FEEL BETTER.
AS A QUICK BITE TO GO, IT WORKS.
IT IS ABOUT BALANCING WHAT YOU
EAT THAT DAY.
DR. OZ: I GO WITH YOU.
I THINK THE EGG SANDWICH IS
HEALTHIER.
YOU HAVE ONE MORE QUESTION.
>> I DO.
I LIKE THE WHOLE SHEBANG ON MY
BREAKFAST SANDWICHES.
ARE THE HASHBROWNS HEALTHIER
THAN FRIES?
DR. OZ: I BET YOU ALL WANT TO
KNOW THAT.
HASHBROWNS OR FRIES, THAT IS THE
BIG QUESTION.
WE ARE TALKING ABOUT OTHER FAST
FOOD BREAKFAST STAPLES INCLUDING
HASHBROWNS.
WE ARE GOING TO THROW COFFEE
INTO IT AS WELL.
[APPLAUSE]
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
I'm not picking it up. You pick
it up!
I'm not picking it up.
I'll pick it up! They're clean!
♪'Cuz my hiney's clean.♪
♪Oh yeah I'm Charmin clean.♪
Charmin Ultra Strong just cleans
better.
Enjoy the Go with Charmin.
>> HASHBROWNS AND COFFEE IS THE
BEST WAY TO START YOUR DAY.
ANYTIME OF DAY, ICED COFFEE WITH
CRISPY HASH BROWN.
>> I LOVE THE HASHBROWNS AND THE
COFFEE.
HOW COULD YOU SAY NO TO A
POTATO?
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE ARE ABOUT TO REVEAL
WHETHER HASHBROWNS ARE BETTER
FOR YOU THAN FRIES.
I'VE ASKED MEMBERS OF MY
AUDIENCE TO HOLD UP THE
INGREDIENTS FOUND IN ONE FAST
FOOD HASHBROWN.
ARE YOU READY?
1, 2, 3.
REVEAL!
MY GOODNESS.
WALK US THROUGH THIS.
IT IS MORE THAN I EXPECTED.
>> A LOT OF POTATO, BUT THERE IS
A LOT OF OTHER STUFF IN HERE.
NATURAL FLAVOR, DEXTROSE, SALT,
CITRIC ACID, CORNFLOWER, CANOLA
OIL, BLACK POWDER EXTRACT,
SODIUM ACID.
SOMETHING ELSE NOBODY CAN
PRONOUNCE.
THIS IS ALL IN THE HASHBROWNS WE
ARE LOVING TO CONSUME EVERY
MORNING.
DR. OZ: YOU CAN LEARN MORE ABOUT
HASHBROWNS RIGHT NOW.
SHE LOVES HER HASHBROWNS.
SHE WAS ASKING US ABOUT
HASHBROWNS OR FRENCH FRIES.
HOW DO YOU COMPARE THEM?
AFTER YOU SEE THE INGREDIENTS,
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I THOUGHT HASHBROWNS WERE
BASICALLY POTATOES.
BUT I DON'T KNOW.
DR. OZ: UNTIL SHE DID HER
INVESTIGATION, I THOUGHT IT WAS
POTATOES AND ONE OR TWO OTHER
THINGS BUT NOT THE BUNCH OF
THINGS WE JUST SAW.
YOU COMPARED THE OPTIONS.
>> I KNOW YOU'RE REALLY INTO
HASHBROWNS.
AND IT WOULD LOVE TO TELL YOU
THEY ARE THE CLEAR ANSWER, BUT
IS ACTUALLY A MIXED BAG.
HASHBROWNS BEAT OUT FRIES WHEN
IT COMES TO CALORIES.
WHEN IT COMES TO SODIUM, THEY
HAVE A LOT MORE.
IT IS ABOUT YOUR DIET AND
HEALTH, WHAT YOU NEED FOR YOUR
DAY.
BUT NEITHER ONE OF THEM ARE
GREAT.
DR. OZ: YOU CAN DO BETTER.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE LAST ALL
DAY MENU STAPLE, THE COFFEE.
I LOVE COFFEE.
I DON'T DRINK MUCH OF IT BUT I
KNOW IT IS GOOD FOR YOU.
THINK YOU OUGHT TO DRINK ENOUGH
OF IT TO FEEL HAPPY IN YOUR
LIFE.
WHEN YOU ORDER FROM A FAST FOOD
CHAIN, YOU GET MORE THAN YOU
BARGAINED FOR.
YOU ORDERED REGULAR COFFEE.
WHAT WENT DOWN?
>> I WAS SURPRISED.
I FELT LIKE I GOT A CUP OF SUGAR
AND MILK.
IT WAS A LOT MORE SWEET THE
NINTH DISSIPATE IT.
FRANKLY, IT WAS NOT ENJOYABLE.
I HAVE A FEW HACKS THAT CAN
HELP.
DR. OZ: PLEASE.
>> IF YOU ARE ORDERING REGULAR
COFFEE COMING WANT TO ORDER
AMERICANA.
THAT WILL BE COFFEE AND WATER.
YOU CAN ADD OTHER THINGS INTO
IT.
IF YOU WANT TO HAVE ICED COFFEE
WHICH A LOT OF PEOPLE LOVE ALL
YEAR ROUND, YOU WANT TO MAKE
SURE YOU ASK FOR REGULAR COFFEE
AND HAVE IT POURED OVER ICE SO
IT WILL NOT HAVE EXTRA SUGAR OR
THE SYRUP AND IT WILL REALLY
JUST BE COFFEE WHICH IS THE HIGH
YOU ARE LOOKING FOR.
YOU ARE NOT LOOKING FOR THE
OTHER STUFF.
DR. OZ: THERE ARE WAYS TO GET
WHAT WE WANT FROM THE FAST FOOD
CHAINS.
CUSTOMIZE IT THE WAY YOU WANT
AND YOU WILL BE HAPPY.
THERE IS A FULL LIST ON HOW TO
MAKE YOUR BREAKFAST HEALTHIER AT
DOCTOROZ.COM.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: NEXT, THE FOOD
INVESTIGATION INTO CREAM CHEESE.
IS IT REALLY CHEESE?
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
♪
You're not just mom.
You're her whole world.
Don't just get away, come
together.
Save up to 30%. Hurry.
Offer ends soon.
YOU ARE REALLY EATING.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: CREAM CHEESE IS THE
BREAKFAST SPREAD THAT MAKES A
BAGEL SOMETHING YOU CRAVE.
TODAY, WE INVESTIGATE THE TRUTH
ABOUT GROCERY STORE CREAM
CHEESE.
WHAT IS REALLY IN IT?
IS IT EVEN REAL CHEESE?
CHEF IS HERE WITH A CLOSER LOOK.
AMERICA'S OBSESSED WITH CREAM
CHEESE.
WE HAVE THE PASSIONATE FOOD
FIGHTS TO PROVE IT.
WALK US THROUGH THE RECENT
CONTROVERSY OVER THE EMOJI.
>> I AM FROM NEW YORK, WE LOVE
OUR BAGELS HERE.
[APPLAUSE]
>> THERE IS NO CAN CHEESE ON THE
BAGEL.
RECENTLY, THEY FIXED IT.
DR. OZ: THEY HAD TO ADD CREAM
CHEESE TO MAKE THE EMOJI TRULY A
BAGEL.
>> IT IS LIKE PEANUT BUTTER AND
JELLY WITHOUT THE PEANUT BUTTER.
DR. OZ: THERE ARE OTHER FOOD
FIGHTS YOU HAVE BEEN HEARING
ABOUT ON TWITTER.
HERE IS A CLASSIC TWEET.
DO YOU CONSIDER CREAM CHEESE
ACTUAL CHEESE?
#CREAMCHEESEDEBATE.
WHAT DO THEY MEAN BY CREAM
CHEESE?
WHAT IS ACTUALLY IN IT?
>> IT IS DIFFERENT FROM MOST>>
CHEESES.
IT IS A NEW CHEESE.
YOU CAN MAKE CREAM CHEESE IN ONE
DAY.
MOST CHEESES ME TO SIT AND
CULTURE AND FIRM UP.
A LOT OF OTHER CHEESES, THEY
AGE.
THIS IS FRESH, NEW CHEESE.
THAT IS THE ONLY DIFFERENCE.
DR. OZ: THE CHEF AND MY TEAM
WENT THROUGH ALL THE CREAM
CHEESE TYPES AND DISCOVERED
SOMETHING YOU MAY NOT KNOW ABOUT
YOUR FAVORITE SPREAD.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE MOST
POPULAR BRANDS YOU MIGHT
TYPICALLY BY.
I KNOW IF YOU GO TO A STORE, IT
IS A LITTLE DIFFERENT WHEN YOU
TRY TO BUY A FRESH.
>> THIS IS SUPER FANCY.
YOU WILL NOT RUN INTO THIS MUCH
UNLESS YOU ARE A HANDS-ON
RESTAURANT OR NICE BAGEL PLACE.
THIS IS WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO GET
AT A GROCERY STORE.
IT IS GOOD QUALITY STUFF.
WE KNOW WHICH ONE IT IS.
I LOVE THIS.
IT IS SIMPLE, HEALTHY.
THE INGREDIENTS ARE SIMPLE.
I CAN PRONOUNCE ALL THE STUFF.
THE WAY PROTEIN IS LIKE
CONCENTRATED POWDERED MILK.
XANTHAN GUM IS USED AS A
STABILIZER.
TOTALLY FINE, NATURAL.
DR. OZ: WHEN YOU BUY IT FRESH,
THEY ADD SELTZER.
I DID NOT REALIZE THAT.
>> THE CARBON DIOXIDE MAKES IT
AREA.
THERE IS A CHEMICAL REACTION
THAT COMES OUT.
DR. OZ: HERE IS WHERE THE DEBATE
STARTS.
LOW-FAT AND FAT-FREE CREAM
CHEESE VERSUS THE REGULAR,
OLD-FASHIONED, FULL FAT STUFF.
HOW DO THEY MAKE IT LOW-FAT?
>> THEY DO NOT ADD IN THE HEAVY
CREAM.
IT GETS WEIRD BECAUSE THEY HAVE
TO START PUTTING OTHER STUFF IN
LIKE POTASSIUM SORBATE.
I DON'T REALLY NEED THAT.
I DON'T NEED HIGH FRUCTOSE CORN
SYRUP.
THEY ARE TRYING TO MAKE UP FOR
THE FACT THERE IS NOT FAT IN IT.
IS NOT FOR ME.
FOR SOME PEOPLE, IT WORKS.
DR. OZ: PEOPLE DO IT BECAUSE
THEY THINK THEY'RE GETTING LESS
CALORIES.
IS THAT THE BEST WAY TO HAVE
YOUR BAGEL WITHOUT THEM -- WITH
LESS CALORIES?
WE WILL EXAMINE THAT.
WHIPPED CREAM CHEESE IS TAKING
OVER THE COUNTRY.
THERE IS A REASON FOR THAT.
SHE IS A BIG FAN.
HAVE YOU COMPARED TO THE CLASSIC
AND LOW-FAT?
>> I LOVE THE WHIPPED CREAM
CHEESE BECAUSE IT IS ALREADY
FLUFFY AND SMOOTH.
IT IS GREAT FOR SWIRLING IN
HOMEMADE JAMS.
IT IS GREAT FOR A QUICK
FROSTING.
DR. OZ: IT SPREADS EASILY.
>> IT IS GREAT FOR SPREADING.
I MAKE GREAT DIPS FOR PARTIES.
IT IS THE PERFECT TEXTURE.
DR. OZ: LOW-FAT DOES NOT SPREAD
SO WELL, I SHOULD POINT OUT.
A LITTLE BIT OF A BATTLE.
>> THIS IS THE REGULAR STUFF.
I'M HAVING TROUBLE WITH THIS
BECAUSE IT IS TEMPERED.
TAKE IT OUT AND LET IT SHOW FOR
A LITTLE WHILE -- CHILL FOR A
LITTLE WHILE.
DR. OZ: I WAS CURIOUS ABOUT
SOMETHING.
I AM STRUGGLING.
I AM NOT A FAN OF LOW-FAT
ANYWAY.
I WANTED TO GIVE IT A CHANCE.
I WANTED TO THOROUGHLY
UNDERSTAND AND TEST WHIPPED
CREAM CHEESE.
THERE IS A THEORY THAT WHIPPED
CREAM CHEESE ALLOWS YOU TO
CONSUME LESS CALORIES.
HAVE YOU HEARD THAT?
>> I WOULD LIKE TO BELIEVE THAT.
DR. OZ: IS IT REALLY TRUE?
MY TEAM DID A BAGEL SPREAD
EXPERIMENT.
THEY EXPERIMENTED WITH CLASSIC,
LOW-FAT, AND WHIPPED CREAM
CHEESE.
THEY USED A FOOD SCALE TO FIGURE
OUT HOW MUCH CREAM CHEESE YOU
ARE SPREADING ON A WHOLE BAGEL.
FOR THE CLASSIC CREAM CHEESE,
YOU SPREAD AN AVERAGE OF ABOUT
ONE TABLESPOON.
1.5 ROUGHLY.
ABOUT 160 CALORIES.
LOW-FAT, ABOUT THE SAME AMOUNT.
1.5 TABLESPOONS, ABOUT 120
CALORIES.
IT IS LESS CALORIES.
HERE IS WHERE IT GOT
INTERESTING.
WHIPPED CREAM CHEESE.
YOU'RE ACTUALLY SPREADING MORE,
ABOUT TWO TABLESPOONS.
WE ONLY GET 95 CALORIES.
YOU GET MORE CREAM CHEESE BUT
FEWER CALORIES.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: YOUR FAMILY KNOWS WHAT
THEY ARE DOING.
ARGUE HAPPY?
--ART YOU HAPPY?
>> I AM ECSTATIC.
DR. OZ: I HAVE MADE TODAY FOR A
LOT OF AMERICANS.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'M PAYING FOR
AIR.
THERE SHOULD BE FREE.
JUST MY THING.
DR. OZ: AIR COMES IN HANDY IN
LIFE.
BUT TALK ABOUT THE FLAVORED
CREAM CHEESE -- LET'S TALK ABOUT
THE FLAVORED CREAM CHEESES.
ARE YOU GETTING REAL
STRAWBERRIES IN YOUR STRAWBERRY
CREAM CHEESE?
>> YES, BUT YOU ARE ALSO GETTING
A LOT OF STUFF.
I DON'T NEED RED 40 DYE.
I AM OK WITH THE FRUIT JUICE AND
VEGETABLE JUICE.
THE CORN SYRUP, AGAIN, EH.
I AM NOT A HUGE FAN.
YOU CAN MAKE YOUR OWN, MAN.
DR. OZ: SHOW US HOW TO DO IT.
YOU WANT THAT TASTE SOMETIMES.
>> YOUR CREAM CHEESE ALREADY
TEMPERED.
STRAWBERRIES I CHOPPED UP
EARLIER.
YOU CAN POP A COUPLE OF THOSE IN
THEIR.
DR. OZ: IS THAT JAM?
>> THAT IS JIM.
THAT IS A LIFE HACK.
I USE THAT AT HOME ALL THE TIME.
DR. OZ: STRAWBERRIES, YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU ARE ADDING.
WHAT IS THAT?
>> SOUR CREAM AND CHIVES.
DR. OZ: YOU PUT POTATO CHIPS IN?
>> YOU COULD.
THOSE ARE THE OG CLASSIC.
LIKE 15 SECONDS, DONE.
DR. OZ: THERE IS ONE OTHER HACK
I'M GOING TO ASK YOU ABOUT.
A LOT OF PEOPLE TAKE THE BREAD
OUT OF THE BAGEL.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> MY GIRLFRIEND -- MY
EX-GIRLFRIEND USED TO DO THAT.
[LAUGHTER]
DR. OZ: THAT GIVES YOU AN IDEA
OF WHAT HE THINKS.
HIS EX-GIRLFRIEND USED TO DO
THAT.
DID NOT WORK OUT SO WELL.
>> IT MAKES SENSE.
I NEED EVERY CALORIE I CAN GET.
IF YOU WANT TO CUT CALORIES OR
CARBS, YOU CAN DO IT.
DR. OZ: WITH WHIPPED CREAM
CHEESE, YOU ARE OK WITH ALL OF
THAT?
>> I AM OK.
THE ONLY ONE THAT WEIRDS ME OUT
IS THE LOW-FAT BECAUSE OF THE
CHEMICALS.
DR. OZ: TAKE THE MAN'S ADVICE.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WHEN THE CAMERAS STOP
ROLLING, I STILL HAVE A LOT I
WANT TO
WANT TO TALK ABOUT
♪ We buy any car ♪
♪ Any make, any model,
any age, any price ♪
♪ From 50 bucks to 100 grand ♪
♪ We buy any car ♪
♪ Any, any, any, any ♪
At webuyanycar.com,
the gimmicks stop with our ads.
Trading in our selling
your car is hassle-free
with just three easy steps.
One, get your free
online valuation.
Two, drive to your local
car buying centre.
And three,
walk out with your check
in as little as 30 minutes.
So don't wait.
Get your free online
valuation now.
♪ Find out how much
your car's worth ♪
♪ At webuyanycar.com ♪
DR. OZ: I'M FEELING A LITTLE
TIRED.
I WONDER IF I SHOULD GET SOME
COFFEE OR GO RIGHT TO THE PLANE.
DR. OZ: I STILL WANT COFFEE.
I WONDER IF I SHOULD GET IT ON
THE FLIGHT OR WAIT UNTIL I GET
HOME.
DR. OZ: I STILL FEEL LIKE
COFFEE.
DR. OZ: I FEEL LIKE SOMEONE IS
CHOOSING FOR ME.
DR. OZ: A LITTLE ODE TO THE
NETFLIX SERIES ALL IN GOOD FUN.
ACTUALLY, YOU DO HAVE TO DECIDE.
OTHER PEOPLE ARE NOT GOING TO DO
IT FOR YOU.
AS WE HAVE BEEN LEARNING THIS
FEBRUARY, GERMS ARE LURKING IN
PLACES YOU WOULD NEVER EXPECT.
TODAY, WE ARE INVESTIGATING
WHETHER YOUR DRINKING COFFEE
THAT IS FILTHY.
WE HAVE THREE WOMEN WHO SAY THEY
ARE CONCERNED THAT THERE ARE
HIDDEN GERMS IN THE PLACES THEY
TURN FOR A QUICK CUP.
SHE WANTS TO KNOW ABOUT GAS
STATION COFFEE.
WHAT IS WORRYING YOU?
>> EVERY TIME I GO INTO A GAS
STATION AND I NEED COFFEE, THERE
IS SO MUCH COFFEE.
I GO BACK AND HOUR LATER, AND
THERE STILL A WHOLE POT OF
COFFEE BUT I NEVER SEE ANYONE
CHANGE IT.
I NEVER SEE ANYONE CLEAN AROUND
IT.
I'M THINKING.
DR. OZ: HAVE YOU EVER WONDERED
WHY THERE IS SO MUCH COFFEE
READY TO GO?
SHE WANTS TO KNOW ABOUT AIRPLANE
COFFEE.
WHAT WORRIES YOU?
YOU JUST SAW MY LITTLE PARODY.
>> THE NUMBER ONE THING IT SEEMS
LIKE THE VIRAL STORIES FROM
PILOTS WERE ATTENDANCE, THEY SAY
DO NOT DRINK THE COFFEE ON THE
PLANE.
I NEED CAFFEINE WHEN I HAVE NOT
SLEPT AND I TRAVEL.
DR. OZ: YOU HAVE TO DECIDE ALL
BY YOURSELF.
NO ONE IS GOING TO DO IT FOR
YOU.
SHE WAS TO KNOW ABOUT COFFEE
FROM BIG CHAIN PLACES.
YOUR CONCERN?
>> THEY MOVE SO QUICKLY BETWEEN
ORDERS.
HOW DO WE KNOW A QUICK WRENCH --
RENTS GETS THE MACHINES CLEAN?
DR. OZ: THREE, PLACES WE GET
COFFEE.
FOR FILTHY FEBRUARY, WE ARE
PUTTING IT UNDER THE MICROSCOPE
WITH THE AUTHOR OF "THE COFFEE
LOVERS BIBLE."
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: THE MEDICAL DOCTOR SO
EXCITED ABOUT THE HEALTH
BENEFITS OF COFFEE, HERE TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT ALL THE QUESTIONS
WE HAVE BEEN RAISING.
FIRST OFF, GAS STATION COFFEE.
I'M CURIOUS WHAT YOU THINK.
HOW LONG DOES THAT POT OF COFFEE
STAY OUT BEFORE THEY CHANGE IT?
>> IT COULD BE 30 MINUTES OR
EIGHT HOURS AT AN OUT-OF-THE-WAY
PLACE.
THERE ARE SOME COFFEE STATIONS
THAT HAVE FANTASTIC COFFEE.
IF IT HAS BEEN THERE FOR EIGHT
HOURS, IT GETS REALLY STALE AND
TASTES TERRIBLE.
DR. OZ: HE IS A PILOT, AN
AIRPLANE PILOT.
YOU FLEW YOURSELF HERE TODAY,
I'M TOLD.
WHO BETTER TO ASK?
WE ARE INVESTIGATING COFFEE ON
AIRPLANES.
HERE IS THE THING.
COFFEE IN AIRPLANES HAS BEEN ALL
OVER THE NEWS.
EVEN PILOTS ARE COMING OUT
AGAINST IT.
EXPLAIN AS A PILOT HOW THEY MAKE
THE COFFEE WE DRINK ON PLANES.
>> IT SAYS POTABLE WATER ON THE
TRUCK.
IT IS A LOCAL WATER SUPPLY.
WHEREVER IT IS, THAT IS THE
WATER YOU GET.
DR. OZ: BOLIVIA?
>> IT COULD BE COMING FROM SOME
OTHER PLACE.
WHO KNOWS WHERE THE WATER CAME
FROM?
DR. OZ: THIS WATER FROM THE
LOCAL SUPPLY, THEY PUT IT IN THE
PLANE.
>> THEY LOADED INTO THE
AIRPLANE.
THIS IS USED IN THE COFFEE MAKER
ON THE AIRPLANE.
THE WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION
SAYS 158 DEGREES KILLS ALMOST
ANYTHING.
THERE IS ALL THIS WORRY AND
CONCERN.
THERE ARE OLDER STUDIES THAT
HAVE SHOWN A LOT OF BACTERIA IN
THE WATER.
BY THE TIME THAT HAS SAT THERE
AT 180 DEGREES FOR FOUR OR FIVE
HOURS, IT DOES NOT TASTE GREAT
BUT IS LIKELY SAFE.
DR. OZ: THEORETICALLY, IT WILL
BE OK.
IS THAT GOOD ENOUGH FOR YOU?
NO.
WE WANTED TO FIND OUT THE TRUTH.
WHEN IT SITS FOR A COUPLE OF
DAYS, CAN IT BE AN ISSUE?
IT GETS PEOPLE CONCERNED.
WE DID OUR OWN TESTING.
IT SEEMS LIKE THE AIRPLANE
COFFEE PANIC IS OVERBLOWN.
THE DATA SHOWS THINGS HAVE
IMPROVED.
FINDING CONTAMINATED WATER IS
REALLY RARE.
I THINK WE WOULD SEE MORE PEOPLE
GETTING SICK IF IT WAS TRULY A
PROBLEM.
I SAY AIRPLANE COFFEE IS CLEARED
FOR DRINKING.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: PEOPLE ALL AROUND ME ON
THE FLIGHT WERE DRINKING COFFEE.
NEXT THING DR. ARNOLD LOOKED
INTO WAS COFFEE'S FROM BIG CHAIN
BRANDS.
WE ASKED A WHISTLEBLOWER WHO WAS
A BARISTA FOR YEARS TO REVEAL A
SOB BEHIND THE BAR.
>> I USED TO WORK IN A COFFEE
SHOP FOR ABOUT 10 YEARS.
I HAVE SEEN SOME REALLY FILTHY
THINGS IN MY TIME.
I HAVE SEEN THINGS NOT IF IT
WERE THE WHOLE PLACE SMELLS LIKE
ROTTEN NEXT.
I HAVE FOUND FOOD IN
REFRIGERATOR WAY BACK.
I HAVE SEEN PEOPLE SERVE EXPIRED
MILK.
I HAVE WATCHED PEOPLE GET
REVENGE ON OTHER PEOPLE THAT
MIGHT HAVE GOTTEN THEM UPSET.
I'VE SEEN SOMEONE HOCK A LOOGEE
INTO SOMEONE ELSE'S FOOD.
ONE TIME, A COWORKER OF MINE WAS
SO UPSET THEY DECIDED TO PUT A
HEALTHY AMOUNT OF EPSOM SALTS
INTO A POT OF COFFEE AND
PROCEEDED TO GET EVERY CUSTOMER
THAT CAME FOR COFFEE THAT DAY
SICK.
I'M SURE YOU KNOW WHAT KIND OF
SICK I AM TALKING ABOUT.
DR. OZ: ACCORDING TO ONE REPORT,
YOU MAY BE BETTER OFF ORDERING
HOT COFFEE.
NOT JUST FOR THE REASONS WE
HEARD.
TESTING IN THE U.K. FOUND E.
COLI IN THE ICE.
IN THE ICE ITSELF.
NOT THE COFFEE, BUT THE ICE.
THAT IS SOMETHING YOU NEVER
WANT.
YOU NEVER WANT E. COLI IN YOUR
ICED COFFEE.
ONE MORE COFFEE LEFT TO
INVESTIGATE.
THE KIND BREWED AT HOME.
IS IT THE TRADITIONAL POT KIND?
FIND OUT THE RESULTS OF OUR
TESTING WHEN WE COME BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
Stouffer's Lasagna With Meat &
Sauce
has two times the beef of the
leading meat sauce lasagna.
That's double the tender ground
beef
baked into every cheesy,
mouthwatering bite.
When it comes to irresistible
taste,
more is always more.
Stouffer's.
Smooth, easy strokes.
When you're raising a child...
Pinch.
be soft.
Ah.
When you're doing
it alone, be strong.
Thanks, dad.
Life takes softness and
strength, which is why
we make Angel Soft
with a balance of both.
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
♪
Oats have a soluble fiber
called beta-glucan,
which can help lower cholesterol
when part of a
heart-healthy diet.
What's more, these oats
have no artificial flavors,
preservatives or added colors.
Now that's something
to celebrate.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE ARE BACK WITH THE
DIRT ON FILTHY COFFEE.
WE ARE PUTTING YOUR OWN
HOMEBREWED COFFEE POT UNDER THE
MICROSCOPE.
WHICH IS GERMIER?
THE TRADITIONAL OR POD KIND?
FROM THEIR VERY OWN KITCHEN,
RYAN, YOU DESCRIBE YOURSELF AS
AN OLD-SCHOOL CUP OF JOE KIND OF
GUY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT COFFEE
MAKER?
>> I TELL YOU, I HAVE THREE
WORDS TO DESCRIBE WHAT I THINK
ABOUT THIS LITTLE MACHINE RIGHT
HERE.
PACIFIC GARBAGE PATCH.
ALL THE PLASTICS RIGHT HERE.
THAT IS THE WHOLE REASON I DON'T
DEAL WITH THIS THING RIGHT HERE.
DR. OZ: THE AUDIENCE IS
APPLAUDING YOU.
YOU SAY THE COFFEE MAKER IS NOT
THE GERM MACHINE YOUR HUSBAND
THINKS IT IS.
IT MIGHT NOT BE AS GREEN, BUT IS
IT BETTER?
>> IT IS BETTER.
FIRST OF ALL, I CANNOT BELIEVE
WHAT YOU JUST SAID ABOUT MY
PRECIOUS POD STYLE MACHINE.
YOU CAN HAVE IT FRESH AND HOT.
IT HAS NOT SAT AROUND ALL DAY.
THIS IS A FRESH CUP PERSONALLY
FOR YOU.
>> I AM TRADITIONAL.
I LIKE MY COFFEE LIKE MYSELF,
BLACK AND STRONG.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
>> THIS IS ALL I NEED RIGHT
HERE.
DR. OZ: TODAY, WE ARE GOING TO
SETTLE THE SCORE ONCE AND FOR
ALL BECAUSE WE DID A GERM TEST
TO FIND OUT WHICH COFFEEMAKERS
ARE GERMIER.
WHICH COFFEEMAKERS YOU THINK IS
GOING TO BE MORE FILTHY?
>> HERS.
>> HIS.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE WILL HAVE THE RESULTS
IN A MOMENT.
FIRST, WE BREAK DOWN THE SCIENCE
BETWEEN THESE OPTIONS.
PEOPLE ARE FIGHTING IN THEIR
HOMES OVER THIS.
>> WE CANNOT DECIDE.
WE HAVE TWO DIFFERENT
COFFEEMAKERS.
I'M GOING TO WALK THROUGH THESE.
DR. OZ: YOU ARE PRETTY GOOD AT
THIS STUFF.
YOU UNDERSTAND ALL THESE THINGS.
BASIC MISCONCEPTIONS ABOUT THESE
OPTIONS.
HOW DO YOU CLEAN THIS AND THAT?
>> YOU ARE SUPPOSED TO CLEAN IT
REGULARLY LIKE ANY OTHER ITEM.
WITH THE POD STYLE MACHINE, YOU
CAN PULL THIS OUT, PULL THE TRAY
OUT.
PULL OUT THE WATER THING.
YOU CAN PUT IT IN YOUR
DISHWASHER.
THERE IS A CLEANING POD YOU CAN
PUT IN HERE.
ANY HOUSEHOLD APPLIANCE YOU
TOUCH A LOT, YOU WANT TO WASH
OFF.
DR. OZ: MY WIFE USES A
TOOTHBRUSH.
SHE DID SEEING HERE --SHE GETS
IN HERE WITH A LITTLE
TOOTHBRUSH.
IT WORKS WELL.
>> YOU WANT TO CLEAN THROUGH
HERE ALL THE DIRTY PARTS.
DR. OZ: WHAT A METICULOUS DOCTOR
.
HOW DO YOU CLEAN THE
OLD-FASHIONED ONE?
>> SAME THING.
YOU WANT TO USE WHITE VINEGAR
WHICH IS VERY ACIDIC.
YOU CAN TAKE THESE PIECES OUT.
PUT IT IN YOUR WASHING MACHINE.
THAT IS THE BEST WAY TO DO THAT.
DO IT EVERY DAY.
DR. OZ: EVERY DAY YOU DO THAT?
>> YOU SHOULD.
DR. OZ: WHO CLEANS THEIR COFFEE
MAKER EVERY DAY?
>> SEE?
DR. OZ: ONE FAMILY IN THE BACK.
[LAUGHTER]
DR. OZ: ALL THE OTHER 90
FAMILIES DO NOT DO THAT.
>> DO IT REGULARLY.
BETWEEN 40 AND 80 BREWS YOU
SHOULD DO IT.
YOU PUT THE VINEGAR IN HERE AND
YOU BREW IT THROUGH.
LET IT SIT FOR HALF AN HOUR.
THAT IS THE WAY YOU CLEAN THAT
MACHINE.
GREAT TASTING COFFEE.
DR. OZ: DON'T MOVE.
RYAN, THIS COULD CHANGE
EVERYTHING.
WE TESTED COFFEE MADE FROM BOTH
TYPES OF MACHINES WE HAVE IN THE
STUDIO.
WE JUST WENT OVER THEM.
AT ONE END OF THE GERM CHART IS
A TOILET SEAT.
THE OTHER SIDE HAS A WHISTLE
MEANING CLEAN AS A WHISTLE.
YOU SEE THE RESULTS?
LELET'S SEE THE RESULTS.
THERE GOES.
BOTH COFFEES CAME OUT GERM FREE.
THEY ARE BOTH FINE.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: USE THE TRICKS HE JUST
GAVE YOU TO KEEP YOUR SPEAK AND
SPAN COFFEE MAKER INTACT.
IT WILL TASTE BETTER AND BE
BETTER FOR YOU.
NO MATTER WHAT KIND YOU HAVE, IT
IS WORTH THE INVESTMENT OF
EFFORT.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
Let's face it,
the world
could use some warmth.
♪ ♪
The in-laws have moved in
with us.
And our adult children are here.
So we save by using Tide.
Which means we use less.
Three generations of clothes
cleaned in one wash.
Anybody seen my pants?
#1 stain and odor fighter, #1
trusted.
It's got to be Tide.
To most, he's
Phil Mickelson...
..pro golfer.
To me, he's...
...well, Dad.
So when his
joint pain from
psoriatic arthritis
got really bad, it scared me.
And what could that pain mean?
Joint pain could
mean joint damage.
ENBREL helps
relieve joint pain...
...helps stop irreversible
joint damage...
and helps skin get clearer.
ENBREL may lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious, sometimes
fatal events...
including infections,
tuberculosis...
lymphoma, other cancers,...
nervous system and
blood disorders...
and allergic
reactions have occurred.
Tell your
doctor if you've
been some place where
fungal infections are common.
Or, if you're
prone to infections,
have cuts or sores,
have had hepatitis B,
have been treated
for heart failure...
or if you have
persistent fever...
bruising, bleeding, or paleness.
Don't start ENBREL...
if you have an
infection like the flu.
Since ENBREL...
Dad's back to being... Dad.
Visit Enbrel.com...
and use the Joint
Damage Simulator
to see how your joint
damage could be progressing.
Ask about ENBREL.
ENBREL.
FDA approved for
over 16 years.
♪ Seed to the oat, to the O ♪
♪ To the honey in each bite ♪
♪ Healthy hearts make life
sweeter ♪
♪ So you can live it right ♪
♪ The good goes around and
around  and around and around ♪
Alright, I brought in
Ensure Max Protein...
To give you
the Protein you need
with less of
the sugar you don't.
(Straining)
I'll take that.
(Cheers)
30 grams of protein
and 1 gram of sugar.
Ensure Max Protein.
In two great flavors.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: IT IS A CHRONIC AND
ABILITY HITTING CONDITION THAT
MAKES SOMETHING AS SIMPLE AS
BREATHING A CHALLENGE.
WE ARE TALKING ABOUT CHRONIC
ABSTRACT OF PULMONARY DISEASE
MORE COMMONLY KNOWN AS COPD.
IT AFFECTS NEARLY 27.7 MILLION
PEOPLE.
OF THAT 27.7 MILLION, MORE THAN
12 MILLION ARE UNDIAGNOSED WHICH
IS WHY TODAY I'M BREAKING DOWN
WHAT COPD IS AND WHY IT IS ON
THE RISE IN THIS COUNTRY.
TO HELP SHED LIGHT ON THE TOPIC
IS THE DOCTOR HERE ON BEHALF OF
MY SPONSOR PARTNER.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: LET'S START WITH THE
BASIC ISSUE OF WHAT COPD IS.
EVERYONE HAS HEARD OF IT BECAUSE
PEOPLE HAVE IT.
WHAT DOES IT MEAN TO A
PULMONOLOGIST?
>> IT IS A CHRONIC DISEASE.
IT INCLUDES CHRONIC BRONCHITIS
AND EMPHYSEMA.
IT OCCURS BECAUSE OF THE
ENVIRONMENT.
IT IS PROGRESSIVE BECAUSE THE
SYMPTOMS PROGRESS OVER TIME AND
THE LUNG DAMAGE CANNOT BE
REVERSED.
AS THE DISEASE PROGRESSES, IT IS
HARDER TO BREATHE AND YOU CANNOT
PERFORM YOUR DAILY ACTIVITIES.
DR. OZ: HOW MANY OF YOU HAVE
HEARD OF COPD?
LITERALLY EVERY PERSON IN THE
AUDIENCE.
IT IS IMPORTANT IF YOU HAVE COPD
TO KNOW YOUR SYMPTOMS AND
TREATMENT PROPERLY WITHOUT
IGNORING THEM.
EXPLAIN TO FOLKS EXACTLY WHAT
THE SYMPTOMS ARE.
I'M GOING TO WALK THEM THROUGH
WHAT IS HAPPENING IN THEIR
BODIES.
>> THE SYMPTOMS THAT MOST PEOPLE
SHOULD BE LOOKING OUT FOR OUR
SHORTNESS OF BREATH, WHICH WILL
IMPACT THEIR DAILY LIVING.
THEY WILL NOT BE ABLE TO PERFORM
EVERYDAY ACTIVITIES.
MORE IMPORTANTLY, THEY MIGHT
FEEL TIRED.
IT IS ABSOLUTELY CRUCIAL THAT
THEY DO NOT ATTRIBUTE IT TO JUST
GETTING OLDER.
THE THINGS THEY NEED TO LOOK OUT
FOR OUR CHRONIC COUGH, WHEEZING.
DR. OZ: LET ME SHOW EVERYBODY
WHAT IS HAPPENING WHEN YOU HAVE
COPD IN YOUR LUNGS.
IT CAN MAKE IT DIFFICULT TO
BREATHE.
IT GETS WORSE OVER TIME WHICH
MAKES YOU UNHAPPY.
EVERYBODY TAKE A DEEP BREATH IN.
AS THE AIR PASSES THROUGH YOUR
NOSE INTO YOUR WINDPIPE DOWN
INTO YOUR LUNGS, WHEN IT GETS TO
YOUR LUNGS, HE GOES INTO TINY
AIR SACS.
THERE ARE MILLIONS OF THESE
CALLED ALVEOLA.
THEY FILL UP.
WHEN THE BREATH GOES OUT, THEY
ARE FINE.
IF IT GETS SICK, THE WALLS
BECOME SWOLLEN.
THE MUSCLES SQUEEZE THE AIRWAYS
MAKING IT HARD FOR THE AIR TO
GET OUT.
THEY ACTUALLY TRACK AIR
SOMETIMES.
THAT MAKES IT HARD FOR YOU TO
BREATHE.
WHAT CAUSES COPD?
YOU MENTION IT COULD BE
ENVIRONMENTAL TOXINS AND THE
LIKE.
WHAT IS HAPPENING INSIDE OF US?
>> OVER TIME, YOUR BREATHING
EVERY DAY AIR.
OVER TIME, LUNG IRRITANTS CAN
CAUSE IRRITATION OF THE INNER
LINING OF YOUR LUNGS AND
AIRWAYS.
WHAT ENDS UP HAPPENING IS YOU
ARE HAVING MORE AND MORE
DIFFICULTY TO BREATHE AND YOUR
SYMPTOMS WORSEN OVER TIME LIKE I
SAID EARLIER.
THE MOST IMPORTANT PART TO
RECALL IS COPD IS MAINLY CAUSED
BY NICOTINE IN CIGARETTES
SMOKING.
HOWEVER, YOU MUST REMEMBER
NON-SMOKERS CAN GET COPD, TOO.
THE AIR YOU BREATHE EVERY DAY
OUTSIDE, AT WORK, AT HOME, MAY
CONTRIBUTE TO THE DEVELOPMENT OF
COPD.
LONG-TIME EXPOSURE TO FUMES,
DUST, AIR POLLUTION, SECONDHAND
SMOKE, CHEMICALS IN THE SETTING
OF WORK, WORK RELATED INJURIES
DEFINITELY, CAN ALSO CAUSE COPD.
DR. OZ: THINGS YOU MAY HAVE DONE
TO YOURSELF, THINGS YOU MAY HAVE
NO IDEA CONTRIBUTE.
KNOW THE SYMPTOMS AND GET
ACTIVE.
THE SYMPTOMS OF COPD ARE
TREATABLE.
THERE ARE MANY TREATMENT OPTIONS
AVAILABLE.
LAST YEAR, A TREATMENT OPTION
WAS APPROVED THAT MAY BE ABLE TO
HELP COPD.
TELL US ABOUT IT.
>> THE INHALATION SOLUTION IS A
MAINTENANCE MEDICATION FOR THE
TREATMENT OF COPD SYMPTOMS.
IT IS PRETTY EASY TO TAKE.
YOU TAKE IT TWICE A DAY.
MAKE SURE YOU ACTUALLY USE IT
WITHOUT USING ANOTHER TYPE.
MORE IMPORTANT TO REMEMBER IS IT
IS NOT A MEDICATION TO TREAT
SUDDEN ONSET SYMPTOMS OF COPD.
DR. OZ: THIS IS THE DEVICE.
SHOW ME HOW YOU USE THIS TWICE A
DAY.
>> YOU USE IT TWICE A DAY.
THE ADMINISTRATION TAKES TWO TO
THREE MINUTES.
IT IS NOT LONG WITH PROPER
ASSEMBLY AND CLEANING.
WHEN YOU ASSEMBLE IT, YOU END UP
CLICKING THIS IN.
THE MEDICATION IS RIGHT IN HERE.
YOU HOLD THE HANDSET BODY.
YOU CLOSE YOUR LIPS AROUND THE
MOUTHPIECE, MAKING SURE YOU DO
NOT COVER THE BLUE FLAP.
WHEN YOU ARE READY, YOU PUT THE
MOUTHPIECE IN YOUR LIPS AND
BRIEF IN AND OUT.
TO INITIATE IT, YOU PUSH ON THE
BLACK BUTTON.
DR. OZ: THIS IS THE MOTOR.
>> YES.
THE GREEN LIGHT TURNS ON,
EXACTLY.
YOU HEARD THE BEEP.
DR. OZ: YES.
>> IT IS VIRTUALLY SILENT.
YOU BREATHE IN AND OUT UNTIL IT
IS DONE.
IT HELPS RELAX THE MUSCLES IN
THE INNER WINDPIPE.
DR. OZ: SIMPLE.
>> VERY SIMPLE.
IT IS SMALL.
YOU CAN USE IT BY PLUGGING IT
IN, USING BATTERIES.
VERY EASY TO TRANSPORT.
YOU CAN PUT IT IN A CARRY-ON BAG
AND TAKE IT WITH YOU.
DR. OZ: WHAT DO YOU PRESCRIBE IT
FOR IN YOUR PRACTICE?
>> IT IS PRESCRIBED FOR PATIENTS
WHO SUFFER FROM COPD THAT NEED A
MAINTENANCE THERAPY LONG-TERM
FOR THEIR COPD SYMPTOMS.
THOSE PATIENTS PREFER TO USE
MEDICATION BY BREATHING
NATURALLY.
ALSO, THOSE PATIENTS MIGHT HAVE
ISSUES USING OTHER COPD DEVICES.
DR. OZ: SIDE EFFECTS, THING
STORY ABOUT?
>> THE MOST COMMON SIDE EFFECTS,
SHORTNESS OF BREATH AND URINARY
TRACT INFECTION.
LONG-TERM, THEY CAN CAUSE
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS ALSO THAT
YOU MUST BE AWARE OF AND DISCUSS
WITH YOUR PHYSICIAN BEFORE
INITIATING IT.
MOST IMPORTANT ONES ARE
SHORTNESS OF BREATH IMMEDIATELY
AFTER USING IT.
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTIONS CAN
OCCUR ALSO.
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE WORSENING OR
NEW ONSET EYE ISSUES LIKE NARROW
ANGLE GLAUCOMA, ACUTE NARROW
ANGLE GLAUCOMA.
THE SECOND THING THAT CAN HAPPEN
IS URINARY RETENTION.
YOU MIGHT HAVE ONSET OR
PROGRESSION OF URINARY RETENTION
BLADDER ISSUES.
WHEN THE ADMINISTRATION IS DONE,
TWO BEEPS AND THE LIGHT GOES
OFF.
DR. OZ: THE TIME IT TOOK YOU TO
DESCRIBE IT, IT IS ALREADY DONE.
>> THE SIDE EFFECTS ARE LISTED
ONLINE.
YOU CAN ALSO FIND COPD
INFORMATION THERE.
DR. OZ: YOU CAN ALSO GO TO
DOCTOROZ.COM FOR MORE
INFORMATION ABOUT COPD.
I WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: THIS IS BABY LUCY.
SHE AND HER TWIN SISTER EVA WERE
BORN AT JUST 29 WEEKS.
DUE TO COMPLICATIONS, LUCY WAS
LEFT WITH CHRONIC LUNG DISEASE.
SHE GREW UP A CHEERFUL BABY,
PLAYING WITH HER SISTER, MAKING
HER PARENTS LACK.
SHE HAS TO USE OXYGEN
CONCENTRATOR.
SHE AND HER MOTHER WERE HEADED
TO THE HOSPITAL WHEN THEY GOT ON
THE PLANE.
A STRANGER STEPPED IN WITH AN
ACT OF KINDNESS SPARKING A
SOCIAL MEDIA POST THAT HAS GONE
TO INSPIRE MILLIONS.
WE ARE JOINED TODAY BY THEM AS
WELL AS THE STRANGER.
WHAT HAPPENED ON THE PLANE THAT
DAY THAT MOVED YOU TO TEARS?
>> WE WERE TRAVELING TO THE
CHILDREN'S HOSPITAL.
WE WERE GOING TO MEET SOME
DOCTORS THERE.
WE BOARDED THE PLANE AND GOT
SETTLED.
A FLIGHT ATTENDANT CAME BACK AND
SAID SOMEONE WANTED TO SWITCH
SEATS WITH US.
SHE SAID THE MAN WAS IN 2D.
IT HAPPENED TO BE A FIRST-CLASS
SEAT HE WAS GIVING UP FOR US.
DR. OZ: JASON, WHAT MADE YOU
GIVE UP YOUR SEAT?
YOU WERE SITTING IN FIRST CLASS
MINDING HER OWN BUSINESS.
WHAT WENT DOWN?
>> I HAD BEEN FLYING IN AND OUT
OF THE AIRPORT FOR A COUPLE OF
MONTHS.
YOU SEE A LOT OF SICK CHILDREN
OWING TO DISNEY.
USUALLY, THERE IS AN ENTOURAGE
OF PEOPLE.
KELSEY WAS ALL BY HERSELF WITH
LUCY.
IT JUST SEEMED LIKE THE RIGHT
THING TO DO.
DR. OZ: CONGRATULATIONS TO BOTH
OF YOU.
KELSEY, YOU AND LUCY, WE WANT
YOU TO FLY AND COMFORT TO NEXT
APPOINTMENT.
OUR FRIENDS AT CHILDREN'S LIGHT
OF HOPE AND AMERICAN AIRLINES
AGREED.
THEY WILL MAKE SURE YOUR NEXT
FLIGHT WITH LUCY IS FIRST-CLASS.
THEY HAVE AGREED ALSO TO COVER
ALL REMAINING FLIGHTS TO
CHILDREN'S HOSPITAL OF
PENNSYLVANIA AFTER THAT.
DOES THAT SOUND GOOD?
[APPLAUSE]
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
DR. OZ: I HOPE YOU ENJOY THE
FLIGHT.
I HOPE YOU HAVE A GOOD TIME WITH
YOUR PASSENGER.
JASON, THANK YOU FOR DOING WHAT
YOU DID.
SHE LOOKS HAPPY.
>> SHE IS REALLY HAPPY.
DR. OZ: TOGETHER, CHANGE IS
HAPPENING.
OUR JOURNEY IS JUST BEGINNING.
[APPLAUSE]
[HEART BEAT]
>>> RIGHT NOW ON "PAGE SIX
TV" -- REAL HOUSEWIVES RAMONA
SINGER IS A TERRIBLE TIPPER.
WE HAVE ALL OF THE DETAILS ON
HER EPIC ETIQUETTE FAIL.
>>> YOU THINK THE FYRE FESTIVAL
WAS BAD, WAIT UNTIL CAN HE SHOW
YOU WHAT JA RULE HAS GOTTEN
HIMSELF INTO NOW.
>>> AND WHAT DOES DR. OZ AND THE
ALL-STAR WEEKEND HAVE IN COMMON?
>> AND RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT IN
2020?
>> I'M GOING TO RUN FOR
PRESIDENT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S ALL COMING UP ON "PAGE SIX
TV.."
>>> WELCOME TO "PAGE SIX TV."
HERE WE HAVE THE SENIOR REPORTER
CARLOS AND THE SENIOR COLUMNIST
MISS ELIZABETH WIESTER.
NOW THEY'RE NOT HAVING FUN
BECAUSE THEY'RE ALL IN THE MIRE
THAT ALL OF THE APPS SEEM TO DO.
TELL US ABOUT IT, CARLOS.
>> KIM KARDASHIAN IS BEING