>> Previously on
"The Young and the Restless"...
>> Summer: Hey, if you need to
get to the showcase, I can just
finish up with these guys and
meet you over there.
>> Fen: No.
No. No, no, no.
I still got a little more time.
>> Devon: So Fen's supposed to
be here right now.
Does anyone know where the hell
he is?
♪
>> ♪ Show me what you're working
with, show me how you do it ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
>> Lola: Because not having sex
is hurting you way more than
you'll have to admit.
>> Kyle: And whether we talk
about it or not, it's creating a
distance between us.
>> Nikki: Christine.
There won't be any trial today.
I have something to tell you.
>> Christine: Nikki, if you're
just trying to stall...
>> Nikki: No, I'm not.
You need to hear what I have to
say.
>> Victor: Sweetheart,
everything is going to be all
right.
>> Nikki: Yes. It will.
You can't do this.
My husband is innocent.
>> Rey: Get him in the car.
>> Nikki: No!
You're arresting the wrong
person!
>> Nick: Mom, please.
>> Victoria: You're making
things worse.
>> Michael: Don't say any more.
>> Nikki: I cannot stand by
another minute and watch my
husband be punished for
something he didn't do.
>> Victor: Nikki, don't do this.
♪
>> Jack: You and the polar bears
out there this morning, huh?
>> Kyle: Yeah.
>> Jack: You know I believe in
exercise, but I can't help
wondering if frostbite might
negate the benefits of swimming
in sub-zero temperatures.
>> Kyle: Yeah, the pool's
heated, and I needed to blow off
some steam.
>> Jack: What's wrong?
Problems at work?
>> Kyle: It's Lola.
I think it's over between us.
>> Fen: Hi, um, I just wanted to
say thank you --
>> Ana: [ Sighs ]
>> Fen: Look, Ana, I know you're
pissed at me.
>> Ana: You think?
>> Fen: Look, I get it, okay?
I screwed up big-time,
but, I swear, this will never
happen again.
>> Ana: You're right about that.
>> Fen: Wait a minute, you're
not saying that...
>> Ana: That Devon's gonna fire
you?
>> Fen: Look, I can make this
right, okay?
If you just give me another
chance...
>> Ana: It's not up to me.
>> Fen: Listen, you're the one
who believed in me from the very
beginning.
Okay?
All I'm asking is don't stop.
Okay? Please, Ana.
>> Victor: I love you for
wanting to help me.
>> Nikki: Then let me.
>> Victor: But this is not the
way.
Nicholas, take care of your
mother.
Make sure she gets to the
courthouse.
>> Nick: Mom, come on.
>> Victoria: Nick and I will
drive you.
>> Nikki: No. No!
No, stop it, both of you.
I can't let this happen.
>> Victor: You're going to be
okay, sweetheart.
>> Nikki: Victor, nothing about
this is okay.
>> Rey: Nikki, I understand that
you are upset, but interfering
like this isn't going to help.
>> Michael: You could make
things a whole lot worse.
>> Nikki: It couldn't get any
worse.
You are making a mistake.
>> Christine: The only one doing
that is you.
>> Rey: Let's go. Come on.
>> Nikki: All right, nobody is
listening to me!
You're arresting the wrong
person.
>> Nick: Mom.
>> Nikki: My husband did not
kill J.T., I did!
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
You can't put a price on love.
But if you did,
it'd cost the exact same
as a Reese's.
Turns out love's kinda
inexpensive.
Not Sorry. Reese's.
There's the same old way
to smooth, and there's
new Fructis Sleek Shot,
our first in-shower styler.
Just mix the shot
with shampoo,
power up with lather.
Five times
smoother hair,
half the time.
Skip the flat iron.
New Fructis
Sleek Shot.
By Garnier,
naturally!
New Fructis
Sleek Shot.
Well, here's to first dates!
You look amazing.
And you look amazingly
comfortable.
When your V-Neck looks more
like a U-Neck...
That's when you know, it's
Half-Washed.
Try Downy Fabric Conditioner.
Unlike detergent alone, Downy
helps prevent stretching
by conditioning and smoothing
fibers,
so clothes look newer, longer.
Downy and it's done.
>> TECH: At Safelite AutoGlass
we know that when you're
spending time with the grandkids
every minute counts.
And you don't have time
for a cracked windshield.
That's why we
show you exactly
when we'll be there.
Saving you time, so you
can keep saving the world.
>> KIDS: ♪ Safelite repair,
Safelite replace ♪
>> Additional sponsorship
provided by...
>> Jack: Look, whatever happened
between you and Lola, I'm sure
it's not as bad as you think it
is.
>> Kyle: She stormed out of
Crimson Lights in the middle of
our date.
>> Jack: Couples fight.
They argue.
>> Kyle: [ Sighs ]
>> Jack: Have you had a chance
to talk since about what
happened?
>> Kyle: Between her pop-up
stand and getting ready for
Abby's restaurant, I doubt she
has time to talk to me.
>> Jack: Oh, come on, you don't
believe that.
>> Kyle: Lola's career is one of
the main reasons there's been so
much tension between us lately.
>> Jack: You knew going into
this how important her work was
to her.
This is the opportunity of a
lifetime.
Of course this is gonna be her
top priority.
>> Kyle: I know!
And I love the way she's gone
after it.
She's never done anything close
to this, but she went into it
with this fearlessness and
confidence and a sense of
herself that blows me away.
She has this passion for what
she does that's so honest and
real, and it makes me want to be
around her all the time.
>> Jack: I'd say that's worth
fighting for.
>> Kyle: [ Sighs ]
>> Jack: And what better time
than Valentine's Week to prove
to her just how much she means
to you?
>> Kyle: Any suggestions?
>> Jack: Always.
Um, jewelry? Always nice.
A trip to New York.
Take in a few shows.
>> Kyle: Spending money is not
the way to impress Lola.
Whatever I do, it has to come
from the heart.
>> Jack: I have just the thing.
>> Fen: I know! I screwed up!
>> Ana: I believed in you.
I fought for you, and this is
how you repay me?
By blowing off an event that was
set up just to showcase you.
>> Fen: I didn't --
>> Ana: You, Fen!
>> Fen: I didn't blow it off!
Okay? I was --
I was dealing with some personal
stuff.
>> Ana: Don't BS me!
>> Fen: Look, what's the big
problem?
You stepped in.
Everyone got to see how great
you are.
>> Ana: This isn't about me.
Or Devon. It's about you!
And how selfish and
unprofessional you are!
Do you have any idea how many
singers would kill for the
opportunity you've been given?
>> Fen: I'm a jerk! I get it!
Okay?
I can't lose this, Ana.
I mean, singing...
It's the only thing I've ever
wanted to do.
And when you asked me to record
your song, and suddenly people
were downloading it and
streaming it...
You know, it all happened really
fast.
And I guess it just went to my
head.
>> Ana: If you went into this
just for the money or the
fame...
>> Fen: I didn't.
I didn't, I swear. All right?
Music means just as much to me
as it does to you.
And I know I'm gonna have to
work really hard if I'm gonna
make a career out of this, and
I'm willing to do that.
So will you just --
talk to Devon?
Please, Ana.
>> Rey: You killed J.T.?
>> Michael: Nikki, not another
word.
>> Christine: That's good
advice, Nikki.
>> Victor: Christine, this is
your fault, okay?
This is an obnoxious abuse of
power, to come here and put
handcuffs on me in front of my
family.
>> Christine: This is a
high-profile case.
We're just following procedure.
>> Victor: Really?
>> Nikki: This has gone on far
too long.
Too many people have been hurt,
and I need to put an end to it.
>> Michael: All right, Nikki,
let's go into another room and
discuss this.
>> Victor: That's a good idea.
>> Nikki: Victor!
I cannot let this go on.
I can't stand by and watch you
be accused of a crime I
committed!
>> Victor: Look, she's obviously
trying to help me, okay?
>> Nikki: You, sir, suspected me
from the very beginning.
>> Rey: Suspicion isn't proof.
>> Nikki: Remember that day you
saw me at the park after you
found J.T.'s watch?
>> Rey: Yeah.
You own Chancellor Park.
Pipe was busted.
It would make sense that you
would be there.
>> Nikki: I wasn't there because
of a plumbing problem.
>> Michael: Nikki, not another
word, I mean it!
Look, this -- this obviously
changes everything.
>> Victor: It doesn't change a
damn thing.
When nighttime
nasal congestion closes in,
Breathe Right strips
are designed to simply
open your nose right back up.
♪
Breathe better. Sleep better.
Breathe Right.
SHOW YOUR GUT SOME LOVE.
ONLY ACTIVIA HAS BILLIONS OF OUR
LIVE AND ACTIVE PROBIOTICS.
A DELICIOUS WAY TO ENJOY
PROBIOTICS EVERY DAY.
WITH 20 YEARS OF
DEVOTION TO GUT HEALTH.
ACTIVIA. LIKE NO OTHER.
(Thunderclap)
If your day doesn't
unfold as predicted.
Unfold this.
New Neutrogena®
Makeup Remover single.
And remove 99% of makeup.
100% rain or shine.
Neutrogena®.
You're going to do your thing.
And no period is going to slow
you down!
With Tampax, you get protection
that moves with you for total
comfort.
Choose Pearl for your chill,
Pocket for your moves,
and Active for your hustle.
Do your thing with Tampax.
>> Christine: Could what Nikki's
saying be true?
>> Rey: We have run a thorough
investigation, included all the
possibilities, including the
fact that Nikki could have
somehow had something to do with
Hellstrom's death.
>> Christine: Yeah, and we
concluded that all evidence
pointed to Victor.
>> Rey: Even before we got the
recording of him practically
confessing.
>> Christine: If Nikki testifies
that she killed J.T., it's gonna
be really difficult to prove
that Victor's guilty, and, my
God, if she's telling the
truth...
>> Rey: No one wants an innocent
man to go to prison.
>> Christine: What a mess.
>> Michael: Okay, you are all to
keep your mouth shut,
understand?
>> Nikki: Michael, I already --
>> Michael: Not a peep from any
of you.
>> Nick: We understand.
>> Michael: Oh, Christine, so,
um, how do you plan to proceed?
>> Christine: In light of this
new information, I think it
would in everyone's best
interest if we postponed
Victor's trial.
>> Nikki: [ Sighs ] Thank God.
Thank God.
>> Christine: Victor will remain
on bail under house arrest,
Nikki will be brought in for
questioning.
>> Victoria: Is she under
arrest?
>> Christine: Considering she
just confessed to a murder,
we have no other choice.
>> Rey: Give me your cuffs.
[ Clears throat ] Nikki Newman,
you are under arrest for the
murder of J.T. Hellstrom.
You have the right to remain
silent.
>> Summer: Hey.
>> Fen: Hey.
>> Summer: What happened?
>> Fen: Um...
Well, do you remember the
showcase I was supposed to be in
the other night?
>> Summer: Yeah, the one that
you were running late for?
>> Fen: Yeah, uh, well, by the
time I showed up, it was
practically over, and Devon and
Ana were super pissed, and now
she thinks he's gonna fire me.
>> Summer: Wait, because you
missed one promotional event?
>> Fen: This was a huge deal for
LP.
I mean, Devon put his reputation
on the line for me, and...
I made him look stupid in front
of a lot of really important
dudes.
I mean, it wasn't -- it wasn't
cool.
>> Summer: Okay, but people make
mistakes.
Who doesn't?
But you're good.
>> Fen: Yeah.
Apparently, that's not enough.
>> Summer: I guess it depends on
how much you want it.
>> Fen: I want it more than
anything, I really do, which...
makes me an even bigger idiot.
I mean, I had this big shot, and
I blew it over a girl who's not
even interested in me.
>> Summer: Fen, I like you.
But I have to be straight with
you.
I was just using you to make
Kyle jealous.
>> Fen: It's good, seriously.
Yeah, I was just using you to
make Lola jealous and to screw
with Kyle.
>> Summer: Oh.
>> Fen: This whole thing is
messed up.
You know, me and Kyle and this
stupid competition with each
other.
>> Summer: Yeah.
Yeah, well, I guess I played my
part in it, too.
>> Fen: No. No, this is all me.
>> Summer: Um, well, what if
there was a way that I could
make it up to you?
>> Fen: What?
Summer, please --
>> Summer: Devon! Hi!
>> Devon: Summer! How you doing?
Hey!
Heard you were back in town.
What's going on?
>> Summer: Yeah, um....
Can I talk to you for a minute?
>> Devon: We're actually kind of
in a rush right now.
>> Summer: I promise it's not
gonna take long at all.
>> Devon: Okay. Sure.
Hey.
>> Fen: Hey.
>> Devon: What would you guys
like to talk about?
>> Jack: The key to solving all
your problems.
>> Kyle: The Abbott cabin.
>> Jack: Isolated, cozy,
romantic, free -- all the things
you need to win Lola back.
>> Kyle: [ Chuckles ]
You think so?
>> Jack: What's the problem?
>> Kyle: Last time I invited
Lola to the cabin, she turned me
down.
>> Jack: She doesn't like life
in the woods?
>> Kyle: That's what I thought.
Turns out, she was worried
I was taking her there
to, uh, you know...
>> Jack: Were you?
>> Kyle: Not gonna lie, it was
on my mind.
>> Jack: Well, you'll have to
convince her this particular
getaway is about more than
just...you know.
>> Kyle: I have to convince her
it's not about that at all.
>> Jack: So you're not
interested, either.
>> Kyle: I'm very interested.
Lola isn't.
Not yet.
>> Jack: So, wait, the two of
you have never...?
>> Kyle: She hasn't...ever.
>> Jack: Okay.
>> Kyle: [ Sighs ]
She's waiting.
>> Jack: You okay with that?
>> Kyle: It's...new territory
for me.
>> Jack: So no.
>> Kyle: But I'm trying to be
understanding and patient.
>> Jack: But it's starting to be
an issue.
>> Kyle: It's what we fought
about.
That's why it's so important I
show her that I care about more
than just that.
I want her to know she's what
matters.
Her heart and soul,
the amazing person she is.
How do I do that?
>> Jack: Well, let's think about
it.
Um, we, uh...
We string lights around all the
trees around the cabin,
twinkling lights.
When you go to the cabin,
stop in town
You know the old General Store
there?
>> Kyle: Yeah.
>> Jack: Park there.
Go inside, get all the supplies
you need, including the makings
for a very simple but lovely
dinner.
>> Kyle: [ Scoffs ] Me, cook for
her?
>> Jack: She will love it, trust
me.
>> Kyle: If I don't kill her.
>> Jack: I will have a
horse-drawn sleigh waiting for
you when you get to the cabin.
>> Kyle: You don't think that's
too much?
>> Jack: Nothing over-the-top.
I'll insist.
It's charming and simple and
rustic.
>> Kyle: Perfect.
You're killing it, Dad.
>> Jack: I still got a few
tricks up my sleeve.
>> Kyle: Huh.
I'm gonna steal one.
Remember that invitation you
sent Kerry for Thanksgiving?
I want to make one like that for
Lola.
>> Jack: I hope it works as well
for you as it did for me.
>> Kyle: Mm.
I'll even hand-deliver it so she
knows I'm serious.
No cost involved whatsoever.
>> Jack: There we have it,
a man with a plan.
>> Kyle: Uh-huh.
Operation "Win Back Lola" is
hereby launched.
>> Jack: [ Chuckles ]
[ Cellphone chimes ]
>> Jack: Oh!
>> Kyle: We're a go.
MOVING?
THAT'S HARDER NOW BECAUSE
OF PSORIATIC ARTHRITIS.
BUT YOU'RE STILL MOVED
BY MOMENTS LIKE THIS.
DON'T LET PSORIATIC
ARTHRITIS TAKE THEM AWAY.
TALTZ REDUCES JOINT
PAIN AND STIFFNESS
AND HELPS STOP THE
PROGRESSION OF JOINT DAMAGE.
FOR PEOPLE WITH MODERATE
TO SEVERE PSORIASIS,
90% SAW SIGNIFICANT IMPROVEMENT.
TALTZ EVEN GIVES YOU A CHANCE
AT COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
DON'T USE IF YOU'RE
ALLERGIC TO TALTZ.
BEFORE STARTING, YOU SHOULD
BE CHECKED FOR TUBERCULOSIS.
TALTZ MAY INCREASE
RISK OF INFECTIONS
AND LOWER YOUR
ABILITY TO FIGHT THEM.
TELL YOUR
DOCTOR IF YOU
HAVE AN
INFECTION,
SYMPTOMS,
OR RECEIVED A
VACCINE OR PLAN TO.
INFLAMMATORY BOWEL DISEASE
CAN HAPPEN WITH TALTZ,
INCLUDING WORSENING OF SYMPTOMS.
SERIOUS ALLERGIC
REACTIONS CAN OCCUR.
FOR ALL THE THINGS
THAT MOVE YOU.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT TALTZ.
Don't let your longwear
weigh you down.
New Infallible Fresh Wear
Foundation by L'Oreal.
Get longwear coverage
from our most lightweight,
breathable formula.
Defies sweat and transfer.
Stays fresh. Feels light.
All day to night.
New Infallible Fresh Wear
by L'Oreal.
This is nice.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is nice.
Mmmm how did you make the
dip so rich and creamy?
Oh, it's a Philadelphia-
-Family Recipe.
Can I see it?
No.
New Philadelphia Dips.
So good,
you'll take all the credit.
Live from the Starlite Lounge.
♪ One plus one equals
too little too late ♪
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]
♪ ♪ ♪
IF YOU HAVE RECURRING
CONSTIPATION AND BELLY PAIN,
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR AND
SAY YESSS! TO LINZESS.
YESSS!
LINZESS TREATS ADULTS WITH IBS
WITH CONSTIPATION
OR CHRONIC CONSTIPATION.
LINZESS CAN HELP RELIEVE
YOUR BELLY PAIN,
AND LETS YOU HAVE MORE FREQUENT
AND COMPLETE BOWEL MOVEMENTS.
SEE IF YOU'RE ELIGIBLE
TO GET 90 DAYS
FOR AS LITTLE AS 30 DOLLARS.
DO NOT GIVE LINZESS TO
CHILDREN LESS THAN 6,
AND IT SHOULD NOT BE GIVEN TO
CHILDREN 6 TO LESS THAN 18,
IT MAY HARM THEM.
DO NOT TAKE LINZESS IF YOU
HAVE A BOWEL BLOCKAGE.
GET IMMEDIATE HELP
IF YOU DEVELOP UNUSUAL
OR SEVERE STOMACH PAIN,
ESPECIALLY WITH BLOODY
OR BLACK STOOLS.
THE MOST COMMON SIDE EFFECT
IS DIARRHEA, SOMETIMES SEVERE.
IF IT'S SEVERE,
STOP TAKING LINZESS
AND CALL YOUR
DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
OTHER SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
GAS, STOMACH-AREA
PAIN, AND SWELLING.
SO SAY YESSS!
TO HELP FOR RECURRING
CONSTIPATION.
YESSS! TO HELP
FOR BELLY PAIN.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
AND SAY YESSS! LINZESS.
Super Emma just about sleeps in
her cape.
But when we realized she was
battling sensitive skin,
we switched to Tide PODS Free &
Gentle.
It's gentle on her skin, and
Dermatologist recommended.
Tide Free and Gentle.
Safe for skin with Psoriasis,
and Eczema.
>> Devon: Thank you.
>> Summer: Yeah.
>> Ana: Thank you.
>> Devon: Ana and I actually
have some business to discuss
with Fen.
>> Summer: Oh, good. Good.
Um, I'm glad because I heard
that you were thinking about
dropping him from your label,
which would be a really huge
mistake.
>> Devon: Well, I appreciate
your input, Summer, but --
>> Summer: Devon, please, you
just have to hear me out.
>> Fen: This wasn't my idea.
>> Devon: Okay.
I'll hear you out.
>> Summer: Okay, um, look, I
know that you guys are really
mad at Fen because he missed a
super-important promotional
event.
>> Ana: He was supposed to be
our featured performer.
>> Summer: I know, and it sucks
that he was a no-show, but that
is on me, 100%.
>> Devon: I don't know how you
figure that because Fen's a
grown man, and he's responsible
for his own decisions, right?
>> Summer: He is, totally, and
he decided to put me ahead of
himself.
Okay, I was having a major
crisis, and instead of just
bailing on me to promote his
singing, he decided to stay with
me.
And he knew what it could cost
him, but he chose being a friend
over his career.
>> Devon: And why didn't you
tell me this before, Fen?
>> Summer: Because Fen doesn't
make excuses, and I cannot let
you guys think that he just
bailed on you because he didn't
care, okay?
I pulled him into my own crap,
and I would just really --
I would just hate to see him
lose his dream because of that.
>> Devon: Well, the thing is,
is, you know, in life, you have
to live with the choices you
make.
>> Summer: Yes, and that's the
biggest irony of it all, is that
I don't even think Fen regrets
what he did.
That's just the kind of guy he
is.
>> Devon: It's nice of you, Fen,
but it's gonna take a bit more
than that to be successful in
the music business.
>> Summer: Okay, well, Fen has
the rest.
You know, he's -- he's talented,
he's passionate.
I mean, he could be a major
star.
You guys wouldn't have signed
him if you didn't think so.
And he was willing to risk all
of that for me.
He put a friend ahead of
himself.
I mean, come on, haven't either
of you guys ever done that
before?
>> Ana: Devon, can I talk to you
for a minute?
>> Devon: Sure.
Excuse me.
>> Summer: Yeah.
>> Fen: That was incredible.
>> Summer: What, you don't think
I'm capable of doing something
nice occasionally?
>> Fen: No, I just --
I just hope it works.
>> Rey: Okay, so...
You claim...
you killed J.T. Hellstrom.
>> Nikki: I did kill him.
>> Rey: Yet you kept quiet for
all those months.
>> Nikki: I was afraid.
>> Rey: You were afraid.
No guilt or remorse?
>> I have felt terrible about
what I had done to J.T., but...
I did what I had to do,
what I was forced to do.
>> Rey: All right.
So, tell me, what happened the
night of J.T.'s death?
>> Michael: Nikki.
You don't have to say a word.
>> Nikki: I have nothing to
hide, not anymore.
It was the Girls' Night at
Victoria's house.
>> Rey: Mm.
>> Nikki: Victoria, Sharon,
Phyllis, Mariah, and me.
We were comforting Victoria over
her break-up with J.T.
She got emotional and went
upstairs to try to calm down a
little bit, and she -- she was
gone for a long time, so...
I got worried and, by then,
Mariah had passed out, so I --
I told Sharon and Phyllis that I
wanted to go up and check on
Victoria.
>> Rey: Mm, so you went upstairs
alone?
>> Nikki: Yes.
And as I approached the bedroom,
I could hear a lot of yelling
and -- and crashing going on
inside.
So I went in, and J.T. was
screaming at her, and he was
choking her.
And I had tried to get him to
stop, and he --
He just threw me off of him, and
I landed on the floor by the
fireplace.
And then I saw the fireplace
poker, and I...
I grabbed it,
and then I yelled at him
to stop it.
>> Rey: And?
>> Nikki: And he did.
But the look in his eyes...
it was pure hate.
>> Rey: Then what happened?
>> Nikki: Then he left through
the window.
>> Rey: So you -- you followed
him?
>> Nikki: I was most concerned
with making sure Victoria was
okay, that she was all right.
And then I promised her that I
would protect her, keep her
safe.
And then she and I went back
downstairs to the party, and
then, when I felt nobody was
really noticing, I slipped out,
determined to keep my promise.
>> Rey: You took the poker with
you?
>> Nikki: For protection.
>> Rey: I assume you, uh,
tracked down J.T.?
>> Nikki: Yes.
>> Rey: What happened next?
>> Nick: I don't think she was
planning on confessing.
So whatever she's saying, she's
winging it.
>> Victoria: Which means she
doesn't have any idea what she's
going to say, and neither do we.
>> Nikki: When I went outside,
he was there.
He took off on foot, so I
followed him to Chancellor Park.
That's -- That's where I
confronted him.
>> Rey: And?
>> Nikki: I told him that I knew
what he had done to Victor.
And to Victoria.
And he laughed.
He said that the police couldn't
stop him and neither could I,
and he vowed to finish what he
had started.
He said it would be easy because
Victor was still in the
hospital and because Victoria
was weak.
I raise the poker and I told him
I wasn't.
And he mocked me.
He taunted me.
He said that I was a coward,
just like the rest of my family.
And he threatened to just take
us all out, one by one, starting
with me.
Well, I -- I knew what he was
capable of, and so I raised my
poker again, and I told him to
back away.
But then he lunged at me.
And I just swung that poker as
hard as I could.
And it hit him in the head.
I was so stunned when he went
down because I --
I didn't mean to hurt him.
>> Rey: Why didn't you call the
police?
>> Nikki: Once I realized he was
dead, I panicked and...
I didn't think that you would
believe that it was in
self-defense.
>> Rey: So you decided to dig a
hole and bury him instead?
>> Nikki: I was already there.
The garden we were planting...
I just rolled his body into the
dirt, and put more on top of it,
and that was it, I left.
>> Rey: Hoping no one would find
out what you did.
>> Nikki: Make no mistake, I am
not proud of what I did.
But wouldn't you protect your
family if somebody threatened
them?
If somebody hurt your wife or
your sister and then threatened
to do it again?
Wouldn't you do anything you
could to stop them?
>> Rey: Let's take a break.
>> Michael: I'll be right back.
Detective!
Care to share anything?
>> Rey: You believe her?
>> Michael: You really expect me
to answer that?
>> Rey: That's what I thought.
If your adventure keeps turning
into unexpected bathroom trips
you may have overactive bladder,
or OAB.
Ohhhh... enough already! We need
to see a doctor.
Ask your doctor about Myrbetriq®
(mirabegron).
It treats OAB symptoms of
urgency, frequency, and leakage.
It's the first and only OAB
treatment in its class.
Myrbetriq may increase blood
pressure.
Tell your doctor right away if
you have trouble
emptying your bladder or have a
weak urine stream.
Myrbetriq may cause serious
allergic reactions
like swelling of the face, lips,
throat or tongue,
or trouble breathing.
If experienced, stop taking and
tell your doctor right away.
Myrbetriq may interact with
other medicines.
Tell your doctor if you have
liver or kidney problems.
Common side effects include
increased blood pressure,
common cold or flu symptoms,
sinus irritation, dry mouth,
urinary tract infection, bladder
inflammation,
back or joint pain,
constipation, dizziness, and
headache.
Need some help managing your OAB
symptoms along the way?
Ask your doctor if Myrbetriq is
right for you,
and visit Myrbetriq.com to learn
more.
Stouffer's Lasagna With Meat &
Sauce
has two times the beef of the
leading meat sauce lasagna.
That's double the tender ground
beef
baked into every cheesy,
mouthwatering bite.
When it comes to irresistible
taste,
more is always more.
Stouffer's.
Ok I'll admit. I didn't keep my
place as clean as I would like
'cuz I'm way too busy.
Who's got the time to chase
around down dirt, dust and hair?
So now, I use Heavy Duty Swiffer
Sweeper and Dusters.
For hard-to-reach places, Duster
makes it easy to clean.
It captures dust in one swipe.
Ha! Gotcha!
And Sweeper Heavy
Duty cloths lock away
twice as much dirt and dust.
It gets stuff deep in the
grooves other tools can miss.
Y'know what? My place... is a
lot cleaner now.
Stop cleaning. Start Swiffering.
On tour, every second counts.
I need great without the wait.
New Elvive
Rapid Reviver
Deep Conditioners
work fast
with no leave in time.
2x easier detangling
2x less breakage
than with a leading conditioner.
New Elvive
Rapid Revivers.
Start reviving.
♪ Seed to the oat, to the O ♪
♪ To the honey in each bite ♪
♪ Healthy hearts make life
sweeter ♪
♪ So you can live it right ♪
♪ The good goes around and
around  and around and around ♪
>> "The Young and the Restless"
will continue.
>> Fen: So, uh, have you guys
made a decision?
>> Devon: Oh, yes, we have.
I don't know if you're gonna
like it, though.
>> Fen: You're dropping me.
>> Devon: All right, Fen, I --
I took a big chance when I
signed you.
>> Fen: No, I know, and I let
you down.
>> Devon: Yes, you did, but Ana
just went to bat for you.
>> Fen: Thanks.
>> Devon: And luckily she's not
just loyal, she's smart and she
reminded me of all the time and
money and energy that we've
already invested into your
career.
>> Fen: Look, I know I haven't
said it, but I appreciate
everything that you guys have
done for me.
>> Devon: Well, we're gonna give
you one last chance to prove
that that's the truth and to
show that you have what it takes
to make it in this business.
>> Fen: Absolutely, yeah.
>> Devon: Okay.
So here's the deal.
Here's what's gonna happen.
We're gonna send you out on the
road, and you're gonna be
opening at small venues for some
of our more established artists.
I'm not talking about
10,000-people arenas or partying
all night.
I'm talking about real hard
work.
>> Ana: It'll give you a chance
to learn from some pros and
prove yourself.
Really develop as a musician.
>> Devon: That's right, and
after the tour, if it went well,
then we will talk about where we
go from there with you.
Is that cool?
>> Fen: I --
>> Summer: Give the man an
answer.
>> Fen: Yes!
Yes, uh...
Thank you.
I can't believe you're taking
another shot on me, I'm --
I won't --
You won't regret this, okay?
Thank you.
>> Devon: Thank Ana.
>> Fen: Thank you.
>> Ana: Don't blow it.
>> Fen: I won't, I swear.
>> Devon: All right.
It was good to see you.
>> Summer: Yeah. You, too.
>> Fen: Oh, my God!
Thank you. That was, um...
That was so cool.
I -- I feel like I should take
you out for dinner or drinks so
I can just...
Thank you.
>> Summer: Sure.
I mean, um, somewhere expensive
will do.
>> Fen: Yeah!
Yeah, uh, well, I mean, maybe
tonight or tomorrow, and then we
can just --
>> Summer: Um, you know,
actually, maybe not tonight,
but, um, if I don't see you,
have a great tour.
Let me know how it goes, okay?
Good job!
>> Fen: Yeah, sure. Will do.
>> Summer: Um, hey.
Uh, do you want to get coffee?
>> Kyle: I'm looking for Lola.
>> Summer: Okay, so now you
can't even be seen talking to
me?
I thought you said that she
wasn't jealous or insecure.
>> Kyle: Lola's fine with me
talking to other women, just...
>> Summer: Mm, not me.
>> Kyle: Look, it's Valentine's
Day tomorrow.
I'm trying to do something
special.
>> Summer: Oh, and three's a
crowd.
>> Kyle: Well, yeah, it kind of
is.
>> Summer: Okay, well, you can
just sit with me while you wait
for her.
>> Kyle: She'll be here any
minute.
>> Summer: Okay.
[ Cellphone chimes ]
>> Kyle: [ Sighs ]
>> Summer: Or not.
>> Kyle: She's just running
late, that's all.
>> Summer: Okay, well, the offer
still stands.
>> Rey: Your son-in-law was
wanted for the attempted murder
of your husband.
I am assuming that Victoria was
gonna press charges.
So why didn't you call the
police when J.T. showed up to
Victoria's house?
>> Nikki: After I saw him attack
her, the only thing I could
think about what protecting her.
>> Rey: Serve and protect.
That's our job.
But instead of coming to us,
you went after J.T. Hellstrom
with a fireplace poker?
>> Michael: That was previously
stated, so unless you have
another question...
>> Nikki: You don't have any
children, do you, Detective?
>> Rey: I'm not sure how that's
relevant.
>> Nikki: If you did, you would
understand this primal feeling
that a parent has to protect
their child.
Reason and logic doesn't enter
into it.
If your child is in danger, you
act, and that's what I did.
I didn't think about anything
else, I just did what I knew I
had to do.
>> Rey: And what you had to do
was...
stop J.T.?
>> Nikki: I already told you
that.
>> Michael: I'd like to state,
for the record, that my client's
confession was made at a time
when she was under tremendous
stress...
>> Nikki: Michael, please don't
make excuses for me.
I know exactly what I'm saying.
I killed J.T. I acted alone.
Nobody else helped me.
And you can put that on the
record.
>> Nick: Where's Mom?
>> Christine: She's being
questioned.
>> Victoria: This is ridiculous.
She's innocent.
Michael, where's Mom?
I need to --
I need to make sure that she's
okay.
Mom!
Mom, are you okay?
>> Nikki: I'm okay, sweetheart.
>> Rey: We need to get her
processed.
>> Nick: Can we have a few
minutes with her?
>> Christine: She can't have
visitors till tomorrow.
>> Nick: Tomorrow?
>> Christine: We are doing our
job and sticking to protocol.
>> Victoria: [ Sighs ]
>> Nick: They cannot keep us
from seeing her.
>> Michael: We have other things
to discuss.
Like how I was blindsided by
your mother's confession.
Did either of you have any idea
that was she was planning to do
this?
>> Victoria: No, we had no idea.
>> Michael: Is what she's saying
true?
Look, if I'm gonna defend anyone
in this family, I need to know
what the hell is going on.
>> Nick: We don't know why she
confessed.
>> Victoria: What did Mom say to
Rey?
>> Michael: You know I can't
tell you that.
That's privileged information.
[ Door opens ]
>> Rey: I need to ask you some
questions.
>> Michael: Is she under arrest?
>> Rey: No, I just need to
verify some elements of Nikki's
story.
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
♪
Your toothpaste may taste fresh,
but is it removing
enough harmful plaque
from hard to reach areas?
Try Arm & Hammer Complete Care.
Its unique 50% baking soda
formula neutralizes acid
and removes
up to 5X more plaque.
Try Arm & Hammer Complete Care.
Oh milk. Am I willing to pay
the price for loving you?
You'll make my morning, but
ruin my day.
Complicated relationship with
milk?
Pour on the Lactaid, 100% real
milk,
just without that annoying
lactose.
Mmm, that's good.
So there you are with
your depression
and your dirty laundry that you
just don't want to deal with.
Because depression is
multiple symptoms.
Yeah, time for a change.
And your doctor tells you
about TRINTELLIX,
a prescription medicine
for depression.
So you're feeling this
overall relief.
And TRINTELLIX had no
significant impact on weight
in clinical trials.
You got this.
Tell your doctor right away if
you have worsening depression,
unusual changes in
mood, behavior
or thoughts of suicide.
Antidepressants can increase
these in children, teens,
and young adults.
Do not take with MAOIs.
Tell your doctor about your
medications including
migraine, psychiatric and
depression medications to avoid
a potentially life-threatening
condition.
Increased risk of bleeding and
bruising may occur especially
if taken with NSAID pain
relievers, aspirin
or blood thinners.
Manic episodes or vision
problems may occur
in some people.
May cause low sodium levels.
Common side effects include
nausea, constipation
and vomiting.
Not living in sweatpants.
Ask your doctor about changing
to Trintellix.
>> Summer: Uh, so, did Lola say
why she was gonna be late?
>> Kyle: It was either because
of work or work.
Between her food truck
and the restaurant opening...
it's always one or the other.
>> Summer: Well, just cut her
some slack, okay?
You know what it's like to be
involved in a big project,
wanting to prove yourself, so...
>> Kyle: You're defending Lola?
>> Summer: Well, yeah, I mean, I
got to admire a woman who's as
determined as she is.
I mean, look at the way that she
is sticking to this whole
"no sex" thing.
>> Kyle: She made a choice.
I respect it.
And there's more to being with
someone than having sex.
>> Summer: Yes, but it is an
important part, though.
I mean, you used to think so.
>> Kyle: It's not like Lola and
I are never gonna do it.
>> Summer: No, of course.
I mean, it's just...
>> Kyle: What?
>> Summer: I just can't help
wondering if there isn't
something else holding her back
besides her principles.
>> Kyle: If you're trying to
make me doubt her or my feelings
about her, you can --
>> Summer: No, no, I'm not.
I'm not.
You have given your heart
and soul to this relationship.
I'm just wondering if Lola's
giving as much as you are.
You deserve that.
>> Lola: I'm sorry I'm late.
>> Kyle: I'm just glad you're
here.
I didn't like the way we left
things the other night.
>> Lola: Yeah. Me, either.
>> Kyle: I wanted to call, but I
wasn't -- I didn't know if --
[ Sighs ]
I don't like the way things have
been between us.
So...
I wanted to change that.
>> Lola: "Please join me for a
romantic Valentine's Day
celebration at the Abbott
cabin."
>> Rey: I'd like to talk to you
about the last time you saw J.T.
The night of your Girls' Party.
>> Michael: We've been through
that several times.
>> Rey: That was before Nikki
confessed.
>> Michael: Still, it doesn't
change Victoria's statement.
>> Rey: Well, let's take a look
at that.
You said...
J.T. came through the bedroom
window, right?
>> Victoria: That's right.
>> Rey: And you gave him cash,
$700, then he left?
>> Victoria: Yes.
>> Rey: How'd you say he left
again?
>> Victoria: The same way that
he came in -- through the
window.
>> Rey: Where was your mother
when he left?
>> Victoria: Shouldn't you have
all of that right there in that
book?
>> Rey: Nikki's version is a
little different.
I thought I might give you a
chance of reviewing the events
as you now remember them.
>> Victoria: My mother's
obviously lying.
She's just confessing to keep my
father from going to trial.
>> Rey: Because she felt guilty?
>> Victoria: Because he's being
accused of a crime that he
didn't commit.
My father was seriously ill in
the hospital when J.T.
disappeared, so he couldn't have
done it.
>> Rey: Well, no one actually
really knows when J.T. was
murdered, so it could have
happened when your father was
fully recovered.
>> Michael: Detective, with due
respect, Ms. Newman has already
made a statement about the night
J.T. came to her house.
So unless you have other
questions, we are done.
>> Rey: One more thing --
Is there a fireplace in your
bedroom?
>> Victoria: Yes.
>> Rey: When was the last time
you used it?
>> Victoria: I don't know.
It's been ages.
>> Michael: Is that all?
>> Rey: For now.
Hey! It's me! Your dry skin!
I'm craving something
we're missing.
The ceramides in CeraVe.
They help restore
my natural barrier,
so I can lock in moisture...
and keep us protected.
We've got to have
each other's backs...
and fronts.
CeraVe. What your skin CraVes.
DENTAL INSURANCE. MANY EMPLOYERS
DON'T OFFER IT. MEDICARE DOESN'T
INCLUDE IT. AND PEOPLE WHO WORK
FOR THEMSELVES OFTEN DON'T
CONSIDER IT. BUT WITH HUMANA YOU
CAN STILL HAVE IT. STARTING AT
JUST $17 A MONTH. THAT'S LESS
THAN 60 CENTS A DAY. CALL TODAY
FOR A FREE QUOTE. WITH A HUMANA
DENTAL PLAN YOU'LL GET 100%
COVERAGE FOR IN-NETWORK
PREVENTIVE CARE SUCH AS ORAL
EXAMS, CLEANINGS, AND X-RAYS.
PLUS, YOU'LL SAVE ON FILLINGS,
CROWNS AND OTHER DENTAL
PROCEDURES. AND YOU CAN'T BE
TURNED DOWN BECAUSE OF AGE OR
PRE-EXISTING CONDITIONS. WITH A
LARGE NETWORK OF DENTISTS AND
SPECIALISTS AND A VARIETY OF
AFFORDABLE PLANS, YOU'RE SURE TO
FIND ONE TO FIT YOUR FAMILY'S
NEEDS AND BUDGET. PLUS, HUMANA
HAS VISION PLANS TOO. WITH
COVERAGE FOR EXAMS, EYE GLASSES,
AND MORE. HOW MUCH COULD YOU
SAVE? THERE'S A QUICK, EASY WAY
TO FIND OUT. CALL HUMANA NOW AT
THE NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN FOR A
FREE QUOTE. AND DISCOVER THE
COVERAGE YOU NEED AT A PRICE
THAT WILL MAKE YOU SMILE.
♪
HEYYYYY!
It's the little things
that make life rich.
Ritz.
Dry mouth has been
a problem for me.
I just drank tons of water
all the time,
it was never enough.
My dentist
suggested Biotene.
My mouth felt more lubricated.
I use the Biotene rinse
and then I use the spray.
Biotene did make
a difference.
[heartbeat]
To most, he's
Phil Mickelson...
..pro golfer.
To me, he's...
...well, Dad.
So when his
joint pain from
psoriatic arthritis
got really bad, it scared me.
And what could that pain mean?
Joint pain could
mean joint damage.
ENBREL helps
relieve joint pain...
...helps stop irreversible
joint damage...
and helps skin get clearer.
ENBREL may lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious, sometimes
fatal events...
including infections,
tuberculosis...
lymphoma, other cancers,...
nervous system and
blood disorders...
and allergic
reactions have occurred.
Tell your
doctor if you've
been some place where
fungal infections are common.
Or, if you're
prone to infections,
have cuts or sores,
have had hepatitis B,
have been treated
for heart failure...
or if you have
persistent fever...
bruising, bleeding, or paleness.
Don't start ENBREL...
if you have an
infection like the flu.
Since ENBREL...
Dad's back to being... Dad.
Visit Enbrel.com...
and use the Joint
Damage Simulator
to see how your joint
damage could be progressing.
Ask about ENBREL.
ENBREL.
FDA approved for
over 16 years.
The best eggs...
in so many ways.
Which cage free eggs
taste fresher and more
delicious?
Only Eggland's Best.
Which organic eggs
have more vitamins
and less saturated fat?
Only Eggland's Best.
Better taste, better
nutrition, better eggs.
>> Kyle: It's too much.
I told my dad going away to the
cabin was a bad idea.
>> Lola: It's not that.
>> Kyle: If you're worried this
is about us having sex, then --
>> Lola: No, I know you wouldn't
pressure me into that.
>> Kyle: Then what's the
problem?
I get that you're busy, but it's
just a few days.
>> Lola: No.
It's not, Kyle.
It's so much more than that.
>> Kyle: I don't understand.
>> Lola: Well, that's just it.
I mean, it's like you don't get
how big this opportunity is for
me.
I mean, Devon and Abby are
giving me the chance to make my
dreams come true.
We're less than two weeks from
opening, and you're asking me to
go on a vacation with you.
It's like you don't understand.
>> Kyle: Of course I do!
>> Lola: Then you're not
listening to me.
>> Kyle: Look, I know how much
your career means to you.
I'm into mine, too, but if you
want to be with somebody, you
got to make time for them.
>> Lola: Maybe you can take off
work whenever you want, but I
can't.
>> Kyle: Can't or won't?
>> Lola: You obviously put a lot
of effort into this.
>> Kyle: Yeah.
I was hoping you'd be willing to
do the same.
>> Lola: Then I guess we're on
different tracks.
Want different things.
>> Kyle: I know what I want.
>> Lola: Me, too.
And I think it's best that we
both admit that and go our
separate ways.
I -- I'm sorry, Kyle.
>> Summer: Kyle --
>> Kyle: Not now, Summer.
>> Victor: How's your mother?
>> Victoria: [ Sighs ] They
wouldn't let us talk to her.
>> Nick: Christine claimed that
she needed to be processed, but
it was just an excuse to keep
Mom and Vick apart.
>> Victoria: They wanted to
question me before we could
coordinate our stories.
>> Victor: What did you tell
them?
>> Victoria: I didn't know what
to tell them.
I just stuck to my original
statement.
I had no choice because I don't
know what Mom told them.
>> Nick: They're gonna want to
question Sharon and Phyllis
next.
>> Victor: Well, we have to warn
them.
>> Nick: Well, Phyllis is in
Chicago on business.
She's not gonna be home till
late.
And Sharon is on a field trip
with Faith.
So calling or texting can be
risky.
>> Victoria: It's gonna be
impossible to coordinate our
stories.
This whole thing is starting to
unravel.
>> Michael: I need you to be
honest with me.
Otherwise, I can't defend you.
>> Nikki: I appreciate you being
here, Michael, but I don't need
your help.
>> Michael: Why do all the
Newmans make it so difficult for
me to do my job, hmm?
[ Door opens ]
>> Rey: Paperwork's done.
>> Nikki: Have the charges
against Victor been dropped?
>> Rey: Victor's trial has been
officially postponed.
He will remain out on bail.
But until this gets all sorted
out, we'll have to keep you in
custody.
>> Nikki: What is there to be
sorted out?
I've confessed.
>> Rey: Did you really think you
could get away with lying to me?
>> Michael: Don't answer that.
>> Nikki: I killed J.T.
>> Rey: Oh, I definitely think
you were involved with his
death, that you know what really
happened, but you didn't do it
alone.
And I'm gonna prove it.