>> IT SEEMS THAT TELEVISION HAS
BECOME AN ELECTRONIC
CONFESSIONAL.
>> IT IS EXCITING STUFF.
>> WHAT ARE WE DOING HERE?
>> ANY TOOL FOR HUMSSION
WORST IN US, ANDION■k
BEEN THERE.
>> HERE'S MICHAEL AT THE FOUL
LINE.
GOOD!
>> PEOPLE ARE NO LONGER
EMBARRASSED TO ADMIT THEY WATCH
TELEVISION.
>> HELLO.
>> PEOPLE USED TO SAY "I WAS
THERE."
NOW THEY SAY THEY WATCH IT ON
TELEVISION.■goo
♪
♪■■■L■■[1 1
>> SLOWLY BUT SURELY, THE 1970s
ARE DISAPPEARING.
THE 1980s WILL BE UPON US.
WHAT A DECADE IT IS COMING UP.
HAPPY NEW YEAR!
>> AS YOU BEGIN THE '80s IN THE
TELEVISION WO
LñLñL■L■L■L■
WAS ON ANY GIVEN EVENING NINE
OUT OF TEN PEOPLE WATCHING ONLY
ONE OF THREE NETWORKS.
>> MORE THAN 30 MILLION PEOPLE
ARE ADDICTED TO IT.
SOCIAL CRITICS ARE MYSTIFIED BY
ITS SUCCESS.
WHAT IS IT?
IT'S TELEVISION'S PRIME TIME
PRAIRIE POT BOILER "DALLAS."
>> A MOVE LIKE THAT WILL DESTROY
ALL OF THE OIL.
AND IT'LL RUIN OUR NAME.
>> BROTHER OR NO BROTHER, I'LL
STOP YOU FROM DESTROYING OIL.
>> DALLAS DID ESTABLISH NEW
GROUNDS IN TERMS OOF A ONE-HOUR
SHOW THAT CAPTIVATED AMERICA FOR
13 YEARS.
>> DALLAS IS A TELEVISION SHOW
ROOTED IN THE 1970s.
AND ONE OF THE CRAZY THINGS THAT
EMERGES IS THIS CHARACTER HAS A
POP PHENOMENON.
>> TELL ME J.R., WHICH SLUT ARE
YOU GOING TO STAY WITH TONIGHT?
>> IT'S GOT TO BE MORE
INTERESTING THAN THE SLUT I'M
LOOKING AT RIGHT NOW.
>> HE WAS SUCH A DELICIOUS
VILLAIN.
EVERYONE WAS ENAMORED BY THIS
CHARACTER.
>> AT THIS POINT SO MANY PEOPLE
WERE WATCHING TELEVISION THAT
YOU COULD DO SOMETHING SO
UNEXPECTED THAT IT WOULD BECOME
NEWS OVERNIGHT.
>> WHO IS HE?
>>
>> THE NATIONAL OBSESSION IN
1980 AROUND WHO SHOT J.R.
IT'S HARD TO IMAGINE HOW
OBSESSED WE ALL WERE WITH THAT
QUESTION.
BUT WE WERE.
>> WHO SHOT J.R. IS ABOUT AS
IDEAL A CLIFFHANGER AS YOU
POSSIBLY COULD GET.
>> WHO DID.?
WE MAY NEVER GET THE ANSWER TO
THAT QUESTION.
THE PEOPLE WHO PRODUCE THAT
PROGRAM ARE GOING TO KEEP US IN
SUSPENSE AS LONG AS THEY
POSSIBLY CAN.
>> WE SHOT J.R., AND THEN WE
BROKE FOR THE SUMMER.
THEN COINCIDENTALLY THE ACTORS
WENT ON STRIKE.
IT DELAYED THE RESOLUTION, AND
IT JUST STARTED TO PERCOLATE
THROUGH THE WORLD.
>> I REMEMBER GOING ON VACATION
TO ENGLAND THAT SUMMER, AND
THAT'S ALL THAT PEOPLE WERE
TALKING ABOUT THERE.
>> WELL, WE KNOW YOU DON'T DIE.
I MEAN, YOU COULDN'T DIE.
>> WE DON'T KNOW THAT.
>> HOW COULD YOU DIE?
YOU COULDN'T COME BACK NEXT
SEASON.
>> THAT'S WHAT I MEAN.
I COULDN'T COME BACK BUT THE
SHOW COULD STILL GO.
>> OH, BUT YOU WOULDN'T.
WHAT IS THAT SHOW WITHOUT J.R.?
>> WELL, THAT'S WHAT I FIGURE,
YEAH.
>> I GUESS IF YOU DON'T KNOW BY
NOW WHO SHOT J.R., YOU PROBABLY
DO NOT CARE.
LAST NIGHT SOME 82 MILLION
AMERICANS DID.
AND THEY WATCHED THE MUCH-TOUTED
"DALLAS" EPISODE."
IT COULD BECOME THE MOST-WATCHED
TELEVISION SHOW EVER.
>> WHO SHOT J.R. IS A REFLECTION
OF OLD-FASHIONED TELEVISION.
IT'S A MOMENT THAT GATHERS
EVERYBODY AROUND THE ELECTRONIC
FIREPLACE WHICH IS NOW THE
TELEVISION SET.
>> ONE SPECIAL AMERICAN
TELEVISION PROGRAM.
CRITICS SAID IT TRANSCENDS IN
POPULARITY EVER OTHER AMERICAN
STATEMENT ABOUT WAR.<=
AND SOMETHING SPECIAL HAPPENED
TODAY TO MOBILE ARMY SURGICAL
HOSPITAL 4077.
THAT WILL TOUCH MILLIONS OF
AMERICANS.
IT WAS THE KIND OF EVENT THAT
WOULD DRAW THE WORLD'S BREATH.
STAGE 9, 20th CENTURY FOX
STUDIOS, THE END OF THE KOREAN
WAR, THE TELEVISION SEASON OF
"M.A.S.H."
>> IT'S BEEN AN HONOR AND A
PRIVILEGE TO HAVE WORKED WITH
YOU.
AND I'M VERY, VERY PROUD TO HAVE
KNOWN YOU.
>> THERE WERE THOSE LANDMARK
TIMES WHEN SHOWS THAT HAD BEEN
WATCHED THROUGH THE '70s AND
INTO THE '80s, LIKE "M.A.S.H."
HAD ITS FINAL EPISODE.
AND WE WERE ALL SAD TO SEE THEM
GO.
>> I'LL MISS YOU.
A LOT.
>> ALL OVER THE COUNTRY, ARMIES
OF FANS CROWDED AROUND
TELEVISION SETS TO WATCH THE
FINAL EPISODE AND TO BID
"M.A.S.H." FAREWELL.
>> THE FINALE OF "M.A.S.H."
WAS UNPRECEDENTED.
123 MILLION PEOPLE WATCHED ONE
TELEVISION PROGRAM AT THE SAME
TIME.
>> YOU KNOW, I REALLY SHOULD BE
ALLOWED TO GO HOME.
I -- THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH
ME.
>> WHEN WE ENDED THE SHOW, WE
GOT TELEGRAMS OF CONGRATULATIONS
FROM HENRY KISSINGER AND RONALD
REAGAN.
THE SIZE OF THE RESPONSE AND THE
EMOTIONAL NATURE OF THE RESPONSE
THAT WE WERE GETTING WAS
DIFFICULT FOR US TO UNDERSTAND.
>> WHO SHOT J.R. AND THE LAST
EPISODE OF "M.A.S.H." ARE THE
LAST CALL FOR THE PRE-CABLE
WORLD OF TELEVISION.
IT'S LIKE THEY ARE THE LAST TIME
THAT THAT HUGE AUDIENCE WILL ALL
TURN UP FOR ONE EVENT.
>>> TV IS GROWING UP WITH CABLE.
TV IS GROWING UP WITH CONTENT.
TV IS GROWING UP WITH DIFFERENT
GENRES.
THE FUNDAMENTAL THING THAT CABLE
DID AND THE VCR DID OR THE
REMOTE CONTROL DID IS IT GAVE
CONSUME .
AND EVERYTHING WAS ABOUT TO
CHANGE.
It is with a very
gratesful heart
that I write you about
your amazing employees.
Eric volunteered to come
to my rescue that evening.
...to a mom, these
things really matter.
From this day forward,
I'm a Lexus
customer for life.
Thank you.
Sincerely...
Ivy, Kim, David, Greg.
Crafting every experience
for our guests with the same
level of care we
craft our vehicles.
That's what makes Lexus,
Lexus.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus dealer.
(Gasp)
(Singsong)
Budget meeting!
Sweet.
If you compare last quarter
to this quarter...
Various: Mmm.
It's no wonder everything
seems a little better
made with fresh milk
and real cream.
The cells in your body...
It's no wonder everything
see...work in harmony.
Like you, they get hungry.
Feed them...
...with new Centrum®
MultiGummies®
specially crafted for men and
women 50 and over.
So you're ready for anything.
Centrum®.
Feed your cells today.
With tough food, your dentures
may slip and fall.
Fixodent Ultra-Max Hold
gives you the strongest hold
ever
to lock your dentures.
So now you can eat tough food
without worry.
Fixodent and forget it.
145 over 92.
180 over 111.
I had a heart attack, a cardiac
arrest, and then a stroke.
Narrator: This is what high
blood pressure looks like.
You might not
feel its symptoms,
but the results from
a heart attack or stroke
are far from
invisible or silent.
Get back on your plan.
Or talk with your doctor
to create an exercise,
diet and medication
plan that works for you.
Go to LowerYourHBP.org
If I would've followed
a treatment plan,
I would not be in
this situation.
Take Prilosec OTC and take
control of heartburn.
So you don't have to stash
antacids here...
Here...
or, here.
Kick your antacid habit with
Prilosec OTC.
One pill a day,
24 hours, zero heartburn.
Summer's not the time
for making bucket lists
Bookers know
Summer is for Booking it
Like booking
a beachside resort,
and ordering two more tacos
than you need to.
Check.
Showing the deep end who's boss!
Starting a
scooter gang we Fam.
Check.
"Awesome"
Bookers know
Summer won't last forever.
"You're gonna thank me"
So be a Booker at Booking.com.
The World's number one choice
for booking accomodations.
♪ ♪ ♪
Discover new
San Pellegrino Essenza.
A twist of
Mediterranean flavors,
with the gentle bubbles
of San Pellegrino.
Add a twist of flavor.
■
San Pellegrino Essenza.
Tastefully Italian.
>>> THOMAS MAGNUM.
>> THE PRIVATE INVESTIGATOR?
>> YOU'RE PROBABLY WONDERING
ABOUT THE GOAT.
JUST LET ME DROP OFF MY FRIEND
AND THEN WE'LL TALK.
>> WHEN WE ENTERED THE '80s, A
LOT OF ONE-HOUR DRAMAS THAT WERE
LIGHT HEARTED LIKE "MAGNUM P.I."
WERE VERY POPULAR.
>> AFTER MASH WENT OFF THE HOUR,
THE NEXT SEASON THERE WASN'T A
SINGLE SITCOM IN THE TOP TEN,
FIRST TIME THAT HAD HAPPENED IN
TV HISTORY.
THE PREVAILING FEELING WAS THE
SI
SITCOM DEAD.
>> BRANDON TARTIKOFF, NBC
PROGRAMMING CHIEF, SAYS REPORTS
OF THE SITCOM'S DEATH WERE
GREATLY EXAGGERATED.
>> TIME AND TIME AGAIN, IF YOU
STUDY TELEVISION HISTORY, JUST
WHEN SOMEONE IS COUNTING A FORM
OUT, THAT'S EXACTLY THE FORM OF
PROGRAMMING THAT LEADS TO THE
NEXT BIG HIT.
>> 1984 "THE COSBY SHOW" COMES
ON.
BILL COSBY IS NOT NEW TO TV.
HE'S HAD OTHER TV SHOWS.
BUT "THE COSBY SHOW" IS VERY
DIFFERENT.
IT STANDS APART FROM EVERYTHING
ELSE HE'S DONE.
>> I WANTED MY EGGS SCRAMBLED.
>> COMING RIGHT UP.
>> THEY TALKED ABOUT PARENTING.
PREVIOUS TO THAT, THE KIDS WERE
COOL AND THE PARENTS WERE
IDIOTS.
THEN "COSBY" SAYS, THE PARENTS
ARE IN CHARGE, AND THAT WAS
SOMETHING NEW.
>> INSTEAD OF ACTING
DISAPPOINTED BECAUSE I'M NOT
LIKE YOU, MAYBE YOU CAN JUST
ACCEPT WHO I AM AND LOVE ME
ANYWAY BECAUSE I'M YOUR SON.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THAT'S THE DUMBEST THING I'VE
EVER HEARD IN MY LIFE!
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> IT HELPS THE CASTING A LOT IN
TELEVISION.
THE KIDS WERE JUST GREAT.
>> IF YOU WERE THE LAST PERSON
ON THIS EARTH, I STILL WOULDN'T
TELL YOU.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO TELL ME
WHAT YOU DID.
JUST TELL ME WHAT THEY'RE GONNA
DO TO YOU.
>> UNLIKE EVERY OTHER SHOW ON
TV, IT'S SHOWING AN UPPER MIDDLE
CLASS BLACK FAMILY.
THIS WASN'T "ALL IN THE FAMILY."
THEY WEREN'T TACKLING DEEP
ISSUES.
BUT THAT WAS OKAY.
THE MERE FACT THEY EXISTED WAS A
DEEP ISSUE.
>> THE DECADE WAS WAR ;p
SOMETHING REAL.
IN OTHER WORDS, UNLESS IT'S
REAL, IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE IT
MOVES ANYBODY.
IF SOMEONE'S FEELING SOMETHING,
YOU GET TO THE HEART, YOU GET TO
THE MIND.
AND IF YOU CAN HIT THE HEARTS
AND MINDS, YOU'VE GOT YOURSELF A
HIT.
>> HOW WAS SCHOOL?
>> SCHOOL?
DEAR, I BROUGHT HOME TWO
CHILDREN THAT MAY OR MAY NOT BE
OURS.
>> COSBY'S SHOW BROUGHT THIS
TREMENDOUS AUDIENCE TO NBC.
AND THAT WAS A BS.
I MEAN, OUR RATINGS WENT WAY UP.
♪ SOMETIMES YOU WANT TO GO WHER■
EVERYBODY KNOWS YOUR NAME ♪
>> EVEN THE THEME SONG TO
"CHEERS" PUTS YOU IN A GOOD
MOOD.
>> EVENING, EVERYBODY.
>> NORM!
>> NORMAN!
>> WHAT'S SHAKING, NORM?
>> ALL FOUR CHEEKS AND A COUPLE
OF CHINS, COACH.
>> BY THE END OF THE "CHEERS"
PILOT, NOT ONLY DID YOU KNOW WHO
EVERYBODY WAS, BUT YOU WANTED TO
COME BACK AND SEE WHAT WAS GOING
TO HAPPEN.
IT'S LIKE ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS
WATCH IT ONCE.
YOU'RE GOING TO LOVE THESE ■h■h
THESE ARE UNIVERSAL CHARACTERS,
AND THE HUMOR WORKED ON SO MANY
LEVELS.
>> I WAS UP UNTIL 2:00 IN THE
MORNING FINISHING OFF
KIERKEGAARD.
>> I HOPE HE THANKED YOU FOR IT.
>> YOU HAVE TO CREATE A
COMMUNITY THAT PEOPLE ARE
IDENTIFYING WITH.
AND "CHEERS" GIVES YOU THAT
>> BOY, I TELL YOU, I'VE ALWAYS
WANTED TO SKYDIVE.
I'VE JUST NEVER HAD THE GUTS.
>> WHAT'S DID IT FEEL LIKE?
>> I IMAGINE A LOT LIKE SEX.
>> I WOULD HAVE TO IMAGINE WHAT
SEX IS LIKE.
BUT I HAVE PLENTY OF SEX.
AND PLENTY OF THIS, TOO.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST GET OFF MY
>> IN THE FIRST EPISODE, THERE
WAS A RATHER PASSIONATE
ANNOYANCE.
I WAS SAYING, AH, SOMETHING'S
GOING ON HERE.
A REALLY INTELLIGENT WOMAN WOULD
SEE YOUR LINE OF B.S. A MILE
AWAY.
>> I'VE NEVER MET AN INTELLIGENT
WOMAN THAT I'D WANT TO DATE.
>> ON BEHALF OF THE INTELLIGENT
WOMEN AROUND THE WORLD, MAY I
JUST SAY, WHEW!
>> WE SAW WHAT TED AND SHELLY
HAD TOGETHER, WE SAID OH, NO,
WE'VE GOT TO DO THIS
RELATIONSHIP.
>> TED AND I UNDERSTOOD WHAT
THEY WERE WRITING RIGHT AWAY.
>> IF YOU'LL ADMIT THAT YOU ARE
CARRYING A LITTLE TORCH FOR ME,
I'LL ADMIT THAT I'M CARRYING A
>> WELL, I AM. YOU.
CARRYING A LITTLE TORCH FOR YOU.
>> WELL, I'M NOT CARRYING ONE
FOR YOU.
>> DIANE KNEW HOW TO TEASE SAM.
SAM KNEW HOW TO TEASE DIANE, ANU
>> THI
BETWEEN THE TWO OF THEM IGNITED
THE SHOW.AT'SDROVE THE SHOW FOR
THE FIRST FIVE YEARS.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
>> OH, I'M DEVASTATED.
I NEED SOMETHING EXPEDITIOUS AND
BRUTAL TO NUMB MY SENSIBILITIES
AND BLAST ME INTO SWEET
OBLIVION.
>> HOW ABOUT A BOILERMAKER?
>> MAKE IT A MIMOSA.
>> WE HAD THE LUCK TO BE ABLE TO
ROTATE CAST, AND EVERY TIME WE
PUT SOMEBODY IN, THEY WERE
EXPLOSIONS.
!
>> THERE WAS SOMETHING VERY
SPECIAL ABOUT THAT SETTING,
THOSE CHARACTERS, THAT I NEVER
GOT TIRED OF WRITING THAT SHOW.
>> SOPHISTICATED SURVEYS,
TELEPHONIC SAMPLINGS, TEST
AUDIENCES.
ALL OF THOSE THINGS HELP TO
SEPARATE WINNERS FROM LOSERS AND
MAKE MIDCOURSE CORRECTIONS.
BUT YOU CAN'T CUT ALL COMEDIES
FROM THE SAME COOKIE CUTTERS.
ALL YOU CAN HOPE IS EVERY NIGHT
TURNS OUT LIKE THURSDAY.
>> YO, ANGELA!
>> NEXT!
>> HOW RUDE.
>> HE'S QUICK, I'LL GIVE HIM
THAT.
>> ALL OF TELEVISION SAID, OH,
WELL, MAYBE THE SITCOMS ARE
ALIVE AGAIN.
AND THAT'S ALL THAT IT TOOK.
IT TOOK ONE SUCCESS.
>> A FEW YEARS FROM NOW,
SOMETHING NEW MAY TEMPT THE
PEOPLE WHO PICK WHAT WE SEE.
BUT IT'S A VERY SAFE GUESS THAT
WHATEVER GETS HOT FOR A SEASON
OR TWO, THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO
CREATE GOOD TELEVISION COMEDY
WILL BE LAUGHING ALL THE WAY TO
THE BANK.
My mom washes the dishes...
...before she puts them in the
dishwasher.
So what does the dishwasher do?
Cascade Platinum does the work
for you,
prewashing and removing
stuck-on foods,
the first time.
Wow, that's clean!
Cascade Platinum.
Wow. We did it.
We built the fastest network for
the latest iPhones.
And the iPhone XR, with a retina
display
that makes everything look
incredible...
It's like the perfect couple
- you know, the ones who look
great in every picture.
Like the ones who always make me
feel like a before photo.
Zoey and Chris.
Hey guys!
Hey... Zoey and Chris!
...how fun is that?
AT&T has the fastest network for
the latest iPhones.
Get the mindblowing iPhone XR on
us
when you buy the latest iPhone.
AT&T. More for your thing.
That's our thing.
(VO) Dogs have evolved,
but their nutritional needs
remain instinctual.
That's why there's
Purina ONE True Instinct.
High protein for
strong muscles.
A different breed of
natural nutrition.
Purina ONE True Instinct.
Also in Grain-Free
for dogs and cats.
Cake in the conference room!
Showing 'em you're ready to be
your own boss.
That's the beauty of your smile.
Bring out the best in it with
Crest 3D White.
Crest removes 95% of surface
stains...
In just three days.
>> LET'S BE CAREFUL OUT THERE.
>> DISPATCH.
WE HAVE A 911.
ARMED ROBBERY IN PROGRESS.
>> WHEN QUALITY DOES EMERGE ON
TELEVISION, THE PHRASE "TOO GOOD
FOR TV" IS OFTEN HEARD.
ONE RECENT NETWORK OFFERING THAT
SEEMS TO DESERVE THAT PHRASE IS
"HILL STREET BLUES."
>> "HILL STREET" IS ONE OF THE
CHANGING POINTS IN THE ENTIRE
INDUSTRY OF THE HISTORY OF TV.
>> WE HAD ALL WATCH AID
DOCUMENTARY ABOUT COPS AND HAD
THIS REAL HAND HELD IN THE
MOMENT QUALITY THAT WE WERE VERY
E
ENAMORED OF.
>> THE MINUTE YOU LOOKED AT IT,
IT LOOKED DIFFERENT.
IT HAD A MOOD TO IT.
YOU COULD ALMOST SMELL THE STALE
COFFEE.
>> WE DIDN'T WANT TO DO A
STANDARD COP SHOW WHERE, YOU
KNOW, YOU GOT A CRIME AND YOU
GOT YOUR TWO COPS, AND YOU GO
OUT AND YOU CATCH THE BAD GUY,
AND YOU SWEAT HIM AND HE
CONFESSES, AND THAT'S IT.
COPS HAVE PERSONAL LIVES THAT
IMPACT THEIR BEHAVIOR IN
PROFOUND WAYS.
>> WELL, WHAT ABOUT IT?
IS HE HERE OR IS HE ELSEWHERE?
>> DON'T GET EXCITED, COSTA,
WE'RE WORKING ON IT.
>> HOW IS THIS FOR LOGIC?
IF HE'S NOT HERE AND HE'S NOT
ELSEWHERE, HE'S LOST.
>> WE DIDN'T SAY THAT
COUNSELOR --
NOT LOST.
>> NEVER IN MY ENTIRE LIFE HAVE
I LISTENED TO SO MUCH
INCOMPETENCE COVERED UP BY SO
MUCH UNMITIGATED CRAP.
FIND MY CLIENT, OR, I SWEAR,
I'LL HAVE YOU UP ON CHARGES.
>> THERE WOULD BE THESE ONGOING
ARCS FOR THESE CHARACTERS THAT
WOULD PLAY OUT OVER FIVE, SIX
EPISODES, SOMETIMES AN ENTIRE
SEASON.
AND IN A WAY, FOR CERTAIN
STORIES, OVER THE ENTIRE SERIES.
AND NO ONE HAD REALLY DONE THAT
IN AN HOUR-LONG DRAMATIC SHOW.
>> THESE PAST FOUR MONTHS, I'VE
MISSED YOU.
I HAD TO FIND THAT OUT.
COME HOME, PIZZA MAN.
>> I THINK IN THE PAST, PEOPLE
HAD WATCHED TELEVISION
PASSIVELY.
AND THE ONE THING I THINK WE DID
SET OUT TO BE WERE PROVOCATEURS.
>> YOU WANT ACTION?
YOU FILL IT OUT.
>> WHAT THE HELL IS THE MATTER
WITH YOU, MAN?
>> I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING, THEY
DON'T PAY ME ENOUGH TO DEAL WITH
ANIMALS LIKE THIS!
THE FIRST THING THEY SEE IS A
WHITE FACE AND THEY WANT --
>> LISTEN TO ME, IT WAS A WHITE
FINGER THAT PULLED THE TRIGGER,
NOT A BLACK ONE, IT WAS A WHITE!
>> IT SET A TREND.
THE IDEA THE AUDIENCE CAN ACCEPT
ITS CHARACTERS■ ■ ■■■■■■■@■@■@■
THIS UNIFORM.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS IMPORTANT TO
FINALLY GET ACROSS.
>> NO BITING!
>> WE WANTED TO MAKE A SHOW THAT
MADE YOU PARTICIPATE.
MADE YOU PAY ATTENTION.
AND I THINK THAT WORKED PRETTY
WELL.
>> AND THE WINNER IS --
>> "HILL STREET BLUES."
>> WE GOT 21 NOMINATIONS, AND WE
WENT ON TO WIN EIGHT EMMYS.
AND IT PUT US ON THE MAP
LITERALLY.
THAT'S WHEN PEOPLE FINALLY
CHECKED US OUT.
>> PROGRAMMING CHIEF OF ONE OF
THE NETWORKS USED TO SAY TO ME
ABOUT SHOWS LIKE "HILL STREET"
AND "ST. ELSEWHERE," WHAT THE
AMERICAN PUBLIC WANTS IS A
CHEESE BURGER AND WHAT YOU'RE
TRYING TO GIVE THEM IS A FRENCH
DELICACY.
AND HE SAID, YOUR JOB IS TO KEEP
SHOVING IT DOWN THEIR THROAT
UNTIL AFTER A WHILE THEY'LL SAY,
THAT DOESN'T TASTE BAD AND MAYBE
THEY'LL EVEN ORDER IT THEMSELVES
WHEN THEY GO TO THE RESTAURANT.
>> NICE FOR YOU TO JOIN US.
>> THE SUCCESS OF "HILL STREET
BLUES" INFLUENCED EVERYTHING
THAT CAME AFTER.
AND THEN OF COURSE YOU SAW SHOWS
LIKE "ST. ELSEWHERE."
>> Ynn■■n■n■nn■//■n■■■■■■//n■■/■
THIS?
ST. ELSEWHERE.
A PLACE YOU WOULDN'T WANT TO ■{+
>> WHEN IT FIRST CAME ON, IT WAS
PROMOTED AS "HILL STREET
HOSPITAL."
>> YOU GIVE YOUR PATIENTS THE
WRONG ANTIBIOTICS.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT MEDICATIONS
THEY'RE ON.
YOU WRITE THE WORST PROGRESS
NOTES.
YOU'RE PATHETIC.
PATHETIC!
>> PHIL!
>> WHAT?
>> DR. MORNING NEEDS YOU RIGHT
AWAY.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> "ST. ELSEWHERE" BROKE EVERY
RULE THERE WAS AND THEN BUILT
SOME NEW RULES.
>> BOBBY, THE BLOOD BANK CALLED
A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
THEY RAN A ROUTINE PANEL ON THAT
PINT OF BLOOD.
T-CELL COUNT WAS OFF.
>> THEY WOULD HAVE TRAGIC THINGS
HAPPEN TO THESE CHARACTERS.
THERE WAS REAL HEARTACHE IN
THESE PEOPLES' LIVES AND YOU
REALLY FELT FOR THEM.
>> I'VE GOT AIDS?
>> TELEVISION AT ITS BEST IS A
MIRROR OF SOCIETY IN THE MOMENT.
>> "ST. ELSEWHERE" CHALLENGED
PEOPLE, AND THEY CHALLENGED YOU
AS AN ACTOR, MUCH LESS THE
AUDIENCE, TO THINK.
THE STUFF THEY GAVE YOU WAS
EXTREME IN WHAT THEY DID,
WHETHER THEY WERE DEALING WITH
AIDS OR HAVING ONE OF THEIR MAIN
DOCTOR CHARACTERS RAPED IN A
PRISON.
>> THEY TACKLED LOTS OF
DIFFICULT SUBJECTS.
>> "ST. ELSEWHERE" WAS RUN BY
PEOPLE WHO WERE TRYING TO
STRETCH THE MEDIUM.
AND IN THE '80s, TELEVISION
PRODUCERS WERE ENCOURAGED TO
STRETCH THE MEDIUM.
>> OKAY.
CLEAR.
>> AS THE '80s GOT SERIOUS,
THERE WAS MORE DRAMA.
THEY WERE GETTING A LITTLE BIT
MORE ADVENTUROUS WITH THE TYPES
OF SHOWS THAT WERE GETTING A
SHOT.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING? I'M DOIN
DONE ALL ALONG.
WHAT I WANTED TO DO ORIGINALLY.
WHAT I SHOULD HAVE DONE LAST
NIGHT.
>> STOP THAT, DAVID.
>> I'M CALLING THE POLICE,
DAVID.
>> HELLO, POLICE?
>> THE NETWORKS REALIZED THERE
WAS AN AUDIENCE LOOKING FOR
SOMETHING LESS PREDICTABLE THAN
TRADITIONAL PRIME TIME FAIR.
>> MOONLIGHTING WAS ANOTHER SHOW
THAT SAID OKAY I SEE THE
FORMULAS WE'VE HAD UP TO HERE.
LET'S DO DIFFERENT THINGS.
>> HELLO.
>> WE'RE LOOKING A LITTLE PALE
TODAY, AREN'T WE?
WHO HAVE WE HERE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> "MOONLIGHTING" WAS A REALLY
EXPERIMENTAL SHOW.
THEY HAD A SHAKESPEARE EPISODE.
THEY HAD A BLACK AND WHITE
EPISODE.
THEY DID A MUSICAL EPISODE.
THEY TRIED A LOT OF DIFFERENT
STUFF.
>> I DON'T GIVE A FLYING FIG
ABOUT THE LINES IN MY FACE, THE
CROWS' FEET BY MY EYES, OR THE
ALTITUDE OF MY CABOOSE.
>> WELL, I'M AT A LOSS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT A FLYING FIG
IS.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
THEY DO.
>> THERE'S NO TROUBLE ON THE
SET.
THERE IS NO TROUBLE ON THE SET.
>> WELL, WE HAVE A VERY VOLATILE
RELATIONSHIP.
THERE IS A HATE/LOVE ELEMENT TO
IT.
>> EASY COME, EASY GO!
>> THE FLIRTATIONS WERE GREAT
AND BRUCE AND CYBILL WERE GREAT.
GLENN CARON KEPT THEM APART FOR
A LONG TIME, AND BRAVO TO HIM.
>> WHAT THEY DID IS THEY TOOK
THE SAM AND DIANE DYNAMIC FROM
"CHEERS" AND ESCALATED IT.
"CHEERS" WAS WILL THEY, WON'T
THEY?
"MOONLIGHTING" WAS, DO THEY EVEN
WANT TO?
>> STAY AWAY FROM ME.
>> HERE I COME.
>> BUT I DON'T WANT YOU.
I NEVER WANTED YOU.
>> YEAH, RIGHT.
>> DOES ENTERTAINING MEAN AT
SOME POINT STOPPING THE TEASE OF
DAVE AND MATTIE?
DO THEY GET TOGETHER AT SOME
POINT?
>> I HOPE SO.
WELL, THAT'S GOING TO BE
RESOLVED THIS YEAR.
WE LIKE TO THINK OF IT AS TWO
AND A HALF YEARS OF FOREPLAY.
>> PEOPLE WHO HAD BEEN WATCHING
"MOONLIGHTING" FOR YEARS WERE
WAITING FOR THIS MOMENT.
AND YOUR EMOTIONS ARE ALREADY
THERE BUILT ON TO THE EMOTIONS
THAT YOU'RE SEEING ON THE
SCREEN.
SO WHEN "BE MY BABY" BY THE
RONETTES STARTS PLAYING, IT'S
LIKE A PERFECT STORM OF ROMANCE.
♪
♪ THE NIGHT WE MET I KNEW I
NEEDED YOU SO ♪
join T-Mobile.re even more reao
One
Do you like Stranger Things?
Sure you do.
That's why Netflix is on us.
Two
Unlimited data. Use as much as
you want, when you want.
Three
No surprises on your bill. Taxes
and fees included.
Still think you have a better
deal?
Bring in your discount, and
we'll match it.
That's right. T-Mobile will
match your discount.
Let's be honest:
you need insurance.
But it's not really something
you want to buy.
It's not sexy.
Or delicious.
Or fun.
But since you need both car
and home insurance,
why not bundle the  Esurance?
Which you can spend on things
you really want to buy, like...
well, I don't know wu'd y■
because I'm just
a guy on your TV.
Esurance. It's surprisingly
painless.
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ TAKE ME TO YOUR
BEST FRIEND'S HOUSE ♪
♪ GOING AROUND
THIS ROUNDABOUT ♪
♪ OH, YEAH ♪
What is that?
Uh mine, why?
It's just that it's...
Lavender. Yes it is, it's for
men
But I like the smell of it
Laughs
♪
This is something big.
This is something bigger.
That is big.
Not as big as that.
Big.
Bigger.
This is big.
And that's bigger.
Coach! It's kinda hard to see
the ball.
I've been there.
I had a TV service with hardly
any sports in 4K.
Couldn't see any of the quality
details.
I switched to DIRECTV, now I get
the most live sports in 4K.
So how does that help me?
It really doesn't.
I don't know why I told you
that. Go get 'em sport!
Live sports that aren't in 4K
are just kinda TV.
Don't just kinda TV. DIRECTV
Don't have 4K? Call
1.855.WATCH.4K and ask for it
today.