>> Announcer: LIVE FROM
NEW YORK CITY, IT'S
"THE WENDY WILLIAMS SHOW."
♪ ♪
NOW, HERE'S NICK CANNON!
A [CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: OH!
OH!
IT'S GOING DOWN!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
GOT IT, GOT IT.
WE READY.
WE READY!
THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> Audience: HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> Nick: I DID IT!
ARE Y'ALL HAVING A GOOD TIME?
SAY HELLO TO MY COHOSTS!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WE GIVING IT IN.
I'M SO EXCITED TO BE HERE AGAIN.
THIS IS AN AMAZING OPPORTUNITY.
AS OF YESTERDAY.
DID Y'ALL SEE THE SHOW
YESTERDAY?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
ONLINE WAS GOING CRAZY.
SOCIAL MEDIA WAS GOING CRAZY.
PEOPLE SAYING I'M DOING A PRETTY
GOOD JOB.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I WISH I COULD STAY LONGER, BUT
I'VE GOT TO GO GET MY MOVIE STAR
ON, Y'ALL!
I'VE GOT TO GO MAKE AN ACTION
MOVIE IN DUBAI.
I CAN ONLY BE WITH YOU FOR SO
LONG, BECAUSE WENDY IS COMING
BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
SHE WAS ONLINE, "YOU LYING!"
SHE TOLD ME, "DON'T GET TOO
COMFORTABLE!"
[LAUGHTER]
>>  "I KNOW IT'S BLACK HISTORY
MONTH, BUT...
"WE SAID HER NOTHING BUT WELL
WISHES, LOVE, AND POSITIVE
ENERGY.
TO HER AND HERS.
[APPLAUSE]
LIKE MY MAMA SAID, DON'T BE A
PEER GETTING TOO MESSY, BUT IT'S
TIME FOR "HOT TOPICS"!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
STAY HYDRATED FOR THESE
"HOT TOPICS"!
SO!
I LOVE THE ENERGY HERE, Y'ALL!
THAT'S THE THING I WANT TO TALK
ABOUT.
ONLINE -- BECAUSE, YOU KNOW I
KEEPS IT ALL THE WAY REAL.
I'M ALL THE WAY 100 WITH IT.
I WOULD ON SOCIAL MEDIA, I'M
TALKING BACK TO PEOPLE.
"WHAT'D YOU SAY?"
I'M DOING ALL THIS.
PEOPLE WERE TALKING ABOUT HOW
MUCH FUN WE WERE HAVING, THAT
THE AUDIENCE HAD GREAT ENERGY.
BUT THEN THEY WOULD LIKE, "NICK,
HE'S JUST TOO LOUD!
I'M TRYING TO HAVE MY BREAKFAST,
YOU SCREAMING AT THE OATMEAL!"
I'M GLAD BECAUSE I'M EXCITED!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
RAH RAH SIS BOOM BAH!
THE BLACK MAN TOO LOUD FOR YOU,
Y'ALL?
[LAUGHTER]
WE'RE GOING TO DEFINITELY -- I'M
ALLOWED TO COME I'M ALLOWED
PERSON!
I'M SORRY!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
NORMAN, IS THAT A PROBLEM?
>> Norman: NO!
>> Nick: NORMAN TOLD ME TO BE
ME!
I SHOULD WHISPER.
WELCOME TO THE WENDY WILLIAMS
SHOW.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET THE ENERGY.
WE DRESSED LOUD.
Y'ALL SEE THESE LOUD SHOES.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
IT'S FUNNY, MY RUBY SLIPPERS.
ONE OF MY BEST FRIENDS, FUNNY
COMEDIAN IN THE GAME, HE SAW ME
AND SOME SHOES LIKE THIS ONE
TIME AND SAID, "MA'AM, WHAT'S UP
WITH THEM SHOES?
YOU CLICK YOUR HEELS THREE TIMES
AND YOU END UP BACK AT MARIAH'S
HOUSE?"
GOING TO MAKE THE MARIAH'S JOKES
ON MY RUBY RED SLIPPERS...
[LAUGHTER]
SPEAKING OF FRIENDS, I TALKED
THE OF THE DAY.
SPEAKING OF COMEDY, I WAS SAYING
IT LAST NIGHT WITH MY LITTLE
BROTHER, PETE DAVIDSON.
[APPLAUSE]
WE WAS IN BROOKLYN!
HE WANTED TO BE HERE, BUT --
LOOK, I WAS FEELING MYSELF LAST
NIGHT.
HAD A LITTLE GREENERY.
IT'S FOR MY LUPUS!
MY LUPUS!
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
I GOT A CARD!
HE'S GOT PEOPLE.
THEY REPRESENT HIM, THEY SAID IT
MIGHT NOT BE THE SMARTEST THING
FOR HIM AND I TO GET UP HERE AND
START TALKING.
BECAUSE WE VOWED TO SAY
ANYTHING.
I GOT PEOPLE, TOO.
I JUST DON'T LISTEN TO THEM.
[LAUGHTER]
I TOLD PETE, WE WERE HAVING GOOD
CONVERSATION.
WE WERE HAVING COUGAR
KATE BECKINSALE.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
I TAUGHT THAT YOUNG BOY WELL.
I'LL TELL YOU, I'M THE ONE -- I
WILL TAKE CREDIT FOR IT.
I'M THE ONE WHO TOLD HIM, "GET
YOU AN OLDER WOMAN, MAN!"
I SAID THAT.
[APPLAUSE]
"LEAVE THEM LITTLE POP STARS
ALONE!
AN OLD WOMAN KNOWS WHAT SHE
WANTS!
SHE DON'T PLAY NO GAMES!"
THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
YOU SOMEBODY OLDER!
THEM LITTLE POP STARS, THEY
DON'T KNOW!
THE GIVING JAPANESE MENUS
TATTOOED ON THEIR --
I'M JOKING, BUT THAT IS ARIANA
GRANDE'S HAND.
I THINK THAT'S EVEN AFTER SHE
TRIED TO FIX IT.
SHE HAS A TATTOO, IT WAS
SUPPOSED TO SAY "SEVEN RANKS,"
FOR HER DOING SO WELL IN JAPAN.
BUT ENDED UP SAYING "TINY
BARBECUE."
[LAUGHTER]
THAT'S SOME YOUNG GIRL STUFF.
OLDER WOMEN DON'T LIKE TARDY
BARBECUES.
THEY LIKE CHITLINS AND GRITS."
[APPLAUSE]
YOU EVER THINK ABOUT GETTING
"GRITS" TATTOOED ON YOU?
GET IT RIGHT ON THE THIGH.
[LAUGHTER]
I FEEL YOUR PAIN, ARIANA GRANDE.
I FEEL YOUR PAIN.
I GOT A JAPANESE TATTOO RIGHT
THERE, TOO.
THAT SAY "CALIFORNIA ROLLS."
[LAUGHTER]
I MADE THE SAME MISTAKE.
BUT I TOLD -- EVERYBODY KNOWS,
YES, I DID AT ONE POINT GET
MARIAH TATTOOED ALL ON MY BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
BUT THAT WAS FOR LOVE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THAT'S LOVE RIGHT THERE!
PEOPLE SAID, "DID YOU GET IT
COVERED UP?"
NO, I JUST ADDED TO IT.
PUT SOME MORE ON THERE.
PUT "JESUS" NEXT TO MARIA, MY
KIDS.
NOW IT'S LIKE A WHOLE FAMILY
PICTURE BACK THERE.
BUT YOU'VE GOT TO GET YOU AN
OLDER WOMAN.
REMEMBER, WE WERE TALKING ABOUT
THAT YESTERDAY.
MY TOP THREE.
NUMBER ONE, MARIAH.
[APPLAUSE]
THE AMAZING MOTHER, SUPERSTAR
SINGER.
NUMBER TWO, HALLE BERRY.
I'M STILL WORKING ON IT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
CALL ME.
I'VE STILL GOT SOME MORE TATTOO
SPACE!
[LAUGHTER]
AND THE NUMBER THREE, YESTERDAY
I HEARD THAT SHE'S OUT DATING.
NAOMI CAMPBELL.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT!
THIS IS WOMEN!
DON'T NONE OF THEM GOT SUSHI
TATTOOS!
[LAUGHTER]
WHO?
>> Norman: JENNIFER LOPEZ.
>> Nick: I DON'T KNOW HER.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
THAT WAS A JOKE!
THAT WAS A JOKE FOR THE LAMBS!
SHOUT OUT TO THE LAMBS.
I'M PLAYING UP -- IN ALL
SERIOUSNESS, I'M GOING TO STOP
USING THE WORD "OLDER WOMAN."
I'M GOING TO STOP.
I WANT MATURED.
[APPLAUSE]
SEASONED.
PUT A LITTLE SPRINKLE ON IT.
SEASON.
THEY'RE WHAT SAYING?
VINTAGE -- I'M SORRY, MAMA.
I'M SORRY, MAMA!
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
I'M SORRY.
I FORGOT IT WAS LIKE TO BE.
BUT THAT'S WHAT I LIKE IN MY
LIFE.
I'M SORRY, MAMA.
I LIKE A COUPLE OF YOUR FRIENDS,
MAMA.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
JUST SAYING.
MISS GERTRUDE GOT A LOT OF
CHURCH AT BOOTY.
THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING, THAT'S
WHAT I LIKE.
[LAUGHTER]
I'M SORRY.
THE ONLY THING -- I'M TRYING TO
MAKE A POINT, I WAS TELLING
PETE.
THESE YOUNG GIRLS -- I'M SINGLE,
I CAN'T DEAL WITH ALL THAT.
[APPLAUSE]
IT'S TOO MUCH!
YOUNG GIRLS, THEY ARE COMING OUT
WITH A PHONE.
THEY WANT TO SNAPCHAT YOU AND
FACE TIME, SEXTING.
I GOT AN ANDROID!
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO WORK ON
THAT.
YOU SENDING ME PICTURES THAT ARE
DISAPPEARING.
I GOT ENOUGH TIME!
GIRL, SEND ME A POLAROID!
[LAUGHTER]
I WANT SOMETHING I CAN SHAKE AND
BLOW ON!
PUT IT ON THE REFRIGERATOR!
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
SHOW MY SON!
"YOUR POPS WAS COLD BACK IN THE
DAY WITH THE COUGARS!"
THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING, THESE
YOUNG GIRLS -- "I'M ABOUT THE
BAG.
WE CAN GET TO THE BAG.
BUY ME A BAG."
I WANT A WOMAN WITH A
POCKETBOOK.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
A MATURE WOMAN GOT A POCKETBOOK!
SHE AIN'T GOT NO BAG!
A POCKETBOOK, WITH ALL THE
NECESSITIES AND IT!
[LAUGHTER]
SHE'S GOT ANYTHING YOU NEED.
CHURCH MINTS.
FIRST AID KIT.
OINTMENT.
[LAUGHTER]
A MATURE SEASONED WOMAN.
ALL THE COUGARS CALL ME.
DMA, OR WHATEVER THEY DO NOW.
[APPLAUSE]
I KNOW I'M LOUD.
I WOULD JUST SAY ANYTHING.
I APOLOGIZE.
[APPLAUSE]
IN ALL SERIOUSNESS, GETTING TO
PROBABLY THE MOST HOT TOPIC -- I
WAS ONLINE, I WAS IN THERE
COMMENTING ON THE SHADE ROOM AND
"THE WENDY SHOW" IN ALL THIS.
WHEN THIS WENT DOWN YESTERDAY, I
WAS LIKE, "I HAVE TO TALK ABOUT
THIS TOMORROW."
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
LIAM NEESON GOT HIMSELF INTO A
LOT OF TROUBLE YESTERDAY!
HE WAS OUT PROMOTING HIS NEW
MOVIE, WHICH IS ABOUT SEEKING
REVENGE.
AND HE TOLD A STORY ABOUT
WANTING TO SEEK REVENGE IN REAL
LIFE.
HE WAS OVER SHARING.
ABOUT A CLOSE FRIEND WHO WAS
RAPED, WHICH IS PROBABLY THE
MOST HORRENDOUS THING THAT CAN
HAPPEN TO ANYONE IN THIS WORLD.
I FEEL HIS ANGER AND HIS PAIN.
BUT THEN IT WAS LIKE, BECAUSE
SHE WAS RAPED BY A BLACK MAN, IT
WENT TO DIFFERENT DIRECTION.
HE STARTED SAYING SOME THINGS --
AS A MATTER OF FACT, LET'S
LISTEN TO IT SO I COULD LET HIM
SPEAK FOR HIMSELF BEFORE I GET
INTO ALL THAT.
WE GOING TO LISTEN.
JUST LISTEN.
>> I ASKED DID YOU KNOW WHO IT
WAS?
NO.
WHAT COLOR WERE THEY?
SHE SAID IT WAS A BLACK PERSON.
I'VE BEEN UP AND DOWN AREAS WITH
A COSH HOPING TO BE APPROACHED
BY SOMEBODY.
I'M ASHAMED TO SAY THAT.
I DID IT FOR MAYBE A WEEK,
HOPING SOME BLACK -- WOULD COME
OUT OF THE PUB AND HAVE A GO AT
ME ABOUT SOMETHING, SO I COULD
KILL HIM.
WHO ARE YOU CALLING -- HE'S
TRYING TO BE THE NEXT MEL GIBSON
OUT HERE!
I'M JUST GOING TO SAY THIS -- WE
THROW THE STUFF AROUND, AND I
UNDERSTAND HIS ANGER.
BUT THERE IS NO REASON TO WANT
TO KILL SOMEONE JUST BASED OFF
OF THE COLOR, THEIR RACE --
[APPLAUSE]
THE THING THAT, WHEN YOU'RE
DEALING WITH RACISM, THE IDEA
THAT HE WAS ANGRY ABOUT THE RAP
RAPE -- AS WE SHOULD ALL BE --
WITHIN THE NEXT QUESTION HE ASKS
IS, "WHAT COLOR WAS HE?"
I DON'T KNOW IF HE'S JUST TRYING
TO FIND A DESCRIPTION, BECAUSE
COLOR SHOULDN'T MATTER.
WE ARE NOT CRAYONS.
[APPLAUSE]
BUT, YOU KNOW -- I SEE WHERE HE
WAS GOING WITH IT.
BUT I THINK YOU JUST REALLY
THINKS HE'S THE CHARACTER FROM "
HE SAID HE WENT OUT FOR A WEEK
OF LOOKING FOR BLACK PEOPLE.
YOU COULDN'T FIND NO BLACK
PEOPLE?
HE SAID HE WENT TO THE PUB.
FIRST OF ALL, BLACK PEOPLE DON'T
GO TO PUBS.
[APPLAUSE]
WE DON'T GO TO THE PUB.
WE GO TO THE CLUB.
OKAY?
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
YOU OUT THERE LOOKING AT PUBS --
IF YOU HAD WENT TO MAGIC CITY,
STARLETS OR SOMETHING, YOU
WOULD'VE FOUND THAT'S WHERE WE
ARE OVER THERE HANGING.
YOU FOUND THEM.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I WANT ALL THE SMOKE.
I WILL TAKE THAT.
I THINK HE WAS OVER SHARING,
BECAUSE EVEN THE TERM "RACISM,"
YOU GO A LITTLE BIT TOO FAR --
WE ALWAYS THROW THAT WORD OUT
THERE.
"OH, THAT'S RACIST."
RACISM IS ABOUT SYSTEMIC
OPPRESSION.
RACISM IS ABOUT POWER.
THIS IS JUST IGNORANCE.
AT THE END OF THE DAY.
[APPLAUSE]
I THINK HE IS AWARE OF THAT.
I THINK HE PROBABLY FELT HE
NEEDED TO CLEAN IT UP, SO THIS
MORNING, AS WE SAW JUST A FEW
MINUTES AGO, HE WENT ON
"GOOD MORNING AMERICA" TO TRY
AND CLEAN UP THE MESS.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
>> IF YOUR FRIEND HAD SAID IT
WAS A WHITE MAN QUESTIONING >>
IF SHE HAD SAID IRISH, OR A
SCOTT, BRITT, A LITHUANIAN COME
I WOULD'VE HAD THE SAME REACTIO
REACTION.
>> IF IT'S AN INNOCENT BLACK MAN
WHO HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH IT --
>> THAT WAS MY FEELING PRAYED
THAT I DID WANT TO LASH OUT.
I DID SEEK OUT -- I WENT TO A
PRIEST, I HAD MY CONFESSION.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT, POWER
WALKING.
TWO HOURS EVERY DAY.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
>> Nick: POWER WALKING?
YOU'RE JUST GOING TO WALK THE
RACISM OFF?
[LAUGHTER]
"YEAH, MAMA!
I'M GOING TO GET ALL THIS
BIGOTRY OUT ME!
TWO MORE MINUTES ON MY FITBIT!"
YOU CAN'T WALK RACISM OFF!
POWER WALKING QUESTION RECORD IS
GOING TO WALK IT OUT, HUH?
IT'S FUNNY WHEN YOU -- HE THINKS
HE'S THE GUY IN THE MOVIE.
"I HAVE SOME VERY SPECIAL RACIST
SKILLS.
."
I WANT TO FIX THIS FOR YOU,
BROTHER.
I DON'T THINK IS RACIST.
I JUST THINK HE'S A LITTLE --
IT'S THAT SOCIOPATHIC BEHAVIOR.
WHERE HE THINKS HE'S THE GUY IN
THE MOVIE.
YOU'RE GOING TO WALK UP ON SO
PEOPLE IN NEWARK, NEW JERSEY,
INCORPORATED GOING TO BE NO
STUNT COORDINATORS!
[APPLAUSE]
WE'VE GOT A WHOLE LOT OF BLACK
PEOPLE YOU CAN FIND.
I'M GOING TO FIX THIS.
I'M A FAN OF THE "TAKEN" MOVIES.
I'M A FAN OF "SCHINDLER'S LIST,"
ALL OF THIS.
I'LL FIX IT.
I'VE GOT A WAY TO FIX IT, YOU
ALL.
GOING TO DO IT.
LIAM NEESON, I CHALLENGE YOU TO
A CELEBRITY BOXING MATCH!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
IT'S GOING DOWN!
WE'RE GOING TO DONATE ALL THE
MONEY TO THE NAACP!
[APPLAUSE]
YOU GET ALL THAT ANGER ABOUT
YOU.
I WILL TAKE THAT FEED.
IT'S A CLEAN FIGHT, WE WILL PUT
ON THE GLOVES.
I THINK IT.
RIGHT?
DO Y'ALL THINK I COULD TAKE HIM?
I'LL DO THIS MOVIE IN DUBAI, I
WILL PULL UP.
I'M GOING TO GET TO IT.
GO SEE HIS MOVIE THIS WEEKEND.
[LAUGHTER]
HE SAID IT'S A DARK COMEDY.
WHY IT GOT TO BE A DARK COMEDY?
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
SPEAKING OF PEOPLE WHO CAN
FIGHT, CARDI B IS BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
SHOULD YOU WITH ONE OF THE RED
BOTTOMS REAL QUICK.
SHE ALSO HAD AN INTERVIEW WITH
"GOOD MORNING AMERICA"
YESTERDAY.
AND SHE WAS TALKING ABOUT HER
DATING LIFE.
YOU KNOW WHEN HER AND OFFSET WAS
UPSET.
[LAUGHTER]
THEY SPLIT FOR A MINUTE, AND
CARDI HAD SOME INTERESTING
THINGS TO SAY.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW HOW DAYS WHO
WANTS YOU FOR YOU.
I THINK PEOPLE WANT ME FOR CARDI
B.
AS SOON AS I SAID I'M DOING A
VIDEO, THAT ARE NOT WITH THIS
GUY ANYMORE, I'VE GOT ALL THESE
MAY ALSO LIVES IN MY DM PLAYER
LIST.
YOU WANT TO GO TO DINNER WITH
ME, CARDI B?
>> [LAUGHS]
ARGUE ABOUT DATES?
>> IT'S LIKE, BRO.
[LAUGHTER]
>> I'M SORRY, IT WAS ME.
I'M SORRY.
I TOLD YOU, I'M SINGLE.
I WAS TRYING TO BE FIRST!
I DON'T DO THE DM THING.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO SLIDE TO THE
DM.
I GOT A BAD HIP, I CAN'T SLIDE.
I DO.
BECAUSE I SEE, I'M ONLINE LIKE
THAT.
IT SEEMS LIKE THAT'S A WEIRD
CONCEPT.
THIS IS A MARRIED WOMAN.
YOU DON'T JUST GO --
THEIR WORKING SURVEY THINGS, BUT
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO SLIDE UP --
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOUR HUSBAND IS
OFFSET!
HE'S GOT FACE TATTOOS!
THERE'S GONNA BE SOME
REPERCUSSIONS FOR SLIDING INTO
HIS WOMAN'S DMs.
IN THE MIDDLE OF ONE OF HIS
SHOWS, HE SAID, "DAMN ALL THAT,
I'M GOING TO GET MY WOMAN BACK!"
THAT'S LIVER THERE.
THEY SAID THEY ARE WORKING IT
OUT.
THEY'VE GOT A BEAUTIFUL BABY,
CULTURE.
THAT SOME STRONG LIVER THERE.
I LOVE ALL OF THAT.
I WILL BE SLIDING INTO ANYMORE
DMs.
SORRY.
[APPLAUSE]
AND THE RATINGS ARE IN!
I'M SO PROUD OF AMERICA RIGHT
NOW.
I HAVE TO SAY THIS.
THE SUPER BOWL WAS A SLEEPER
BOWL!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THIS YEAR'S SUPER BOWL WAS THE
LOWEST RATED SUPER BOWL IN TEN
YEARS.
A LOT OF PEOPLE SAY IT'S FOR
MANY DIFFERENT REASONS.
PEOPLE TIRED OF TOM BRADY
WINNING.
I'M GOING TO KEEP IT.
I LOVE TOM BRADY.
KEEP ON WINNING.
I HONESTLY BELIEVE THAT WE WERE
ON THE RIGHT SIDE OF HISTORY AT
THIS.
WE SAID WE'RE GOING TO STEP BACK
AND MAKE A STATEMENT, A PEACEFUL
PROTEST FOR MY BROTHER,
COLIN KAEPERNICK.
[APPLAUSE]
TO SHOW THAT --
YEAH.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
A PEACEFUL PROTEST.
AND THAT IS A SALUTE TO THE
VETERANS, A SALUTE TO
LAW ENFORCEMENT, AND HONESTLY,
THE FACT THAT HERE IN AMERICA WE
CAN PEACEFULLY PROTEST WITHOUT
PUNISHMENT.
THAT'S WHAT IT'S ALL ABOUT.
IT SHOULDN'T BE ABOUT ANY KIND
OF BANNING SOMEONE OR
BLACKBALLING OR ANY TYPE OF
STUFF.
I KNOW THIS BROTHER PERSONALLY.
HE'S A FRIEND OF MINE, AND HE
DID IT AND IS DOING IT FOR ALL
THE RIGHT REASONS.
[APPLAUSE]
SPEAKING OF THE RIGHT REASONS,
TODAY IS A SPECIAL DAY.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN TRAVE ON
MARTIN'S 24TH BIRTHDAY TODAY
THAT RIGHT THERE IS THE REASON
WHY MY BROTHER, COLIN KAEPERNIC
COLIN KAEPERNICK, WAS TAKING
MONEY.
I'M GOING TO CONTINUE.
WE ARE GOING TO ALL TAKE THE
KNEE.
NFL, PAY ATTENTION!
WE KNOW THAT WAS A GIANT DISPLAY
OF CAPITALISM.
YOU NEED THE RATINGS THAT.
GIVE MY MAN COLIN A JOB.
I WANT TO SEE HIM SO THAT
FOOTBALL AGAIN!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
BRING JANET JACKSON BACK!
LET HER CONTROL!
I'M GOING TO PULL MY NIPPLES OUT
THIS TIME!
I'LL DO THE DRUM LINED AND
EVERYTHING.
WE WILL HAPPEN.
THAT WAS "HOT TOPICS."
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
KENAN THOMPSON IS UP NEXT.
MY FRIEND IS HERE.
GRAB A SNACK AND COME ON BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Nick: [WHISPERING]
WELCOME BACK TO THE
WENDY WILLIAMS SHOW.
YOU KNOW FAMILY, WHERE WE AT?
WE LOVE THAT!
I'M REALLY EXCITED TO INTRODUCE
YOU TO MY FAMILY, A TRUE FAMILY
MEMBER.
ONE OF MY BEST FRIENDS.
YES.
REALLY, MY BROTHER PRAYED THIS
IS MY BROTHER, Y'ALL.
HE'S ALSO THE LONGEST RUNNING
CAST MEMBER IN
"SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE" HISTORY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
TAKE A LOOK.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
IT IS NORMAL THAT SHE WOULD
VOLUNTEER TO COOK FOR EVERYONE.
ALTHOUGH I HAVE NEVER HAD POTATO
SALAD, I SENSE THAT THIS WHITE
WOMAN DOES NOT SEE HER FOOD.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> AND IF SHE DOES, IT IS ONLY
WITH A TINY BIT OF SALT.
AND NO PAPRIKA.
AND SHE WILL PROBABLY ADD
SOMETHING UNNECESSARY LIKE
RAISINS.
>> I KNOW, RIGHT?
[LAUGHTER]
>> SOMETHING TELLS ME THAT I
SHOULD SAY --
>> SAY IT.
"AW HELL NAH, KAREN!
KEEP YOUR POTATO SALAD
YOURSELF!"
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
>> YOU GOT IT!
BLACK PANTHER, WELCOME TO BLACK
JEOPARDY.
>> Nick: LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
GIVE IT UP FOR KENAN THOMPSON!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
ONE TIME FOR THE ONE TIME!
HE JUST GOT ON SOCIAL MEDIA.
HE'S GETTING IT TOGETHER, MAN.
>> Kenan: I'M DOING IT FOR THE
GRAHAM GRAHAM.
>> Nick: ONE TIME
I AM GOING TO BE HONEST, I WOULD
BE SITTING THERE THIS MOMENT
TODAY IF IT WASN'T FOR THIS
BROTHER RIGHT HERE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
ARE USED TO DRIVE UP AFTER
SCHOOL, TWO AND A HALF HOUR
DRIVE COME ALL THE WAY TO
HOLLYWOOD TO STAND IN LINE TO DO
STAND-UP COMEDY FOR LIKE
2 MINUTES.
THIS DUDE WOULD COME OUT,
SUPPORT, BE IN THE CLUB, SHOW
LOVE.
WE WERE THE ONLY YOUNG GUYS.
HE WAS ALREADY POPPING!
HE WAS ALREADY --
THAT WAS BACK IN THE DAY!
>> Kenan: [LAUGHS]
>> Nick: HE WAS ALREADY ON
NICKELODEON.
A SUPERSTAR.
I WAS A HUGE FAN.
I WAS A FAN OF "ALL THAT."
NOT ONLY DID HE INTRODUCE ME TO
HIS MANAGER, WHO BE STILL ROCK
WITH TODAY.
THAT'S ANOTHER FAMILY MEMBER.
THAT'S LOYALTY.
[APPLAUSE]
THIS IS THE THING -- I USED TO
TAKE MY MOM'S OLD BROKE DOWN BMW
FROM THE '80s, LIKE AN OLD
DOPE DEALER CARD.
[LAUGHTER]
I WOULD DRIVE UP, AND I WOULD
HAVE TO SLEEP IN MY CAR.
KENAN LET ME STAY IN HIS HOUSE.
[APPLAUSE]
HE BROUGHT ME IN!
HE MAY BE EVER MADE!
I WAS LIKE HIS LITTLE BROTHER.
>> Kenan: LET ME BACK UP -- I
MEAN, THE AMOUNT OF HUSTLE THAT
YOU HAVE IN THE AMOUNT OF DRIVE
AND THE AMOUNT OF TALENT, YOU
WOULD HAVE BEEN WHEREVER YOU WAS
GOING TO BE REGARDLESS.
>> Nick: THANK YOU, MAN!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Kenan: I RECOGNIZED THAT
HUSTLE A NEW PAIR THAT'S WHY I
EMBRACE YOU.
BECAUSE I HAD AN APARTMENT AND
IT WAS A TWO BEDROOM APARTMENT.
THE OTHER BEDROOM WAS JUST WIDE
OPEN.
I SAW A YOUNG BROTHER WHO HAD
DRIVE, WHO WANTED TO DO IT LIKE
I DID IT.
COMING FROM ATLANTA, I KNOW WHAT
IT'S LIKE TO GET ON THAT
FREEWAY.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Wendy: I APPRECIATED!
I WAS BROKE AT THE TIME
BETWEEN EVERYTHING GOING DOWN, I
GOT A JOB.
>> Kenan: HE GOT A LITTLE
CHANGE.
>> Nick: I HAD A COUPLE CHECKS
AFTER THAT.
WHAT ENDED UP HAPPENING, BECAUSE
HE BECAME MY FRIEND, MY MENTOR,
MY BIG BROTHER, I ACTUALLY
BECAME THE AUDIENCE WARM-UP.
ENTERTAINING AUDIENCE.
EXACTLY, I WAS A WARM-UP.
>> Nick:        >> Kenan: GIVE P
BAND SOME LOVE!
YOU'VE GOT TO START SOMEWHERE!
>> Nick: HE INTRODUCE ME TO
THE WRITERS ON THE SHOW AND I
BECAME ONE OF THE YOUNGEST
WRITERS IN TELEVISION HISTORY,
WRITING FOR THIS MAN'S TV SHOW.
>> Kenan: AND THEN HE GOT ON
THE SHOW!
AND I LOOK AT YOU.
>> Nick: WE BECAME INMATES FOR
REAL.
I STARTED PAYING SOME RENT!
AND THEN WE GOT HOUSE IN THE
HOLLYWOOD HILLS.
AND WE WAS DOING IT BIG!
>> Kenan: OUT OF CONTROL.
NOW WE ARE 40 AND WE ARE
DADDIES.
>> Nick: YEAR 40, I'M STILL IN
MY 30s!
I DO WANT TO HEAR THAT!
I'M GOING TO HOLD ONTO THE
30s!
I'M GOING TO HOLD ON LIKE A
HUBCAP IN THE FAST LANE!
SPEECH I MIGHT BE ABOUT MY
40s.
MY 40s ARE LOOKING GOOD.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Wendy: THEY LOOK GOOD!
SPEECH TO THE CAST MEMBER OF US
AND HIM
HOW ARE THE GIRLS?
>> Kenan: MY BABIES?
>> Nick: LOOK AT THAT!
A HOUSEFUL>> Kenan: I LOVE MY BL
WIFE, CHRISTINA, MY BABIES.
THAT'S GEORGIA, LOOK AT HER.
SO SWEET.
>> Nick: SHE WAS THE HAPPIEST
BABY EVER!
>> Kenan: THEY BOTH ARE.
>> Nick: IT'S CRAZY, MAN.
TO GET THE OPPORTUNITY TO DIG
HER DAUGHTER JUST SCHOOL EVERY
DAY.
>> Kenan: WORKING ON "SNL,"
WHEN I'M IN NEW YORK, MY
SCHEDULE IS PRETTY PREDICTABLE.
SO WE WORKED NIGHTS, AND DURING
THE MORNINGS I'M UP WITH HER
TAKING HER TO SCHOOL.
>> Nick: OVER THE WEEKEND WE
HAD DINNER.
WE PULLED UP.
OUR MOTHERS ARE BEST FRIENDS.
>> Kenan: OUR MOTHERS ARE
SUPERTIGHT.
>> Nick: THEY HELD THE STEM WE
WE WERE ON TV.
I COMMEND YOUR MOTHER AND MY
MOM.
THEY WEREN'T --    MOMAGERS, BUE
BELT WAS IN FRONT.
THEY SAID YOU'RE GOING TO TREAT
ADULTS WITH RESPECT.
YOU GET YOUR HOMEWORK DONE.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU THINK YOU'RE
A STAR OR NOT!
>> Kenan: I GOT THAT TALK LAST
WEEK!
IT'S NONSTOP.
>> Nick: SHOUTS OUT TO OUR
MATRIARCHS, OUR BEAUTIFUL QUEEN
QUEENS.
MY MOTHER'S.
NOW LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
BUSINESS, MAN!
YOU'RE DOING IT!
YOU GOT ANOTHER NEW SHOW.
CONGRATS ON "BRING THE FUNNY."
>> Kenan: "BRING THE FUNNY" IS
GOING TO HAPPEN!
>> Nick: TELL ME ABOUT IT.
>> Kenan: IS A COMEDY
COMPETITION SHOW.
ANYTHING INVOLVING COMEDY, WE
ARE GOING TO HAVE STANDS UP,
SKETCH TROOPS, ANYTHING TO DO IS
COMEDY.
FOR A GRAND PRIZE OF $250,000.
>> Nick: THOSE ARE SOME FUNNY
PEOPLE, RIGHT THERE!
SPEECH YOU MYSELF, JEFF
FOXWORTHY, AND CHRISSY TEIGEN
ARE GOING TO BE THE JUDGES.
>> Nick: AND THEN AMANDA IS
HILARIOUS.
>> Kenan: IS IT -- HOW DO YOU
PRONOUNCE IT?
IT MIGHT BE PRONOUNCED TEIGEN.
>> Kenan: CHRISSY AND THEM.
JOHN LEGEND'S BOO-BOO.
"WINTER PARK" IS COMING UP.
"THE GRINCH IS OUT."
AND I'M WORKING ON MY OWN
SITCOM!
I'VE GOT THE TALK LETTER!
I'M WORKING ON MY SITCOM EXCEPT
PILOT!
AT ITS FUNNY, I'M GOING TO BE A
DADDY IN!
I'VE GOT DAUGHTERS!
IT'S GOING TO BE ON NBC!
I'M STILL GOING TO DO SATURDAY
NIGHT LIVE, TOO!
SO I WILL BE UP ON LIKE THREE
THINGS ON NBC!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: THAT'S SO FUNNY.
PEOPLE TO UNDERSTAND THE ENERGY,
WE FEEL LIKE WE'VE GOT TO TALK
LOUD BECAUSE IT'S SO --
>> Kenan: WE WANT TO DO GOOD
SHOW FOR YOU, HOLD IT DOWN!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: YOU HAD YOUR PHONE
OUT, SOCIAL MEDIA AND ALL THAT.
GOOD STUFF.
>> Kenan: IT'S FUN.
>> Nick: YOU JUST JOINED
INSTAGRAM.
>> Kenan: I'M TWO WEEKS IN.
>> Nick: THAT'S HER FIRST
PICTURE.
WHAT TOOK SO LONG?
>> Kenan: AND MY SECOND POST
WAS NIGHT BABY.
THAT'S THE FIRST TIME GEORGIA
CAME TO WORK WITH ME.
I JUST MISSED THE WHOLE SOCIAL
MEDIA AGE BECAUSE I NEVER HAD A
MYSPACE.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Nick: YOU DIDN'T WANT THE
FRIENDS QUESTION LIKE YOU HAD
ENOUGH FRIENDS?
>> Kenan: I JUST ENJOYED MY
PRIVACY FOR SO LONG.
BUT THEN I FELT OUT OF THE LOOP
BY THE TIME INSTAGRAM CAME
AROUND.
I DIDN'T FEEL LIKE I COULD CATCH
UP.
IF YOU WANT BUT YOU HAVE ABOUT
70,000 FOLLOWERS!
>> Kenan: 87,000.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: HOW CAN THEY FOLLOW
YOU?
>> Kenan: I'M @KENANTHOMPSON.
SUPER EASY.
>> Nick: I'LL GIVE YOU A FEW
TIPS.
I'VE GOT A FEW MILLION FOLLOWER
FOLLOWERS.
I AIN'T BRAGGING, I'M JUST
SAYING.
I'M GOING TO TELL YOU WHAT YOU
GOT TO DO.
THIRST TRAP OF PHOTOS.
TAKE YOUR CLOTHES OFF.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THIRST TRAP BY THURSDAYS.
>> Kenan: THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE
DOING.
>> Nick: FLEX FRIDAYS.
SEXY SATURDAYS.
YOU'VE GOT TO PUT IT ALL OUT
THERE.
>> Kenan: PUT IT ALL OUT
THERE, ALL RIGHT.
>> Nick: PUT THE EGGPLANT
EMOJI UP EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE.
IT WORKS.
>> Kenan: WE CAN GO AND PULL
THAT DOWN.
THAT'S GOOD.
THAT WAS REAL NICE.
>> Nick: PUT IT BACK UP THERE
ONE MORE TIME!
UP NEXT, YOU'RE GOING TO FIND
OUT HOW WELL KENAN AND I KNOW
EACH OTHER.
YOU'RE GOING TO PLAY A LITTLE
GAME CALLED BFS BATTLE.
YOU WON'T WANT TO MISS IT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: OH, YEAH!
KENAN AND I ARE BACK.
MAKING IT HAPPEN.
THIS IS "THE WENDY SHOW," I'M
NICK CANNON, AND THIS IS KENAN
THOMPSON.
>> Kenan: YES, SIR!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: WE'VE BEEN BEST
FRIENDS AND BROTHERS FOREVER.
I JUST TOLD YOU GUYS HOW WE MET
AND HOW HE GAVE ME SO MANY
OPPORTUNITIES.
THIS IS MY GUY RIGHT HERE.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS CLIP!
I DIDN'T EVEN TELL YELLOW I WAS
GOING TO DO THIS PRINT THIS IS
US FROM 20 YEARS AGO ON "ALL
THAT."
>> I'M SORRY I'M LATE, GIRL!
THEY WAS HAVING A BOMB SALE!
>> I WAS JUST DOWN THERE MYSELF!
>> THESE ARE THE EARRINGS I WAS
TALKING ABOUT!
>> CHECK OUT THE SCARF!
>> IT GOES WITH WHAT I'VE GOT O
ON.
>> WE GOT CLOTHES FOR LESS!
>> EXCUSE ME?
>> NO YOU DIDN'T!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: WE WOULD GET ALL
KINDS OF COMPLAINTS IF WE DID
THAT TODAY!
THAT WAS ON NICKELODEON!
WE WERE IN DRAG.
I HAD 6-INCH HEELS ON, WITH MY
THIGHS ALL OUT!
I WOULD NEVER DO THAT AGAIN.
I'M SORRY.
IT WAS A GOOD TIME BACK THEN.
>> Kenan: OH, MAN.
IT'S CALLED FREEDOM.
>> Nick: I REMEMBER I USED TO
DRIVE HOME IN THE DRUG OUTFITS.
>> Kenan: WHY?
>> Nick: I DON'T KNOW!
I DIDN'T DO IT THAT MUCH.
I COULD HAVE CHANGED.
WE WILL PLAY THIS GAME, IT'S
CALLED BFS BATTLE.
[APPLAUSE]
WE ARE GOING TO FIND OUT EXACTLY
HOW WELL WE KNOW EACH OTHER.
WE ARE GOING TO ASK EACH OTHER
THREE QUESTIONS, AND SEE WHO
GETS THE MOST RIGHT.
I WILL GO FIRST.
ARE YOU READY?
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT WAS OUR BIGGEST MAINTENANCE
ISSUE AT OUR HOLLYWOOD HILLS
HOME AND WE WERE ROOMMATES?
>> Kenan: OKAY, I FEEL LIKE WE
GOT THIS PLACE AND WE THOUGHT IT
WAS COOL BECAUSE IT WAS LIKE A
WOODEN TYPE OF LOG CABIN.
>> Nick: A TREE HOUSE.
>> Kenan: IN THE BACK THEY HAD
A WOODEN-MADE HOT TUB BUT IT
NEVER WORKS.
SO I'M GOING TO GO WITH A
HOT TUB THAT NEVER WORKED.
>> Nick: REALLY COSMIC THAT'S
WHERE HE WENT WITH IT.
SPEECH SHOOT BROKEN JACUZZI.
>> Nick: I SAID CLOGGED
TOILET!
>> Kenan: THAT WAS YOUR
BATHROOM, THOUGH!
>> Nick: THAT WAS MY BATHROOM!
IT WASN'T TO BE RUNNING ALL DOWN
THE STREET!
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
>> Kenan: IT WOULD STAY
FLASHING, ONE OF THE TOILETS
WOULD SAY FLUSHING.
SOMEBODY KNOCKED ON THE DOOR
LIKE, "EXCUSE US, Y'ALL HAVE
TISSUE RUNNING DOWN THE STREET
BECAUSE YOU DON'T KNOW HOW TO
TURN THE WATER OFF."
THAT'S DISGUSTING.
>> Nick: GIRLS WERE LIKE "I
AIN'T COMING OUT TO YOUR HOUSE,
NO MORE!"
WHAT'S MY FAVORITE CANDY?
SPEETHREE DON'T ASK ME TO HOLD
ON,
I'M STILL LAUGHING.
[LAUGHS]
I FORGOT ALL ABOUT THAT!
THAT'S HILARIOUS.
YOU HAD THIS WEIRD TABASCO --
WEIRD SPICY CANDY THAT YOUR DAD
WOULD DESCRIBE AS A PEEPEE
CANDY.
>> Nick: IT'S ACTUALLY
BECAUSE -- PART OF MY CANDY, WE
ARE MULTICULTURAL.
THERE IS SOME MEXICAN AND MY
FAMILY.
SO I LOVE MEXICAN CANDY.
SO THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
>> Kenan: SPICY PEEPEE CANDY.
I'M NOT DISSING MEXICAN CANDY.
THAT'S WHAT YOUR DAD SAYS.
>> Nick: WHAT TYPE OF WOMEN IN
MY OBSESSED WITH?
I THINK EVERYBODY KNOWS THIS.
>> Kenan: I JUST SAID FAMOUS
PEOPLE, I THINK.
FAMOUS WOMEN.
>> Nick: FAMOUS OLDER WOMEN!
PUT THEM TOGETHER!
WE DIDN'T EVEN GET TO YOUR
QUESTION.
I'M JUST GOING TO GO AHEAD
AND --
>> Kenan: LET ME DO MY
QUESTION.
OKAY.
>> Nick: WE WILL GIVE YOU ONE.
SPEECH OKAY, LET ME SEE.
GO ALL THE WAY BACK.
WHAT KIND OF CAR DID I USED TO
DRIVE?
>> Nick: A 4RUNNER!
BOOM!
>> Kenan: BE OF TIME FOR ONE
MORE?
YOU DON'T LOOK LIKE A NICK.
WHAT NAME DID I SAY YOU DID LOOK
LIKE?
>> Nick: A JABARI!
THERE IT IS.
THE LAST QUESTION WAS ABOUT MY
GRANDMAMMA'S TACOS.
SHE HOOKED IT UP.
KENAN THOMPSON RIGHT THERE, MY
BFF!
HIS NEW MOVIE, "WONDER PARK,"
HITS THEATERS MARCH 15TH.
CHECK THEM OUT ON SATURDAY NIGHT
LIVE, ON SATURDAYS, OF COURSE,
AND BC.
LOOSE CANNON IS NEXT.
I LOVE YOU, BOY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
(Cat 1) Friskies World...
(Cat 2) Smell that?
(Cat 1) Gravy!
(Cat 2) That's not gravy, that's
extra gravy.
(Cat 1) Whoa!
(Cat 2) That's Friskies
Extra Gravy! Paté and Chunky!
(Cat 1) Gravy purr-adise.
(Cat 2) Purr-adise? Really?
(VO) Feed Their Fantasy.
Friskies.
[phone ringing]
Remember the way we
used to do things?
Hey man...
Like connect with friends?
Dig it!
Or get in shape?
Or sell a house
and pay a real estate
agent a big commission.
[crash]
At Redfin, we charge
you a 1% listing fee.
And because Redfin.com is
America's #1 brokerage site
our agents get more
eyes on your home
so you sell for
thousands more
than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin Agent.
than the one next door.
>> A LUNCHEON FOR SURE!
AS A MATTER FACT, BOTH OF US IS
GOING ON TO!
SO AT THIS GAME, YOU ALREADY
KNOW THE SCORE.
TOO BAD MY TOUR IS SELLING
BETTER THAN YOURS!
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
>> ARE SO YOUR PAYCHECK FOR YOUR
SHOW.
YOU KNOW IT IT REAL.
COME WORK WITH ME.
YOU KNOW WE'D GET THAT BREAD FOR
REAL.
SIGN THAT [BLEEP].
TO BE REACHED.
SET YOUR BLACK -- DOWN AND WATCH
THIS TEACHER TEACH!
>> Nick: BOW WOW WANT TO BE
TOUGHER AT THE!
YOU WANT TO BE TOUGH!
CALL ME COME ABOUT WHILE!
WE STILL GOT SOME TALKING TO DO.
WE ARE GOING TALK ABOUT THAT.
WE'RE GOING TO TALK.
THAT'S MY FRIEND.
BOTH OF MY FRIENDS.
WE WILL TALK ABOUT THAT WOULD
APPEAR THAT WAS A CLIP FROM
"WILD N' OUT."
IT'S A NEW SEASON, AND MTV.
IT'S TIME FOR "LOOSE CANNON."
ARE YOU READY?
>> MY NAME IS GLORIA.
>> Nick: WHERE ARE YOU FROM
CLOSE TO MIKE >> EDISON,
NEW JERSEY.
>> Wendy: YOU HAD TO THINK
ABOUT!
ARE YOU IN THE WITNESS
PROTECTION PROGRAM?
>> MAY BE!
>> Nick: QUESTION?
>> HOW YOU DOIN'!
>> Wendy: I CAN'T DO IT.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
>> I LOVE YOUR ENERGY, BY THE
WAY.
>> Nick: THANK YOU.
>> I HAVE TWO KIDS AT HOME, A
3-YEAR-OLD.
HOW YOU HANDLE TEMPER TANTRUMS
VOTE DON'T WORK WITH CRAZY
CUSTOMER GOING TO HAVE KIDS.
LET ME KNOW.
>> Nick: LOTS OF PRAYER.
>> THAT'S A GOOD ONE!
>> Nick: REALLY COME A QUIET
TIME.
PEOPLE TO UNDERSTAND HOW
IMPORTANT MEDITATION IS FOR
CHILDREN.
IF YOU ALLOW YOUR CHILDREN TO
SIT STILL FOR 15 MINUTES A DAY,
TEACHES THE DISCIPLINE AND GET
SOME FOCUS.
IT ALLOWS THEIR BRAIN TO WORK
MORE.
THAT'S REAL.
NO DOUBT.
THAT'S WHAT I DO.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME, BRO?
MR. DOUGLAS.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHAT'S YOUR QUESTION?
>> COOL, MAN.
A LITTLE BACKGROUND KNOWLEDGE --
I'VE A LOT OF BEAUTIFUL FEMALE
FRIENDS.
I'M NOW GOING PERSON.
>> Nick: ME TOO.
LOOK AT THEM, THEY'RE ALL HERE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> CHECK ME OUT.
UNFORTUNATELY THAT CAUSED SOME
PROBLEMS IN MY PREVIOUS
RELATIONSHIPS, LITTLE JEALOUSY.
MY QUESTION, MOVING FORWARD AS A
SINGLE MAN, I WANT TO DO BETTER.
HOW CAN MAKE SURE MY WOMAN IS
SECURE IN MY RELATIONSHIP?
>> LET HER KNOW.
LET HER KNOW HOW IMPMPORTANT SHE
IS AND HOW MUCH OF A QUEEN SHE
IS.
AND THAT SHE IS YOUR CROWN.
IF YOU UPLIFT HER, SHE WILL
NEVER BE INSECURE.
THE MORE YOU BUILD HER UP AND
GIVE HER THAT SECURITY, SHE WILL
BUILD YOU UP.
IT'S ABOUT BEING EQUALLY YOKED.
IT'S ABOUT THAT BALANCE.
YOU CAN RIDE TOGETHER RIGHT
THERE.
UP NEXT WE'RE GOING TO PLAY
"STAR FLASHBACK."
WE BALANCE OUT HERE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
Ordinary tissues left Dakota's
nose sore and red.
So Dad slayed the problem with
Puffs Plus Lotion, instead.
With lotion to soothe and
softness to please.
A nose in need deserves
Puffs, indeed.
This is why you do it.
The big smiles those
little surprises can bring.
Kinder Joy is a simple way to
add surprise to your kid's day.
Now with over 50 new toys
to build.
Kinder Joy.
A Little Surprise Goes
a Long Way.
>> Nick: WE ARE BACK, AND IT'S
TIME TO PLAY "STAR FLASHBACK"!
LET'S MEET OUR PLAYER.
WE ARE GOING TO -- WHAT'S YOUR
NAME?
>> PRISCILLA.
>> Nick: WHERE ARE YOU FROM?
>> PRECLUDES IN THE HOUSE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: WE ARE GOING TO SHOW
A CELEBRITY FLATBACK PHOTO NEED
TO GET TO IT IS.
LET'S SEE THE PICTURE.
I THINK I KNOW WHO THAT IS.
YOU WANT ME TO GIVE YOU A HAND?
YOU NEED A HAND?
SHE'S AN ACADEMY AWARD WINNING
ACTRESS AND MY NEXT BABY MAMA.
[LAUGHTER]
>> HALLE BERRY!
>> Nick: THERE IT IS!
BAM!
YOU ARE RIGHT, AND YOU WON A
PAIR OF MY INCREDIBLE WIRELESS
BLUETOOTH HEADPHONES RIGHT
THERE!
THE NEON ONCE.
THAT'S A LIMITED EDITION!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I LIKE GIVING, Y'ALL.
I KNOW YOU JUST WON THIS GAME,
BUT YOU WANT IT FOR EVERYBODY.
I DIDN'T FORGET ABOUT THE
AUDIENCE!
YOU ARE ALL GOING HOME WITH MY
INCREDIBLE HEADPHONES!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK, Y'ALL.
IS
HOW DOES RON MAKE SURE
HE'S ON TIME TO FACE BROCK
THE SADISTIC STRENGTH TRAINER?
HIS IKEA DRESSER HELPS HIM
ORGANIZE HIS... EQUIPMENT?
WOO!
BE THE MORNING
PERSON YOU'RE NOT.
Breathe In, You're Home.
This uplifting scent of
Tuscan fields can only be
the powerful clean of
Clorox Scentiva.
(Cat 1) Friskies World...
(Cat 2) Smell that?
(Cat 1) Gravy!
(Cat 2) That's not gravy, that's
extra gravy.
(Cat 1) Whoa!
(Cat 2) That's Friskies
Extra Gravy! Paté and Chunky!
(Cat 1) Gravy purr-adise.
(Cat 2) Purr-adise? Really?
(VO) Feed Their Fantasy.
Friskies.
Your digestive system has
billions of bacteria,
but life can throw them off
balance.
Re-align yourself,
with Align probiotic.
And try Align Gummies,
with prebiotics and probiotics
to help support digestive health
Take Prilosec OTC and take
control of heartburn.
So you don't have to stash
antacids here...
Here...
or, here.
Kick your antacid habit with
Prilosec OTC.
One pill a day,
24 hours, zero heartburn.
NOW THAT KATE AND JOE HAVE BEEN
SLEEPING ON AN IKEA MATTRESS,
JOE'S SUDDENLY INTO MAKING
EVERYONE'S MORNING EASIER.
I MADE YOU BREAKFAST.
I ALSO MADE THE KIDS LUNCH
AND I MADE MYSELF A MIXTAPE.
AND IT'S GOOD.
OH!
BE THE MORNING
PERSON YOU'RE NOT.
THE BUTTER.
>> Nick: HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> Audience: HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> Nick: IF YOU'RE EVER IN THE
NEW YORK CITY AREA AND YOU WANT
TO BE PART OF OUR STUDIO
AUDIENCE, THE TICKETS ARE FREE.
GO TO WendyShow.com AND COME
HAVE FUN WITH US!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
BE RIGHT]
BE RIGHT BACK.
♪ ♪
♪ We buy any car dot com ♪
♪ we buy any car dot com ♪
♪ ANY ANY ANY ANY ♪
Did you know trading in your car
at a dealer could cost
you money?
A recent study found consumers
who trade in their car
pay an average of $990
dollars more.
So don't trade in...
sell it....
to We Buy Any Car.
Learn more and get your free
online valuation
now at we buy any car dot com
♪ Find out how much your car is
worth at WeBuyAnyCar.com ♪
>> Nick: WE ARE HAVING AN
AMAZING TIME HERE!
TOMORROW, KILLER MIKE IS ON THE
COUCH.
I LOVE YOU ALL FOR WATCHING!
HEY, YOU KNOW HOW WE DO.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.