putting you on the spot.
Either you want to be--
- It means tend my garden.
- Okay.
- You know.
- Yeah.
I don't have many experiences,
so I don't know if I could
tend the garden.
- Me neither.
Um, yeah,
so you can be my gardener.
- Oh, okay.
- You can plant some seeds.
- All right.
- Um...
it's a sexual innuendo.
- Yeah.
Shaun, did you undress me?
Except your underpants.
How long
have you been here?
All night.
You should be at work.
I'm taking the day off.
No, you should be at work.
You're sick all the time,
not just after hours.
Shaun, you shouldn't
give up your life.
You have my number.
You check in with me.
I have 15 paid vacation days
and 10 sick days per year,
but I can only take sick days
when I'm sick,
not when you are,
so this is a vacation.
[ Sighs ]
The plan is
to align your eyes
using what's called
distraction osteogenesis.
We cut the bone
and implant posts
on either side
of your eye orbits.
Then we slowly expand
that distance,
allowing for new bone to grow
in the gaps.
Molly: Will it hurt?
Mm, for mere mortals
it would,
but with your pain tolerance,
it'll tickle.
You up for this?
So I'll have
perfectly aligned eyes
but still look like
a wad of chewing gum.
Molly...
You lost an awful lot
of bone and soft tissue
in the accident,
and in terms of
facial reconstruction,
we've actually come a long way
in the past two years.
Claire:
And after 12 surgeries,
you get your own
personalized coffee mug.
Oh,
I forgot about that.
Okay, when can
we get prepped?
Is now too soon?
[ Chuckles ]
Car accident.
Karin Tindle, 14.
She was sleeping
in the back.
Trucker in the oncoming lane
fell asleep.
She wasn't
wearing a seatbelt.
Head trauma,
not responsive,
GCS of 5
with decorticate posturing.
Morgan: Sounds like
a bleed in the brain.
And she has a 25-point
difference in blood pressures
between her arms.
-Possible aortic dissection.
-Head and heart.
Lim: Page Dr. Melendez.
Have him meet us
in the O.R.
Have you contacted
Karin's father?
He passed away
three years ago.
Let's go.
Why isn't she waking up?
We're gonna take
good care of her.
♪
-- Captions by VITAC --
Park: CT confirmed
an aortic dissection.
She needs a thoracotomy.
Aorta hasn't ruptured yet...
And she has
a pseudoaneurysm.
We need to get after
her head trauma first.
I don't see
any major brain bleeds
and we can monitor
pressures.
In this case,
the heart trumps the head.
♪
Okay.
I have two major symptoms --
nausea and boredom.
I didn't know boredom was
a symptom of chemotherapy.
It's a symptom of
sitting on my ass all day.
I used to run
a 700-bed hospital
with a staff of thousands.
Now all I have to think about
is how I keep my food down
and how many bowel movements
I've had all week.
Four.
And I don't have to
think about that.
You know what I need?
My meds.
Will you do me a favor
and run
and pick these up?
When I come back,
we can do "Mad Libs."
♪
Melendez: Unclamp.
Graft is holding.
Lim: That's one fire out.
Drill.
Morgan: Pupils are blown.
Park: ICPs are
spiking way up,
brain perfusion CPP
is down.
She needs
a hemicraniectomy.
Let's sit her up.
It's marijuana.
Yes, it is.
Medicinal marijuana.
Hold on.
One...for the boredom.
One for the nausea.
Can I try one?
I met someone
who said cannabidiol
improved his ASD symptoms.
A person?
You met a person once?
Shaun, have you heard of
the scientific method?
I'd like to perform
a practical,
albeit anecdotal,
experiment.
Since you're on vacation...
and we can keep an eye out
on each other...
♪
One. One. Uh, whoa.
One. Take one.
♪
Lim: Cruciate wide incision
of the dura.
-Brain edema.
-She's bradycardic.
Push another 50 grams
of Mannitol
and ventilate down
her CO2.
Morgan: No corneal reflex.
No overbreathing vent.
No brain stem reflexes.
She's brain-dead.
♪
[ Sighs ]
[ Monitor beeping,
ventilator hissing ]
(Nora)
Before we start - how much is my
tax prep going to cost?
(Tax Guy)
I can't really say that until
the end.
(Lisa) [off-screen]
Wait, no.
H&R Block has upfront,
transparent pricing
so you know the price
before you begin.
(Nora)
So, it can work like that.
(Lisa)
Yup!
(Tax Guy)
Oh, so you want transparency.
Oh, um I could give you a
ballpark...
Ummm, hmmmm.
(Lisa)
That's not a price.
(Lisa VO) ♪
Know the price before you begin.
With new upfront transparent
pricing at H&R Block.
In-person or online.
Block has your back.
Take a moment.
To unwind...
with Lindor.
A milk chocolate shell
with a smooth, melting center
From the Lindt
Master Chocolatiers
Lindor, only from Lindt.
From the Lindt
Master Chocolatiers
Sweat.
Dedication.
Cupcakes.
We played football together for
the Titans.
Now, we own a cupcake shop.
I love this new Surface Pro.
It's light, it's sleek, it's
fast.
Cupcakes are a great business.
As long as you don't eat the
profits!
It's back!
Lobsterfest is on
at Red Lobster.
With the most lobster dishes
of the year,
what'll you choose?
How 'bout Lobster Lover's Dream?
More like a lobster dream
come true.
A butter-poached Maine tail,
roasted rock tail
and creamy lobster linguine.
Or try NEW Lobster in Paradise.
It's a crispy coconutty,
vacation on a plate.
New Ultimate Lobsterfest
Surf & Turf is here, too.
'Cause what's better than
steak and lobster?
Steak and LOTS of lobster.
So hurry in and see how
you're going to Lobsterfest.
♪ I FEEL MOST TIMES
WE'RE HIGH AND LOW ♪
♪ HIGH AND LOW ♪
♪ IF I HAD MY WAY ♪
ENHANCE YOUR MOMENTS.
SAN PELLEGRINO.
TASTEFULLY ITALIAN.
[ Glass shatters ]
Glassman: Fore!
[ Both laugh ]
You broke my house.
You got to club down.
It's just 12 yards.
It's a little dog leg.
Here. Watch this.
[ Thudding ]
[ Laughing ]
It's in the cup.
Nice shot, Glassy.
You're gonna call me
Glassy?
All right.
I'm gonna call you Smurf.
Smurf. This --
This is very interesting.
I find that very funny.
But it's not.
It's not. Am I high?
I think you're pretty high,
yeah.
Am I acting more...
normal?
No, you're acting high.
Smurf. Smurf.
Why is Smurf funny?
I don't know.
It's -- It's, um --
You take the first letter
of the first name
and you attach it to the first
syllable of your last name, see?
S-S-S-Murph. Smurf.
We did it all the time
in high school.
So your name was A-Glass?
Yeah, no,
it didn't work for me.
Okay, serious now.
Where's the next hole?
Right there. Careful of
the hazard right behind it.
Okay, Sam Snead.
Dr. Glassman.
See what you got.
[ Club hits golf ball ]
♪
How's Lea?
Lee-Ya.
[ Chuckles ]
Lee-Ya!
There should be a "Y"
in her name.
Lee-Ya.
She still into Jack?
No.
She is into Jake.
Who the hell is Jake?
Jake is the guy
Lea is into.
You okay with that?
I don't think
you're okay with that.
I think that's why
you're here.
I'm here to help you
through chemo.
When a guy is stoned,
he can tell another guy
anything that's in his heart.
You know, all the messy,
scary, embarrassing stuff
that he would otherwise never,
ever, ever tell anyone.
So what are you thinking?
A dog pooped on your lawn.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
[ Door opens ]
You were right to insist
that we deal with the aorta
before the brain.
I appreciate you
saying that.
Don't let guilt make you
second-guess yourself.
Why would I have guilt?
You shouldn't.
That's my point.
Good.
I'm hungry.
Are you hungry?
I think I am.
When a man's hungry,
you know what a man wants?
There's an open can of chickpeas
in the fridge.
Mallomars.
What are Mal--
What are -- what --
what is the Mallomar?
Pure chocolate,
fluffy marshmallows
on a crispy bed
of graham goodness.
Get us an Uber.
♪
The next few days
are going to be filled
with many
difficult decisions.
Decisions no parent
should ever have to make.
We've kept your daughter
on life support
because we --
You...
want to ask
about organ donation.
Yes.
You want her what?
Her heart?
[ Sniffles ]
Unfortunately, her heart
was injured by the trauma,
as were
several other organs.
We have a 16-year-old girl
who had a tragic accident
a couple of years ago
that destroyed her face.
And we were hoping
that you might --
You...want to take
my daughter's face...
and put it
on someone else?
This young girl's life
has been devastated,
and you have a chance --
No.
I'm sorry, Dr. Andrews.
[ Sniffles ]
♪
She's not the only one.
She's a Light Fury.
Go introduce yourself.
[ grunting ]
It's the final quest.
Did she just disappear?
And the epic conclusion...
Show them what you got!
Wow.
to one of the best film
trilogies of all time.
It's time, bud.
[ roaring ]
Now that's a king.
Almost time for me to go.
Well, what if I...
drove me home?
[♪♪]
What if we lost track of time?
What if we took a leap of faith?
Whoo-hoo!
What if you...
missed my flight next week?
[♪♪]
The All-New RAV4.
Toyota.
Let's go places.
This is not a bed.
It's a revolution in sleep.
The Sleep Number 360
smart bed is on sale now,
from $899, during the
Ultimate Sleep Number Event.
It senses your movement,
and automatically adjusts
to keep you both comfortable.
It even helps with this.
So you wake up ready to
hit the ground running.
Only at a Sleep Number store.
Save 50% on the Sleep Number 360
Limited Edition smart bed.
Plus, 24-month financing
on all smart beds.
Only for a limited time.
Sleep Number.
Proven, quality sleep.
Hi. I'm Toffifay.
And I'm the
irresistible combination
of a chewy caramel cup,
a crunchy hazelnut,
hazelnut cream
and a drop of chocolate.
Wow.
So, let's have some fun.
Toffifay.
(VO)
This is the Avery's.
This is the Avery's trying the
hottest new bistro.
Wow.
Wait...and the
hottest taqueria?
And the hottest...What are
those? Oh, pierogis?
And this is the Avery's
wondering if eating out
is eating into saving for
their first home.
This is JC...
(Team Member)
Welcome to Wells Fargo,
how may I help?
(VO)
who's here to help with a free
Financial Health Conversation,
no strings attached.
This is the Avery's with the
support they needed to get
back on track. Well done guys.
(Team Member)
This is Wells Fargo.
♪♪
♪
Okay, how about this one?
Mm-hmm.
"The ugly
can be beautiful.
The pretty, never."
[ Chuckles ]
Seems a little judge-y.
Yeah, well,
it was Oscar Wilde.
Hmm. Fair enough.
So I'm guessing you didn't see
the Quakes last night.
The San Jose Earthquakes?
Your home team?
Yeah, I know who
the Quakes are.
I recorded it.
No, you didn't.
Don't worry.
I watch enough soccer
for the both of us.
[ Elevator bell dings ]
They won 3 to 2,
by the way.
Beautiful goal
in extra time.
They didn't have any either.
Well, that's all
the major chains.
We're 0 for 4.
Our next place
is on Thornwood Drive,
just west
of Santa Teresa Boulevard.
That's in Alamitos.
Yes.
There are still 28 stores
in the greater San Jose area
that we can try
and I've devised a route
starting in the south
working counterclockwise
around the city
to best avoid traffic.
We'll buy you a box,
I promise.
Okay, guys, I, uh,
like a big fare
as much as the next driver
but racking up hundreds of
dollars on a munchie quest
is starting to feel
exploitative.
What do you say
I order ahead for pizza
and then we just pick it up
on the way home?
I don't want pizza.
What takeout food
do you like?
I like pancakes.
I don't want pancakes.
I don't want to go home.
[ Clears throat ]
We're paying you
to drive us.
You want these cookies?
What is the real reason?
You'll laugh.
What's the funny reason?
[ Sighs ]
I had a crush on a girl.
Robin Demayne.
Senior year in high school.
Her favorite snack.
[ Sighs ]
Okay.
Are we going
to get Mallomars?
Nope.
You have been harboring
feelings for this girl
for over 40 years.
That is a worthy quest.
Now, how do you spell
"Demayne"?
D-E?
You're the same sex, race,
approximate age,
share compatible blood types
and antigens,
and a whole bunch
of other things
that make you
the perfect match.
And we just received permission
from her next of kin.
♪
Yeah.
Our donor's on life support
but her heart is compromised,
so we are very much
on the clock.
Cancel all elective surgeries,
all personal plans,
and all hopes of sleep.
[ Laughter ]
This is your home
for the next two days.
Let's give Molly a new face.
[ Applause ]
♪
♪♪
Try new Nature Valley
Fruit & Nut Granola.
THE FIRST DAY CAN
FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE.
YOUR CLOTHES SHOULDN'T.
COTTON. THE FABRIC OF OUR LIVES.
THIS PRESIDENTS DAY,
HAVERTYS IS HONORING
PRESIDENT MOM.
SHE MADE THE EXECUTIVE DECISION
TO BUY STORE BOUGHT COOKIES
FOR THE BAKE SALE.
SHE PARDONED EMMA FOR...
BEING EMMA.
AND THEN THERE WAS THE WHOLE
CONE CRISIS THING.
PRESIDENT MOM, THIS PRESIDENTS
DAY SALE IS FOR YOU!
EVERYTHING IS ON SALE.
GET BIG SAVINGS ON SOFAS, BEDS,
DINING SETS AND MORE.
NOW THAT'S FISCALLY RESPONSIBLE
LEADERSHIP.
HAVERTYS.
Life Looks Good.
Your favorite restaurants now
deliver with DoorDash.
♪
It doesn't matter
where you are.
♪
It doesn't matter what
you're hungry for.
It doesn't even matter
how many you are.
♪
Restaurants come to you.
Delicious at your door.
Download DoorDash.
First order, no delivery fee.
There is another Robin Demayne
living in San Mateo.
That's less than
half an hour from here.
Ooh, I found one in Los Gatos,
even closer.
You realize
how stupid this is, right?
This is a quest.
A quest is never stupid.
A quest is, by definition,
almost always stupid.
Why would I want to see
Robin Demayne
after all these years?
To tell her you love her?
I just want a cookie!
I wasn't in love with her.
I was a teenager.
I was infatuated.
And whenever you thought
about her,
it made you happy.
And you thought about her
all the time.
And every time you saw her,
you felt a rush, light-headed...
Is that how you know
you're in love?
That's how it starts.
And when you're not
with that person,
you miss them so much you're
willing to drive to 32 stores
to find a sensory reminder
that might bring back
those memories.
[ Nathaniel Rateliff & The Night
Sweats' "You Worry Me" plays ]
♪
♪ I'm all right today ♪
♪ You gonna find a way to cross
and you gonna get there ♪
♪ I'm gonna leave it all
out there to dry ♪
out there ♪
♪ I'm gonna leave it all
out there to dry up ♪
♪ I'm gonna
leave it all out there ♪
♪ But you worry me ♪
♪ You worry me ♪
♪
Ride home's on me.
Flake.
Flake's a guy
from my high school.
He knew everyone,
he kept track of everyone,
and I guarantee you
he never left Livermore.
We need to go to Livermore
and ask Flake about Robin.
We're going to Livermore.
[ Turn signal clicking ]
[ Knock on door ]
Claire:
Every lab and imaging test
that comes back
just reinforces the fact
that this really is
a one-in-a-million match.
Nice.
Yeah, it is.
It's also very scary
and natural to be having
second thoughts.
It's just...
I-I don't know how to
accept a gift like this...
Someone else's face,
someone else's identity...
The face is just a mask.
It's what's --
Underneath that counts?
[ Laughs ] Really?
Those lame quotes
we've been mocking,
you're gonna use them
on me?
Yeah.
[ Sighs ]
♪
Molly.
Right now, your face is
the only thing anyone sees.
This operation
will change that.
It'll let the world see
not your new face
but what has always
been behind it.
♪
Will it count towards
the coffee mug?
[ Both chuckle ]
Shaun: Flake lives at
your old high school?
Glassman: He was
the janitor back then.
He's the janitor now.
He'll probably be the janitor
when this planet
crashes into the sun.
Flake.
Findlay Lake
was his name.
Hey, Flakey.
Hey yourself,
Glaaron Assman.
[ Chuckles ] Your name
was Glaaron Assman.
[ Laughs ]
His name was
Glaaron Assman.
1973 state championship.
He threw for 460 yards.
And if you squint hard enough,
you'll see who was named MVP.
Glassman: You said you had
something to show us?
Oh, yeah. Wait right here.
♪
[ Ventilator hissing ]
Shannon?
[ Voice breaking ] I keep
thinking she's just sleeping.
[ Sniffles ]
How can I say goodbye?
♪
We call it
the Walk of Honor.
To thank your daughter
for her sacrifice.
♪
(MEG VO)
I can just suck up my
endometriosis pain...
Or I can...
(DIANE VO)
I can keep apologizing...
Or I can...
(SHERRY VO)
I can hope my pain gets better
on its own...
Or I can talk to
my gynecologist today!
(AVO)
You didn't choose to have
endometriosis...
but you can choose to ask
if ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA is specifically
developed for women
with moderate to severe
endometriosis pain.
In clinical trials,
ORILISSA was proven to reduce 3
common types of
endometriosis pain,
painful periods,
pelvic pain in between
periods,
and pain with sex.
Don't use ORILISSA if you are or
may be pregnant,
have osteoporosis,
severe liver disease, or are
taking drugs like
cyclosporine or gemfibrozil.
It may cause abnormal
liver tests.
ORILISSA may change your
periods, making it hard
to know if you are pregnant.
It does not prevent pregnancy.
Use birth control that does not
contain hormones.
ORILISSA may cause suicidal
thoughts or actions.
It may also cause bone loss.
Ask your gynecologist if
ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA. Made for endo pain.
Julie means more to
me than anything.
And I wanted to ask you
before I ask her.
May I have your permission,
to marry her?
You're not just marrying her.
You're marrying...
...her whole world.
Get zero-down special financing
on bridal purchases
with the Kay Jewelers
credit card.
♪♪
SURPRISE!
(VO) Living with Ammonia odor?
Not a pretty picture.
(VO) Tidy Cats LightWeight
with Ammonia Blocker
tackles tough odor.
Now 100% dust free!
So long Stankface!
(VO) Bye bye dust!
There's a Tidy Cats for that.
This is the all-new
Chevy Silverado.
It's beautiful.
Beefy and mean looking.
It's the strongest, most
advanced Silverado ever.
The cab is bigger than
the last generation.
It's the first truck I've
seen make you look small.
But that's not all...
Whoo!
Oh my...
Whoa!
The Silverado has
more cargo volume
than any competitor.
Very impressive.
Get a total
value of over
$7,000 on this
all-new Silverado
when you finance
with GM Financial.
Find new roads at your
local Chevy dealer.
People aren't talking
about how much
money they saved
buying Giant Brand Chicken.
They're not talking
about how our
pre-chopped veggies are
perfect time-savers.
They're also not talking
about our unique assortment
of over 1,300 Nature's
Promise Items.
Or our fresh grab and
go salads and sandwiches.
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Oh hello, that
looks so good.
At Giant, it's the little
things that make
meal time easy,
so you have more time with
the people you love.
Do you remember a guy
named Bobby Juarez?
Tall kid but too clumsy
to play hoops?
He told me that Robin
married a dentist named Scaplin
and moved out of state.
You couldn't tell me that
when I called?
I wanted to see you.
[ Chuckles ]
Shaun: I found her.
Robin Scaplin
is in Portland, Oregon.
It's an 11 hour
and 27 minute drive.
Fill up the tank,
I guess.
We're going to Portland.
[ Exhales sharply ]
[ Monitor beeping ]
♪
Melendez: 10 blade.
Andrews: 10 blade.
♪
Proximal facial nerve
isolated and dissected.
Okay, let's start
the heavy lifting.
[ Tool whirs ]
♪
[ Water squirting ]
[ Tool whirs ]
Clamping the left and right
common carotid arteries
and jugular veins...
Cutting the carotids
and jugulars...
Let's do it.
♪
[ Ventilator hissing,
monitor beeping ]
♪
[ Flatline ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
It's a long way to go
to visit a married woman
you haven't seen
since high school
who may not even be home.
She's home.
I called at the last stop.
What did she say?
"Hello."
What did you say?
Nothing.
He hung up.
When you sober up,
you are gonna want to
turn around and go home.
Probably.
[ Monitor beeping ]
♪
Andrews: As rehearsed --
veins, arteries, nerves,
in that order, from the chin up.
Yes?
♪
Can I get the osteosynthetic
plates and screws, please?
[ Scoffs ] Damn it.
I tore part
of the donor's artery.
I need more
interrupted sutures.
Let's keep our focus,
people.
Nurse Petringa:
Dr. Browne,
Molly's parents
would like to see you
on your next break.
Take it now.
You, too.
Uh...
Dr. Park?
♪
I had a huge crush
on Robin Demayne.
A thoroughly
unrequited crush...
that slowly turned into
a grudge.
Last day of school,
kids were passing around
their yearbooks,
and I signed in hers
something that was
borne out of anger
and resentment
and pettiness.
It was designed to be
somewhat humorous, but...
was really just
mostly hurtful.
Later that day,
at the award ceremony,
I was skimming through
my yearbook
and saw what she wrote me...
"I have only two regrets --
my haircut
in junior year
and that you never
asked me out."
And just then, I looked out
in the crowd and saw her.
Her eyes were red,
obviously crying,
obviously very hurt.
And at that exact moment,
I was awarded my trophy.
I looked for her after
but never saw her again.
Is that all the scary,
messy, embarrassing stuff
that guys never,
ever tell anyone?
♪
Pretty much.
[ Car door opens ]
♪
Dean and Lori?
This is Shannon.
Lori: Thank you
for meeting with us.
And for...
everything.
Dean: If you don't mind, we have
so many questions for you,
about your daughter.
We'd like to know
what she was like,
what she liked to do.
Molly wants to know, too.
Uh...
Her name was Karin.
And I killed her.
♪
I'm supposed to tell you
to get back in.
Don't let him get to you.
It's not him, it's you.
Your advice that I shouldn't be
second-guessing myself
is making me think you must be
second-guessing yourself.
About what?
You're the one who insisted
we deal with the heart
before the brain.
And you didn't fight me.
Why not?
Because you were right.
I was right.
But you have
never thought anyone
other than yourself was right
in an O.R.
since you first
stepped foot in one.
You backed off 'cause
we're sleeping together.
♪
The car accident
was my fault.
It was my idea
to leave so early.
to let her sleep in the back.
It was up to me to make sure
she was wearing her seatbelt.
Claire: None of which
would've mattered
if the truck driver
hadn't fallen asleep.
It's natural to feel guilt,
but you have to understand
this wasn't your fault.
It doesn't work that way,
Dr. Browne.
It was my handgun
that hurt Molly.
And you can say that
it was a freak accident
or that Molly knew
she wasn't supposed to touch it
or some other B.S.,
but...
it was my fault.
I had one job...
...and that was
to protect my family.
I didn't do my job.
And you could try
to make sense of it,
try to find something,
some pleasure somewhere,
some meaning.
But there just isn't.
♪
And then your daughter...
...does this for us...
♪
[ Sighs ]
Hi, Robin.
Aaron?
♪
Not much here,
except the usual.
What if we spice
things up a bit?
Alexa...
"Fire"
by The Ohio Players
♪Fire (uh) (uh)♪
What if we turn it up a notch?
♪Fire (It's all about) (Uh, uh)♪
What if we go off the map?
♪Fire (Woo, woo, woo)♪
♪Fire♪
The all-new RAV4.
Toyota.
Let's go places.
When Taco Bell's
Nacho Fries disappear...
Where did you go?
...one man must bring them back.
♪
♪Daddy's gonna bring
you Nacho Fries... ♪
Now Serving.
[BONG]
Sweat.
Dedication.
Cupcakes.
We played football together for
the Titans.
Now, we own a cupcake shop.
I love this new Surface Pro.
It's light, it's sleek, it's
fast.
Cupcakes are a great business.
As long as you don't eat the
profits!
♪♪
♪'Cause this is already bigger♪
♪'This is already bigger
than love♪
Dare to be devoted.
Jared.
♪♪
Give the gift of devotion
With our incredible
selection of jewelry
Including hundreds
of pieces under $299
Dare to be devoted.
Only at Jared.
It's tough to quit smoking
cold turkey.
So CHANTIX can help you quit
Da"slow turkey."ed.
Along with support, CHANTIX is
proven to help you quit.
With CHANTIX you can keep
smoking at first
and ease into quitting.
CHANTIX reduces the urge so when
the day arrives,
you'll be more ready to kiss
cigarettes goodbye.
When you try to quit smoking,
with or without CHANTIX.
you may have nicotine withdrawal
symptoms.
Stop CHANTIX and get help right
away if you have changes in...
behavior or thinking,
aggression, hostility,
depressed mood, suicidal
thoughts or actions, seizures,
new or worse heart or blood
vessel problems, sleepwalking,
or life- threatening allergic
and skin reactions.
Decrease alcohol use.
Use caution driving or
operating machinery.
Tell your doctor if you've had
mental health problems.
The most common side effect
is nausea.
Quit smoking "slow turkey."
Talk to your doctor about
CHANTIX.
[ Birds chirping ]
He had
a huge crush on you.
Yeah. Uh...
[ Chuckles ]
That's not
why I'm here, though.
I'm here to apologize.
For what I wrote
in your yearbook.
Yearbook?
Yeah. Uh...
I wrote something, um...
[ Chuckles ]
...hurtful and untrue
and really stupid.
And then I read
what you wrote in mine.
What did I write?
She had a bad haircut
in junior year.
Oh. [ Chuckles ]
I certainly remember that.
Yeah, well,
it was a long time ago.
Anyway, I just --
I wanted to say I'm sorry.
Well...
Apology accepted.
Thank you.
Mallomars.
Robin's favorite snack.
♪
Right side donor to recipient
vessels are anastomosed.
Ditto on the left.
Let's see
how our plumbing works.
Unclamp them, please.
[ Ventilator hissing,
monitor beeping ]
Park:
She's pinking up.
♪
Moving on. Motor and sensory
neurorrhaphies...
♪
How's our girl doing?
She's just waking up now.
[ Chuckles ]
Hi, Molly.
How are you feeling?
Molly: Terrible.
Then we're right
on target.
You want
to have a look?
No.
No rush.
It is going to look...
surreal.
Like you're looking at
a stranger.
But it won't always.
Because nobody laughs
or holds their head
or looks someone in the eye
exactly the way you do.
♪
[ Quietly ] Okay.
[ Door opens ]
I apologize
for telling you how to react
to losing a patient.
Thank you.
When I accused you
of second-guessing yourself,
that's because
I'm doing it, too.
Our relationship has me
questioning everything I do
and everything you do.
You're making this way more
complicated than it has to be.
It is complicated.
The fact that
we're seeing each other
changes the context
of all of our interactions.
I guess that's why
there are rules against it.
I think I can keep
being a jerk to you at work
if that's what you want.
You think
we should end it?
No.
♪
See you tomorrow.
[ Door opens, closes ]
[ Bag zips ]
Claire: So, once you're feeling
a little less woozy,
we'll set you up with
a whole bunch of therapists --
speech, occupational,
physical.
Lori: Shannon.
Please come in.
Shannon:
I'm Karin's mom.
Hi.
I brought something
for you.
♪
[ Sighs ]
She was beautiful.
♪
Thank you.
And thank you for timing
that elevator ride so perfectly.
[ Exhales ]
Can I ask you for a favor?
I'd like to say goodbye.
♪
[ Door opens ]
Glassman: Eh,
we'll clean up tomorrow.
Shaun:
And buy a new vase.
Yeah, buying a new vase
is easy.
Vacuuming up
my grandmother's ashes,
not so easy.
Are you glad
you apologized?
Yeah.
Do you still
feel guilty?
Yeah.
Guilt must be a bad thing
if it makes people feel badly
about something
they can never fix.
Or maybe it's a deterrent
so we do the right thing
the next time.
You loved Robin
but could never be
with her.
Do you wish
you'd never met her?
Not for one second.
I'm not okay
that Lea is into Jake.
♪
Good night, Smurf.
Night, Glassy.
♪