DR. OZ: R. KELLY, THE STORY THE
WORLD IS WATCHING.
WHAT DOES THE FUTURE HOLD FOR
R. KELLY?
>> JAIL TIME.
I THINK HE MIGHT NEED BEHIND
BARS AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED.
DR. OZ: WE HAVE THE FIRST WOMAN
TO TESTIFY AGAINST HIM.
>> HE SAID THEY SHOULD HAVE
MERKED ME.
MERKED MEANS TO KILL YOU
SGLFMENT AND A DAYTIME
EXCLUSIVE.
GLORIA ALLRED WEIGHS IN ON THE
THREAT HE MADE AGAINST HER
CLIENT.
WILL A CONVICTION BE COMING
SOON?
>> TOUGH WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT
IT.
DR. OZ: COMING UP NEXT.
COULD R. KELLY BE GOING BACK TO
COURT ON NEW SEXUAL ASSAULT
ALLEGATIONS?
THE HIP-HOP SUPERSTAR HAS BEEN
ACCUSED OF PREYING ON TEENAGE
GIRLS FOR DECADES.
R. KELLY HAS ALWAYS DENIED
EVERY ALLEGATION.
AND HIS FANS HAVEN'T KNOWN WHAT
TO THINK.
BUT NOW THE ACCUSATIONS AND
BACKLASH H HAVE HIT A RECORD HI
WITH REPORTS THAT HE'S BEING
INVESTIGATED BY THE F.B.I.
TODAY, WE HAVE EXCLUSIVE
INTERVIEWS AND INSIGHT FROM
PEOPLE WHO SAY THEY KNOW HIM
BEST.
AND THESE ACCUSATIONS COULD
CHANGE EVERYTHING.
THERE IS NO SHORTAGE OF
SHOCKING ACCUSATIONS AND CLAIMS
AGAINST R&B SUPERSTAR R. KELLY.
ALLEGATIONS HE HAD SEX WITH
UNDER AGE GIRLS AND ABUSIVE
RELATIONSHIPS WITH DOZENS OF
WOMEN.
SOME BELIEVE TO BE KEPT BY
KELLY AGAINST THEIR WILL.
SPARKING BACKLASH AND A
MOVEMENT.
>> A GROUP OF WOMEN ARMED WITH
PETITIONS ASKED FULTON COUNTY
LEADERS TO CANCEL AN R&B
CONCERT FEATURING R. KELLY.
>> A COUPLE CLAIMS THE SINGER
R. KELLY IS HOLDING THEIR
DAUGHTER AGAINST HER WILL.
>> THE FIRST TIME SINGER R.
KELLY IS RESPONDING THROUGH HIS
ATTORNEY TO THE DOCUSERIES
ACCUSING HIM OF HOLDING YOUNG
WOMEN AGAINST THEIR WILL.
DR. OZ: A SUPERSTAR UNDER
SCRUTINY AS MUTT TIM ACCUSERS
SPANNING DECADES CLAIM SINGER
R. KELLY ABUSED AND KEPT WOMEN
CAP ACTIVE AS SEX SLAVES.
SHARING INSIGHT INTO THE
ALLEGED SHOCKING AND SOMETIMES
SECRETIVE WORLD OF R&B STAR R.
KELLY.
TODAY WE'RE UNRAVELING THE
SHOCKING ACCUSATIONS OF SEXUAL
ABUSE AGAINST HIP-HOP SUPERSTAR
R. KELLY.
NOW, HE HAS ALWAYS DENIED EVERY
ALLEGATION.
BUT NOW WITH HIS FAMILY
SPEAKING OUT AGAINST HIM, AND
REPORTS OF A CRIMINAL
INVESTIGATION, WHAT DOES THE
FUTURE HOLD FOR R. KELLY?
CRIME ONLINE FOUNDER AND FORMER
PROSECUTOR NANCY GRACE JOINS ME
NOW.
THE ALLEGATIONS AS WE SHOULD
ALL KNOW AGAINST R. KELLY HAVE
BEEN SCROLLING FOR YEARS.
WHY NOW ARE WE HEARING REPORTS
OF CRIMINAL INVESTIGATIONS?
>> WELL, I THINK WE'RE HEARING
ABOUT IT NOW MORE SO THAN
BEFORE IS BECAUSE FAMILY
MEMBERS ARE SPEAKING OUT.
BUT THIS GOES BACK BEFORE 1994
AND I HAD TO ADD THAT UP.
THAT'S OVER 20 YEARS THAT THIS
HAS BEEN SWIRLING.
HE MARRIED ALEA.
THEY LIED ABOUT THEIR MARRIAGE
CERTIFICATE.
HE MARRIED HER WHEN SHE WAS
JUST 15 YEARS OLD.
AT BEST.
ALL RIGHT?
SO SINCE 1994, WE'VE KNOWN THIS
IS WHO ROBERT SILVESTER KELLY
IS.
HE'S NOT R.
HE'S NOT R. KELLY.
HE'S ROBERT SYLVESTER KELLY.
DR. OZ: EXPLAIN THE
ALLEGATIONS.
WHAT ARE THEY SPECIFICALLY
AGAINST R. KELLY?
>> YEAH.
HERE'S THE PROBLEM.
AND IT STEMS FROM THE
ALLEGATIONS.
THE ALLEGATIONS CURRENTLY ARE
THAT FEMALE FAMILY MEMBERS,
YOUNG LADIES, ARE BEING HELD
AGAINST THEIR WILL IN A
CULT-LIKE ATMOSPHERE SPANNING
TWO LOCATIONS.
CHICAGO AND ATLANTA.
AND SIX PROPERTIES OWNED OR
RENTED BY ROBERT SILVESTER
KELLY, ALIAS R. KELLY, ALIAS R.
THAT THESE WOMEN, HERE'S THE
PROBLEM, ARE OF AGE AND IN MANY
CASES WHERE THE VICTIMS ARE NOW
COMING OUT AND SPEAKING ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED TO THEM, THE
STATUTE OF LIMITATIONS HAS
PASSED.
NOW, CHICAGO, THEY HAVE A
CHANCE.
BECAUSE A NEW LAW IS
RETROACTIVE.
THESE WOMEN WANT TO COME
FORWARD AND PROSECUTE, THERE
MAY BE A CHANCE THEY CAN.
BUT RIGHT NOW, IT HASN'T
HAPPENED.
AND NOBODY SEEMS TO BE
BELIEVING THESE WOMEN.
I DON'T GET IT.
NOBODY IS LISTENING TO THEM.
IT'S BECAUSE THEY'RE WOMEN?
IS IT BECAUSE THEY'RE
MINORITIES?
I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S WHAT THEY THINK.
AND I TEND TO AGREE WITH THEM.
DR. OZ: AND YOU SAY NO ONE IS
LISTENING BUT A BACKLASH
AGAINST R. KELLY.
>> IS HE IN JAIL?
DID I MISS THAT?
NO, HE'S NOT.
DR. OZ: WHAT IS THE BACKLASH
AGAINST HIM?
AND THERE ARE --
>> THE BACKLASH IS --
DR. OZ: SEPARATING THEMSELVES
--
>> THE INDUSTRY.
DR. OZ: A DOCUSERIES THAT MADE
A LOT OF NOISE.
>> THE DOCUSERIES MADE A LOT OF
NOISE BECAUSE SOME ACTUAL
ALLEGED VICTIMS SPOKE OUT.
AND I COMPLETELY BELIEVE THEM.
AND THE VICTIMS ARE BEING
DEMONIZED TO SUGGEST THAT THEY
WANT MONEY.
THEY WANT FAME.
THEY'RE JUST A BUNCH OF
GROUPIES.
THEY ARE A BUNCH OF GIRLS.
THEY'RE NOT GROUPIES.
AND THEY THINK -- ONE OF THEM
SAID, OH, I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE
THIS LAVISH LIFESTYLE WITH THIS
STAR.
NO.
THEY HAVE TO KNOCK TO GET OUT
OF THEIR ROOM OF THE THEY HAVE
TO WEAR BAGGY CLOTHES SO NOBODY
CAN SEE THEIR CURVES.
THEY HAVE TO LOOK DOWN AT THE
FLOOR.
THEY CAN'T -- THEY HAVE TO ASK
R. KELLY TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
AND THEY HAVE BEEN TRAINED LIKE
PETS.
THEY DON'T KNOW ANY BETTER AND
YOU ASK THEM THEY SAY THEY'RE
IN LOVE AND DON'T WANT TO
LEAVE.
DR. OZ: I'VE HEARD THESE
ALLEGATIONS AND KNOW THIS
DOCUMENTARY THERE'S BEEN A LOT
OF NOISE.
LADY GAGA, CELINE DION HAVE
PULLED THEIR COLLABORATIONS
WITH HIM AND OFFLINE AND YOU
CAN'T FIND THEM ANYWHERE.
KIKI PALM, JADA PINKETT SMITH,
CHRISTINE AGUILERA, AND R.
KELLY HAS BEEN DROPPED BY SONY
MUSIC.
SO HOW DO -- DOES IT IMPACT ON
THIS WHOLE CASE THAT HIS
DAUGHTER HAS GONE ON SOCIAL
MEDIA CALLING HIM A MONSTER,
WHAT DOES THAT TELL YOU?
>> IT TELLS ME THAT THE
DAUGHTER -- AND I HATE TO --
THIS SO MUCH BECAUSE THE
CHILDREN OBSERVE THE WAY HE
TREATED THEIR MOTHER.
SHE THOUGHT HE WAS GOING TO
KILL HER IN HIS HUMMER.
SHE THOUGHT SHE WAS DYING.
DR. OZ: THE MOTHER?
>> THE MOTHER.
AND THE CHILDREN SAW THIS.
AND WHEN -- ONE OF THOSE
CHILDREN FINALLY TOLD THEIR
STORY, I THINK IT'S GOING TO
HAVE A TREMENDOUS IMPACT.
DR. OZ: ALL RIGHT.
SO BACK TO THIS -- THE COURT OF
PUBLIC OPINION.
WHAT DO THE FANS THINK ABOUT
THIS AND WHAT ARE THEY SAYING
ONLINE?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I HATE SO
MUCH?
WHEN THESE CLAIMS FIRST STARTED
SURFACING AND THESE WOMEN WERE
COMING OUT AND SPEAKING
SPECIFICALLY THREE OF HIS
VICTIMS, PEOPLE WERE SAYING,
YOU'RE LYING.
AND YOU CAN SEE THE COMMENTS
ONLINE.
YOU'RE LYING.
YOU JUST WANT MONEY.
THAT'S THE WAY THAT THEY ARE
TREATED.
AND I'M -- I SEE -- AND I THINK
THAT, TOO.
R. KELLY HAS ALREADY WON AT
TRIAL ONCE ON CHARGES HE MADE A
VIDEO OF HIM HAVING SEX WITH A
14-YEAR-OLD GIRL AND THEN
YOU'RE DEMERITTED ON HER --
URINATETD ON HER AND I THINK IN
HER MOUTH.
IF THEY DON'T CONVICT HIM WHERE
WILL YOU GET A JURY THAT WILL?
DR. OZ: ONE OF THE MOST
SHOCKING ALLEGATIONS IS GIRLS
WERE BEING GROOMED AND FOR THAT
REASON BEING HELD UNDER HIS
CONTROL.
WHETHER THEY WANT TO OR NOT,
AND THESE ARE ALLEGATIONS AND
REPORTED THAT THE FULTON COUNTY
DISTRICT ATTORNEY'S OFFICE AND
THE COOK COUNTY STATE
ATTORNEY'S OFFICE ARE IN THE
PROCESS OF LAUNCHING
INVESTIGATIONS ON BEHALF OF
PARENTS CONCERNED ABOUT THEIR
DAUGHTERS BEING HELD.
YOU SHOULD ALL KNOW THAT
BECAUSE THAT MEANS THERE'S SOME
MOVEMENT HAPPENING HERE.
WE REACHED OUT TO BOTH OFFICES.
FULTON COUNTY DECLINED TO
COMMENT AND COOK COUNTY DID NOT
GET BACK TO US IN TIME FOR THIS
TAPING AND WE REACHED TOUT R.
KELLY'S LEGAL TEAM AFTER THE
DOCUSERIES AIRED AND THEY
HAVEN'T GOTTEN BACK TO US.
BUT HIS ATTORNEY STEPHFON
GREENBERG MADE THE FOLLOWING
PUBLIC STATEMENTS.
I WANT YOUR THOUGHTS ON THIS.
HE SAID WHERE'S THE PROOF?
HE DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG.
AND THERE ARE NO UNDER AGE
VICTIMS.
THERE ARE NO SEXUAL ASSAULT
VICTIMS AND NO VICTIMS OF
DOMESTIC VIOLENCE THAT THEY'RE
GOING TO FIND AND DIDN'T EVER
HAPPEN.
THOSE ARE VERY SPECIFIC
DEFENSES.
AS A PROSECUTOR HOW DO YOU
RESPOND TO THAT?
>> I THINK THAT'S A LIE.
AND I'LL TELL YOU WHY.
AND LOOK AT HIS TRACK RECORD.
DID HE BEAT HIS WIFE?
SHE SAYS HE DID.
I BELIEVE SHE IS TELLING THE
TRUTH.
OTHER WITNESSES WOULD BE HIS
CHILDREN.
DID THEY OBSERVE IN THE HOME?
IF THESE WOMEN, HE'S GOT NOW
ARE BRAINWASHED, THEY'RE NEVER
GOING TO REVEAL WHAT'S
HAPPENING.
AND IT'S NOT JUST HIM.
IT'S LIKE WEINSTEIN, WHERE THEY
HAVE THE FEMALE RECEPTIONIST
SET UP THE MEETING AND THEY ALL
KNEW WHAT WAS HAPPENING, HE'S
GOT A WHOLE GROUP AROUND HIM
CALLED RUNNERS THAT DO ALL HIS
BIDDING.
THEY'RE THE ONES THAT ENFORCE
HIS LAWS, HIS RULES ON THESE
YOUNG LADIES.
AND REMEMBER, SOME OF THEM ARE
AT AGE NOW.
AND THEY'RE STILL IN THERE.
THE LAW CAN'T TOUCH IT.
DR. OZ: WHAT KIND OF LEGAL
ACTION CAN WE EXPECT THEN?
>> I DO BELIEVE THAT THE
DISTRICT ATTORNEY'S OFFICE IN
FULTON AND COOK ARE
INVESTIGATING AND BELIEVE YOU
ME, OZ, WHEN THEY GET ONE GIRL
THAT FITS WITHIN THE STATUTE OF
LIMITATIONS, THEY'RE GOING TO
PROSECUTE.
IF THEY CAN JUST GET ONE GIRL
WITHIN THE STATUTE THAT WAS
UNDER AGE, HE'S TOAST.
DR. OZ: IF THEY CAN GET ONE
GIRL THAT FITS THEIR NEEDS,
WHAT DOES THE FUTURE HOLD FOR
R. KELLY?
>> JAIL TIME.
HE CAN MAKE MUSIC BEHIND BARS
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED.
DR. OZ: UP NEXT, WE WILL MEET A
WOMAN WHO SAYS SHE KNOWS THE
REAL R. KELLY.
SHE WAS THE FIRST WOMAN TO EVER
TESTIFY AGAINST HIM IN COURT
FOR SEXUAL ABUSE.
STAY WITH US.
DR. OZ: WE REACHED OUTEACHED OU
Our grandparents checked
their smartphones
zero times a day.
Times change.
Eyes haven't.
That's why there's Ocuvite.
Screen light...
Sunlight...
Longer hours...
Eyes today are stressed.
But Ocuvite has vital
nutrients...
...to help protect them.
Ocuvite.
Eye nutrition for today.
Who said olive oil is the only
heart-healthy cooking oil?
Mazola corn oil has more
cholesterol-blocking
plant sterols than olive oil.
And a clinical study showed
it can help
lower cholesterol 2X more.
When it comes to heart-health,
Mazola is a smart choice.
Darrell's family uses Gain
Flings now,
so their laundry smells more
amazing than ever.
[Darrell's wife] Isn't that the
dog's towel?
[Dog SFX]
Hey, mi towel, su towel.
More scent plus Oxi Boost and
Febreze in every Gain Fling.
Never ending is now even better
at Olive Garden.
All new Never Ending Stuffed
Pastas starting at $12.99.
Pick your favorite stuffed
pasta, sauce and topping.
It's all never ending.
All new
Never Ending Stuffed Pastas.
Only for a limited time,
at Olive Garden.
TO US IN TIME FOR THIS TAPING.
WE'RE BACK UNRAVELING THE
ALLEGATIONS AGAINST R&B
SUPERSTAR R. KELLY.
WHO IS NOW REPORTEDLY UNDER
CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION AFTER
NEW EXPLOSIVE ACCUSATIONS OF
SEXUAL ABUSE HAVE SURFACED.
BUT SOME WOMEN HAVE BEEN
SPEAKING OUT AGAINST HIM FOR
YEARS.
LISA VAN ALLEN KNOWS R&B SINGER
R. KELLY'S ALLEGEDLY SORDID
SIDE FAR TOO WELL.
SHE WAS JUST 17 WHEN SHE SAYS
THE SINGER SEDUCED HER AND THAT
HE BEGAN AN ABUSIVE NINE-YEAR
RELATIONSHIP.
ONE IN WHICH SHE WITNESSED MANY
THINGS SHE CLAIMS CONFIRMS THE
WORST ACCUSATIONS AGAINST HIM.
SHE WAS ALSO THE FIRST WOMAN TO
OPENLY CONFRONT R. KELLY.
TAKING THE STAND AGAINST HIM IN
2008 WHEN HE FACED 14 COUNTS OF
CHILD PORNOGRAPHY.
HE WOULD BE ACQUITTED OF ALL
CHARGES IN THAT TRIAL.
BUT COULD NOT BE -- BUT COULD
BE FACING NEW ONES AND LISA VAN
ALLEN REMAINS HIS MOST
OUTSPOKEN CRITIC.
AND AN ADVOCATE FOR HIS ALLEGED
VICTIMS.
LISA VAN ALLEN JOINS ME NOW.
REMEMBER, SHE RISKED CHARGES
AGAINST HERSELF WHEN SHE CAME
FORWARD ABOUT BEING IN A SEX
TAPE THAT INVOLVED MY I
DON'TERS.
-- THAT INVOLVED MINORS.
AND WAS GRANTED IMMUNITY FOR
HER TESTIMONY.
I KNOW THIS IS HARD TO DO AND
THANK YOU FOR SHARING A PART OF
YOUR LIFE.
WHAT MADE YOU DECIDE TO TESTIFY
IN COURT AGAINST R. KELLY?
>> WELL, THERE WERE MULTIPLE
THINGS.
BUT ONE OF THEM WAS THEY
ACTUALLY THREATENED MY LIFE.
HIS TEAM SAID THEY SHOULD HAVE
MERKED ME FROM THE BEGINNING.
MERKING MEANS TO KILL YOU.
IT WAS TOUGH.
IT WAS REALLY TOUGH WHEN I
DIDN'T EVER KNOW THEY WERE
THINKING ABOUT KILLING ME.
DR. OZ: HOW DIFFICULT WAS THE
TRIAL FOR YOU?
HAVING TO GO INTO COURT AND BE
ASKED THEE QUESTIONS AND BE
JUDGED?
>> IT WAS VERY DIFFICULT.
BECAUSE I WAS ALONE, YOU KNOW?
HE HAD ALREADY THREATENED MY
LIFE.
I DIDN'T HAVE ANYONE ELSE
BACKING ME.
NO ONE ELSE COMING OUT.
IT WAS TOUGH.
DR. OZ: SORRY.
>> IT'S TOUGH WHEN YOU THINK
ABOUT IT.
DR. OZ: IT'S OK.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
>> JUST THINKING ABOUT
EVERYTHING, YOU KNOW?
I WANTED TO SPEAK OUT FOR THE
YOUNG GIRL ON THE TAPE.
DR. OZ: SORRY.
>> AND THEY KNOW WHAT WAS IN
IT.
THEY SAID THAT ONE OF THE
REASONS THAT THEY COULDN'T
PROSECUTE HIM WAS BECAUSE THE
VICTIM SAID IT WASN'T HER AND
HER FATHER SAID IT WASN'T HER.
BUT I WOULD LIKE TO PUT OUT
THERE THAT THE PROSECUTOR TOLD
ME WHEN HER FATHER WATCHED THE
TAPE, HE CRIED WHEN HE SAID IT
WASN'T HER.
AND IF IT'S NOT YOUR DAUGHTER,
WHAT WERE YOU CRYING ABOUT?
DR. OZ: LET'S GO BACK TO THE
BEGINNING.
I WANT TO UNDERSTAND HOW YOU
MET HIM AND HOW YOUR
RELATIONSHIP WITH R. KELLY
EVOLVED.
>> UH-HUH.
DR. OZ: WHEN YOU DID FIRST SEE
HIM?
>> I MET HIM AT A VIDEO SHOOT
IN ATLANTA, GEORGIA.
IT WAS -- HIS HOME ALONE VIDEO
SHOOT.
DR. OZ: SO THE RELATIONSHIP
STARTS, YOU BECAME INTIMATE
RELATIVELY QUICKLY?
>> YES.
DR. OZ: AND YOU WERE HAPPY?
>> FROM THE BEGINNING, IT
WASN'T REALLY BAD.
YOU KNOW?
FIRST IT WAS LIKE WHEN I MOVED
UP THERE, THE FIRST TIME WE HAD
A THREESOME HE TOLD ME HE WOULD
NEVER HAVE ONE.
SO I FELT LIKE AS HIS
GIRLFRIEND THAT IT WAS
SOMETHING THAT I WOULD DO FOR
HIM BECAUSE HE IS A STAR.
AND I'M SURE WOMEN COME ON TO
HIM ALL THE TIME, YOU KNOW?
AND I'M 17.
SO I DIDN'T KNOW THAT YOU CAN
SAY NO.
AND THAT CAN BE OK.
AND IF HE LOVES YOU, HE'LL BE
OK WITH THAT.
DR. OZ: BUT OVER TIME, HOW DID
YOU FIND THE RELATIONSHIP
CHANGED?
>> OVER TIME, I GOT OLDER.
AND WISER.
BECAUSE IT REALLY DIDN'T
CHAPING.
THE THREESOMES BECAME MORE
FREQUENT.
ONCE IT HAPPENED WITH THE GIRL
THAT WAS 14, AND IN THE
BEGINNING, WHEN I WAS 17 SHE
TOLD ME SHE WAS 16 AND THE
REASON FOR THAT, I BELIEVE, IS
BECAUSE HE THOUGHT THAT, YOU
KNOW F. SHE WAS MY AGE, I WOULD
BE OK WITH IT.
BUT ONCE I FOUBD OUT THROUGH
HER THAT SHE WAS 14, IT NEVER
HAPPENED AGAIN.
I WAS NOT OK WITH THAT.
YOU KNOW, THAT MADE ME SICK TO
MY STOMACH TO KNOW THAT I WAS
17 WHEN SHE WAS 14.
AND STILL WITH A MINOR, IT WAS
JUST -- IT WASN'T OK WITH ME.
DR. OZ: DID YOU FEEL THAT HE
WAS MANIPULATING YOU?
>> YES.
I FEEL LIKE EVERY WOMAN OR GIRL
THAT HE'S WITH, HE MANIPULATES
THEM.
HE MAKES SURE HE DOES THINGS
THE WAY HE NEEDED THEM TO GET
DONE TO GET WHAT -- THE OUTCOME
HE WANTS.
DR. OZ: SO AFTER GOING THROUGH
THIS FOR A WHILE, YOU DECIDE TO
END THE RELATIONSHIP.
>> YEAH.
DR. OZ: HOW MANY YEARS INTO
KNOWING HIM DID YOU END IT AND
WHY DID YOU END IT?
>> WELL, I LIVED WITH HIM FOR
THREE YEARS.
SO AT 21, THAT'S WHEN I DECIDED
TO LEAVE.
I NEVER TOLD HIM THAT I WAS
LEAVING.
I TOLD HIM I WANTED TO GO VISIT
WITH MY FAMILY.
AND I MADE UP SOME LITTLE
URGENT SITUATION THAT I NEEDED
TO LEAVE FOR.
AND I JUST DIDN'T GO BACK.
DR. OZ: UP NEXT THE MOST
SHOCKING ALLEGATION TO COME OUT
ABOUT R. KELLY.
LISA REVEALS WHAT SHEE
TOLD HER.
STAY WITH US.
People everywhere
are confusing Quilted Northern
for a Bouncy Castle.d Northern
for a Bouncy Castle.
They're both durable, flexible
and nice to have at parties.
But Quilted Northern
is not a Bouncy Castle.
It's just really nice
toilet paper.
Cancer won't wait for
appointments to open up,
test results to come back,
or treatment plans to start.
At Cancer Treatment Centers of
America,
we make time for cancer
patients.
Time to answer questions,
relieve worries,
and turn indecision into good
decisions.
Because cancer won't wait,
and we don't think you should
either.
Call or go online anytime
to set up an appointment with
our team of cancer experts.
Cancer Treatment Centers of
America.
Appointments available now.
When you feed yourself
some oats,
the oats feed your body fiber.
Fiber helps keep things
moving through your system.
Which is great.
Because when you're good
to your system,
it'll be good to you.
New Year's resolutions are hard.
But a New Year's deal
on the best entertainment
and the quickest
way to find it?
The Crown.
Easy.
Getting the kids to
school on time? Hard.
But getting the
most reliable Internet
so you can stream
while you frost?
Easy.
It's the Xfinity
New Year New Deal.
And it's simple,
easy, awesome.
Get this deal on
TV, Internet and Voice
for $79.99 a
month for 2 years
with DVR free for a year.
And ask about Netflix,
Prime Video and Youtube
in 4K ultra HD.
Click, call or visit us today.
DR. OZ: WE'RE BACK WITH LISA
VAN ALLEN.
THE FIRST WOMAN TO TESTIFY
AGAINST R. KELLY FOR SEXUAL
ABUSE ALLEGATIONS.
SO WHEN YOU SPOKE ABOUT AGAINST
HIM, AND LIFETIME SERIES YOU
WERE INTERVIEWED.
>> UH-HUH.
DR. OZ: WHAT KIND OF BACKLASH
DID YOU EXPERIENCE AND WHAT
HAPPENED TO R. KELLY?
HOW DIFFICULT HAS IT BEEN FOR
YOU SINCE TELLING YOUR STORY?
>> I'VE ACTUALLY HAD A LOT OF
SUPPORT LIKE ON MY SOCIAL MEDIA
ACCOUNTS AND THINGS LIKE THAT,
I'VE HAD A LOT OF SUPPORT.
THERE ARE SOME DIEHARD FANS.
THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE THAT JUST
CHOOSE NOT TO BELIEVE WHAT -- I
FEEL LIKE IS JUST IN YOUR FACE.
IT'S PUBLIC RECORD.
YOU CAN GO TO COOK COUNTY
COURTHOUSE AND PULL UP ALL
THESE CASES THAT HE PAID GIRLS
OFF.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY YOU
WOULD PAY ANYONE OFF IF IT'S
NOT TRUE.
DR. OZ: SO NANCY, DO YOU LIVE
-- YOU LIVE IN THIS WORLD.
IF THERE WAS A NEW TRIAL TODAY,
WOULD IT TURN OUT DIFFERENTLY
FOR --
>> I THINK IT ABSOLUTELY WOULD.
AND WILL TURN OUT DIFFERENTLY.
BECAUSE I BELIEVE -- NOT JUST
FROM MY HEART BUT AS A
PROSECUTOR, THAT EITHER FULTON
OR COOK COUNTY, CHICAGO OR
ATLANTA, ARE GOING TO FIND THAT
GIRL THAT FITS IN THE STATUTE
OF LIMITATIONS SO LEGALLY THEY
CAN BRING THIS CASE.
DR. OZ: LISA, WOULD YOU TESTIFY
AGAIN?
>> IT'S CRAZY BECAUSE WHEN I
THINK ABOUT THAT, THEY HAD ME
ON THE STAND FOR THREE HOURS.
AND I WAS SIX MONTHS' PREGNANT
WITH MY SON.
AND THEY DIDN'T ASK ME ONE
QUESTION ABOUT ROB.
FOR THREE HOURS.
AND THEY -- LIKE THEY TRIED TO
-- IT'S HARD.
I DON'T KNOW IF I WOULD WANT TO
RELIVE THAT.
LIKE MY GOAL RIGHT NOW IS TO
RAISE AWARENESS AND I WANT TO
HELP -- I WANT TO HELP ALL
ABUSE VICTIMS LIKE -- IT'S
TOUGH.
DR. OZ: WHAT'S MOST SHOCKING
ABOUT THIS CASE IS PEOPLE VERY
CLOSE TO R. KELLY ARE COMING
FORWARD.
CARRIE KELLY HAS CLAIMED THAT
BOTH AND HE HIS BROTHER WERE
VICTIMS OF SEXUAL ABUSE AT THE
HANDS OF THEIR SISTER.
THEIR OLDER SISTER.
>> I BELIEVE HIM.
BECAUSE ROBERT TOLD ME THAT HE
WAS ABUSED BY HIS SISTER,
TERESA.
HE DID.
DR. OZ: R. KELLY TOLD THAT YOU?
>> HE TOLD ME THAT.
HE DID.
DR. OZ: DID HE SHARE WITH YOU
MORE DETAILS ABOUT THAT?
>> THAT SHE WOULD HAVE HIM
PENETRATE HER WITH A PENCIL.
THAT'S WHAT HE TOLD ME.
DR. OZ: SO WE'VE BEEN UNABLE TO
FIND HIS OLDER SISTER.
>> UH-HUH.
DR. OZ: PEOPLE WHO WOULD HAVE
BEEN THERE AT THE TIME.
>> RIGHT.
DR. OZ: SO I'M TRYING TO PUT
THE PIECES OF THIS VERY
COMPLICATED PUZZLE TOGETHER.
>> UH-HUH.
DR. OZ: WHILE WE'RE ALL TRYING
TO ALSO UNDERSTAND WHY THERE
HASN'T BEEN SOMETHING DONE.
>> YES.
DR. OZ: FOR ALL THESE YEARS.
DR. OZ: SO I APPRECIATE YOU
COMING FORWARD.
I KNOW IT'S HARD AND GOT SPEED
AND ALL THE THINGS YOU'RE
TRYING TO DO.
>> THANK YOU.
DR. OZ: THANKS, LISA.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
DR. OZ: MORE ACCUSATIONS A
LAWSUIT AGAINST R. KELLY THAT
TOOK EVERYONE BY SURPRISE AND
ALLEGATIONS OF RE
Honey, you know,
some things you can't take back.
It's one of those things...
...unless you got it from ALDI.
Their Twice as Nice Guarantee
means if you're not happy
for any reason,
they'll give you a refund
and replace it.
Well fine, why don't you just
return me then?
But, you didn't come
from ALDI.
I'm sure you'll love
Kevin forever, huh?
One thing you'll never regret
is saving big at ALDI.
Save on select Mama Cozzi's
16 inch take-and-bake pizzas,
now just four ninety-nine.
ALDI. Shop differentli.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪
DR. OZ: WE'RE BACK ASKING COULD
R. KELLY BE GOING BACK TO
COURT?
A NEW SEXUAL ASSAULT CHARGE?
ANOTHER WOMAN HAS COME FORWARD
WITH HER OWN PERSONAL ACCOUNTS
OF R. KELLY'S ALLEGED ABUSE.
SHE IS SPEAKING OUT IN A
DAYTIME EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW FOR
THE FIRST TIME SINCE FILING AN
UNEXPECTED LAWSUIT AGAINST R.
KELLY.
WHAT SHE HAS TO SAY ABOUT HIM
COULD CHANGE EVERYTHING:--
CHANGE EMPING.
THERE ARE NEW LEGAL TROUBLES
FOR SINGER R. KELLY AS GLORIA
ALLRED IS REPRESENTING SOME OF
HIS VICTIMS INCLUDING FAITH
RODGERS.
>> TAKING THE STAND AGAINST R.
KELLY, SOMEONE WHO'S BEEN
TERMED THE KING OF R&B, AND IS
LOVED BY MANY HAS NOT BEEN
EASY.
I DECIDED AFTER A GREAT DEAL OF
THOUGHT THAT I SHOULD SPEAK MY
TRUTH BECAUSE IT IS TIME I
STAND UP FOR MYSELF.
DR. OZ: IN 2018, RODGERS FILED
A CIVIL LAWSUIT AGAINST KELLY
IN NEW YORK FOR FALSE
IMPRISONMENT, ALLEGED SEXUAL
BATTERY, AND DELIBERATELY
INFECTING HER WITH AN S.T.D.
>> ROBERT KELLY, THE FAITH
RODGERS YOU KNEW THAT YOU MET
WHEN I WAS 19 NO LONGER EXISTS.
SHE WAS VULNERABLE AND
IMPRESSIONABLE.
THE 21-YEAR-OLD FAITH RODGERS
YOU'RE SEEING NOW IS MUCH WISER
AND MUCH STRONGER.
DR. OZ: FAITH RODGERS JOINS ME
NOW.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
>> THANK YOU.
DR. OZ: I KNOW IT'S HARD TO GO
OVER SOME OF THIS.
BUT IT'S VITALLY IMPORTANT.
>> RIGHT.
DR. OZ: HOW DID R. KELLY COME
INTO YOUR LIFE?
>> I MET R. KELLY AT A CONCERT
WITH MY OLDER SISTER.
IT WASN'T EVEN, YOU KNOW, A
PLANNED THING, RANDOM WEEKDAYS,
LIKE COME TO R. KELLY SHOW WITH
ME.
AND I END UP GOING.
WE END UP MEETING AT THE
CONCERT.
WE EXCHANGED NUMBERS BACK STAGE
THAT NIGHT.
DR. OZ: AND THE SECOND TIME YOU
MET HIM, IT WASN'T QUITE SO
INNOCENT?
>> RIGHT.
DR. OZ: WHAT DID HE DO THAT
MADE YOU CONCERNED?
>> JUST -- YOU REALLY GOT TO
SEE HIS -- HOW HIS CONTROLLING
WAYS COME OUT AND THE
MANIPULATION COMES OUT WHEN
SOMEBODY IS TEXTING YOU, WHEN
THEY'RE CALLING YOU AND THEN
WHEN THEY'RE IN FRONT OF YOU
AND THE VIBE IS COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT.
DR. OZ: SO WHAT -- IN WHAT WAYS
WOULD HE CONTROL YOU AND GET
YOU TO DO THINGS YOU WOULDN'T
NORMALLY DO?
>> THERE ARE TIMES ME AND HIM
WILL BE TALKING NORMAL.
AND HE'S NOT ALWAYS JUST THIS
PERSON THAT'S SO MEAN AND SO
DARK.
HE KNOWS HOW TO SLIP IT, YOU
KNOW?
SO THERE WILL BE TIMES WHERE
WE'RE SITTING HERE AND HE'LL
TELL ME I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
AND HE NEVER COMES BACK.
AND I'M CALLING AND I'M TECHING
AND I'M READY TO LEAVE AND THE
DOORS ARE LOCKED AND YOU CAN'T
LEAVE AND NO WAY TO GET OUT.
AND JUST, YOU KNOW, YOU'LL BE
IN THE STUDIO WITH HIM.
AND HE'LL BE SINGING FOR YOU
AND PLAYING THE PIANO FOR YOU
AND HE'LL DISAPPEAR AND BEFORE
YOU KNOW IT THREE HOURS HAVE
GONE BY.
AND YOU HAVEN'T USED THE
BATHROOM.
YOU HAVEN'T ATE.
AND YOU'RE IN A SITUATION LIKE
THAT AND TRYING TO MAKE NORMAL
OUT OF WHAT'S NOT NORMAL IT
DOESN'T ADD UP.
A LOT OF PEOPLE SAY SHE WAS 19
AND SHE KNEW WHAT SHE WAS
DOING.
WHEN USUAL 19, YOU'RE FRESH OUT
OF HIGH SCHOOL.
YOU GRADUATE, 17, 18, AND YOU
DON'T KNOW EVERYTHING.
YES, I THOUGHT I KNEW
EVERYTHING AND I THOUGHT I WAS
GROWN ENOUGH TO GET INVOLVED
WITH AN OLDER MAN NOT KNOWING
THERE'S REPERCUSSIONS BEHIND
THE SITUATION.
SO THAT'S WHAT I WANT TO SHED
LIGHT ON.
IT'S NOT SOMETHING THAT PEOPLE
SIGN UP FOR.
DR. OZ: DID IT SEEM CULT-LIKE
WHEN YOU WERE THERE?
WERE THERE OTHER WOMEN WHO WERE
GOING THROUGH THE SAME JUGGLING
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHY
THEY'RE EVEN IN THIS SITUATION?
>> WHEN I MET HIM, THAT WAS
BEFORE ANY OF THE NEWS HAD GOT
OUT ABOUT THIS HARME -- HAREM
OR ANYTHING BEFORE SPEAKING
OUT.
I WAS ALREADY INVOLVED WITH HIM
AND TOO LATE TO GO BACK.
AND I HAD NEVER SEEN ANYTHING.
SO ONE OF THE LAWSUIT FEW TIMES
I SAW HIM THAT'S WHEN HE
FINALLY ADMITTED TO ME THERE
WAS A GROUP OF GIRLS.
AND I SAW HIS BEHAVIOR WITH ME,
HOW CONTROLLING IT WAS.
SO THE FACT THAT YOU HAVE A
WHOLE BUNCH OF WOMEN THAT
YOU'RE DOING THIS TO, AND
YOU'RE ADMITTING TO ME THAT YOU
TRAINED THEM AND YOU'RE RAISING
THESE GIRLS AND SOME OF THEM
HAVE BEEN WITH YOU FOR FIVE
YEARS AND 15 YEARS.
AND IT'S LIKE WHAT SCARED ME
WAS THAT HAD BECAME HIS NORMAL
AND HE WAS TRYING TO MAKE IT
NORMAL TO ME.
THAT'S SCARY.
AND A LOT OF PEOPLE SAY WHY --
WHY YOU DIDN'T TRY TO HELP
THEM?
YOU KNOW AND I'M -- I COULDN'T
HELP THEM IF I CAN HELP MYSELF.
SO I HAVE TO COME TO TERMS AND
ACCEPT.
AND I DON'T COME FROM A FAMILY
OF ABUSE.
I DON'T -- I'VE NEVER HAD TO GO
THROUGH ANYTHING LIKE THIS.
SO WHEN IT'S IN FRONT OF YOU
AND NEVER HAPPENED TO YOU, YOU
HAVE TO REALLY PROCESS AND
UNDERSTAND AND ACCEPT WHAT'S
GOING ON IN FRONT OF YOU.
SO WAS THERE CULT BEHAVIOR?
ABSOLUTELY.
HAVING TO USE THE BATHROOM,
HAVING TO ASK PERMISSION TO
EAT, I CAN REMEMBER I WALKED
INTO A HOTEL.
AND THEY DIDN'T EVEN ASK FOR MY
NAME.
THEY KNEW WHO I WAS.
AND THEY WALKED ME UP TO MY
ROOM.
NO HOTEL THAT I'VE EVER BEEN TO
HAS DONE THAT.
SO THINGS LIKE THAT DEFINITELY
WERE RED FLAGS.
DR. OZ: HOW DID YOU FINALLY
BREAK FREE FROM R. KELLY?
I ASK BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY OTHER
WOMEN, THE WOMEN HE'S RAISING
AS YOU SAID HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO.
>> IT'S DEFINITELY A PROCESS.
AND I DON'T THINK THAT PEOPLE
GET -- IT'S NOT SOMETHING YOU
JUST WALK AWAY FROM.
BECAUSE YOU HAVE ALREADY BEEN
MANIPULATED.
IT'S LIKE FOR ME AND I CAN'T
SPEAK ON EVERYBODY ELSE, BUT I
KNOW FOR ME, THE HARDEST PART
WAS ACCEPTING WHAT I HAD GONE
THROUGH, ACKNOWLEDGING IT'S
WRONG.
BUT WHERE I WENT WRONG IS I
THOUGHT THAT I COULD TALK TO
HIM.
I THOUGHT THAT I COULD CHANGE
I THOUGHT THAT I COULD MAYBE
MAKE HIM DO SOMETHING DIFFERENT
IN ME.
AND YOU'RE NO DIFFERENT.
HE'S NOT GOING TO LOOK AT YOU
ANY DIFFERENT BECAUSE THIS IS
WHAT HE'S DONE FOR YEARS.
SO WHAT MAKES YOU SO SPECIAL?
SO FOR ME, I REALLY HAD TO LOOK
INSIDE OF MYSELF AND THINK BACK
TO THE WAY MY PARENTS HAVE
RAISED ME.
I HAVE NO BUSINESS DEALING WITH
SOMEBODY THREE TIMES MY AGE.
THAT'S SOMETHING I SHOULDN'T
HAVE DID.
AND REALLY, LIKE MY GUILTY
CONSCIENCE WAS JUST EATING ME
UP BECAUSE KNOWING THAT ANOTHER
YOUNG LADY IS IN THAT POSITION,
AND I'M JUST SITTING HERE AND
I'M NOT SAYING ANYTHING.
IT JUST MADE ME FEEL WORSE THAN
EVEN BEING INVOLVED WITH HIM.
SO I JUST KNEW I HAD TO GO.
DR. OZ: I'M HAPPY YOU'RE HERE.
>> THANK YOU.
DR. OZ: AND I KNOW IT'S GOING
TO MAKE A BIG DIFFERENCE AND A
LOT OF PEOPLE ARE STRUGGLING TO
UNDERSTAND HOW THIS WHOLE THING
WORKS.
>> RIGHT.
DR. OZ: I GATHER THAT SOME OF
THESE YOUNG WOMEN ARE SITTING
THERE ALMOST ASHAMED THAT
THEY'VE BEEN MANIPULATED FOR
WHATEVER REASON BY SOMEONE WHO
SEEMS TO BE PRETTY GOOD AT IT.
THOSE ARE THE ALLEGATIONS.
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE FEELING?
>> THAT FEELING --
DR. OZ: THEY'RE ASHAMED AND
THAT'S PART OF WHAT'S HOLDING
THEM BACK?
IS THAT PART OF WHAT SLOWED YOU
DOWN WHEN -- YOU PROBABLY KNEW
DEEP DOWN YOU SHOULD HAVE LEFT
HIM?
>> I WAS ASHAMED.
NOT ONLY WAS I ASHAMED, THOUGH,
IT KIND OF WAS JUST LIKE THIS
MAN THIS H-ALREADY RECORDINGS
OF -- THIS MAN ALREADY HAD
RECORDINGS OF ME.
IMFLAGRANT R PLANTED --
IMPLANTED SO MUCH FEAR IN MY
HEART.
AND I HAD NO THOUGHT OF
CROSSING HIM OR LEAVING HIM.
IT MORE WAS LIKE JUST OK, WHAT
ARE YOU GOING TO DO FOR YOU?
IT WASN'T -- IT WAS ABOUT ME.
AND I THINK SOME PEOPLE ARE
SCARED.
I WAS SCARED.
BUT I WALKED AWAY JUST BECAUSE
I WANT TO KNOW PARTS OF IT.
WHEN I -- WHEN I WALKED AWAY, I
HAD NO INTENTIONS OF BEING
RIGHT HERE, OF TALKING TO
PARENTS, OF TALKING TO OTHER
VICTIMS.
I REALLY WAS JUST -- I DIDN'T
WANT ANYTHING TO DO WITH THE
SITUATION.
I KNEW IT WAS WRONG.
DR. OZ: ARE YOU SCARED NOW?
>> SOMETIMES.
YEAH.
SOMETIMES.
I AM SCARED.
DR. OZ: ALL RIGHT.
SO UP NEXT, THE S.T.D., FAITH
SAYS SHE HAS PROVE CAME FROM R.
KELLY.
DON'T GO AWAY.
When you shop with us, you
know how to score.
But did you know you could be
saving even more?
With the TJX rewards credit card
- every time you shop at
our stores,
you earn 5% back in rewards.
TJX Rewards credit card.
An even better value every day.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE'RE BACK WITH FAITH
RODGERS AND HER ATTORNEY,
GLORIA ALLRED.
JOIN ME IN A DAYTIME EXCLUSIVE
INTERVIEW.
SO IT'S A BIG DECISION BY YOU.
YOU ARE OFTEN PRESENTED WITH
OPPORTUNITIES TO HELP PEOPLE.
WHY DID YOU DECIDE TO TAKE
FAITH'S CASE?
>> WELL, FAITH IS DEFINITELY A
YOUNG WOMAN WHO HAS COURAGE.
AND HER MOTIVES ARE NOT ONLY TO
ASSERT HER OWN RIGHTS, DR. OZ,
BUT ALSO AS SHE SAID, SHE WANTS
TO HELP OTHER YOUNG WOMEN.
BECAUSE THIS HAS BEEN A REALLY
TRAUMATIC LEARNING EXPERIENCE
FOR HER.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: SO FAITH --
>> AND SHE'S WILLING TO DO
THAT.
SHE'S WILLING TO SAY, AND SHE
SAYS THIS IN HER LAWSUIT, THAT
WHAT'S FILED BY HER WONDERFUL
ATTORNEY, LYDIA AGEW, THAT HE
KNEW THAT HE HAD HERPES.
DR. OZ: THIS IS R. KELLY?
>> YES.
AND HE GAVE IT TO HER AND DID
NOT DISCLOSE TO HER THAT HE HAD
IT AND HE KNEW THAT HE HAD IT.
AND THAT IS SOMETHING THAT IS
VERY DANGEROUS.
AND THAT IS WHY IT'S IMPORTANT
TO KNOW THAT IT IS A VIOLATION
OF PUBLIC HEALTH LAW IN NEW
YORK TO HAVE A SEXUALLY
TRANSMITTED DISEASE AND NOT
TELL YOUR SEXUAL PARTNER THAT
YOU HAVE IT.
DR. OZ: ALL RIGHT.
SO TO REITERATE, FAITH HAS
FILED A LAWSUIT AGAINST R.
KELLY CLAIMING THAT HE
KNOWINGLY GAVE HER AN INCURABLE
SEXUALLY TRANSMITTED INFECTION.
AN S.T.D.
AT WHAT POINT DID YOU REALIZE
THAT YOU HAD BEEN INFECTED?
>> AFTER I LEFT.
DR. OZ: YOU WERE ALREADY GONE?
>> YES.
DR. OZ: AND DID YOU HAVE ANY
IRVIN WILLING THAT HE WAS
INFECT -- INC.ALING THAT HE WAS
INFECTED?
HAD HE EVER INTUITED THAT?
>> NO.
>> AND I NOW REPRESENT ANOTHER
YOUNG WOMAN WHO ALLEGES THAT
SHE WAS UNDER AGE WHEN MR.
KELLY INVOLVED HIMSELF IN
SEXUAL INTERCOURSE WITH HER.
AND THAT HE GAVE HER HERPES.
THIS IS PRIOR TO HIS EVER BEING
INVOLVED WITH FAITH.
SO THAT'S ONE OF THE REASONS
THAT IN THE LAWSUIT, IT IS
ALLEGED THAT HE KNEW THAT HE
HAD HERPES BECAUSE SOME YEARS
EARLIER, HE HAD GIVEN IT TO
SOMEONE ELSE.
DR. OZ: AND SHE HAD TOLD HIM
THAT SHE HAD GOTTEN THE
ILLNESS?
THAT'S HOW YOU WOULD KNOW?
>> WELL, WHETHER OR NOT SHE
TOLD HIM, SHE ALLEGES THAT HE
WOULD HAVE KNOWN FAITH --
ALLEGES HE WOULD HAVE KNOWN IF
IN FACT HE HAD IT AND GAVE IT
TO SOMEONE ELSE.
SO, YOU KNOW, THIS IS GOING TO
BE A VERY INTERESTING AND
IMPORTANT PART OF THE LAWSUIT.
MANY PEOPLE DON'T KNOW, THEY
HAVE LEGAL RIGHTS AGAINST
SOMEONE WHO GIVES THEM A
SEXUALLY TRANSMITTED DISEASE.
HERPES OR ANYONE ELSE, IF THAT
PERSON KNEW OR SHOULD HAVE
KNOWN THAT THEY HAD THAT
DISEASE AND FAILED TO DISCLOSE
IT.
THAT'S WHY ONE OF THE CAUSES OF
ACTION, DR. OZ, IN THE LAWSUIT
IS IT'S CALLED FRAUD.
FRAUDULENT CONCEALMENT IF YOU
DON'T MAKE THAT REPRESENTATION
OR MISREPRESENT YOUR HEALTH
CONDITION.
>> I WAS REALLY TELLING MY
PARENTS PROBABLY THE HARDEST
THING THAT I HAD TO DO.
SORRY.
DR. OZ: THAT'S OK.
>> I HATE CRYING ON CAMERA AND
ALWAYS TELL MYSELF I'M NOT
GOING TO CRY.
DR. OZ: WHAT DOES YOUR MOM TELL
YOU WHEN YOU TOLD HER?
>> SHE WAS MORE IN SHOCK
BECAUSE WHEN I TOLD HER, I TOLD
HER EVERYTHING.
NOT JUST THIS ONE THING.
HEY, MOM, THIS IS WHAT I'VE
BEEN DOING FOR THE PAST 11
MONTHS.
SO EVERYTHING, WE SAT MY DAD
DOWN AND I TOLD MY DAD.
OF COURSE, THEY WEREN'T HAPPY,
YOU KNOW?
IT'S WHY, FAITH?
WE TAUGHT YOU BETTER.
I KNEW BETTER.
AND I KNEW I KNEW BETTER
BECAUSE I FELT LIKE OK, THIS IS
NOT SOMEBODY THAT I COULD EVEN
BRING HOME, YOU KNOW?
SO TO HAVE -- TO SIT DOWN AND
ADMIT TO YOUR FATHER AND LOOK
YOUR FATHER IN THE EYE, AND NO
BUSINESS BEING WITH THAT --
PROBABLY ONE OF THE MOST
EMBARRASSING FEELINGS.
DR. OZ: IT TAKES A LOT TO DO
WHAT YOU'RE TRYING TO
ACCOMPLISH NOW IS VERY BRAVE.
>> THANK YOU.
DR. OZ: I'M GOING TO ASK THE
QUESTION EVERYONE IS THINKING,
WHY WOULD YOU PUT YOURSELF IN
THE BULL'S EYE?
WHY EXPOSE YOURSELF?
YOU'VE ALREADY ACKNOWLEDGED
THINGS THAT ARE VERY PRIVATE
AND VERY SENSITIVE.
AND I APPLAUD YOU FOR DOING IT.
BUT WHY NOT JUST GO HIDE?
>> UH-HUH.
I FEEL LIKE I DID TRY HIDING.
AND IT DIDN'T WORK FOR ME.
SO IF I HAVE TO EMBARRASS
MYSELF, AND TO HELP SOMEBODY
ELSE, I'M WILLING TO DO THAT.
>> AND THIS SHOULD BE A
TEACHING MOMENT.
[APPLAUSE]
BECAUSE TAKE A LESSON FROM WHAT
FAITH JUST SAID.
SO I WOULD ASK THE QUESTION,
DR. OZ, WHAT DID HE PUT HIMSELF
AS A 50 PLUS-YEAR-OLD MAN IN
THIS POSITION WITH A
19-YEAR-OLD AND WITH OTHER
YOUNG WOMEN, SOME OF WHOM
ALLEGEDLY WERE UNDER AGE, WHY
DID HE DO WHAT HE'S ALLEGED TO
HAVE DONE?
WHY WON'T HE ACKNOWLEDGE IT?
WHY WON'T HE TRY TO MAKE THINGS
BETTER?
THAT'S THE QUESTION WE NEED TO
ASK ABOUT R. KELLY.
INSTEAD, HIS -- DEFINITELY.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: AND I HAVE NOT SEEN
YOUR MEDICAL RECORDS.
BUT I AM CURIOUS WHAT YOUR
DOCTORS ARE ADVISING FOR YOU.
>> UH-HUH.
SO THEY HAVE SOME MEDICATION
OUT THERE.
I'M NOT REALLY TAKING IT, YOU
KNOW, I TAKE CARE OF MYSELF BY
EATING RIGHT, KEEPING MY STRESS
DOWN, SO THERE'S -- AND A LOT
OF PEOPLE HAD ASKED ME OR
ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW, I'VE HAD A
LOT OF PEOPLE WHO SHARED THE
SAME DISEASE AS ME WHO HAVE
GIVEN ME TIPS WHO HAVE DONE
THINGS THAT HAVE HELPED ME TO
WHERE I CAN LIVE A NORMAL LIFE
WHICH THAT'S WHY -- THAT'S WHY
I CAN COME ON HERE AND PUT MY
FACE NEXT TO THIS UGLY S.T.D.
AND SAY IT'S OK.
YOU KNOW?
>> BUT SHE'S ALSO -- YEAH.
THAT'S FANTASTIC.
I'M JUST GOING TO SAY SHE DID
TAKE A TEST PRIOR TO THE
LAWSUIT ALLEGES PRIOR TO BEING
INVOLVED WITH MR. KELLY.
AND SHE WAS CLEAN.
SHE HAD NO S.T.D.
DR. OZ: AND TAKING THE TEST --
>> I CAN TELL YOU WHY I TOOK
THE TEST.
I WAS ON BIRTH CONTROL, THE
DEPO SHOT AND EVERYBODY KNOWS
YOU GO EVERY THREE MONTHS.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO THE RIGHT
DOCTOR, THEY'RE GOING TO CHECK
YOU FOR S.T.D.'S, FOR
PREGNANCY.
SO EVERY THREE MONTHS, I WAS
GETTING TESTED.
DR. OZ: LET'S GET INTO THE
LEGAL ISSUES A TINY BIT.
WHAT ARE THE NEXT STEPS FOR R.
KELLY?
YOU BROUGHT LEGAL ACTION
AGAINST HIM.
>> THERE'S A LAWSUIT PENDING ON
BEHALF OF FAITH, AGAINST MR.
KELLY.
HE'S GOING TO HAVE TO ANSWER
IT.
IF HE DOESN'T ANSWER IT, THEN
IT'S POSSIBLE TO TAKE HIS
DEFAULT.
ASSUMING HE'S PROPERLY SERVED.
AND I THINK HE SHOULD ANSWER
IT.
AND LET HIM PUT FORTH ALL OF
HIS DEFENSES IF HE HAS ANY, WE
HAVE YET TO SEE THEM.
DR. OZ: SO IN THE MEANTIME,
YOU'VE BEEN GETTING OTHER NOTES
FROM HIM, AND THIS IS A LETTER
THAT YOU SAID THAT YOU RECEIVED
FROM R. KELLY'S LEGAL TEAM
THREATENING RETALIATION AGAINST
FAITH.
AND I GATHER YOU HAVE SEEN THIS
NOTE?
>> RIGHT.
DR. OZ: MAY I READ IT TO THE
AUDIENCE?
>> YES.
DR. OZ: IT SAYS IN PART PLEASE
ADVISE MS. RODGERS, FAITH, YOUR
CLIENT TO ABANDON THIS
HEARTLESS EFFORT TO TRY TO
DESTROY MY MUSICAL LEGACY FOR
SELFISH ENRICHMENT.
IF SHE PERSISTS IN COURT SHE
WILL BE SUBJECT TO PUBLIC
OPINION DURING THE DISCOVERY
PROCESS.
IF MS. RODGERS CARES ABOUT HER
OWN REPUTATION SHE SHOULD CEASE
HER PARTICIPATION AND
ORGANIZATION WITH THE
ORGANIZERS OF THIS NEGATIVE
CAMPAIGN.
FAITH, WHAT'S IT LIKE SEEING
THOSE WORDS NOW?
WHAT'S IT LIKE READING THAT THE
FIRST TIME?
>> THE FIRST TIME IT DEFINITELY
I WAS LIKE HEART -- BUT I HAVE
TO REALIZE WHO I'M DEALING
WITH.
SO NOW RARINGD IT NOW --
READING IT NOW IT'S COMICAL TO
ME.
DR. OZ: COMICAL?
>> COMICAL BECAUSE IT'S A JOKE.
IT'S A LIE.
I DON'T NEED PERSONAL
ENRICHMENT.
I COME FROM A FAMILY OF HARD
WORKING PARENTS WHO HAVE BEEN
NOTHING BUT PROVIDED FOR ME.
SO TO SAY I'M DOING THIS FOR MY
OWN PERSONAL GAIN, LIKE LET'S
BE CLEAR, WHEN HE WAS SEEING
ME, HE WOULD ASK ME WHO'S
BUYING THAT?
SO I NEVER NEEDED YOU FOR
ANYTHING.
>> I READ NEWS REPORTS THAT HE
DENIED HE SENT THAT LETTER.
BUT ANYWAY, IT WAS SENT AFTER
THE LAWSUIT WAS FILED.
BUT THE POINT IS THIS.
WE DO FEEL THAT THERE HAS BEEN
RETALIATION.
AND ATTEMPTS TO INTIMIDATE
FAITH FROM PROCEEDING.
AND SHE'S NOT GOING TO BE
INTIMIDATED.
SHE IS -- SPEAKING THE TRUTH IN
THIS CASE, THE POWER OF MR.
KELLY AND SHE HAS STRONG
SUPPORT FOR HER PARENTS, STRONG
SUPPORT FROM HER LAWYERS.
AND WE'RE GOING FORWARD.
AND THE FACT THAT HE'S A
CELEBRITY DOESN'T MEAN THAT HE
IS ABOVE THE LAW.
IT DOESN'T MEAN THAT HE HAS A
LICENSE TO GO AND HURT PEOPLE.
ANY MORE THAN ANYONE ELSE DOES.
SO THAT'S WHY SHE IS
PROCEEDING.
AND YOU CAN SEE DR. OZ HOW
PAINFUL IT IS FOR HER, YOU
KNOW, TO HAVE TO EVEN TALK
ABOUT THIS.
BUT SHE IS ONE COURAGEOUS YOUNG
WOMAN.
AND I APPLAUD HER FOR IT.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: UP NEXT, CAN MORE WOMEN
BE AT RISK AND WHAT CAN PARENTS
DO TO PREBT THEIR DAUGHTERS?
A PLEA YOU HAVE TO HEAR.
THAT IS NEXT.
[APPLAUSE]
When you feed yourself
some oats,
the oats feed your body fiber.
Fiber helps keep things
moving through your system.
Which is great.
Because when you're good
to your system,
it'll be good to you.
Ok I'll admit.
I didn't keep my place
as clean as I would like
'cuz I'm way too busy.
Who's got the time to chase
around down dirt, dust and hair?
So now,
I use Heavy Duty Swiffer
Sweeper and Dusters.
For hard-to-reach places,
Duster makes it easy to clean.
It captures dust in one swipe.
Ha! Gotcha!
And (New) Sweeper
Heavy Duty cloths
lock away a twice as
much dirt and dust.
It gets stuff deep in the
grooves other tools can miss.
You know what?
My place is a lot cleaner now.
Stop cleaning.
Start Swiffering.
♪♪
Heartburn and gas?
Fight both fast
TUMS Chewy Bites
with gas relief
All in one relief
of heartburn and gas
♪♪
♪ TUM TUM TUM TUMS ♪
TUMS Chewy Bites
with gas relief
Okay, Max...time
to help Mrs. Tyler
reach her health goals!
I'm in! But first...
Shelfie!
The great-tasting
nutrition of Ensure.
With up to 30
grams of protein
and 26 vitamins
and minerals!
Ensure.
For Strength and Energy.
My mom washes the dishes...
...before she puts them in the
dishwasher.
So what does the dishwasher do?
Cascade Platinum does the work
for you,
prewashing and removing
stuck-on foods,
the first time.
Wow, that's clean!
Cascade Platinum.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE'RE BACK IN A DAYTIME
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW WITH FAITH
RODGERS WHO CLAIMS R. KELLY
INTENTIONALLY INFECTED HER WITH
HERPES.
WOMEN'S RIGHTS ATTORNEY GLORIA
ALLRED IS BACK WITH US.
AND I'M PLEASED TO INTRODUCE
FAITH'S MOTHER, KELLY, AND HER
DAD, CHARLES.
[APPLAUSE]
YOUR DAUGHTER REFLECTED VERY
WELL ON BOTH OF YOU.
AND SHE'S SPOKE ABOUT THE
VALUES THAT YOU TAUGHT HER.
SO I'M SURE THIS WAS DIFFICULT
FOR ANY PARENT TO HEAR.
BUT IN PARTICULAR FOR YOU,
BECAUSE YOU TRIED TO TELL HER
TO GO IN DIFFERENT ROADS THAN
YOU THOUGHT SHE WAS ON.
KELLY, HOW HAS IT BEEN FOR YOU
HOPING WITH THE NEWS FROM WHAT
YOU'VE BEEN HEARING?
>> I HAVE JUST REALLY BEEN
TRYING TO STAY VERY PRAYERFUL.
IT'S VERY DIFFICULT WHEN YOU
WATCH YOUR DAUGHTER ON A DAILY
BASIS BEING DISCUSSED IN A
NEGATIVE MANNER.
BUT WE STAND WITH HER.
IN THIS SITUATION.
AND WE'RE JUST --
[APPLAUSE]
WE'RE JUST GOING TO STAND WITH
HER AND SUPPORT HER AND GUIDE
HER THROUGH THIS.
DR. OZ: WHY DON'T YOU -- WHAT
DID YOU TELL HER WHEN SHE FIRST
OPENED UP TO YOU ABOUT WHAT HAD
HAPPENED?
>> I LET HER KNOW THAT I LOVED
HER.
THAT WAS THE FIRST THING.
AND THAT SHE DIDN'T HAVE TO BE
ASHAMED, THAT WE'VE ALL MADE
SOME MISTAKES AND THAT WE WOULD
GET THROUGH THIS.
AND THAT WE LOVED HER NO MATTER
WHAT.
IT WASN'T GOING TO CHANGE.
IT DOESN'T CHANGE TODAY.
IT HASN'T CHANGED.
DR. OZ: DO YOU FEEL THAT LOVE?
>> I DO.
DR. OZ: THAT'S IMPORTANT.
SO DAD, WHAT DO YOU WANT TO SAY
TO R. KELLY?
WHAT DO YOU WANT HIM TO HEAR?
>> WHAT I WANT TO SAY TO HIM IS
PROBABLY BE RESPONSIBLE.
BE ACCOUNTABLE.
ACKNOWLEDGE THAT HIS BEHAVIOR
IS NOT NORMAL.
AND THAT HE HAS DAMAGED SOME
WOMEN.
STOP USING YOUR CELEBRITY AS
BAIT.
YOU KNOW, HE HAS TO ANSWER TO
GOD, YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE HE HAS THE FINAL SAY IN
EVERYTHING, YOU KNOW?
AND I THINK HE --
[APPLAUSE]
AND I WOULD SAY, YOU KNOW, THE
GOD THAT LOVES US ALL LOVES
HIM.
YOU KNOW, WE ALL HAVE SINNED.
WE ALL HAVE FAILED IN DIFFERENT
TIMES IN OUR LIFE.
AND SO THAT PART OF ME IS --
HAS SOME EMPATHY FOR HIM, SOME
SYMPATHY FOR HIM.
HOWEVER, THERE'S ANOTHER PART
OF ME THAT IS -- YOU KNOW, THE
DAD PART OF ME, THE MAN PART OF
ME IS ANGRY.
AT TIMES I HAVE DIFFERENT
THOUGHTS.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: UNCHRISTIAN THOUGHTS.
>> RIGHT.
UNCHRISTIAN THOUGHTS.
>> I DO.
BUT I KNOW THAT THE GOD PART OF
ME, YOU KNOW, BRINGS ME BACK
INTO CHARACTER.
>> AND THAT'S BECAUSE CHARLES
IS A PASTOR.
AND SO I THINK HE'S GOT THE
PAST I DON'T RECALL -- THE
PASTORAL APPROACH.
SOMETIMES CONFLICTING WITH THE
DAD APPROACH.
MY MESSAGE IS YES, MR. KELLY,
YOU SHOULD BE ACCOUNTABLE TO
GOD.
BUT IN ADDITION, YOU NEED TO BE
ACCOUNTABLE IN THE JUSTICE
SYSTEM BECAUSE WE NEED JUSTICE
FOR FAITH.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: FAITH, WHAT DO YOU WANT
TO SAY TO R. KELLY IF HE
WATCHES THIS?
AND A PRETTY GOOD CHANCE HE
WILL.
>> I WOULD TELL HIM I FORGIVE
YOU.
I ALREADY FORGAVE YOU A LONG
TIME AGO.
I NEED YOU TO STOP WHAT YOU'RE
DOING.
I NEED YOU TO JUST FREE
YOURSELF AND FREE THESE YOUNG
LADIES.
THEY MAY NOT BE -- THEY MAY NOT
-- EXCUSE ME.
THEY MAY NOT BE KIDNAPPED.
THEY MAY NOT BE HELD AGAINST
THEIR WILL.
BUT THEY'RE IN A TOXIC
SITUATION THAT THEY CAN'T EVEN
SEE WHAT'S GOING ON IN THE
OUTSIDE WORLD.
AND THAT'S SCARY.
AND TO KNOW THAT AT THIS POINT,
I'VE SEEN IT AFFECT ME AND I'VE
SEEN IT AFFECT MY PARENTS.
SO IT'S -- IT'S A AFFECTING
EVERYBODY.
NOW YOU NEED TO BE AFFECTED.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE REACHED OUT TO R.
KELLY'S LEGAL TEAM ASKING ABOUT
THE ALLEGATIONS THAT HE
KNOWINGLY INFLICTED WOMEN WITH
AN S.T.D.
AND WE DID NOT GET A RESPONSE
IN TIME FOR THIS TAPING.
WE ARE STAYING ON TOP OF THIS
STORY.
AND AS DEVELOPMENTS UNFOLD WE
WILL UPDATE OUR VIEWER IF WE
HEAR CONFLICTING FROM R.
KELLY'S TEAM.
I WANT TO THANK YOU ALL VERY
MUCH.
I KNOW HOW HARD THIS WAS.
MOM AND DAD FOR COMING ON, FOR
SUPPORTING THESE WONDERFUL
WOMEN AND YOU BEING BRAVE AND
GLORIA AS WELL FOR BEING IN
CHARGE.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
New Tide PODS 2.0
with upgraded 4-in-1 technology.
Your detergent,
Stain removers,
And odor fighters
All fit, in the palm of your
hand.
#1 stain and odor fighter, #1
trusted.
It's got to be Tide.
♪ Before I head
out the door ♪
♪ It's what I'm lookin' for ♪
♪ Today's the Daisy I do ♪
♪ Daisy it's true ♪
♪ Before I get on the move ♪
♪ I grab my special food ♪
♪ Today's the Daisy I see ♪
♪ the difference in me ♪
♪ Today's the Daisy for cottage
cheese (cottage cheese) ♪
♪ Today's the Daisy! ♪
(Cat 1) Friskies World...
(Cat 2) Smell that?
(Cat 1) Gravy!
(Cat 2) That's not gravy, that's
extra gravy.
(Cat 1) Whoa!
(Cat 2) That's Friskies
Extra Gravy! Paté and Chunky!
(Cat 1) Gravy purr-adise.
(Cat 2) Purr-adise? Really?
(VO) Feed Their Fantasy.
Friskies.
♪
Oats have a soluble fiber
called beta-glucan,
which can help lower cholesterol
when part of a
heart-healthy diet.
What's more, these oats
have no artificial flavors,
preservatives or added colors.
Now that's something
to celebrate.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WHO KILLED JONBENET
RAMSEY?
THAT HAS BEEN A MYSTERY FOR THE
LAST 22 YEARS.
OUR NEXT SHOW AN EXCLUSIVE
INTERVIEW WITH A MAN WHO SAYS
HE KNOWS WHO DID IT.
BUT CAN WE BELIEVE HIM?
JONBENET RAMSEY.
THE 6-YEAR-OLD BEAUTY QUEEN
FOREVER ETCHED INTO OUR MIND AS
THE HAUNTING FACE OF THE
COUNTRY'S MOST BAFFLING MURDER
MYSTERY.
TODAY, MORE THAN TWO DECADES
LATER, JONBENET'S MURDER
REMAINS UNSOLVED DESPITE
EXTENSIVE INVESTIGATIONS AND
THEORIES THAT HAVE FOCUSED ON A
VARIETY OF SUSPECTS.
SOMEONE INSIDE THE HOUSE,
INTRUDERS, EVEN INTERNATIONAL
PEDOPHILES.
BUT ALL LEADS HAVE LED NOWHERE.
NOW NEW ALLEGATIONS CLAIM HER
KILLER HAS CONFESSED.
AND IS ALREADY BEHIND BARS.
ON THE NEXT TRUE CRIME AN
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW AND
SHOCKING PRISON CONFESSION.
PLUS NANCY GRACE IS HERE ALONG
WITH ONE OF THE ORIGINAL
INVESTIGATORS IN THE CASE.
WILL THERE BE JUSTICE FOR
JONBENET?
I'LL SEE YOU NEXT TIME.
[APPLAUSE]
>>> COMING UP RIGHT NOW ON "PAGE
SIX TV" -- THE LATEST ON
SMOLLETT'S ATTACKERS.
CHICAGO PD IS STILL
INVESTIGATING.
WE'LL TELL YOU WHAT WE KNOW.
>>> AND ARE CARDI