What would she do without me?
Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> James: I MEAN, DON'T GET ME
WRONG, BILLY.
I LOVE HOSTING A TALK SHOW, IT'S
JUST THAT IT CAN BE TOUGH
BECAUSE SOME GUESTS THINK
THEY'RE WAY MORE INTERESTING AND
FUNNY THAN THEY ACTUALLY ARE.
>> YEAH, WELL, LUCKY FOR YOU,
JAMES, TALK SHOW HOSTS LOVE
HAVING ME AS A GUEST.
>> James: HOW DO YOU KNOW?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN "HOW DO I
KNOW?"
I KNOW.
>> James: BECAUSE THEY...
>> YES.
BECAUSE THEY...
>> James: HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT
THEY'RE REALLY...
>> WHAT ARE YOU SAYING, THAT
THEY FAKE ENTHUSIASM?
>> GET OUT OF HERE.
>> JAMES: WHY?
MOST TALK SHOW HOSTS AT ONE TIME
OR ANOTHER HAVE FAKED IT.
>> WELL, THEY HAVEN'T FAKED IT
WITH ME.
>> JAMES: HOW DO YOU KNOW?
>> BECAUSE I KNOW.
>> JAMES: OH, RIGHT.
I FORGOT.
YOU'RE IN ICONIC MOVIES.
>> WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED TO
MEAN?
>> James: I'M JUST SAYING MOST
ACTORS FROM BELOVED FILMS ARE
SURE IT NEVER HAPPENED TO THEM
AND MOST TALK SHOWS AT ONE TIME
OR ANOTHER HAVE DONE IT SO YOU
DO THE MATH.
>> YOU DON'T THINK THAT I COULD
TELL THE DIFFERENCE?
>> JAMES: NO.
>> GET OUT OF HERE.
( LAUGHTER )
>> JAMES: HA, HA, HA.
YES.
OH, YES.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
( LAUGHING AND MOANING )
>> James: THAT'S WHY YOU HOST
THE OSCARS NINE TIMES!
THAT'S WHY YOU DID IT NINE
TIMES!
( LAUGHTER )
IT'S INCREDIBLE!
I LOVE THE MOVIE.
I LOVE THE MOVIE AND YOU ARE
GREAT IN IT!
WE'VE GOT TO GO TO BREAK!
IT'S ALWAYS A HOOT!
I'VE GOT TO STOP!
STOP!
( LAUGHTER )
BILLY CRYSTAL, EVERYBODY!
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK!
( APPLAUSE )
>> YEAH, I'LL HAVE WHAT HE'S
HAVING.
( APPLAUSE )
♪ ARE YOU READY Y'ALL
TO HAVE SOME FUN
♪ FEEL THE LOVE TONIGHT
DON'T YOU WORRY 'BOUT
♪ WHERE IT IS YOU COME FROM
IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT
♪ IT'S THE LATE, LATE SHOW ♪
>> Announcer: LAIDGED, ALL THE
THE -- LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
GIVE IT UP FOR YOUR HOST, THE
ONE, THE ONLY JAMES CORDEN!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
( THEME SONG PLAYING )
>> JAMES: GOOD EVENING LADIES
AND GENTLEMEN, WELCOME TO THE
SHOW.
HOPE YOU HAD A GOOD DAY.
WE'VE GOT A FUN ONE PLANNED FOR
YOU.
LET'S GET RIGHT INTO THE NEWS.
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
OF COURSE, TONIGHT WAS PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S BIG STATE OF THE UNION
ADDRESS.
IF YOU MISSED THE SPEECH, IT WAS
AN HOUR OF REPUBLICANS DOING
THIS --
AND DEMOCRATS DOING THIS --
AND ME DOING THIS --
"IS THERE NOTHING ELSE ON?
EVERY SINGLE CHANNEL?!"
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
EVERY CHANNEL!
IN TRUMP'S SPEECH, HE CALLED FOR
UNITY.
AND AS A LITTLE WARM-UP FOR ALL
THIS "UNITY," JUST THIS MORNING,
THE PRESIDENT TOOK TO TWITTER TO
ATTACK DEMOCRATIC SENATOR CHUCK
SCHUMER, WRITING, "I SEE SCHUMER
IS ALREADY CRITICIZING MY STATE
OF THE UNION SPEECH, EVEN THOUGH
HE HASN'T SEEN IT YET.
HE'S JUST UPSET THAT HE DIDN'T
WIN THE SENATE."
( LAUGHTER )
TRUMP SAID SCHUMER CRITICIZED
THE SPEECH WITHOUT SEEING IT.
BUT TO BE FAIR, AS OF THIS
MORNING, I DON'T THINK TRUMP HAD
EVEN WRITTEN IT.
( LAUGHTER )
( APPLAUSE )
THE PRESIDENT HATE-TWEETED A
DEMOCRAT AND THEN GAVE A SPEECH
CALLING FOR UNITY.
( LAUGHTER )
YOU KNOW, IT'S LIKE SLAMMING
THAT LAST CHEESEBURGER RIGHT
BEFORE STARTING YOUR DIET.
( LAUGHTER )
I'M LIKE --
"OKAY, IT STARTS NOW."
( LAUGHTER )
OH, FRIES!
TRUMP WAS SUPPOSED TO GIVE HIS
( LAUGHTER )
STATE OF THE UNION SPEECH LAST
TRUMP WAS SUPPOSED TO GIVE HIS
WEEK, BUT, BECAUSE OF THE
STATE OF THE UNION SPEECH LAST
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN, IT WAS
WEEK, BUT, BECAUSE OF THE
RESCHEDULED FOR TONIGHT.
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN, IT WAS
SO TRUMP ENDED UP GIVING AN
RESCHEDULED FOR TONIGHT.
HOUR-LONG TELEVISED SPEECH ON
SO TRUMP ENDED UP GIVING AN
CHINESE NEW YEAR.
HOUR-LONG TELEVISED SPEECH ON
WHAT A PERFECT WAY TO KICK OFF
CHINESE NEW YEAR.
THE YEAR OF THE PIG!
WHAT A PERFECT WAY TO KICK OFF
( LAUGHTER )
THE YEAR OF THE PIG!
( APPLAUSE )
( LAUGHTER )
IT IS TRUE.
( APPLAUSE )
FOR THE MOST PART, DONALD TRUMP
IT IS TRUE.
STUCK TO THE PREPARED SPEECH
FOR THE MOST PART, DONALD TRUMP
TONIGHT.
STUCK TO THE PREPARED SPEECH
WHICH IS A GOOD THING, BECAUSE
TONIGHT.
NO ONE WANTS TO SEE TRUMP GO
WHICH IS A GOOD THING, BECAUSE
FULL ADAM LEVINE.
NO ONE WANTS TO SEE TRUMP GO
( LAUGHTER )
FULL ADAM LEVINE.
IN OTHER TRUMP NEWS, THIS
( LAUGHTER )
MORNING THE PRESIDENT TOOK TO
IN OTHER TRUMP NEWS, THIS
TWITTER TO ONCE AGAIN MAKE A
MORNING THE PRESIDENT TOOK TO
PUSH FOR HIS BORDER WALL, AND,
TWITTER TO ONCE AGAIN MAKE A
APPARENTLY, IF HE DOESN'T GET
PUSH FOR HIS BORDER WALL, AND,
THE FUNDING HE NEEDS, HE HAS A
APPARENTLY, IF HE DOESN'T GET
PLAN B --
THE FUNDING HE NEEDS, HE HAS A
BECAUSE HE TWEETED, "WE WILL
PLAN B --
BUILD A HUMAN WALL IF
BECAUSE HE TWEETED, "WE WILL
NECESSARY."
BUILD A HUMAN WALL IF
( LAUGHTER )
NECESSARY."
A HUMAN WALL.
( LAUGHTER )
AND YOU THOUGHT GETTING CALLED
A HUMAN WALL.
FOR JURY DUTY WAS BAD.
AND YOU THOUGHT GETTING CALLED
( LAUGHTER )
FOR JURY DUTY WAS BAD.
WHAT?!
( LAUGHTER )
SO, LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
WHAT?!
IN ONE TWEET, TRUMP JUST
SO, LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
DOWNGRADED HIS CEMENT WALL TO A
IN ONE TWEET, TRUMP JUST
HUMAN WALL.
DOWNGRADED HIS CEMENT WALL TO A
IF HE KEEPS GOING AT THIS RATE,
HUMAN WALL.
NEXT WEEK IT WILL BE AN AIR
IF HE KEEPS GOING AT THIS RATE,
WALL.
NEXT WEEK IT WILL BE AN AIR
( LAUGHTER )
WALL.
"IT'S GONNA BE AN AIR WALL!
( LAUGHTER )
A BIG, BEAUTIFUL WALL MADE OF
"IT'S GONNA BE AN AIR WALL!
AIR!"
A BIG, BEAUTIFUL WALL MADE OF
( LAUGHTER )
AIR!"
MOVING ON
( LAUGHTER )
BUDGET FURNITURE STORE IKEA JUST
MOVING ON
ANNOUNCED A NEW WAY FOR YOU TO
BUDGET FURNITURE STORE IKEA JUST
FILL YOUR APARTMENT WITH THEIR
ANNOUNCED A NEW WAY FOR YOU TO
ITEMS.
FILL YOUR APARTMENT WITH THEIR
SOON YOU'LL BE ABLE TO RENT IKEA
ITEMS.
FURNITURE AND RETURN IT WHEN
SOON YOU'LL BE ABLE TO RENT IKEA
YOU'RE DONE WITH IT.
FURNITURE AND RETURN IT WHEN
YEAH.
YOU'RE DONE WITH IT.
THE ONLY PROBLEM WITH THIS, BY
YEAH.
THE TIME YOU FIGURE OUT HOW
THE ONLY PROBLEM WITH THIS, BY
TO PUT THE FURNITURE TOGETHER,
THE TIME YOU FIGURE OUT HOW
YOUR RENTAL'S UP AND YOU'LL HAVE
TO PUT THE FURNITURE TOGETHER,
TO TAKE IT BACK.
YOUR RENTAL'S UP AND YOU'LL HAVE
( LAUGHTER )
TO TAKE IT BACK.
( APPLAUSE )
( LAUGHTER )
BUT IKEA RENTAL FURNITURE SOUNDS
( APPLAUSE )
GREAT.
BUT IKEA RENTAL FURNITURE SOUNDS
WHEN YOU GET TIRED OF YOUR
GREAT.
SKULSFJORD, YOU CAN SWAP IT OUT
WHEN YOU GET TIRED OF YOUR
FOR A GODFJORD.
SKULSFJORD, YOU CAN SWAP IT OUT
IT'S LIKE A TAFJORD SMORGASBORD!
FOR A GODFJORD.
AND WE THOUGHT THIS WAS
IT'S LIKE A TAFJORD SMORGASBORD!
INTERESTING --
AND WE THOUGHT THIS WAS
ACCORDING TO A RESEARCH STUDY
INTERESTING --
THAT CAME OUT TODAY, SINGLE MEN
ACCORDING TO A RESEARCH STUDY
TEND TO HAVE STRONGER BODY ODOR
THAT CAME OUT TODAY, SINGLE MEN
THAN MEN IN RELATIONSHIPS
TEND TO HAVE STRONGER BODY ODOR
( LAUGHTER )
THAN MEN IN RELATIONSHIPS
ALL RIGHT?
( LAUGHTER )
RESEARCHERS BELIEVE THIS IS
ALL RIGHT?
BECAUSE SINGLE MEN HAVE HIGHER
RESEARCHERS BELIEVE THIS IS
LEVELS OF TESTOSTERONE.
BECAUSE SINGLE MEN HAVE HIGHER
ONLY A GROUP OF SCIENTISTS WOULD
LEVELS OF TESTOSTERONE.
BE, LIKE, "THIS IS FASCINATING!
ONLY A GROUP OF SCIENTISTS WOULD
( LAUGHTER )
BE, LIKE, "THIS IS FASCINATING!
WE'RE NOT SURE WHY, BUT THE
( LAUGHTER )
SMELLY GUYS SEEM TO BE THE ONES
WE'RE NOT SURE WHY, BUT THE
WHO DON'T HAVE GIRLFRIENDS!"
SMELLY GUYS SEEM TO BE THE ONES
( LAUGHTER )
WHO DON'T HAVE GIRLFRIENDS!"
( APPLAUSE )
( LAUGHTER )
THIS IS TRUE.
( APPLAUSE )
RESEARCHERS RECRUITED MEN TO
THIS IS TRUE.
WORK UP A SWEAT AND THEN HAD
RESEARCHERS RECRUITED MEN TO
WOMEN SNIFF THEIR ARMPITS.
WORK UP A SWEAT AND THEN HAD
SO, YES, THERE IS SOMETHING
WOMEN SNIFF THEIR ARMPITS.
WORSE THAN WATCHING TRUMP GIVE A
SO, YES, THERE IS SOMETHING
STATE OF THE UNION SPEECH.
WORSE THAN WATCHING TRUMP GIVE A
( LAUGHTER )
STATE OF THE UNION SPEECH.
AND FINALLY, WE HAD TO TELL YOU
( LAUGHTER )
ABOUT THIS.
AND FINALLY, WE HAD TO TELL YOU
SUPERMODEL TYRA BANKS HAS
ABOUT THIS.
ANNOUNCED THE OPENING OF A
SUPERMODEL TYRA BANKS HAS
MODELING-THEMED AMUSEMENT PARK
ANNOUNCED THE OPENING OF A
CALLED MODEL-LAND.
MODELING-THEMED AMUSEMENT PARK
YEAH.
CALLED MODEL-LAND.
ETH COMPLETELY REAL.
YEAH.
LIKE ANY AMUSEMENT PARK, PEOPLE
ETH COMPLETELY REAL.
ARE VOMITING ALL OVER THE PLACE,
LIKE ANY AMUSEMENT PARK, PEOPLE
EXCEPT HERE THERE ARE NO RIDES.
ARE VOMITING ALL OVER THE PLACE,
( LAUGHTER )
EXCEPT HERE THERE ARE NO RIDES.
THE PARK AIMS TO LET VISITORS,
( LAUGHTER )
"BE THE DREAM VERSION OF
THE PARK AIMS TO LET VISITORS,
THEMSELVES."
"BE THE DREAM VERSION OF
A PLACE WHERE ANY RANDOM PERSON
THEMSELVES."
CAN PRETEND THEY'RE A MODEL?
A PLACE WHERE ANY RANDOM PERSON
I THOUGHT THAT WAS CALLED
CAN PRETEND THEY'RE A MODEL?
INSTAGRAM.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS CALLED
( LAUGHTER )
INSTAGRAM.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
( LAUGHTER )
THE MODELING-THEMED PARK WILL
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
EVEN HAVE CONCESSIONS, THEY'VE
THE MODELING-THEMED PARK WILL
GOT THIS FUNNEL CAKE.
EVEN HAVE CONCESSIONS, THEY'VE
AND THIS HOT DOG.
GOT THIS FUNNEL CAKE.
( LAUGHTER )
AND THIS HOT DOG.
AND YOU CAN EVEN GET THIS COMBO
( LAUGHTER )
MEAL.
AND YOU CAN EVEN GET THIS COMBO
( LAUGHTER )
MEAL.
SHALL WE SEE WHO OUR GUESTS
( LAUGHTER )
ARE ON THE SHOW TONIGHT?
SHALL WE SEE WHO OUR GUESTS
IN THE BLUE ROOM, HE'S A TONY
ARE ON THE SHOW TONIGHT?
AND EMMY WINNING ACTOR, WRITER
IN THE BLUE ROOM, HE'S A TONY
HOST, AND COMEDY LEGEND.
AND EMMY WINNING ACTOR, WRITER
WE'RE SO THRILLED EVERY TIME
HOST, AND COMEDY LEGEND.
HE'S ON OUR SHOW.
WE'RE SO THRILLED EVERY TIME
THE ONE AND ONLY, BILLY CRYSTAL!
HE'S ON OUR SHOW.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
THE ONE AND ONLY, BILLY CRYSTAL!
BILLY!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> JAMES.
BILLY!
JAMES.
>> JAMES.
SO SORRY, MR. CRYSTAL HAS BEEN,
JAMES.
SHALL WE SAY, DETAINED.
SO SORRY, MR. CRYSTAL HAS BEEN,
>> James: WOW, AND HE SENT
SHALL WE SAY, DETAINED.
VLADIMIR PUTIN IN HIS PLACE!
>> James: WOW, AND HE SENT
>> I LOVE SPEECH TONIGHT BATTLE!
VLADIMIR PUTIN IN HIS PLACE!
YOU AND ME AGAINST THE WORLD,
>> I LOVE SPEECH TONIGHT BATTLE!
BABY!
YOU AND ME AGAINST THE WORLD,
LET'S WIN IT 2020.
BABY!
I'LL GET RID OF THE PEE TAPE, I
LET'S WIN IT 2020.
PROMISE YOU!
I'LL GET RID OF THE PEE TAPE, I
>> James: VLADIMIR PUTIN AND
PROMISE YOU!
HOPEFULLY BILLY CRYSTAL!
>> James: VLADIMIR PUTIN AND
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
HOPEFULLY BILLY CRYSTAL!
IN THE ORANGE ROOM, A TALENTED
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
ACTRESS YOU KNOW FROM, "SCRUBS,"
IN THE ORANGE ROOM, A TALENTED
"ROSEANNE" AND "SPEECHLESS."
ACTRESS YOU KNOW FROM, "SCRUBS,"
THE DAZZLING, THE CHARMING,
"ROSEANNE" AND "SPEECHLESS."
SARAH CHALKE!
THE DAZZLING, THE CHARMING,
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
SARAH CHALKE!
HEY, SARAH, HOW ARE YOU?
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> HI.
>> James: THANK YOU FOR BEING
HERE.
HOW'S EVERYTHING.
ARE YOU GOOD?
>> I COULD USE SOME MORE -- I'M
OUT OF WATER HERE.
IT'S A MESS.
>> James: REALLY?
YOU SEEM LIKE SOMEONE WHO WOULD
BE NEAT AND TIDY.
>> NO, THIS IS ALL JUST PRETEND.
>> James: WELL, WE'RE SO
THRILLED THE PRETEND YOU IS
HERE, ALSO.
SARAH CHALKE, EVERYBODY!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
IN THE RED ROOM, HE'S A
BRILLIANT HIP-HOP ARTIST HAILING
FROM RIGHT HERE IN LOS ANGELES.
THE DELUXE VERSION OF HIS DEBUT
STUDIO ALBUM "HARLAN AND
ALONDRA" IS OUT FRIDAY.
HI IS SO INCREDIBLE.
WE'RE SO EXCITED HE'S HERE.
THE ELECTRIC, THE SPECTACULAR
BUDDY AND ASAP FERG!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
HEY, BUDDY, HOW ARE YOU?
ALL GOOD?
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> James: VERY, VERY WELL.
YOU GOOD?
>> YEAH.
>> James: A$AP FERG,
EVERYBODY!
HOW WE DOING, EVERYBODY OKAY?
>> YOU KNOW HOW THE COOKIE
CRUMBLES!
>> James: HOW DOES THE COOKIE
CRUMBLE, BUDDY?
I WANT TO KNOW.
>> I COULD SHOW YOU, BUT --
( UNINTELLIGIBLE )
>> James: HOW DOES THE COOKIE
CRUMBLE?
>> HOW THE COOKIE TASTES.
HOW THE COOKIE TASTES?
REGGIE, ARE YOU READY?
HE'S REGGIE WATTS, I'M JAMES
CORDEN AND THIS, THIS IS THE
"LATE LATE SHOW."
ROLL THE TITLES!
Captioning sponsored by CBS
♪ THE LATE, LATE SHOW, OH, OH
THE LATE, LATE SHOW, OOH
THE LATE, LATE SHOW
♪ THE LATE, LATE SHOW, OH, OH
♪ OH, OH
THE LATE, LATE SHOW
IT'S THE LATE, LATE SHOW ♪
>> James: IT CERTAINLY IS!
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
WE'VE GOT A LOT OF GREAT SHOWS
COMING UP.
IF YOU'D LIKE TO COME SEE ONE IN
PERSON, YOU CAN HEAD TO
1IOTA.COM AND CLICK ON THE LINK
THAT SAYS, "THE LATE LATE SHOW."
YOU CAN ALSO CHECK OUT PAST
EPISODES AND ALL OF OUR "CARPOOL
KARAOKE" VIDEOS ON OUR YOUTUBE
PAGE.
AND PLEASE DON'T FORGET TO
FOLLOW ME ON TWITTER AT "LATE
LATE SHOW."
YOU CAN ALSO HEART ME ON
INSTAGRAM, LINK ME ON LINKEDIN
PIN ME ON PINTEREST, SNAP ME ON
SNAPCHAT, MESSAGE ME ON SKYPE
WESLEY ME ON SNIPE, SEND ME A
MESSAGE ON WHATSAPP, SEND ME A
SQUIRREL ON NUTSAPP, LOOK UP MY
FAVORITE SONGS ON GENIUS, LOOK
UP MY FAVORITE DONGS ON PENIUS,
SHOUT ME OUT ON CAMEO, GLAZE ME
OUT ON HAMEO, FIND ME A MATCH ON
BUMBLE, LET'S GET READY TO ON
RUMBLE, RIDE ME ON BIRD, CHEESE
ME ON CURD, SHAKEN ME ON
STIRRED, SHREK ME ON THE THIRD
FOLLOW ME ON TUMBLR, HUGH GRANT
ME ON BUMBLR, SAVE ME A P.D.F.
ON ADOBE, SAVE ME SOME P.D.A. ON
A-DO-ME, SAY "CALL DAD" USING
SIRI, ACCIDENTALLY CALL BRAD
USING SIRI, SAY "CALL DAD" USING
SIRI, CALL BRAD AGAIN USING
SIRI, SAY "CALL DAD! CALL DAD!
CALL DAD!" USING SIRI, CALLING
RYAN FOR SOME REASON USING SIRI.
TELL ME A STORY ON TIKTOK, BUY
ME A HORSE ON CLIPCLOP, I.D. MY
MUSIC ON SHAZAM, MAKE SHAQ MY
GENIE ON "KAZAAM," TELL ME
SHOWTIMES ON MOVIEFONE, MAKE MY
DOG LOOK SAD ON GLOOMYCONE, PAY
ME ON PAYPAL, TELL ME "I'M
WALKIN' HERE" ON HEYPAL, ORDER
ME BURGERS ON STEAK 'N SHAKE,
SMOKE ME OUT ON WAKE 'N BAKE,
PRANK MY FRIENDS ON FAKE 'N
SNAKE, THROW MY DREAM PARTY ON
CAKE 'N DRAKE, BOOK ME A FLIGHT
ON THE UNITED APP, SEE WHO'S A
SIR ON THE YOU-KNIGHTED? APP,
PRESERVE MY MEMORIES ON
SHUTTERFLY, PRESERVE MY PHARAOHS
ON MUMMIFY, OR, IF YOU WISH,
FEEL FREE TO WRITE ME AN
OLD-FASHIONED LETTER BY
ADDRESSING IT TO CBS TELEVISION
CITY, 7800 BEVERLY BOULEVARD
LOS ANGELES, CALIFORNIA 90036.
SINCE VALENTINE'S DAY IS COMING
UP, THROW IN ONE OF THOSE CHEESY
CARDS WITH A PICTURE OF A WHALE
SAYING SOMETHING LIKE, "WHALE
YOU BE MINE?"
BECAUSE, HEY, I LIKE TO
LAUGH, TOO, YOU KNOW.
NOT TO BE OUTDONE, I'LL WRITE
BACK, "OF COURSE I WHALE!
IN FACT, THAT SOUNDS
FIN-TASTIC!"
A FEW WEEKS LATER, YOU'LL WRITE
BACK, "YOU'RE SHRIMP-LY THE
BEST."
REALIZING THAT THIS IS NOW A
FULL-ON PUN BATTLE, I'LL GO TO
WRITE MY WITTY RETORT WHEN I
REALIZE-- I GOT NOTHING.
NOTHING.
I'LL SPEND SO LONG THINKING
ABOUT HOW I'M GOING TO RESPOND,
I'LL SLOWLY LET THE WHOLE SHOW
DRIFT AWAY FROM ME.
MOST OF MY TIME ON AIR WILL JUST
BE ME SITTING AT THIS DESK
STARING BLANKLY AHEAD, TRYING TO
CRACK THAT PERFECT PUN.
I'LL GET FIRED FROM CBS DUE TO
PLUMMETING RATINGS, MY WIFE WILL
LEAVE ME, MY CHILDREN WON'T EVEN
LET ME COME TO THEIR SOCCER
GAMES ANYMORE BECAUSE THEY'RE
EMBARRASSED OF THEIR, "HOMELESS
DADDY."
AND THEN, ONE DAY, WHILE I'M
FIGHTING WITH A RACCOON OVER AN
OLD SLICE OF PIZZA, IT'LL COME
TO ME, "WHALE YOU BE MINE?"
"DOLPHINATELY."
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH BILLY
CRYSTAL AND SARAH CHALKE!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
( BAND PLAYING )
♪
-Morning.
-What do we got?
-Keep an eye on that branch.
Might get windy.
Have a good shift.
Fire pit.
Last use -- 0600.
I'd stay close.
Morning.
♪
Get ready to switch.
Protected by Flo.
Should say, "Protected
by Alan and Jamie."
-Right?
-Should it?
When you bundle
home and auto...
Run, Alan!
...you get more
than just savings.
You get 'round-the-clock
protection.
...you get more
than just savings.
♪
Celebrate Valentine's Day!
with hundreds of gifts
under $199!
And, find great deals on other
gifts she'll love!
Now through Valentine's Day.
Only at KAY.
Plaque psoriasis can be
relentless.
TREMFYA® is for adults with
moderate
to severe plaque psoriasis.
With TREMFYA®, you can get
clearer.
And stay clearer.
In fact, most patients who saw
90% clearer skin at 28 weeks
stayed clearer through 48 weeks.
TREMFYA® works better than
Humira® at providing clearer
skin
and more patients were symptom
free with TREMFYA®.
TREMFYA® may lower
your ability
to fight infections and may
increase
your risk of infections.
Before treatment,
your doctor should check you for
infections and tuberculosis.
Tell your doctor if you have an
infection
or have symptoms such as:
fever, sweats, chills, muscle
aches or cough.
Before starting TREMFYA®
tell your doctor if you plan to
or have recently received a
vaccine.
Ask your doctor about TREMFYA®.
TREMFYA®. Because you deserve to
stay clearer.
Janssen wants to help you
explore cost support options.
Moderator:
This is the Chevy Equinox.
Various:
Beautiful. Wow.
Ooh, this is fancy.
Moderator:
That's the available
HD surround vision camera.
The top of your car?
Moderator:
Mm-hmm. It helps you see
dangers around the vehicle.
What is that?
Various:
Wait, wait, wait,
what is that? Oh, my...
(Mixed shouting)
Man:
These are big alligators.
Moderator:
So who's getting out first?
(Laughter)
Get 0% financing for 60 months
on most Equinox models.
Or, current GM owners
can get $3,500
total cash allowance
when financing
with GM Financial.
Find New Roads at your
local Chevy dealer.
Cheez-It snacks are
the most satisfying
when financing
with GM Financial.
combination of
crunch with-
Cheese.
With their
delicious perfection-
Cheese.
It's not all about
you Cheese.
You think I have a mouth.
I'm a wheel of cheese.
Got a point.
[yeah]
Cheez-It.
Cheesy,
crunchy satisfaction.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
( BAND PLAYING )
>> James: WELCOME BACK.
LET'S MEET OUR GUESTS TONIGHT!
SHE STARS IN "FRIENDS FROM
COLLEGE," SARAH CHALKE!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
( BAND PLAYING )
HE STARS IN "UNTOGETHER," BILLY
CRYSTAL!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
( BAND PLAYING )
>> James: THANK YOU FOR BEING
HERE!
THANK YOU FOR COMING TO SEE US!
IT'S SO GOOD THAT YOU'RE HERE.
SARAH, YOU'RE FROM VANCOUVER,
AND YOU'VE MOVED BACK TO
VANCOUVER.
YOU MOVED YOUR FAMILY BACK THERE
TWO YEARS AGO, BUT YOU STILL
COMMUTE TO WORK HERE IN L.A.
>> YEAH.
>> James: WHICH FEELS LIKE
QUITE A FULL-ON COMMUTE.
HOW IS THAT?
>> OH, THE COMMUTE IS AMAZING.
THE COMMUTE IS UNBELIEVABLE.
I JUST TRAVELED RECENTLY FOR THE
FIRST TIME WITH, YOU KNOW,
BABIES, AND WE HAVE CHILDREN
SIMILAR AGES, AND I WAS, LIKE,
WHY DO PEOPLE COMPLAIN ABOUT
FLYING?
I GOT THERE AND I SAID I'M GOING
TO GET THE FACE CHAIR MASSAGE,
TWO GIANT STARBUCKS VENTIS, I
HAD A MAGAZINE.
I WAS SO EXCITED, I WAS GOING TO
WATCH EVERY MOVIE AND TELEVISION
SHOW AND I SLEPT THE WHOLE TIME.
>> James: WHEN YOU TRAVEL ON A
PLANE WITH CHILDREN, THE SECOND
YOU DON'T HAVE TO IS LIKE A
VACATION.
IT'S AMAZING FEELING.
IT'S GREAT.
HOW OFTEN DO YOU MAKE THE TRIP?
>> A LITTLE FREQUENT LATELY.
BUT NOT WITH KIDS.
MY TWO-YEAR-OLD LOVES TO PRETEND
SHE HAS TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
SO EVERY FIVE MINUTES SHE LOVES
TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
SHE LOVES THE TININESS OF
EVERYTHING.
AND WE GET IN THERE AND SHE
SAYS, I'M JUST KIDDING.
( LAUGHTER )
IT'S REALLY FUN.
>> I DO GO TO THE BATHROOM EVERY
FIVE MINUTES.
AND I HAVE A COLLECTION OF
LITTLE SOAPS.
( LAUGHTER )
>> James: BILLY, THIS YEAR
MARKS THE 30th ANNIVERSARY OF
"WHEN HARRY MET SALLY"
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> CRAZY.
>> James: THIS IS INCREDIBLE.
IN CELEBRATION OF THIS, YOU HAVE
BEEN ASKED TO PUT YOUR HAND AND
FOOTPRINTS IN FRONT OF THE
CHINESE THEATER HERE IN
HOLLYWOOD, WHICH IS AN
INCREDIBLE HONOR.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THIS?
>> THEY NOTIFIED ME TODAY.
>> James: TODAY?
YEAH.
AND IT'S A CRAZY FEELING
BECAUSE, WHEN I WAS GROWING UP,
YOU WOULD SEE BOGART AND GABLE'S
HAND AND FOOTPRINTS AND I KEPT
THINKING OF SOMETHING MY MOTHER
SAID WHEN I MOVED OUT HERE IN
THE '70s, DON'T LET THEM WALK
ALL OVER YOU, AND NOW THEY WILL.
( LAUGHTER )
WHEN DO YOU ACTUALLY GET TO --
>> THEY'RE HAVING A 30t
30th ANNIVERSARY SCREENING OF
THE MOVIE AT THE CHINESE
THEATER.
MEG AND ROB AND I WILL BE THERE
AND THE NEXT MORNING WE'LL DO
THAT.
>> James: OH!
THERE'S A SCENE WHERE YOU'RE
RACE WALKING.
>> IT'S NOT MY FAVORITE MOMENT
IN THE MOVIE.
>> James: NO.
THOSE TIGHTS.
>> James: YEAH.
AND THEY WERE REALLY TIGHT.
>> James: YES.
AND BRUNO AND I WERE WALKING
THROUGH, AND IT WAS RAINING, AND
IT'S NOT MY FAVORITE LOOK IN THE
MOVIE.
>> James: NO.
WHY DO YOU BRING IT UP?
>> James: BECAUSE, SO YOU WERE
ON YOUR RACE WALKING TEAM IN
HIGH SCHOOL.
>> YOU DON'T COUNT IT AS A
SPORT.
IT'S AN OLYMPIC SPORT.
>> James: OKAY.
NOT A COVERED ONE.
3:00 IN THE MORNING.
>> James: I'M NOT SAYING IT'S
NOT DIFFICULT, I JUST DON'T
COUNT IT FOR A SPORT.
I THINK IT'S FOR PEOPLE WHO
COULD DON'T OTHER SPORTS BUT
WANTED TO DO SOMETHING.
( LAUGHTER )
>> IF YOUR HUNCH IS CORRECT, I
HAD TRIED OUT FOR VOLLEYBALL
TEAM, THE BASKETBALL TEAM, I
WOULD PLAY IN MY NEIGHBOR'S HOOP
IN THE POURING RAIN THINKING
THIS WOULD BE MY YEAR.
NO.
TRACK AND FIELD, DIDN'T MAKE THE
A, B, C TEAM ON RELAYS, BECAUSE
RELAYS ARE REALLY COOL.
SO I FINALLY SAID TO THE COACH,
I JUST WANT TO GET ON THAT BUS
WITH MY FRIENDS AND GO TO THE
TRACK MEET, SO TELL ME WHAT IS
THE MOST UNDERATTENDED SPORT NO
ONE IS SIGNING UP FOR THAT I
COULD JUST GET ON THE TEAM?
AND HE SAID RACE WALKING, SO I
DID IT.
>> James: YOU DID IT?
I FOUND MY NIECE.
I MADE IT TO THE STATE FINALS IN
RACE WALKING.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> WALKING IS ILLEGAL IN BEVERLY
HILLS.
>> James: ABSOLUTELY IS.
COULD YOU TEACH US THE PROPER
WAY TO RACE WALK?
>> OH, NO.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> YEAH!
>> James: WILL YOU TEACH US?
I'LL TEACH YOU.
M ON THE UBERING TEAM.
( LAUGHTER )
>> SO THE MAIN THING -- I'M
GOING TO TAKE MY SHOES OFF
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T RACE WALK WITH
HEELS ON.
>> JamON.
>> James: NO.
THE ONLY THING THAT
DIFFERENTIATES IT FROM RUNNING
IS YOU HAVE TO HAVE ONE FOOT ON
THE GROUND AT ALL TIMES
OTHERWISE IT'S RUNNING.
>> James: YES.
THE BIGGEST THING IS YOU HAVE
TO PUMP YOUR ARMS.
>> James: HOW MUCH SPACE DO WE
NEED?
>> HERE.
>> James: DOWN HERE TO THERE.
OKAY.
( APPLAUSE )
>> YOU'RE GOING TO GET YOUR ARMS
GOING BUT THE BIGGEST THING IS
YOUR HIPS.
IN ORDER TO GO THE FASTEST
POSSIBLE IN THE RACE IS YOU'RE
LOCKING YOUR HIPS FROM SIDE TO
SIDE BECAUSE THAT ALLOWS ONE
FOOT TO BE ON THE GROUND AND YOU
GO YOUR FASTEST.
>> James: CAN I SHOW YOU WHAT
I'VE GOT AND YOU TELL ME IF I'M
DOING OKAY?
>> PLEASE, PLEASE.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: IS THAT IT?
( LAUGHTER )
( APPLAUSE )
>> LET'S GO IT ALTOGETHER.
A LITTLE MINI RACE.
>> James: AND WE'RE JUST GOING
TO GO UP TO THIS LADY'S SHOES.
WATCH OUT, WE'LL SEE YOU IN
COURT.
OKAY.
READY?
>> YEAH.
>> James: REG, GIVE US A GO.
ON YOUR MARK, GET SET, GO!
( BAND PLAYING )
( CHEERING )
>> James: COMPLETELY FINE.
MY RELATIVES DO THAT WHEN
SOMEBODY YELLS BUFFET.
>> James: YES.
I JUST FEEL LIKE WHENEVER I'M
DOING IT, IT'S LIKE I HAVE BEEN
CAUGHT SHORT IN THE PARK AND I
IMMEDIATELY NEED THE REST ROOM.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
>> AND IT'S WHY IT LOOKS LIKE I
CLEARLY DIDN'T HAVE A BOYFRIEND
AT THE TIME.
>> SARAH, WHAT'S THE DISTANCE.
THREE AND THREE QUARTERS TIME
AROUND THE TRACK.
NOT EVEN FOUR TIMES.
AND THE GUYS AND THE GIRLS
AREN'T COMPETING BUT EVERYONE
JUST GET ON THERE AT THE SAME
TIME AND GET IT DONE.
>> James: SARAH CHALKE,
EVERYBODY.
ABSOLUTELY INCREDIBLE.
AMAZING.
NOW BILLY.
>> YEAH.
>> James: WE HAVE TO CALCULATE
YOU ON YOUR BRILLIANT NEW MOVIE
UNTOGETHER.
ALL YOUR FILMS, YOU PLAY A SORT
OF COOL RABBI.
>> A COOL RABBI.
>> James: TELL US WHAT THE
FILM IS ABOUT.
>> IT'S CALLED "UNTOGETHER."
IT HAS A GREAT CAST.
I PLAY A RABBI WHO BECAME A
RABBI IN THE LATE '70s, AND HE
HAS A VERY HIP CONGREGATION, AND
HE'S IN A DULL PART OF HIS
MARRIAGE, AND A YOUNG WOMAN SORT
OF TAKES A LIKING TO HIM, AND HE
HAS A CRISIS IN QUESTIONING OF
HIS FAITH, AND THAT'S LOLA KIRK,
WHO I MEET.
I THINK THE CLIP IS SHE'S A
FACIAL AND MASSAGE THERAPIST,
AND MY WIFE HAS SENT ME THERE TO
GET A FACIAL FOR THE FIRST TIME.
>> James: NOW, THIS FILM HAS A
LOWER BUDGET.
>> YEAH.
NO BUDGET.
( LAUGHTER )
NO, BUT I LOVED IT.
I DID.
IT WAS ALL ABOUT THE WORK.
WE CHANGE IN OUR CAR, BASICALLY.
WE BROUGHT OUR OWN FOOD.
SERIOUSLY.
AND IT WAS ALL ABOUT THE WORK.
IT WAS LESS THAN A MILLION
DOLLARS.
ALL HERE, ABOUT FIVE OR SIX
DIFFERENT PEOPLE ALL IN
DIFFERENT STATES OF MENTAL
DISTRESS HERE IN LOS ANGELES,
AND IT'S A LITTLE SEXY.
NOT ME.
( LAUGHTER )
JAMIE DORNIN FROM 50 SHADES OF
HANDCUFFS, HE'S THE GUY.
( LAUGHTER )
YES, IT'S A VERY INTERESTING
LITTLE MOVIE.
>> James: I THINK IT'S
CHARMING.
A CLIP FROM "UNTOGETHER" WHICH
WILL BE IN SELECT THEATERS THIS
FRIDAY.
>> SO WHAT DO YOU DO?
I'M A RABBI.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
NO.
YOU'RE JUST SAYING THAT
BECAUSE OF WHAT I JUST SAID.
YOU'RE JUST MAKING FUN OF ME
BECAUSE YOU HAVE A BEARD.
>> THAT I GREW JUST SO I COULD
TELL PEOPLE I'M A RABBI.
NO.
WHY ARE YOU SO SURPRISED?
>> I JUST DIDN'T THINK YOU WOULD
BE ABLE TO DO SOMETHING LIKE
THIS.
>> WHY?
ISN'T IT VAIN?
T FEELS VAIN, YEAH.
DO YOU FEEL LIKE AN (  BLEEP  )?
I'M SORRY.
I'M A REALLY BAD JEW.
>> James: MORE OF THESE TWO
WHEN WE COME BACK!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
( BAND PLAYING )
You know that look?
That life of the party look.
Walk it off look.
One more mile look.
Reply all look.
Own your look with fewer lines.
There's only one
BOTOX® COSMETIC.
It's the only one FDA approved
to temporarily make
frown lines,
crow's feet and forehead
lines look better.
The effects of BOTOX® COSMETIC
may spread hours to weeks
after injection,
causing serious symptoms.
Alert your doctor right away
as difficulty swallowing,
speaking, breathing,
eye problems,
or muscle weakness
may be a sign of
a life-threatening condition.
Do not receive BOTOX® COSMETIC
if you have a skin infection.
Side effects may include
allergic reactions,
injection site pain, headache,
eyebrow, eyelid drooping
and eyelid swelling.
Tell your doctor about
your medical history,
muscle or nerve conditions,
and medications
including botulinum toxins
as these may increase the risk
of serious side effects.
So, give that
just saw a puppy look
and whatever that look is.
Look like you with fewer lines.
Own your look
with the one and only
BOTOX® COSMETIC.
(Burke)
Parking Splat. And we covered
it.
Own your look
Talk to Farmers.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
(alarm goes off)
♪
Wake up Sweetie.
Doctor Dave.
See ya.
♪
Here's your order.
Hey.
Applebee's To Go.
Now That's Eatin' Good
in the Neighborhood.
Looking good!
At Booking.com, we can't
guarantee
you'll good at that
water jet thingy...
But we can guarantee the
best price on this hotel.
Or any accommodation,
from homes to yurts.
Booking.com
Booking.yeah
I had this chest cold, but my
medicine kept wearing off.
(coughs)
Ah!
I missed you!
Then I discovered Mucinex.
One pill lasts 12 hours,
and I'm good.
Mucinex releases fast
and lasts 12 hours, not 4.
Let's End This.
>> I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU IN SUCH A
LONG TIME.
>> HI, GORGEOUS.
YOU LOOK AMAZING.
>> A FULL TIME JOB WHEN YOU
REACH MY AGE.
( LAUGHTER )
I'M MERRILL MORGAN.
>> I'M SAM.
WE WERE IN CLASS TOGETHER.
>> OH, SORRY.
OF COURSE, NOW I REMEMBER.
MERRILL MORGAN.
>> ETHAN TURNER, WE WERE ALSO IN
CLASS TOGETHER.
EXCELLENT.
IT'S LIKE A LITTLE REUNION.
A BLAST.
MERRILL MORGAN.
>> NO THANK YOU.
( LAUGHTER )
( BAND PLAYING )
>> James: THAT WAS A GOOD ONE.
"FRIENDS FROM COLLEGE" SEASON
TWO IS OUT NOW ON NETFLIX.
CONGRATULATIONS ON THE SHOW.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
WHAT'S HAPPENING THIS SEASON AND
WHO DO YOU PLAY?
>> SO I WATCHED THE WHOLE SEASON
IN TWO NIGHTS WHEN I WAS NURSING
MY BABY AND I WAS SO IN LOVE
WITH IT AND I WAS INVESTED IN
THE CHARACTERS AND WHAT THEY
WERE DOING SO I WAS EXCITED TO
BE A PART OF IT.
THE PART WAS SUPER COLD AND
WASPY, AND THE ONLY PERSON SHE
REMEMBERS IS NICK AND SHE
FORGETS EVERYONE ELSE'S NAME.
EVERYONE IN HER FAMILY IS EITHER
A MERRILL OR A MORGAN.
AND WHEN THEY COME BA BACK IN TE
SECOND SEASON, ALL THE FRIENDS
FROM COLLEGE HAVEN'T SPOKEN A
YEAR AND COME BACK TOGETHER FOR
MAX AND PHYLLIS' ENGAGEMENT
PARTY AND HAVE THIS SORT OF
RECKONING OVER THE SEASON.
>> James: TALKING ABOUT
COLLEGE, YOU HAD TO LIE ABOUT
YOUR COLLEGE PLANS IN ORDER TO
GET YOUR BIG BREAK ON
"ROSEANNE."
>> YES.
>> James: HOW?
WHAT DID YOU HAVE TO DO?
>> IT WAS DOWN TO SEVEN OF US.
I WAS LIVING IN VANCOUVER AND IN
HIGH SCHOOL AND 16 YEARS OLD.
THE FIRST AUDITION WAS SEVEN OF
US IN MATCHING BECKY SHIRTS.
THE KIDS WERE MAKING OUT, THE
NEXT ROUND WAS ROSEANNE ON THE
COUCH AND THEY SAID THEY'D LET
ME KNOW IN A WEEK.
AFTER THAT, TOM ARNOLD CALLED ME
UP ON THE PHONE AND SAID SO WHAT
ARE YOUR PLANS FOR COLLEGE
BECAUSE LISA AND SAM HAD GONE TO
COLLEGE.
I KNEW EXACTLY WHY HE WAS
ASKING.
I SAID, COLLEGE, GROSS, NO THANK
YOU.
>> James: YOU DID GO TO
COLLEGE AFTER.
>> YEAH, I KNEW AT THE TIME I
WOULD LOVE TO GO BUT I COULD DO
IT AFTERWARDS.
SO I WENT TO COLLEGE AFTER AND
SIX CREDITS SHORT OF MY DEGREE.
DON'T NIL CHILDREN.
( LAUGHTER )
I WAS WORKING AT THE TIME AND I
THOUGHT I'LL JUST FINISH IT
LATER.
>> James: SURE.
AND THEN, I MEAN --
>> James: BILLY, YOU STUDIED
FILM AT N.Y.U.
>> YEAH.
>> James: ONE OF YOUR
PROFESSORS WAS THE LEGENDARY
DIRECTOR MARTIN SCORSESE.
>> YEAH.
>> James: THIS WAS BEFORE HE
WAS THE LEGENDARY DIRECTOR.
>> '68, '69 AND '70.
>> James: WHAT WAS HE LIKE
THEN?
>> INTENSE.
LIKE NOW BUT YOUNGER.
( LAUGHTER )
HE WAS MAKING HIS FIRST MOVIE.
HE WAS A GRADUATE STUDENTS AT
N.Y.U., I WAS A DIRECTING MAJOR,
NOT AN ACTING MAJOR.
HE WAS SO INTENSE AND SPOKE SO
QUICKLY, IF YOU WERE EDITING
YOUR MOVIE, I DON'T KNOW IF YOU
REMEMBER THIS, BUT WHEN IT WAS
FILM, WHEN WE ACTUALLY USED
FILM, THERE IS A MACHINE CALLED
THE MOVIE-OLA.
YOU HAD YOUR FILM ON ONE REEL
AND THE SOUND TRACK ON THE OTHER
AND YOU HAD GLOVES ON AND RUN
THE FILM AND YOU HAD BRAKES,
YOU'D RUN THE EDIT, STOP THE
BRAKES, TAKE A GREASE PENCIL AND
MAKE THE MARK AND HE WOULD TALK
SO QUICKLY, WHAT DID YOU DO IT
FOR, WHAT, WHAT, HERE'S WHAT I
THINK, USE THE WIDE CHART.
I'M NOT HOWARD HAWKS, I'M 18
YEARS OLD!
IF YOU WANT TO USE THE DOLLY, GO
DOWN TO THE SUPERMARKET AND GET
THE CART AND GET THE CAMERA AND
PUSH THE -- AND ONE TIME HE
SPOKE SO QUICKLY HE DISAPPEARED
INTO THE FUTURE!
AND CAME WACK SMOKING HOT.
OH, MY GOD!
I'M GOING TO WIN AN OSCAR!
( LAUGHTER )
BUT IT WAS A GREAT TIME.
THE CLASSMATES, WE DIDN'T KNOW
WHO WE WERE THEN, BUT IT WAS
OLIVER STONE, CHRISTOPHER GUEST,
MICHAEL MCKEON.
WE WERE IN THE THEATER PROGRAM,
AND THAT'S WHERE WE ALL MET WAS
BACK THEN.
>> YOU MENTIONED THE OSCARS
THEN.
THE OSCARS ARE COMING UP SOON.
YOU ARE THE MOST BELOVED HOST
BECAUSE YOU'VE DONE IT NINE
TIMES.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
THIS YEAR, SEEMS LIKE THEY'RE
GOING WITHOUT A HOST.
>> YEAH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THEM
GOING WITHOUT A HOST AND WAS IT
EVER MOOTED, DID ANYONE CALL
YOU?
>> NO ONE CALLED.
>> James: YEAH.
BUT THAT'S FINE.
VERY CREATIVE PRODUCERS.
I KNOW REALLY FUNNY PEOPLE WHO
WERE DOING IT.
I THINK IT CAN WORK GREAT,
THOUGH I DO LIKE THE FACT THAT,
WHEN I WAS THERE OR ELLEN OR ANY
OTHER SUCCESSFUL HOSTS, THAT
YOU'RE THERE TO COMMENT ON
SOMETHING THAT HAPPENS, BECAUSE
WHEN YOU'RE THE HOST, YOU WANT
SOMETHING BAD TO HAPPEN.
>> James: RIGHT.
YOU WANT, YOU KNOW -- AND
IT'S EXCITE PORG THE AUDIENCE.
THE LAST TIME THAT I REMEMBER
THERE WAS A NO HOST WAS THE
INFAMOUS ROB LOWE THING.
I FOLLOWED THAT YEAR, WAS A
PRESENTER AND THE NEXT YEAR I
STARTED HOSTING.
GOD KNOWS WE WANTED IT TO BE
GREAT.
I WISH EVERYONE LUCK AND I THINK
IT COULD BE FUN.
>> James: I THINK IT WILL BE
GREAT.
YOU HAVE BEEN TO THE EMMYS.
DO YOU ENJOY GLAMMING UP FOR THE
RED CARPET?
IS IT SOMETHING YOU LOVE DOING?
>> OUR FIRST TIME GOING TO THE
EMMYS, I WAS REALLY EXCITED AND
EVERYONE IS LIKE YOU'VE GOT TO
GET A STYLIST AND BORROW A VERY
PRETTY DRESS AND THE STYLIST
SAID YOU NEED TO GO GET A SUNTAN
BECAUSE THE DRESS I WAS WEARING
WAS VERY PALE AND I WAS PALE.
I SAID I'M NOT DOING THAT.
SHE SAYS GO TO THE BOOTH AND YOU
GO GET A SPRAY TAN.
>> WHERE TRUMP GOES, RIGHT?
EXACTLY.
THAT WAS THE BOOTH.
DID YOU SEE THE EPISODE OF
FRIENDS WHERE ROSS IS LIKE A
NINE?
THAT'S KIND OF WHAT HAPPENED.
SO I'M AT THE BOOTH AND THERE'S
LIKE CREAM ON YOUR FINGERS, HAIR
NET ON, ALL THESE STEPS, I
HADN'T DONE IT, THERE ARE THESE
WEIRD POSES THAT YOU'RE DOING,
AND I PUT A HAIR NET ON MY FACE
SO I WOULDN'T GET ANY ON MY FACE
AND I TOOK IT OFF AND THEY KEPT
SPRAYING.
SO I GET TO SCRUBS TO SHOOT THAT
DAY, AND AS I'M THERE, THIS TAN
IS INCREASING OVER TIME.
>> James: THAT'S RIGHT,
BECAUSE IT GETS DEEPER.
>> DEEPER.
>> James: YES!
BILL LAWRENCE WHO CREATED
"SCRUBBS" CAME UP AND SAID,
CHALKE, HARDER THAN ANY SPECIFIC
ON THE SHOW IS GOING TO BE
MAKING YOU LOOK LESS LIKE AN
OOMPA LOOMPA IN ALL THE FOOTAGE
WE SHOT YESTERDAY.
( LAUGHTER )
>> James: WOW.
HAVE YOU GONE BACK AND DONE IT
SINCE?
>> I'M NOT COORDINATED ENOUGH
FOR THAT.
>> James: MY WIFE'S DONE A
TANNING THING AND THEN GOT INTO
BED AND THEN YOU WAKE UP IN THE
MORNING AND IT'S, LIKE, YOUR
FIRST THOUGHT IS SOMEONE'S HAD
AN ACCIDENT.
AND THE END YOUR FIRST THOUGHT
IS, OH, THANK GOD IT'S NOT ME.
( LAUGHTER )
NO, NO, NO, SHE GETS SPRAYED,
AND THEN GOES TO BED AND THE
IDEA IS YOU WAKE UP AND YOU HAVE
A SHOWER AND YOU'RE IN A GOLDEN
GLOW, EXCEPT THE FACT THAT IT
REALLY MAKES YOUR BED LOOK LIKE
SOME KIND OF PROTEST.
STICK AROUND!
MORE OF THESE TWO WHEN WE COME
BACK!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
( BAND PLAYING )
♪ ♪
Only TYLENOL® Rapid Release Gels
have laser drilled holes.
They release medicine fast,
for fast pain relief.
TYLENOL®
HVR.
You either love it
or you really love it.
♪
Charmin Ultra Soft!
It's softer than ever.
Charmin Ultra Soft is
softer than ever...
so it's harder to resist.
Okay, this is getting a little
weird.
Enjoy the go!
With Charmin!
After months of wearing
only a tiger costume,
we're finally going on the
trip I've been promising.
Because with Expedia,
I saved when I added
a hotel to our flight.
♪
So even when she outgrows
her costume,
we'll never outgrow the memory
of our adventure together.
Unlock savings when
you add select hotels
to your existing trip.
Only when you book
with Expedia.
(ding)
Hey, who are you?
Oh, hey Jeff, I'm a car thief...
What?!
I'm here to
steal your car because,
well, that's my job.
What?
What??
WHAT?!
(laughing)
What??
WHAT?!
What?!
[crash]
WHAT?!
Haha, it happens.
And if you've got
cut-rate car insurance,
paying for this could
feel like getting robbed twice.
So get Allstate...
and be better protected
from Mayhem...
like me.
Colon cancer screening
for people
50 and older at average risk.
I think it's time
for a new screen.
For a different
kind of screen...
for colon cancer.
Thought about it?
His wife asked
about screening options
and her doctor
ordered me.
I'm Cologuard,
the noninvasive
test you use at home.
No special drink.
Just a trip
to the bathroom!
Cologuard.
Colon cancer screening
that's as easy as get,
go, gone.
Cologuard is not
right for everyone,
so ask your doctor if
it's right for you.
Cologuard is not
right for everyone,
♪
It hasn't always
been easy, has it?
♪
There have been days
when you doubted yourself.
♪
And days when you
were ready to quit.
♪
But you didn't.
Because you had the courage to
venture into something powerful.
Education.
If I leave you with just
three words of advice:
never...stop...growing.
[cheering]
[ music playing ]
♪ Here Comes the Sun ♪
You, all of you.
How you live. What you love.
[ laughter ]
That's what inspired us
to create America's
most advanced Internet.
Internet that
puts you in charge.
[ chattering ]
That protects what's important.
That handles everything
[ group cheering ]
and reaches everywhere.
This is beyond WiFi.
This is xFi.
Simple. Easy. Awesome.
Xfinity.
The future of awesome.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
( BAND PLAYING )
>> James: WELCOME BACK!
REGGIE, DO YOU HAVE A QUESTION
FOR ANY OF OUR GUESTS THIS
EVENING?
>> Reggie: I DO.
TONIGHT'S QUESTION GOES TO --
WHEN THERE'S A TIME THAT YOU
FEEL UNCERTAIN ABOUT WHERE LIFE
IS GOING AND YOU FEEL AS THOUGH
THOSE AROUND YOU ARE OUT OF
KNOWING, HOW DOES YOU FIGURE OUT
HOW TO GET BACK YOUR OWN
GLOWING?
( LAUGHTER )
>> YOU WANT TO GO?
I WAS JUST HITTING THE
BUTTON.
>> I VAPE.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Reggie: THAT'S BEYOND
CORRECT.
>> James: IT'S BEYOND CORRECT!
THANK OUR INCREDIBLE GUESTS
SARAH CHALKE, BILLY CRYSTAL!
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH BUDDY
AND A$AP FERG!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
( BAND PLAYING )
Cheez-It snacks are
the most satisfying
combination of
crunch with-
Cheese.
With their
delicious perfection-
Cheese.
It's not all about
you Cheese.
You think I have a mouth.
I'm a wheel of cheese.
Got a point.
[yeah]
Cheez-It.
Cheesy,
crunchy satisfaction.
When I walked through a
snowstorm for a cigarette,
that's when I knew
I had to quit.
For real this time.
That's why I'm using Nicorette.
Only Nicorette Gum has patented
dual-coated technology
for great taste.
Plus intense
craving relief.
Every great why,
needs a great how.
Could switching to GEICO really
save you fifteen percent or more
on car insurance?
Did the little piggy
cry wee wee wee
all the way home?
Weeeeeeeee!
We we weeeee!
Weeeeeeee!
Max.
MAXWELL!
Yeah?
You're home.
Oh, cool.
Thanks Mrs. A.
GEICO.
Fifteen minutes could save
you fifteen percent or more.
Julie means more to me
than anything.
And I wanted to ask you
Before I ask her
May I have your permission
to marry her?
You're marrying her and
her whole world
Shop Neil Lane diamond
engagement rings...
...at KAY.
I'M MISSING OUT ON
OUR FAMILY OUTINGS
BECAUSE I CAN'T FIND A BLADDER
LEAKAGE PRODUCT THAT FITS.
EVERYTHING WAS TOO LOOSE.
BUT DEPEND® FIT-FLEX®
FEELS TAILORED TO ME.
WITH A RANGE OF SIZES
FOR ALL BODY TYPES.
DEPEND® FIT-FLEX® UNDERWEAR
IS GUARANTEED TO
BE YOUR BEST FIT.
DEPEND® FIT-FLEX® UNDERWEAR
♪
Oo!
Blackberry Bublé, my favorite.
You mean Bubly.
No, I mean Bublé.
You're Michael Bublé.
That's a Bubly.
No, Bublé.
She's right, Michael Bublé.
It's pronounced...
Bublé, I know. Thanks,
Dav-é.
(loud instrumental) Bublé?
Chorus: It's Bubly!
Sparkling water.
Crack a smile.
Can I have your autograph,
Mr. Bubly?
It's Bublé.
Beauty editors have tried
everything.
In search of a whiter smile.
Their choice? Crest
3D Whitestrips.
Our exclusive whitening
formulation
safely whitens 25 times better*.
For a noticeably whiter, smile.
Trust America's #1
whitening treatment.
Crest 3D Whitestrips.
Think only specialty stores have
what's new?
Olay has the hottest debut.
New Olay Clay Stick Masks,
Hydrating Facial Mist,
And Brightening Eye Cream.
Only by Olay.
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: HERE TO PERFORM
"BLACK" FROM HIS OUTSTANDING
ALBUM "HARLAN AND ALONDRA,"
PLEASE WELCOME, BUDDY AND
SPECIAL GUEST A$AP FERG!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> HEY, YO!
STOP THE DEPORTATION OF 21
SAVAGE!
>> FREE 21!
>> HOW MANY BLACK PEOPLE WE GOT
IN THE STUDIO AUDIENCE TONIGHT?
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
HANDS UP!
LET'S GO!
♪ BLACK
BLACK BLACK BLACK
♪ BLACK ON BLACK, BLACK
YEAH, HEY, OKAY
♪ BLACK, BLACK, BLACK
BLACK ON BLACK
♪ BLACK, MY THOUGHTS SO BLACK
BLACK, BLACK ON BLACK
♪ MY SKIN IS SO BLACK
I'M ROCKIN' THAT
♪ BLACK ON BLACK, IT'S BLACK
BLACK RIMS ON THESE BLACK WHEELS
♪ IN THIS BLACK WHIP
WITH THIS BLACK BITCH I'M SO
♪ BLACK ON BLACK ON BLACK ON
BLACK ON BLACK, BLACK, BLACK,
♪ BLACK BLACK ON BLACK
BLACK MY THOUGHTS SO BLACK
♪ BLACK, BLACK ON BLACK
MY SKIN IS SO BLACK
♪ I'M ROCKIN' ALL BLACK
EVERYTHING IS BLACK
♪ BLACK RIMS
ON THESE BLACK WHEELS
♪ IN THIS BLACK WHIP
WITH THIS BLACK BITCH I'M SO
♪ BLACK ON BLACK ON BLACK ON
BLACK ON BLACK
♪ AY, HEY
BLACK OUT THE COUPE
♪ HOP OUT THE ROOF
WHEN I RUN INTO YOU
♪ THOUGHTS BLACK AS THE
DARK SIDE OF THE MOON
♪ WON'T BE NO TRUCE
WON'T BE NO TRUCE
♪ AT YOUR FUNERAL
IN AN ALL-BLACK SUIT
♪ COUPLE WHITE GIRLS
ROCKING ALL-BLACK TOO
♪ MILLION MEN MARCH
IN THE ALL-BLACK BOOTS
♪ CALL UP THE TROOPS
CALL UP THE TROOPS
♪ PUNCH YOU IN THE MOUTH
THEN KNOCK OUT YOUR TOOTH
♪ I CAN TELL WHEN
THEY NOT TELLIN' THE TRUTH
♪ TALKIN' THAT STUFF
WHAT YOU GON' DO?
♪ WHAT YOU GON' DO?
♪ BACK AND I'M BLACK
WHAT YOU GON' DO?
AND I'M ACTING BRAND-NEW
♪ BACK AND I'M BLACK
♪ IN THE BACK
AND I'M ACTING BRAND-NEW
LIKE, "OH WORD"
♪ IN THE BACK
♪ DIAMONDS ALL BLACK LIKE
LIKE, "OH WORD"
WHAT YA HEARD
♪ DIAMONDS ALL BLACK LIKE
♪ WHAT YA HEARD
WHAT YA HEARD
♪ SPILLIN' SOME HENNESSY
BLACK ON THE CURB
♪ THIS FOR THE MEMORY
OF THE DECEASED
♪ WHEN I BLACK OUT
I AWAKEN THE BEAST
♪ WHAT IT'S GON' BE?
WHAT IT'S GON' BE?
♪ YOU DON'T WANNA MESS
WITH A BROTHER LIKE ME
♪ BET YOU NEVER SEEN A
BROTHER SO BLACK
♪ I'M BLACK ON BLACK
ON BLACK ON BLACK
♪ BLACK, BLACK, BLACK
BLACK ON BLACK
♪ BLACK MY THOUGHTS SO BLACK
BLACK, BLACK ON BLACK
♪ MY SKIN IS SO BLACK
I'M ROCKING THAT
♪ BLACK ON BLACK IT'S BLACK
BLACK RIMS ON THESE BLACK WHEELS
♪ IN THIS BLACK WHIP
WITH THIS BLACK BITCH I'M SO
♪ BLACK ON BLACK ON BLACK ON
BLACK ON BLACK, BLACK, BLACK
♪ BLACK, BLACK ON BLACK
BLACK MY THOUGHTS SO BLACK
MY SKIN IS SO BLACK
♪ BLACK, BLACK ON BLACK
♪ I'M ROCKING ALL BLACK
MY SKIN IS SO BLACK
EVERYTHING IS BLACK
♪ I'M ROCKING ALL BLACK
♪ BLACK RIMS
EVERYTHING IS BLACK
ON THESE BLACK WHEELS
♪ BLACK RIMS
♪ IN THIS BLACK WHIP
ON THESE BLACK WHEELS
WITH THIS BLACK BITCH I'M SO
♪ IN THIS BLACK WHIP
♪ BLACK ON BLACK ON BLACK ON
WITH THIS BLACK BITCH I'M SO
BLACK ON BLACK
♪ BLACK ON BLACK ON BLACK ON
♪ THIS KID BLACK TIMBS BLACK
BLACK ON BLACK
KILL TRACKS LIKE I'M SIX BLACK
♪ THIS KID BLACK TIMBS BLACK
♪ BLACK ASS--
KILL TRACKS LIKE I'M SIX BLACK
HAIR BLACKER THAN BLACK
♪ BLACK ASS--
♪ LIPS BLACK
HAIR BLACKER THAN BLACK
EVEN MY-- BLACK
♪ LIPS BLACK
♪ GRANDAD IRISH TRINIDAD
EVEN MY-- BLACK
GUESS I AM HALF
♪ GRANDAD IRISH TRINIDAD
♪ BLACK ASS
GUESS I AM HALF
I GOTTA GO TO ancestry.com
♪ BLACK ASS
♪ I THINK I'M 'BOUT TO BLACK
I GOTTA GO TO ancestry.com
ALL THE POLICE
♪ I THINK I'M 'BOUT TO BLACK
♪ AIN'T ABOUT THE BLACK
ALL THE POLICE
HE STILL A PIG
♪ AIN'T ABOUT THE BLACK
♪ EVEN THOUGH HE BLACK
HE STILL A PIG
WILLIE GOT A LYNCH, HEAD IN THAT
♪ EVEN THOUGH HE BLACK
♪ IF YOU BLACK YOU DEAD IN THAT
WILLIE GOT A LYNCH, HEAD IN THAT
STRANGE FRUIT HANG FROM A TREE
♪ IF YOU BLACK YOU DEAD IN THAT
♪ ON THE LEAVES IS RED AND THAT
STRANGE FRUIT HANG FROM A TREE
DO IT RIGHT LIKE A GARVEYITE
♪ ON THE LEAVES IS RED AND THAT
♪ AFRICA, I'M HEADING BACK
DO IT RIGHT LIKE A GARVEYITE
IN THE STREET
♪ AFRICA, I'M HEADING BACK
♪ BLACK ON BLACK
IN THE STREET
KILL HIM WITH THE HEAT
♪ BLACK ON BLACK
♪ BLAT, BLAT, BLAT
KILL HIM WITH THE HEAT
CUT OFF HIS FEET
♪ BLAT, BLAT, BLAT
♪ PUT EM IN THE SHACKLE
CUT OFF HIS FEET
MANSA MUSA BEEN HAD THE CASH
♪ PUT EM IN THE SHACKLE
♪ MIX BLACKS TO DILUTE BLACKS
MANSA MUSA BEEN HAD THE CASH
DON'T WANT BLACKS
♪ MIX BLACKS TO DILUTE BLACKS
♪ TO PRODUCE BLACKS
DON'T WANT BLACKS
TAKE BLACK AND THEY BOOT THAT
♪ TO PRODUCE BLACKS
♪ ORANGE IS THE NEW BLACK
TAKE BLACK AND THEY BOOT THAT
BLACK, BLACK, BLACK
♪ ORANGE IS THE NEW BLACK
♪ BLACK ON BLACK
BLACK, BLACK, BLACK
BLACK MY THOUGHTS SO BLACK
♪ BLACK ON BLACK
♪ BLACK, BLACK ON BLACK
BLACK MY THOUGHTS SO BLACK
MY SKIN IS SO BLACK
♪ BLACK, BLACK ON BLACK
♪ I'M ROCKING THAT
MY SKIN IS SO BLACK
BLACK ON BLACK IT'S BLACK
♪ I'M ROCKING THAT
♪ BLACK RIMS
BLACK ON BLACK IT'S BLACK
ON THESE BLACK WHEELS
♪ BLACK RIMS
♪ IN THIS BLACK WHIP
ON THESE BLACK WHEELS
WITH THIS BLACK BITCH I'M SO
♪ IN THIS BLACK WHIP
♪ BLACK ON BLACK ON BLACK ON
WITH THIS BLACK BITCH I'M SO
BLACK ON BLACK, BLACK, BLACK
♪ BLACK ON BLACK ON BLACK ON
♪ BLACK, BLACK ON BLACK
BLACK ON BLACK, BLACK, BLACK
BLACK MY THOUGHTS SO BLACK
♪ BLACK, BLACK ON BLACK
MY SKIN IS SO BLACK
♪ I'M ROCKING ALL BLACK
EVERYTHING IS BLACK
♪ BLACK RIMS
ON THESE BLACK WHEELS
♪ IN THIS BLACK WHIP
WITH THIS BLACK BITCH I'M SO
♪ BLACK ON BLACK ON BLACK
ON BLACK ON BLACK
♪ I FEEL LIKE TRAYVON
WITH THIS BLACK HOODIE ON
♪ HUEY P. NEWTON
BLACK REVOLUTION
♪ I'M WITH A NUBIAN QUEEN
AND SOME ILLEGAL ALIENS
♪ I GOT A BLACK FIST BALLED UP
AND IT AIN'T JUST ME
♪ IT'S ALL US
400 YEARS OF OPPRESSION
♪ I'M ABOUT TO GET ME
THAT BLACK TESLA
♪ BLACK SKID MARKS
ON THE PAVEMENT
♪ COPS WANNA SEE ME
IN A BLACK CAGE
♪ BLACK ON BLACK ON BLACK
MASTER JUBA WITH THE TAP DANCE
♪ GUCCI WITH THE DAPPER DAN
TELL 'EM, KISS MY BLACK ASS
♪ RIDIN' ON THE DYNO
WITH THE BLACK MAGS
♪ JUST ANOTHER BLACK MAN
TRYIN' STAY UP OUT THE CASKET
♪ YEAH, BLACK DON'T CRACK
MATTER FACT
♪ WHERE THE HELL
OUR 40 ACRES AT ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
BUDDY AND A$AP FERG, EVERYONE!
CHECK OUT BUDDY ON HIS TOUR
RIGHT NOW!
COME ON BACK, EVERYBODY!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
♪ ♪ ♪
Digestive Advantage Probiotics
have a strong natural
protein shell.
So while other brands
may have billions of probiotics
many can struggle in stomach
acid.
Ours survive 100 times better.
Let our strength
help you stay strong.
(Thunderclap)
If your day doesn't
unfold as predicted.
Unfold this.
New Neutrogena®
Makeup Remover single.
And remove 99% of makeup.
100% rain or shine.
Neutrogena®.
Dove gives you
fashion ready underarms
so you can wear anything.
From athletic tops
to zebra dresses,
and everything in between.
Enjoy 48 hour protection
and softer, smoother underarms.
With Dove antiperspirants.
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: THANKS SO MUCH FOR
WATCHING.
TOMORROW NIGHT: ALICIA KEYS,
HAILEY BIEBER, AND STAND UP FROM
JOE LIST.
WE'LL SEE YOU THEN.
REGGIE, TAKE US HOME.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
♪ ♪ ♪
I was on the fence about
changing
from a manual to an electric
toothbrush.
But my hygienist said going
electric
could lead to way cleaner teeth.
She said, get the one inspired
by dentists,
with a round brush head.
Go Pro with Oral-B. Oral-B's
gentle rounded brush head
removes more plaque along the
gum line.
For cleaner teeth and healthier
gums.
And unlike Sonicare, Oral-B
is the first electric toothbrush
brand
accepted by the ADA
for its effectiveness and
safety.
What an amazing clean!
I'll only use an Oral-B!
Oral-B.
Brush like a pro.
So you finally got Fios, huh?
Yep, and wanna know what the
best part about it is?
Nope.
Gaming with less lag?
Watching movies in 4K?