CARRIE ANN: IT'S THURSDAY,
FEBRUARY 14, VALENTINE'S DAY,
AND "THE TALK" IS LIVE.
"EMPIRE" STAR JUSSIE SMOLLETT
SPEAKS OUT FOR THE FIRST TIME
SINCE HIS ATTACK LAST MONTH.
HE TELLS ROBIN ROBERTS HE'S NOT
JUST ANGRY AT THE MEN WHO BEAT
HIM.
HE'S ALWAYS OUTRAGED AT THE
SKEPTICS WHO DOUBT HIS STORY.
A WANNABE INSTAGRAM INFLUENCER
POSTS HERSELF THROWING A CHAIR
OFF A BUILDING'S 45TH FLOOR.
IS YOUR SEX DRIVE IN SYNC WITH
YOUR PARTNER'S?
ONE COMPANY CLAIMS IT'S FOUND A
WAY TO MAKE SURE YOU'RE BOTH IN
THE MOOD.
JUSTIN BIEBER IS REPORTEDLY
BEING TREATED FOR DEEP
DEPRESSION ISSUES.
FIND OUT HOW HIS WIFE HALEY IS
HELPING HIM.
AND OUR NEIGHBORHOOD IS ABOUT
TO GET A WHOLE LOT FUNNIER
THANKS TO THE STARS OF THE HIT
CBS SHOW "THE NEIGHBORHOOD,"
CEDRIC THE ENTERTAINER AND
TICHINA ARNOLD ARE HERE.
SO LET'S START TALKING.
[CAPTIONING FUNDED BY CBS
TELEVISION STUDIOS AND CBS
BROADCASTING INC.]
CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY THE
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE,
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTION CONTENT AND ACCURACY.
VISIT NCICAP.ORG.
[APPLAUSE]
SARA: HELLO, AND WELCOME TO
"THE TALK."
HAPPY VALENTINE'S DAY,
EVERYBODY!
[APPLAUSE]
NOW, LET'S GET STARTED WITH
"EMPIRE" -- ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET STARTED WITH "EMPIRE"
STAR JUSSIE SMOLLETT SPEAKING
OUT FOR THE FIRST TIME AFTER
HIS ATTACK.
IT'S BEEN 2 1/2 WEEKS SINCE
JUSSIE SAID HE WAS ATTACKED IN
CHICAGO BY TWO MEN WHO YELLED
RACIAL AND HOMOPHOBIC SLURS,
PUNCHED HIM, WRAPPED A ROPE
AROUND HIS NECK, THEN DOUSED
HIM WITH BLEACH.
BECAUSE POLICE SAID JUSSIE
INITIALLY REFUSED TO TURN OVER
HIS PHONE RECORDS AND THAT THE
ONES HE DID EVENTUALLY GIVE
THEM WERE HEAVILY EDITED, SOME
PEOPLE HAVE ACCUSED THE STAR OF
LYING.
TODAY JUSSIE SAT DOWN WITH
"G.M.A.'S" ROBIN ROBERTS TO SET
THE RECORD STRAIGHT.
>> I'M PISSED OFF.
>> WHAT IS IT THAT HAS YOU SO
ANGRY?
>> IT'S THE ATTACKERS, BUT IT'S
ALSO THE ATTACKS.
WANTING ME TO GIVE MY PHONE FOR
THREE TO FOUR HOURS.
I'M SORRY, BUT I'M NOT GOING TO
DO THAT.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE I HAVE PRIVATE
PICTURES AND VIDEOS AND
NUMBERS.
MY PARTNER'S NUMBER.
MY FAMILY'S NUMBER.
MY CASTMATES' NUMBERS.
MY FRIENDS' NUMBERS.
MY PRIVATE EMAILS.
MY PRIVATE SONGS.
MY PRIVATE VOICE MEMOS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT'S GOING
TO BE TO HAND OVER MY PHONE.
[APPLAUSE]
SARA: WHILE CHICAGO POLICE HAVE
SCREENED LOTS OF FOOTAGE FROM
NEIGHBORHOOD SECURITY CAMERAS,
THEY STILL HAVE NOT FOUND VIDEO
OF THE ACTUAL ATTACK.
JUSSIE SHARED HIS FRUSTRATION.
>> I WANT THAT VIDEO FOUND SO
BADLY BECAUSE FOR PROBABLY FOUR
REASONS.
NUMBER ONE, I WANT THEM TO FIND
THE PEOPLE THAT DID IT.
NUMBER TWO, I WANT THEM TO STOP
BEING ABLE TO SAY ALLEGED
ATTACK.
NUMBER THREE, I WANT THEM TO
SEE THAT I FOUGHT BACK.
AND I WANT A LITTLE GAY BOY WHO
MIGHT WATCH THIS TO SEE THAT I
FOUGHT [BEEP] BACK.
AND IT DOES NOT TAKE ANYTHING
AWAY FROM PEOPLE THAT ARE NOT
ABLE TO DO THAT.
BUT I FOUGHT BACK.
THEY RAN OFF.
I DIDN'T.
[APPLAUSE]
SARA: AND WE HAVE THIS NEW
UPDATE FROM CHICAGO POLICE WHO
ANNOUNCED THEY ARE QUESTIONING
TWO PERSONS OF INTEREST IN
CONNECTION WITH JUSSIE'S
ATTACK.
POLICE STRESS NEITHER PERSON
HAS BEEN CHARGED WITH A CRIME,
AND AS OF NOW, THERE IS NO
EVIDENCE THEY WERE INVOLVED.
SO, DO YOU THINK SPEAKING OUT
IS THE BEST WAY TO SHUT DOWN
SKEPTICS?
AUDIENCE: YES!
SHARON: OH, ABSOLUTELY.
AND I -- I'VE GOT TO, YOU KNOW,
SIDE WITH JUSSIE ON THE THING
THAT I DON'T WANT MY PHONE TO
BE LOOKED AT.
OR MY NUDE SHOTS AND THINGS.
NO.
[APPLAUSE]
OURS.
HOURS AND HOURS OF SEXUAL
FOOTAGE OF MYSELF.
NO, I -- I WOULDN'T WANT MY
PHONE TO BE TAKEN AWAY AND
ANALYZED.
I JUST WOULDN'T WANT IT.
NOT FOR ANYTHING OTHER THAN
IT'S MY PERSONAL LIFE ON THERE.
AND I JUST WOULDN'T WANT IT.
SO I TOTALLY GET THAT WITH HIM.
AND I TOTALLY GET THAT HE MIGHT
HAVE, YOU KNOW, DELETED SOME
THINGS, AND IT'S HARD.
I MEAN, HE'S BEEN THROUGH A
REALLY TOUGH TIME.
SARA: AND THE MEDIA HAS REALLY
CAST SO MUCH DOUBT ON HIS
STORY, WHICH I FIND SO
PERSONALLY OFFENSIVE, THAT A
GAY BLACK MAN IS TARGETED AND
THEN SUDDENLY HE BECOMES THE
VICTIM OF PEOPLE'S DISBELIEF?
IT'S SO --
[APPLAUSE]
AND THERE HAVE BEEN THINGS
LIKE, WELL, WHY WOULD HE BE
GETTING A SUBWAY SANDWICH AT
2:00 A.M.
HE SAID WELL, THEY'RE HOPE AT
THAT TIME BECAUSE PEOPLE GO.
SHARON: WE GO.
I GO.
SARA: OR PEOPLE SAY IN THAT
NEIGHBORHOOD, YOU COULDN'T GET
A -- SAYS WHO?
I MEAN, IT'S JUST LIKE THESE
SORT OF RIDICULOUS THINGS WHERE
I FEEL LIKE WHY DON'T WE
BELIEVE THIS PERSON?
WHY?
EVE: IT REALLY IS SAD AND WITH
ALL THAT HE HAS BEEN THROUGH,
THE FACT THAT HE HAS TO COME
OUT.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, BECAUSE
OF SOCIAL MEDIA, THERE'S SO
MANY OPINIONS, IT'S BETTER TO
HEAR IT FROM HIS OWN MOUTH AND
HEAR IT -- AND FEEL HIS ENERGY.
AND I'M GLAD WITH EVERYTHING
THAT HAS HAPPENED, I AM HAPPY
THAT HE, YOU KNOW, IS BEING
BRAVE ENOUGH TO SIT WITH ROBIN
ROBERTS AND SHARE HIS STORY.
SHERYL: AND IF THE NAYSAYERS
KNOW SO MUCH ABOUT WHAT THEY
THINK HAPPENED, WHY YOU DON'T
KNOW WHO DID IT?
SINCE YOU KNOW SO MUCH.
[APPLAUSE]
TELL US WHAT YOU KNOW, AND I
HATE THE FACT THAT WE ARE IN A
SOCIAL MEDIA -- EVEN THE COMMON
PERSON, USUALLY IT'S THE
CELEBRITY AND THEIR FANS AND
THEIR FOLLOWERS.
NOW IT'S EVEN THE COMMON PERSON
WHO MAY HAVE SOMETHING HAPPEN
TO THEM THAT THEY'RE GOING TO
THEIR SUPPORTERS OR WHATEVER
FOR ACKNOWLEDGMENT.
THAT'S WHY PEOPLE DON'T WANT TO
TALK.
COME FORWARD BECAUSE THEY'RE
GOING TO BE JUDGED.
AND THAT DOESN'T HELP THE
SITUATION.
[APPLAUSE]
SARA: WELL, WHAT I HOPE IS THAT
-- I HOPE THAT THE POLICE ARE
ONTO SOMETHING WITH THESE TWO
PERSONS OF INTEREST.
I HOPE THEY GET THEM AND THAT
PEOPLE HAVE TO LOOK AT HOW, AS
A MEDIA AND AS CULTURE WE TWIST
THINGS AND CAST DOUBT ON THINGS
THAT WE SHOULD NOT CAST DOUBT
ON.
[APPLAUSE]
SHERYL: WILL PEOPLE APOLOGIZE?
WHEN THE TRUTH COME OUT, WILL
YOU APOLOGIZE AS HARD AS YOU
JUDGED HIM?
WILL YOU APOLOGIZE?
[APPLAUSE]
SARA: I HOPE.
SO BUT I DOUBT IT.
IN OTHER NEWS, A 19-YEAR-OLD
WANNA BE INSTAGRAM INFLUENCER
WITH LESS THAN 4,000 FOLLOWERS
THREW TWO CHAIRS OFF A 45TH
STORY BALCONY IN TORONTO OVER
THE WEEKEND, PRESUMABLY TO GET
MORE LIKES.
NOW, SHE'S BEEN ARRESTED.
[APPLAUSE]
TAKE A LOOK.
>> THE VIDEO OF A WOMAN TOSSING
A PATIO CHAIR OFF THE BALCONY
OF A TORONTO HIGH RISE TAKES
YOUR BREATH AWAY.
PEOPLE ARE STUNNED AS THEY SEE
IT FOR THE FIRST TIME.
>> IT'S RIDICULOUS.
WHY RISK PEOPLE'S LIVES?
FOR A MOMENT OF JUST INTERNET
FAME?
>> BELOW THAT BALCONY, THE
EXPRESSWAY AND LOTS OF FOOD
TRAFFIC.
POLICE THINK IT WAS TWO CHAIRS
FOUND IN A HEAP AT THE BASE OF
THE BUILDING.
SARA: SHE HAS BEEN CHARGED WITH
ENDANGERING LIFE AND HAS NOW
BEEN RELEASED ON $1,500 BAIL
AND ORDERED TO LIVE WITH HER
MOTHER.
SO, DO YOU THINK ALL SOCIAL
MEDIA PLATFORMS SHOULD BAN HER
FOR LIFE?
AUDIENCE: YES!
SHARON: OH -- OH, YEAH.
I MEAN, HERE IS A PERFECT
EXAMPLE OF A YOUNG PERSON WHO
WANTS INSTANT FAME, INSTANT,
YOU KNOW, THE RECOGNITION,
EVERYTHING THAT COMES WITH IT
FOR NOTHING.
EXCEPT BEING STUPID, IGNORANT,
NO TALENT.
[APPLAUSE]
WHY WOULD YOU -- 45 -- I CAN'T
EVEN BELIEVE THAT THE WINDOW
OPENED ON THE 45TH FLOOR.
BUT, HOWEVER, IT DID.
AND HER CHUCKING -- CAN YOU
IMAGINE IF THAT HAD HIT A CAR?
THEN THAT CAR WOULD HAVE
CRASHED INTO ANOTHER CAR AND
ANOTHER AND ANOTHER.
I MEAN, THE THOUGHT OF IT JUST
MAKES YOU SHIVER.
IT'S JUST RIDICULOUS THAT THESE
WANNABE KIDS OUT THERE THINK
OVERNIGHT THEY'RE GOING TO GET
FAME AND FORTUNE FOR BEING
PATHETIC.
YOU ARE A PATHETIC YOUNG GIRL.
[APPLAUSE]
SHE WANTS TO BE -- WHY DON'T
YOU WORK ON YOUR WRITING?
YOU KNOW, YOU WANT TO INFLUENCE
PEOPLE?
WORK ON SOMETHING.
YOU DON'T GET SOMETHING WORTH
HAVING OVERNIGHT FOR BEING
RIDICULOUSLY IGNORANT, AS YOU
ARE.
SARA: YEAH, AND IT'S OVER
LIKES.
THAT'S NOT EVEN A REAL THING,
PEOPLE.
[APPLAUSE]
PRIYANKA JONAS CO-STARS IN A
NEW ROM-COM AND SHE SAYS HER
NEW HUSBAND NICK JONAS IS SUPER
ROMANTIC.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> YOU HAVEN'T BEEN MARRIED FOR
TOO LONG, BUT WHAT IS THE MOST
ROMANTIC THING THAT HE'S DONE
FOR YOU?
>> OH, MY GOD.
THE NIGHT BEFORE WHEN WE WERE
GETTING MARRIED, I WAS DOING A
BRIDESMAIDS' HANGOUT AND WHEN
WE OPENED MY ROOM TO COME IN,
THERE WERE FLOWERS ALL THE WAY
WITH ABOUT 18 OR 19 GIFTS WITH,
LIKE, LITTLE NOTES ON EACH ONE.
I WILL PROTECT YOU.
I WILL ALWAYS KEEP YOU SAFE.
LIKE, IT WAS JUST -- EVERYONE
WAS CRYING.
>> HE WINS.
>> HE DOES.
HE WINS LIFE.
[APPLAUSE]
SARA: WHAT'S THE MOST ROMANTIC
THING ANYONE'S EVER DONE FOR
YOU?
EVE: FOR ME, MY HUSBAND IS THE
KING AT ROMANTIC THINGS,
ROMANTIC GESTURES.
AND HE'S ON HIS WAY TO COME SEE
ME RIGHT NOW.
[APPLAUSE]
EVE: THIS MORNING I WOKE UP AND
HE POSTED THIS BEFORE HIS
FLIGHT.
AND I'M, LIKE, IT JUST MELTS MY
HEART.
BECAUSE HONESTLY, HE'S AMAZING.
HE IS -- HE'S JUST GREAT.
[APPLAUSE]
CARRIE ANN: AUDIENCE, TELL ME,
HOW CAN I GET THE ROMANCE?
I WANT TO ASK THE AUDIENCE.
GUYS, HOW AM I GOING TO GET
THAT KIND OF ROMANCE IN MY
LIFE?
ANYONE?
NOBODY HAS ANY SUGGESTIONS?
ANY SUGGESTIONS?
SARA: YOU'RE OUT OF LUCK.
CARRIE ANN: ANY ADVICE PLEASE?
YES?
YES, MA'AM?
>> I'M SO PSYCHED.
MY NAME IS VANESSA, AND I
WANTED TO SING A SONG TO MY
FIANCEE -- I'M SO SCARED.
>> I'M THINKING AUT YOU RIGHT
AHHH!
OH, MY GOD.
[APPLAUSE]
CARRIE ANN: ARE YOU CRYING?
SARA: WHEN WE WALKED OUT, I
WAS, LIKE, LOOKING AT THE
CEILING.
WHAT'S GOING TO DROP?
THIS PERSON, IS SHE GOING TO
BE?
>> LOOK WHAT I DID FOR HER.
I COVERED MY TATTOOS.
[APPLAUSE]
EVE: YOU WENT ALL OUT.
SARA: BEFORE WE CAME OUT, AGAIN
I LOOKED AT THE SCHEDULE, LIKE,
NO, SHE'S GOT A MEETING FROM
10:30 TO 12:00.
SHE CAN'T TORTURE ME ON THE
AIR.
>> HAPPY VALENTINE'S DAY.
[APPLAUSE]
EVE: GREAT GUESTS.
BIG GIVEAWAYS.
GO TO THETALK.COM FOR TICKETS.
If you're 65 or older,
even if you're healthy,
you may be at increased risk
for pneumococcal pneumonia
- a potentially serious
bacterial lung disease
that can disrupt
your life for weeks.
In severe cases,
pneumococcal pneumonia can
put you in the hospital.
It may take weeks to recover
making you miss out on the
things you enjoy most.
Just one dose of the
PREVNAR 13® vaccine
can help protect you from
pneumococcal pneumonia.
It's not a yearly shot.
PREVNAR 13® is approved
for adults
to help prevent infections
from 13 strains of the bacteria
that cause pneumococcal
pneumonia.
Don't get PREVNAR 13®
if you have had a severe
allergic reaction
to the vaccine
or its ingredients.
Adults with weakened
immune systems
may have a lower
response to the vaccine.
The most common side
effects were pain,
redness and swelling
at the injection site,
limited arm movement, fatigue,
headache, muscle pain,
joint pain, less appetite,
vomiting, fever, chills,
and rash.
Prevention begins
with PREVNAR 13®.
Ask your doctor or
pharmacist about PREVNAR 13®.
♪
When cravings hit, hit back.
Choose Glucerna, with
slow release carbs
to help manage blood sugar, and
start making everyday progress.
Glucerna.
Unwanted odors lingering
too long in your car?
Try Febreze Car vent clips!
Just snap the clip
and insert in the vent
to eliminate lingering
odors for up to 30 days.
Try Febreze Car vent clips,
available in a range
of light to bold scents.
Brushing only reaches
25% of your mouth.
LISTERINE® cleans
virtually 100%.
Helping to prevent gum
disease and bad breath.
Never settle for 25%.
Always go for 100.
Bring Out the Bold™
Our grandparents checked
their smartphones
zero times a day.
Times change.
Eyes haven't.
That's why there's Ocuvite.
Screen light...
Sunlight...
Longer hours...
Eyes today are stressed.
But Ocuvite has vital
nutrients...
...to help protect them.
Ocuvite.
Eye nutrition for today.
This is RAGÚ Simply.
Simply Made with
100% Olive Oil.
Simply No Sugar Added.
Simply Dinner.
Simply Delicious.
( ♪ )
RAGÚ Simply.
CARRIE ANN: ARE YOU EVER IN THE
MOOD BUT AREN'T SURE YOUR
PARTNER?
AN OHIO COUPLE HAS COME UP WITH
A UNIQUE SOLUTION.
THEY'RE RAISING MONEY FOR IT.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> LOVE SYNC IS A DEVICE WHEN
BOTH OF YOU ARE IN THE MOOD.
>> IT'S SIMPLE.
PLACE A BUTTON AT EACH OF YOUR
BED SIDES, AND WHEN YOU'RE
FEELING A LITTLE RANDY, YOU
JUST PUSH THE BUTTON.
THERE'S NO RISK OF REJECTION.
IF ONLY ONE OF YOU PUSHES THE
BUTTON, NOTHING HAPPENS.
AND YOUR PARTNER IS NONE THE
WISER.
BUT IF YOUR PARTNER IS ALSO
READY FOR A PANTS-OFF DANCE
OFF, THEY'LL PRESS THEIR
BUTTON.
THE TECHNOLOGY COMBINES THESE
INPUTS AND RECOGNIZES THERE IS
CONSENSUS.
IT LETS YOU BOTH KNOW BY
EMITTING A SWIRLING GLOW FROM
THE BUTTONS.
CARRIE ANN: ALL RIGHT.
SERIOUS QUESTION.
DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU AND YOUR
MATE'S SEX DRIVES ARE IN SYNC?
SHERYL: WELL, FIRST THE BUTTON
IS UNNECESSARY.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST POKE ME IN
THE BACK OR TAP ME ON THE
SHOULDER LIKE OTHER PEOPLE DO?
COME ON.
THAT'S HOW IT WORKS.
[APPLAUSE]
AND THEN -- I GOT ENOUGH
GADGETS ON MY NIGHTSTAND.
I DON'T NEED THIS BUTTON.
SHARON: I THINK I WAS JUST
SAYING TO THE GIRLS, I THINK
IT'S GOING TO BE, LIKE, A JOKE
GIFT TO GIVE OUT FOR BIRTHDAY
GIFTS OR WHEN SOMEONE'S GETTING
MAIERRIED.
THEY HAVE A SILLY LITTLE NOVELY
GIFT.
IT'S GOING TO BE THE PET ROCK,
USELESS, BUT EVERYBODY GOT ONE.
SARA: I THINK IT'S KIND OF CUTE
FOR SOME REASON.
I THINK IT'S KIND OF CUTE.
BUT I ALSO COULD SEE A FIGHT,
LIKE, BETWEEN PEOPLE, LIKE, I
PUSHED MY BUTTON!
EVE: THERE IS REJECTION.
IF THE PERSON DOESN'T PUSH THE
BUTTON BACK, YOU FEEL SOME TYPE
OF WAY.
CARRIE ANN: IT'S WEIRD.
ARE YOU AND LINDA'S SEX DRIVES
IN SYNC?
SARA: I DON'T ANSWER THOSE KIND
OF QUESTIONS.
SHERYL: OK, SO WHAT IF YOU
PRESSING THE BUTTON BUT I'M
SLEEP AND I DON'T SEE YOU
PRESSING THE BUTTON?
SO NOW YOU MAD AT ME.
WHAT IF THE BUTTON GETS JAMMED?
SHARON: THEY'RE NOT THAT FAR
AWAY THAT THEY CAN'T UNJAM IT
FOR IT.
SHERYL: I'D RATHER USE MY
BATTERIES FOR OTHER THINGS,
SHARON.
[APPLAUSE]
SARA: HAVE YOU GUYS EVER HAD
RELATIONSHIPS WHERE YOU'RE IN
SYNC OR NOT IN SYNC?
EVE: I'VE HAD BOTH.
I MEAN, YEAH, ME AND MAX --
CARRIE ANN: THE ONE THAT GOT
AWAY THAT I THINK ABOUT WAS MY
FIRST LOVE WHEN I WAS 23, OUR
SEX DRIVES WERE ABSOLUTELY IN
SYNC.
I HAD A GOOD GIRLFRIEND IN
HAWAII TELL ME, AND HER
RELATIONSHIP HAS BEEN GOING ON,
I PUT MY ENERGY TOWARDS HER
CAREER.
HE'S PUT HER ENERGY TOWARDS HER
MARRIAGE.
SHE SAYS THAT THE SEX DRIVE IS
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
BECAUSE IT'S HOW YOU SORT OF
KEEP COMING BACK TOGETHER, THAT
ATTRACTION ON ALL LEVELS,
RIGHT?
SHERYL: I HAD A GUY WE WERE SO
OUT OF SYNC THAT I WOULD STAY
UP ALL NIGHT JUST SO I DIDN'T
HAVE TO DO NOTHING.
AND THEN I WOULD SLEEP ALL DAY.
I'D DRINK COFFEE AND STAY UP.
SHARON: HOW LONG WAS THIS
RELATIONSHIP?
SHERYL: EVERY TIME THIS GUY
CALLS ME, HE NORMALLY CALLS ME
AROUND VALENTINE'S DAY -- I'M
BUSY, I CAN'T.
SARA: HE'S GOING TO TAKE HIS
BUTTON AND JUST HIT -- ALL
RIGHT.
CARRIE ANN: WE'LL BE RIGHT
BACK.
You know that look?
That life of the party look.
Walk it off look.
One more mile look.
Reply all look.
Own your look with fewer lines.
There's only one
BOTOX® COSMETIC.
It's the only one FDA approved
to temporarily make
frown lines,
crow's feet and forehead
lines look better.
The effects of BOTOX® COSMETIC
may spread hours to weeks
after injection,
causing serious symptoms.
Alert your doctor right away
as difficulty swallowing,
speaking, breathing,
eye problems,
or muscle weakness
may be a sign of
a life-threatening condition.
Do not receive BOTOX® COSMETIC
if you have a skin infection.
Side effects may include
allergic reactions,
injection site pain, headache,
eyebrow, eyelid drooping
and eyelid swelling.
Tell your doctor about
your medical history,
muscle or nerve conditions,
and medications
including botulinum toxins
as these may increase the risk
of serious side effects.
So, give that
just saw a puppy look
and whatever that look is.
Look like you with fewer lines.
Own your look
with the one and only
BOTOX® COSMETIC.
♪
Those arms, they'll be jelly
tomorrow.
It'll hurt to sit.
And laugh.
'Cause that workout, is working.
Feed it, with Special K
with iron, protein and
B vitamins.
Feed your progress.
Feed your power.
Feed your change.
(KATY)
I was thrilled to be able to go
with my friends to our annual
get-together, especially after
being diagnosed last year
with advanced non-small cell
lung cancer.
(AVO)
Another TRU story with KEYTRUDA.
(DR. KLOECKER)
I started Katy on KEYTRUDA and
chemotherapy and she's getting
results we rarely
saw five years ago.
(AVO)
In a clinical trial,
significantly more patients
lived longer and saw their
tumors shrink than
on chemotherapy alone.
(DR. KLOECKER)
It's changed my approach to
treating patients.
(AVO)
KEYTRUDA may be used with
certain chemotherapies as
your first treatment if you have
advanced nonsquamous, non-small
cell lung cancer and you do not
have an abnormal
"EGFR" or "ALK" gene.
KEYTRUDA helps your immune
system fight cancer,
but can also cause your immune
system to attack healthy
parts of your body. This can
happen during or after treatment
and may be severe
and lead to death.
See your doctor right away if
you have new or worse cough,
chest pain, shortness of breath,
diarrhea, severe stomach pain
or tenderness, nausea or
vomiting, rapid heartbeat,
increased hunger or thirst,
constipation, dizziness
or fainting, changes in
urine or eyesight,
muscle pain or
weakness, joint pain,
confusion or memory problems,
fever, rash,
itching, or flushing.
These are not all the
possible side effects.
Tell your doctor about all your
medical conditions,
including immune system
problems, if you've had
an organ transplant, had or plan
to have a stem cell transplant,
or have lung, breathing, or
liver problems.
(KATY VO)
Where I am now compared to a
year ago,
it's a story worth sharing.
(AVO)
Living longer is possible.
It's TRU.
KEYTRUDA, from Merck.
With more FDA-approved uses for
advanced lung cancer
than any other immunotherapy.
CARRIE ANN: JUSTIN BIEBER IS
REPORTEDLY PUTTING HIS WEDDING
PLANS ON HOLD BECAUSE OF HIS
MENTAL HEALTH.
JUSTIN AND HIS WIFE WERE
MARRIED IN A SECRET CEREMONY
LAST YEAR AND HAD PLANNED TO
SAY I DO AGAIN IN A RELIGIOUS
SERVICE, BUT THOSE PLANS HAVE
BEEN DELAYED WHILE JUSTIN SEEKS
COUNSELING FOR HIS DEPRESSION.
"PEOPLE" MAGAZINE SAYS THE
24-YEAR-OLD HAS FELT
OVERWHELMED BY FAME.
THE SOURCE SAYS, "BEING
FOLLOWED, HAVING HIS EVERY MOVE
STALKED BY FANS, CAMERAS IN HIS
FACE, IT ALL SETS HIM OFF.
AND HE OFTEN FEELS LIKE
EVERYONE IS OUT TO GET HIM.
HAVE YOU EVER HAD TO PUT
SOMETHING ON HOLD TO FOCUS ON
YOUR MENTAL HEALTH?
AUDIENCE: YES.
SHARON: YEAH, I THINK THAT MOST
OF US HAVE.
YOU KNOW, LIFE BECOMES, YOU
KNOW, YOU LOSE CONTROL OF
WHAT'S GOING ON AND YOU JUST
THINK, I CAN'T DO IT.
I CAN'T.
I NEED TO TAKE, YOU KNOW, A
BREATH.
AND I FEEL BADLY FOR HIM
BECAUSE I KNOW THAT A LOT OF
PEOPLE ARE PROBABLY SAYING
WELL, WHAT'S HE, YOU KNOW,
DEPRESSED?
HE'S GOT EVERYTHING.
HE'S GOT THIS, THAT, THE OTHER.
AND IT JUST DOESN'T WORK THAT
WAY.
WITH SEVERE DEPRESSION.
IT REALLY DOESN'T.
AND I FEEL, YOU KNOW, REALLY
BAD FOR HIM RIGHT NOW.
AND I'M HAPPY THAT HE'S GETTING
HISSELF TOGETHER, HIS HEAD
TOGETHER, HIS PRIORITIES HE'S
GOT RIGHT.
AND I'M GLAD HE'S TAKING A
BREAK FOR HIMSELF.
[APPLAUSE]
CARRIE ANN: THERE WAS A TIME
WHEN MY FATHER DIED BEFORE
"DANCING WITH THE STARS," LIKE
FOUR DAYS BEFORE.
AS -- I FELT MYSELF GOING INTO
A DEPRESSION.
BUT I HAD TO PUT IT OFF.
HAVE YOU EVER DONE THIS AS
WELL?
THERE'S A TIME, I HAD TO PUT,
LIKE, A STEEL WALL BETWEEN ME
AND MY EMOTIONS SO I COULD GET
THROUGH THE SEASON WITH
"DANCING WITH THE STARS" AND
EVERYTHING THAT WAS COMING.
I HAD JUST BROKEN UP WITH MY
FIANCE, MY DAD DIED, I MOVED, I
WAS DIAGNOSED WITH CHRONIC
ILLNESS.
I KNEW I DIDN'T HAVE TIME.
BUT WHAT WAS IMPORTANT IS YOU
SHOULDN'T PUSH OFF YOUR
EMOTIONS UNLESS YOU KNOW YOU
CAN HAVE A TIME TO DEAL
WITNESS.
THAT'S THE PART THAT WAS KEY.
I KNEW AFTER THE SEASON WAS
OVER I DO SPEND, LIKE, THREE
MONTHS JUST TAKING CARE OF
MYSELF.
I WAS FORTUNATE TO HAVE THAT.
BUT I HAD IT ALMOST THE
OPPOSITE.
SARA: DID YOU FEEL DURING THAT
TIME THAT YOU WERE ACTING OUT
AT ALL OR HAVING WEIRD EMOTIONS
KIND OF SNEAK OUT?
CARRIE ANN: YEAH.
THEY DOO SNEAK OUT.
EMOTIONS REMOTIONS.
THEY HAVE THEIR OWN TEMPO,
THEIR OWN DESIRES TO COME OUT.
AND THEY WILL FIND A WAY OUT.
YOU CAN PUT THEM OFF.
YOU KNOW, "DANCING WITH THE
STARS" IS 10 WEEKS OUT OF THE
YEAR.
FOR 10 WEEKS I COULD KIND OF
PUT THEM ON HOLD.
I WOULD WATCH AND ANDY DICK WAS
ON OUR SHOW.
I LOST IT.
IT WAS REALLY SIMPLE.
IT WAS MY OWN EMOTIONS WITH MY
OWN LIFE COMING OUT.
SHERYL: BUT THEN WHAT DID YOU
DO ONCE YOU HAD THAT TIME?
CARRIE ANN: I WENT TO
COUNSELING.
THERE'S SO MANY GREAT BOOKS TO
READ.
I BOUGHT EVERY BOOK I COULD
FIND ON DEPRESSION.
AND I WENT AND SAW MY FRIENDS
AND MY SUPPORT SYSTEM.
I WAS VERY LUCKY.
SARA: WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
So there you are with
your depression
and your dirty laundry that you
just don't want to deal with.
Because depression is
multiple symptoms.
Yeah, time for a change.
And your doctor tells you
about TRINTELLIX,
a prescription medicine
for depression.
So you're feeling this
overall relief.
And TRINTELLIX had no
significant impact on weight
in clinical trials.
You got this.
Tell your doctor right away if
you have worsening depression,
unusual changes in
mood, behavior
or thoughts of suicide.
Antidepressants can increase
these in children, teens,
and young adults.
Do not take with MAOIs.
Tell your doctor about your
medications including
migraine, psychiatric and
depression medications to avoid
a potentially life-threatening
condition.
Increased risk of bleeding and
bruising may occur especially
if taken with NSAID pain
relievers, aspirin
or blood thinners.
Manic episodes or vision
problems may occur
in some people.
May cause low sodium levels.
Common side effects include
nausea, constipation
and vomiting.
Not living in sweatpants.
Ask your doctor about changing
to Trintellix.
SARA: WITH HARSH WINTER STORMS
AFFECTING NEARLY EVERY PART OF
THE COUNTRY THIS WEEK, SNOWBALL
FIGHTS ARE A COMMON OCCURRENCE,
BUT ONE SEATTLE WOMAN GOT
ARRESTED AFTER SHE NEARLY RAN
OVER A GROUP OF PEOPLE WHO
ALLEGEDLY THREW SNOWBALLS AT
HER CAR.
THE LOCAL CBS STATION HAS
DETAILS.
>> [BEEP]
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> JOEY WISER SHOT THIS CELL
PHONE VIDEO THAT'S NOW GONE
VIRAL.
>> [BEEP].
[BEEP].
>> HE TOLD ME HE COULDN'T
BELIEVE THE WOMAN BEHIND THE
WHEEL OF THIS BLUE JEEP WOULD
SWERVE PAST HIM BEFORE RUNNING
STRAIGHT INTO A GROUP OF PEOPLE
ACROSS THE STREET NARROWLY
MISSING THEM.
>> IT SEEMED LIKE HER INTENTION
WAS TO RUN THEM OVER.
>> IT WAS A NEIGHBORHOOD
SNOWBALL FIGHT THAT WENT WRONG.
>> THE PERSON SEEN IN THE VIDEO
TRYING TO HOLD THE WOMAN DOWN
SAID SHE GOT UPSET BECAUSE HER
CAR WAS HIT BY ONE OF THE
SNOWBALLS.
THE WOMAN'S CAR ENDED UP
GETTING STUCK IN THE SNOW.
NEIGHBORS CALLED POLICE AND HER
ARREST WAS ALSO CAUGHT ON
CAMERA.
AUTHORITIES SAID THE WOMAN NOW
IDENTIFIED IS FACING CHARGES OF
D.U.I. AND RECKLESS DRIVING.
CARRIE ANN: OH, MY GOSH.
WHAT IS WRONG WITH PEOPLE?
WHAT IS WRONG WITH HER?
PEOPLE NEED TO CALM DOWN.
YOU DON'T GO AFTER SOMEBODY
WITH YOUR CAR, A VEHICLE THAT
COULD KILL PEOPLE WHEN YOU ARE
HIT BY A SNOWBALL.
IT'S JUST RIDICULOUS.
SHARON: THE THING IS, SHE COULD
HAVE LOST CONTROL OF THAT CAR
IN THE SNOW.
SO IT'S SO RIDICULOUS.
EVE: I'M GLAD NOBODY GOT HURT
BUT I ALSO GLAD SHE WAS CAUGHT
BECAUSE SHE WAS DRINKING AND
DRIVING.
SO AT LEAST SHE GOT ARRESTED.
SO I'M GLAD SHE DID DO WHAT SHE
D
SARA: IT'S ALSO A GOOD REMINDER
OF THESE KIND OF VIDEOS
EVERYWHERE, RIGHT?
EVEN IF YOU'RE NOT DRUNK.
WHEN I WAS AT THE GRAMMYS THE
OTHER DAY, I WAS TRYING TO SEE
LINDA PERFORM HER SECTION WITH
DOLLY AND I WAS BACKSTAGE WITH
HER, AND THEN I WENT TO GO GET
SEATED DURING IT, AND THEY KEPT
SAYING OH, IT'S A COMMERCIAL,
YOU CAN'T GO IN.
OH, OK, NOW YOU CAN'T SIT IN
YOUR SEAT.
AND I WAS, LIKE, YOU KNOW THOSE
MOMENTS WHEN YOU'RE, LIKE, BUT
I HAVE TO SEE IT.
BUT I WAS, LIKE, COOL IT, SARA.
YOU'RE EVERYWHERE.
YOU'VE LEARNED, YOU CAN'T --
NOT THAT I WOULD ANYWAY, BUT
YOU JUST CAN'T TAKE YOUR LIFE
OUT ON OTHER PEOPLE.
WHICH IS WHAT I ALWAYS THINK
THESE THINGS ARE.
SOMETHING ELSE IS BOTHERING
THIS PERSON.
THEY'RE TAKING IT OUT --
[APPLAUSE]
SHERYL: AND TO ME, IT'S A
LITTLE NEIGHBORHOOD SNOWBALL
FIGHT.
WHY DIDN'T YOU GET INVOLVED IN
THE FIGHT?
SHE COULD HAVE JUMPED OUT THE
CAR, BALLED A SNOWBALL UP AND
SAID I GOT YOU, THEN WOULD IT
HAVE BEEN FUN IN THE
NEIGHBORHOOD.
WE'RE JUST NOT NEIGHBORS
ANYMORE.
SHARON: IT WOULD HAVE SOBERED
HER UP.
SHERYL: BEING OUT IN THE COLD
IN THAT SNOW.
WE THINK OF EVERYTHING.
SARA: SOBER UP AND DON'T RUN
PEOPLE OVER.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
CARRIE ANN: COMING UP NEXT,
FROM "THE NEIGHBORHOOD" TO OUR
TABLE, CEDRIC THE ENTERTAINER
AND TICHINA ARNOLD.
In the wat,
You ready for this? She doesn't
like it... you've gotta get in
there.
Okay.
Careful not to get it in her
eyes.
I know, I know what a bath is...
Smile honey.
This thing is like...
First kid.
Here we go.
Second kid.
You coming in mommy?
Ahh not a chance!
By  their second kid, every
parent is an expert and more
likely to choose LUVS than first
time parents.
LUVS with Nightlock plus absorbs
wetness faster than
Huggies Snug and Dry for
outstanding overnight
protection at a fraction of the
cost.
Live, Learn and Get Luvs.
On tour, every second counts.
I need great without the wait.
New Elvive
Rapid Reviver
Deep Conditioners.
L'Oréal's patented conditioners
work fast with no leave-in time.
Enriched with
damage-repairing serum.
2x easier detangling
2x less breakage
than with a leading conditioner.
Works deep. Repairs damage fast.
Hair's transformed instantly.
New Rapid Reviver
Deep Conditioners.
Elvive revives damaged hair.
We're worth it.
METASTATIC BREAST
CANCER IS RELENTLESS,
BUT I'M RELENTLESS TOO.
MBC DOESN'T TAKE A DAY OFF,
AND NEITHER WILL I.
I TREAT MY MBC WITH
EVERYDAY VERZENIO,
THE ONLY ONE OF ITS KIND THAT
CAN BE TAKEN EVERY DAY.
VERZENIO IS THE ONLY CDK4 &
6 INHIBITOR APPROVED WITH
HORMONAL THERAPY THAT
CAN BE TAKEN EVERY DAY
FOR POST MENOPAUSAL WOMEN
WITH HR+, HER2 NEGATIVE MBC.
VERZENIO PLUS AN AI HELPED
WOMEN HAVE SIGNIFICANTLY
MORE TIME WITHOUT
DISEASE PROGRESSION,
AND MORE THAN HALF OF WOMEN SAW
THEIR TUMORS SHRINK VS AN AI.
DIARRHEA IS COMMON,
MAY BE SEVERE,
OR CAUSE DEHYDRATION
OR INFECTION.
BEFORE TAKING VERZENIO, TELL
YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU HAVE FEVER,
CHILLS, OR OTHER
SIGNS OF INFECTION.
VERZENIO MAY CAUSE LOW
WHITE BLOOD CELL COUNTS,
WHICH MAY CAUSE
SERIOUS INFECTION
THAT CAN LEAD TO DEATH.
SERIOUS LIVER
PROBLEMS CAN OCCUR.
SYMPTOMS INCLUDE TIREDNESS,
APPETITE LOSS, STOMACH PAIN,
AND BLEEDING OR BRUISING.
BLOOD CLOTS THAT CAN
LEAD TO DEATH HAVE OCCURRED.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF
YOU HAVE PAIN OR SWELLING
IN YOUR ARMS OR LEGS,
SHORTNESS OF BREATH, CHEST PAIN,
RAPID BREATHING OR HEART RATE,
OR IF YOU ARE PREGNANT,
NURSING, OR PLAN TO BE PREGNANT.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS
INCLUDE NAUSEA, INFECTIONS,
LOW BLOOD CELLS AND PLATELETS,
DECREASED APPETITE, HEADACHE,
ABDOMINAL PAIN, TIREDNESS,
VOMITING, AND HAIR
THINNING OR LOSS.
I'M RELENTLESS.
AND MY DOCTOR AND I CHOOSE TO
TREAT MY METASTATIC BREAST
CANCER WITH VERZENIO.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
EVERYDAY VERZENIO.
Nivea Essentially Enriched
body lotion,
with two times the almond oil.
It deeply nourishes
skin for 48 hours.
♪ One, two ♪
♪ Three, whoo! ♪
Nivea Essentially Enriched.
Deeply nourishes for 48 hours.
SHERYL: TODAY'S GUESTS CRACK US
UP EVERY MONDAY NIGHT AS
HAPPILY AND HILARIOUSLY MARRIED
COUPLE TINA AND CALVIN BUTLER
ON THE HIT CBS COMEDY "THE
NEIGHBORHOOD."
[APPLAUSE]
YEAH.
IN NEXT WEEK'S EPISODE, THEY
TEAM UP TO GIVE THEIR ADULT SON
A PEP TALK ABOUT HIS NEW JOB.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I AIN'T NEVER WORKED IN SALES
BEFORE.
>> WELL, YOU'RE IN LUCK.
I MEAN, I'VE HAD MY AUTO SHOP
FOR 30 YEARS.
I CAN TEACH YOU ALL ABOUT THE
ABC'S OF SALES.
ALWAYS BE CAREFUL.
>> YOU MEAN BE GROUCHY AND
ALWAYS FORGET TO PUT THE TOILET
SEAT DOWN?
>> NO.
BE CONFIDENT.
BE CHARMING.
AND ALWAYS MAKE IT ABOUT THE
CUSTOMER'S NEEDS.
>> THIS CUSTOMER REALLY NEEDS
YOU TO PUT THE TOILET SEAT
DOWN.
SHERYL: PLEASE WELCOME OUR GOOD
FRIENDS, TICHINA ARNOLD AND
CEDRIC THE ENTERTAINER!
[APPLAUSE]
EVE: CONGRATULATIONS ARE IN
ORDER BECAUSE YOU WERE JUST
NOMINATED FOR AN NAACP AWARD.
[APPLAUSE]
CEDRIC: IT'S NICE.
EVE: CONGRATULATIONS TO BOTH OF
YOU BECAUSE "THE NEIGHBORHOOD"
HAS ALREADY BEEN RENEWED FOR
ITS SECOND SEASON.
[APPLAUSE]
WHICH IS AMAZING.
AND WE ACTUALLY HAVE THE MOMENT
THAT IT HAPPENED.
WE HAVE THE MOMENT THAT YOU
GUYS FOUND OUT.
SO, TICHINA, WHAT WAS GOING
THROUGH YOUR MIND?
TICHINA: MY DAUGHTER'S TUITION.
I WAS SHOCKED.
[APPLAUSE]
LISTEN, WE'RE REGULAR PEOPLE.
WE'RE JUST WORKING ACTORS.
WE'RE BLESSED TO BE WORKING.
AND I LITERALLY -- YES.
SHE TWERKED ANY TIME.
SARA: NOW ON THE SHOW ITSELF,
MAX GREENFIELD AND BETH BEHRS
PLAY YOUR WHITE NEIGHBORS, THE
ONLY WHITE COUPLE IN THE
NEIGHBORHOOD.
BUT, CEDRIC, I HEARD WHEN YOU
MOVED TO L.A., YOU SORT OF HAD
A SIMILAR FISH OUT OF WATER
EXPERIENCE?
CEDRIC: YEAH, I MOVED INTO AN
ALL LATINO NEIGHBORHOOD WHEN I
FIRST MOVED TO L.A.
[APPLAUSE]
VERY NICE.
SO, YOU KNOW, I HAD TO LEARN
THAT THERE'S A LOT OF FOOD
GOING TO COME OVER.
YOU KNOW, IT'S A LOT OF COOKING
GOING ON.
AND CORN WITH SAUCE YAND
MAYONNAISE ON IT.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT WAS GOING
ON.
YOU KNOW?
BUT IT WAS COOL.
SARA: BUT THEN YOU ACTUALLY,
YOUR WALK OF FAME --
CEDRIC: OH, YEAH, MY STAR ON
THE WALK OF FAME --
[APPLAUSE]
THAT'S KIND OF COOL, RIGHT?
I USED TO WALK AROUND THERE, OF
COURSE, AND SEE ALL THESE STARS
AND, YOU KNOW, YOU JUST COME TO
HOLLYWOOD FROM ST. LOUIS, AND
SO NOW YOU KNOW, WHEN I GOT MY
STAR, I WAS LITERALLY A BLOCK
OVER FROM WHERE I FIRST MOVED
TO L.A.
THAT WAS JUST KIND OF, LIKE, SO
COOL.
[APPLAUSE]
IT WAS CRAZY, RIGHT?
IT'S AWESOME.
SHARON: TICHINA.
TICHINA: HI, SHARON!
SHARON: HI, DARLING!
YOU AND CEDRIC HAVE BEEN
PLAYING HUSBAND AND WIFE FOR A
YEAR NOW.
NOW, DOES ANY OF THAT, LIKE, GO
ON OFF, WHEN YOU'RE NOT
WORKING?
DO YOU TAKE CARE OF HIM?
TICHINA: MOST DEFINITELY.
I DON'T PLAY WITH HIS LIFE.
LORNA DOES NOT PLAY.
I FILL HER SHOES AS BEST AS I
CAN WHEN HE'S ON THAT SET.
SO I MADE SURE THAT HE RESTS.
YOU KNOW, HE TAKES MOMENTS.
I DIDN'T TELL YOU I DID A VIDEO
OF YOU SNORING THE OTHER DAY.
CEDRIC: IT HAPPENS, GUYS.
TICHINA: PEOPLE DON'T REALIZE,
THIS MAN RUNS THE WHOLE SHOW.
BUT HE'S ALSO ON THE ROAD.
SO HE'S DOING COMEDY ON THE
WEEKENDS.
SO I GOT TO TAKE CARE OF MY
BOO.
MY BOO.
I GOT TO MAKE SURE HE'S ALL
RIGHT.
[APPLAUSE]
TICHINA: SUCH AN AMAZING HUMAN
BEING.
THIS MAN I'VE KNOWN FOR
20-SOMETHING YEARS.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME HE AND I
HAVE WORKED TOGETHER.
I'VE SEEN THIS MAN TREAT
EVERYBODY WITH RESPECT, TO THE
PRN THAT MOVES THE TABLE, TO
THE PERSON THAT IS THERE -- THE
FIRST PERSON IN THE MORNING ON
OUR SET.
HE TREATS EVERYBODY THE SAME.
SO I'M HAPPY TO HAVE HIM.
[APPLAUSE]
SHERYL: THE GREAT MARLA GIBBS,
WHO WE ALL LOVE FROM "227" WAS
A GUEST ON THE SHOW THIS WEEK.
SO WHAT WAS IT LIKE WORKING
WITH HER?
CEDRIC: OF COURSE, MARLA GIBBS
IS AN ICON.
YOU KNOW, I WAS ALWAYS A FAN,
OF COURSE, "227" BUT WHEN HE
WAS ON "THE JEFFERSONS."
SO, YOU KNOW, I WANTED TO GET
INTO A LITTLE RIF WITH HER.
SHE WAS FUNNY.
SHE IS SO GREAT.
SO GREAT.
AND, YOU KNOW, IT WAS JUST
AWESOME TO HAVE HER ON THE SET,
THIS ICONIC PERSONALITY.
AND SHE LOVED IT.
SHE LOVED BEING AT WORK AND,
YOU KNOW, BEEN DOING IT SO
LONG, THAT IT WAS JUST REALLY
AWESOME FOR US TO BE ABLE TO
PROVIDE THAT OPPORTUNITY.
AND SHE HAD A GREAT TIME.
[APPLAUSE]
TICHINA: MARLA HAS DONE A LOT
FOR THE BLACK COMMUNITY.
CEDRIC: YEAH.
[APPLAUSE]
CARRIE ANN: LAST WEEK ON THE
EPISODE THAT FEATURED A GIRLS'
TRIP TO MAGIC MIKE'S IN LAS
VEGAS.
A LITTLE BIT IN ON THE PARTY.
CRASH THE PARTY A LITTLE THERE?
CEDRIC: I JUST KIND OF WANTED
TO GO OUT THERE.
WITH THESE GUYS RIGHT HERE.
CARRIE ANN: LOOK AT THIS.
LOOK AT THIS.
CEDRIC: OH.
OH.
I GOT A LITTLE BIT -- THE GUYS
WERE A LITTLE NERVOUS ABOUT
TAKING THEIR SHIRTS OFF.
AND SO I SAID, GUYS, LET ME
SHOW YOU HOW IT'S DONE.
YOU KNOW?
CARRIE ANN: YOU DANCED.
YOU DO ALL OF THAT STUFF.
TICHINA: THAT'S RIGHT.
[APPLAUSE]
CEDRIC: YEAH.
SHERYL: HE DOES EVERYTHING.
CEDRIC: IN COLLEGE I WAS KNOWN
AS CUPCAKES.
EVE: I GOT TO SEE YOU JUST
RECENTLY.
YOU WERE HOSTING THE "MOTOWN
60: A GRAMMY CELEBRATION,"
WHICH WAS INCREDIBLE.
AND IT AIRS ON APRIL 21.
[APPLAUSE]
AND YOU CO-HOSTED WITH MR.
SMOKEY ROBINSON.
AND SO MANY OTHER INCREDIBLE
PERFORMERS.
DID YOU GET TO HANG OUT WITH
ANYBODY OR SEE ANYBODY THAT YOU
HAD NEVER MET BEFORE?
CEDRIC: ONLY PERSON I REALLY
WAS STALKING WAS DIANA ROSS.
AND I GUESS IT GOT PRETTY
OBVIOUS THAT I WAS STALKING HER
BECAUSE SECURITY WOULDN'T LET
ME GET CLOSE ENOUGH.
BUT I DID THE WHOLE, YOU KNOW,
WENT TO BARRY GORDY FIRST.
YOU KNOW?
BUT THEY WOULDN'T LET ME GET
CLOSE TO HER.
SHARON: I WONDER WHY.
TICHINA: WE SHOULD HAVE CALLED
TRACY.
WE LOOKING FOR HER.
SHERYL: LET ME ASK YOU THAT
SOMEBODY'S LOOKING FORWARD, TO
THE "MARTIN" REBOOT.
EVERYBODY'S LOOKING FOR THAT
AND HOPING FOR IT.
WHAT YOU CAN TELL US?
WHAT YOU CAN SHARE?
TICHINA: I WILL SHARE THAT
MARTIN CALLED ME ABOUT A MONTH
AGO AND HE GOT SOME GOOD NEWS
ABOUT, YOU KNOW, A HUGE NETWORK
WANTING TO TAKE IT ON.
SO WE'LL SEE.
FINGERS CROSSED.
[APPLAUSE]
IT WON'T BE THE SAME WITHOUT
TOMMY.
THE SHOW WILL NEVER BE THE SAME
WITHOUT TOMMY.
IT'S NOT A REBOOT.
I CALL IT A REBIRTH.
SARA: REBIRTH.
WELL, WHEN WE COME BACK, IT IS
A VALENTINE'S DAY CHALLENGE
THAT WILL TEST THE FOUNDATION
OF CEDRIC AND TICHINA'S TV
MARRIAGE.
GET READY TO PLAY "HUSBAND AND
WIFE BUT NOT IN REAL LIFE."
When you eat a bowl
of oatmeal,
you're getting beta-glucan.
That's a soluble fiber
that slows the breakdown
of carbohydrates.
And that provides energy
that lasts.
s
before she puts them in the
dishwasher.
So what does the dishwasher do?
(VO) Cascade Platinum does the
work for you.
Prewashing and removing
stuck-on foods, the first time.
(Mom) Wow! That's clean!
(VO) Cascade Platinum.
The day after chemo
shouldn't mean going
back to the doctor
just for a shot.
With Neulasta Onpro
patients get their day back...
to be with family,
or just to sleep in.
Strong chemo can put you at
risk of serious infection.
In a key study Neulasta
reduced the risk of infection
from 17% to 1%,
a 94% decrease.
Neulasta Onpro is designed
to deliver Neulasta
the day after chemo
and is used by most patients
today.
Neulasta is for certain
cancer patients
receiving strong chemotherapy.
Do not take Neulasta if you're
allergic to it
or Neupogen (filgrastim).
An incomplete dose could
increase infection risk.
Ruptured spleen,
sometimes fatal as well as
serious lung problems,
allergic reactions,
kidney injuries and capillary
leak syndrome have occurred.
Report abdominal or shoulder
tip pain, trouble breathing
or allergic reactions to
your doctor right away.
In patients with sickle
cell disorders,
serious, sometimes fatal crises
can occur.
The most common side effect
is bone and muscle ache.
Ask your doctor about
Neulasta Onpro.
Pay no more than $5 per dose
with copay card.
90% of women
have a skincare routine.
But what about a
lip care routine?
Pay your lips some attention.
The ChapStick Total
Hydration Collection.
Exfoliate
Nourish
Naturally enhance
your lips.
ChapStick.
Put your lips first.
♪ When you have nausea, ♪
♪ heartburn, ♪
♪ indigestion, ♪
♪ upset stomach, ♪
♪ diarrhea... ♪
Girl, Pepto ultra coating will
treat your stomach right.
♪Nausea, heartburn, ♪
♪ indigestion, upset stomach,♪
♪ diarrhea... ♪
Try Pepto with Ultra coating.
In an era of online retail,
where everything
is just a few clicks away,
buying a car should be
no different.
That's why, at Carvana,
you can buy a car
100% online.
We made it easy
to browse, view,
and buy from over 10,000 cars.
You can even trade-in
your old car
all while binge watching
your favorite TV show.
Afterwards, we'll deliver
your car to you.
Or you can pick it up
from one of our
car vending machines.
Either way, your car comes with
a 7-day return policy.
So grab a seat,
relax in your comfy pants,
and enjoy the new way to buy
a car-- at Carvana.
♪ ♪
Guess I'll bring a can of this
stuff everywhere.
Made with real cream.
Reddi-wip, instant
greatification.
SARA: WE'RE BACK WITH THE STARS
OF "THE NEIGHBORHOOD," CEDRIC
THE ENTERTAINER AND TICHINA
ARNOLD.
NOW, WE WANT TO HAVE A LITTLE
VALENTINE'S DAY FUN WITH THE
TWO OF YOU.
SO WE ARE GOING TO FIND OUT HOW
MUCH AMERICA'S FAVORITE NEW TV
COUPLE REALLY KNOWS ABOUT EACH
OTHER IN A GAME WE'RE CALLING
"HUSBAND AND WIFE BUT NOT IN
REAL LIFE."
[APPLAUSE]
SO, BEFORE THE SHOW, WE ASKED
TICHINA AND CEDRIC A FEW
QUESTIONS ABOUT THEMSELVES, AND
NOW IT'S TIME TO SEE IF THEY
CAN GUESS HOW THE OTHER PERSON
ANSWERED.
IF THEY CAN GET THREE MATCHES,
EVERYONE IN OUR STUDIO AUDIENCE
GOES HOME WITH A PRIZE.
ARE YOU READY?
[APPLAUSE]
CEDRIC: IT'S PRESSURE.
SARA: PRESSURE'S ON.
EVE?
EVE: ALL RIGHT, GUYS, NO
WHISPERING ANSWERS!
NO WHISPERING!
CEDRIC: JOHN DAVID?
TICHINA: I'M NERVOUS!
EVE: WHO IS TICHINA'S FAVORITE
MUSICAL ARTIST?
CEDRIC: OH, WOW.
I'M GOING TO SAY -- ARETHA
FRANKLIN.
SARA: TICHINA, IS HE RIGHT?
TICHINA: CLOSE, BABY.
CLOSE.
[BUZZER]
SARA: VERY CLOSE.
OK, SHARON, YOU'RE UP.
CEDRIC: GLADYS KNIGHT.
TICHINA: SHE MEANS EVERYTHING
TO ME.
SHARON: OK.
WHO --
TICHINA: YOU WERE CLOSE.
SHARON: NOW, YOU GUYS, COME ON?
SARA: WE GOT TO MOVE IT ALONG.
SHARON: WHO IS CEDRIC'S
CELEBRITY CRUSH?
TICHINA: I'M GOING TO GO WITH
RIHANNA.
BECAUSE SHE'S YOUNG STILL, BUT
SHE'S STILL, YOU KNOW, A WOMAN.
AND SHE'S JUST TALENTED.
SARA: LET'S SEE THE ANSWER.
[BUZZER]
OK.
CARRIE ANN, YOU'RE UP.
YOU GUYS BETTER PULL IT
TOGETHER HERE.
CARRIE ANN: WHO IS -- CEDRIC,
FOCUS, WHO IS TICHINA'S
CELEBRITY CRUSH?
CEDRIC: CEDRIC THE ENTERTAINER.
SARA: FINAL ANSWER?
IS HE RIGHT, TICHINA?
TICHINA: NO, HE AIN'T RIGHT.
SARA: JOHN DAVID WASHINGTON.
DENZEL'S SON, RIGHT?
SOCK, NOW, SHERYL --
SHERYL: TICHINA, WHAT MOVIE
ALWAYS MAKES CEDRIC CRY?
TICHINA: I WANT TO SAY "THE
FIVE HEARTBEATS."
SARA: IS SHE CORRECT?
I'M GUESSING SHE'S NOT, BASED
ON --
[BUZZER]
SARA: ALL RIGHT.
WE'VE GOT ANOTHER QUESTION.
EVE: SO, WHAT IS TICHINA'S
BIGGEST FEAR?
CEDRIC: I'M GOING TO GO WITH --
BUGS.
MAYBE BUGS OR SOMETHING.
SARA: BUGS?
IS HE RIGHT?
TICHINA: ARE YOU SO RIGHT!
[APPLAUSE]
SARA: ALL RIGHT.
SHARON, LET'S DO ONE MORE.
ONE MORE QUESTION QUICKLY HERE.
SHARON: ALL RIGHT.
WHICH CELEBRITY DOES CEDRIC
TEXT THE MOST?
TICHINA: OH, THIS IS A
NO-BRAINER.
STEVE HARVEY.
SARA: CEDRIC S. SHE RIGHT?
LET'S SEE IT, CEDRIC.
WE GOT TO GO TO BREAK.
LET'S SEE.
[BUZZER]
SARA: WELL, GUYS, YOU ONLY GOT
ONE MATCH.
THANK GOD YOU'RE NOT MARRIED IN
REAL LIFE.
BUT WE DON'T WANT ANYONE TO
LEAVE EMPTY HANDED, SO EVERYONE
IN OUR STUDIO AUDIENCE IS BEING
TREATED TO SOMETHING SPECIAL
FOR VALENTINE'S DAY.
A HOTEL VIA SAN FRANCISCO
THREE-DAY, TWO-NIGHT STAY FOR
YOU AND YOUR VALENTINE.
HOTEL VIA IS A BOUTIQUE HOTEL
IN SAN FRANCISCO ROOFTOP
LOUNGE.
IT HAS GUEST ROOMS WHICH BOAST
A MINIMALIST DESIGN CONCEPT.
VISIT HOTELVIASF.COM.
THIS GETAWAY VALUE RETAILS FOR
$950.
FOR YOUR CHANCE TO WIN AT HOME,
GO TO THETALK.COM/GIVEAWAYS.
TICHINA ARNOLD AND CEDRIC THE
ENTERTAINER, THANK YOU.
"THE NEIGHBORHOOD" AIRS MONDAY
NIGHTS AT 8:00 ON CBS AND WE'LL
BE RIGHT BACK.
CARRIE ANN: IT'S FRIDAY.
LET YOUR HAIR DOWN.
SHERYL: I DON'T LOOK THE SAME
EVERY DAY.
EVE: "THE TALK" ON CBS.
and your state's Medicaid,
here's something
important to know.
Now you could get even
more health benefits
than you already have.
It's the UnitedHealthcare
Dual Complete plan.
To find out if you - or someone
you care about - is eligible,
It's easy...
call now to talk with us.
We can explain it all and
answer any questions.
Medicaid gives you benefits and
Medicare gives you some, too.
But a Dual Complete Plan can
add even more benefits
and features compared to
Original Medicare.
You'll have lots of doctors and
hospitals to choose from.
Plus, prescription drug coverage
And depending on where you live,
you could enjoy other
benefits, too.
Like dental care,
vision coverage
and rides to and from
you doctor or hospital.
You can even get a
Health Products Catalog,
with credits you can use to
shop for everyday things, like
vitamins, oral health
items and first aid kits.
And best of all, with this plan,
there's no additional
cost to you.
Remember, if you have
Medicare and Medicaid,
chances are, you could get
a Dual Complete Plan.
So call now to talk with
us and learn more.
Or ask to have a licensed
agent visit your home
and take you through
everything, step by step.
We know healthcare
can be confusing.
UnitedHealthcare can
straighten things out.
With 40 years of experience,
you can count on us to be
there all along the way.
With a Dual Complete Plan you
could have a wide choice
of doctors to choose from,
better prescription
drug coverage...
dental and vision
coverage, too...
all at no additional cost.
You have Medicare.
You have Medicaid.
You may be eligible
for Dual Complete.
So call the number on
your screen now
to see if you're eligible
or to enroll...
in a Dual Complete Plan
from UnitedHealthcare.
CHARMIN ULTRA SOFT!
IT'S SOFTER THAN EVER.
CHARMIN ULTRA SOFT IS SOFTER
THAN EVER SO IT'S HARDER TO
RESIST.
OKAY, THIS IS GETTING
A LITTLE WEIRD
ENJOY THE GO WITH CHARMIN
Oh milk. Am I willing to pay
the price for loving you?
You'll make my morning, but
ruin my day.
Complicated relationship with
milk?
Pour on the Lactaid, 100% real
milk,
just without that annoying
lactose.
Mmm, that's good.
EVE: GREAT GUESTS.
BIG GIVEAWAYS.
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN "THE TALK"
NTIL YOU'VE SEEN IT IN PERSON.
CARRIE ANN: THANK YOU FOR BEING
HERE.
YOU'VE BEEN A SPECTACULAR
AUDIENCE.
EVE: GO TO THETALK.COM FOR
TICKETS.
AND JOIN THE FUN.
SARA: WE CAN'T SAY GOODBYE ON
VALENTINE'S DAY WITHOUT GIVING
YOU ONE MORE PRESENT.
IT'S TIME TO BRING YOU
SOMETHING WE THINK YOU'LL LOVE
IN TODAY'S MUST HAVE.
[APPLAUSE]
KATE SPADE NEW YORK IN FULL
BLOOM EAU DE PARFUM IS A MODERN
ROSE FLORAL SCENT WITH A FRESH
TWIST PERFECT FOR VALENTINE'S
DAY GIFTING.
EVERYONE IN TODAY'S STUDIO
AUDIENCE IS GOING HOME WITH A
KATE SPADE NEW YORK IN FULL
BLOOM FRAGRANCE.
FOR YOUR CHANCE TO WIN AT HOME,
RETWEET OUR POST ON TWITTER
TODAY OR GO TO
THETALK.COM/GIVEAWAY.
THANK YOU ALL FOR JOINING US
AND REMEMBER, IT'S ALWAYS THE
RIGHT TIME TO HAVE "THE TALK"!