BARTENDERS ARE RESPONSIBLE IF
YOU LEAVE THEIR BAR AND YOU'RE
TOASTED OR YOU HIT SOMEBODY,
THEY'RE COMING TO FIND OUT Wh RE
THE LAST PLACE YOU WERE WAS.
AND I FEEL LIKE SOMETIMES, YOU
KNOW, THIS IS A WAKE-UP CALL.
DO YOUR HOMEWORK.
FOR EVERYBODY.
DON'T JUST -- JUST BECAUSE IT
LOOKS LIKE IT'S GOING TO BE GOOD
AND YOU THINK THEY'RE GOING TO
BE THERE PROBABLY THEY'RE NOT
GOING TO BE, SO MAYBE ONE IS
SAVE YOUR MONEY AND DO SOMETHING
BETTER.
>> PEOPLE LOST OVER $20 MILLION.
>> YEAH.
>> AND IT'S A LOT OF DOUGH FOR
FOLKS.
>> SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
>> HERE WE ARE.
WE'LL BE BACK.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: FORMER STARBUCKS
CEO HOWARD SCHULTZ SAYS HE MAY
RUN FOR PRESIDENT AS AN
INDEPENDENT.
HOW DOES HE ANSWER CRITICS WHO
SAY HE'LL DERAIL DEMOCRATS AND
HAND TRUMP A VICTORY?
HE'S LIVE ON "THE VIEW" NEXT.
and you're gonna sing.
-Jamie, this is your house?
-I know, it's not much,
but it's home.
Right, kids?
-Kids?
-Papa, Papa!
-[ Laughs ]
-You didn't tell me
your friends were coming.
-Oh, yeah.
-This one is tiny like a child.
-Yeah, she is.
Oh, but seriously,
it's good to be surrounded
by what matters most --
a home and auto bundle
from Progressive.
-Oh, sweetie,
please, play for us.
-Oh, no, I couldn't.
-Please.
-Okay.
[ Singing in Spanish ]
-Please.
-Okay.
My gums are irritated.
I don't have to worry about
that, do I?
Actually, you do.
Harmful bacteria lurk just below
the gum line.
New Crest Gum Detoxify
works below the gum line
to neutralize harmful plaque
bacteria
and help reverse early
gum damage.
Gum Detoxify, from Crest.
People everywhere
are confusing Quilted Northern
for robes.
They're both cushiony,
comforting,
and add elegance to your home.
But Quilted Northern
is not a robe.
It's just really nice
toilet paper.
When I walked through a
snowstorm for a cigarette,
that's when I knew
I had to quit.
For real this time.
That's why I'm using Nicorette.
Only Nicorette Gum has patented
dual-coated technology
for great taste.
Plus intense
craving relief.
Every great why,
needs a great how.
What about this guy?
This guy's...
been through a lot.
Dogs bring out the good in us.
Pedigree brings out the good
in them.
Feed the good.
Sometimes, the pressures of
today's world can make it tough
to take care
of yourself.
But Nature's Bounty
has innovative ways
to help you
maintain balance
and help keep you
active and well-rested.
Because hey,
tomorrow's
coming up fast.
Nature's Bounty.
Because you're
better off healthy.
Nature's Bounty.
L'OREAL PARIS INTRODUCES
ROUGE SIGNATURE
MATTE COLORED INK
LESS TEXTURE
MORE COLOR
LESS EXCESS
MORE IMPACT
ALL DAY MATTE
BARE LIP SENSATION
ROUGE SIGNATURE
MATTE COLORED INK
BY L'OREAL PARIS
WE'RE WORTH IT
(VO) For a nasty cold,
take new DayQuil Severe with
Vicks VapoCOOL.
(ACAPELLA) Whoa!
(VO) And vaporize it with an
intense rush of Vicks vapors.
(ACAPELLA) Ahhhhhhhhhhh!
(VO) New DayQuil Severe with
Vicks VapoCOOL.
The Daytime Coughing, Stuffy
Head,
Vaporize your cold,
Medicine.
Stronger is rebuilding
a newborn's heart...
and restoring a
father's faith.
It's standing tall
after one surgery...
not six.
Stronger is being
a typical kid...
despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding
it earlier ...
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is
seeking answers...
And not giving up,
until you find them.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
GEICO makes it easy to get help
when you need it.
With licensed agents
available 24/7.
It's not just easy.
It's having-a-walrus-in-goal
easy!
ROOOAAAAR!
It's a walrus!
Ridiculous!
Yes! Nice save, big guy!
Good job Duncan! Way to go!
[chanting]
It's not just easy.
It's GEICO easy.
Oh, Duncan. Stay up.
No sleepies.
♪ LET'S GO ♪
[ APPLAUSE ]
>>> FORMER STARBUCKS CHAIRMAN
AND CEO HOWARD SCHULTZ WAS A HOT
TOPIC HERE YESTERDAY FOR SAYING
HE'S SERIOUSLY CONSIDER RUNNING
FOR PRESIDENT AS AN INDEPENDENT.
AND HE'S HERE TO TELL US RIGHT
NOW WHY HE WANTS TO DO THAT
PLEASE WELCOME AUTHOR OF THE NEW
BOOK "FROM THE GROUND UP,"
HOWARD SCHULTZ.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> SO I AM GOING TO ASK YOU
ABOUT THAT BECAUSE I THINK
YOU'VE BEEN A LIFELONG DEMOCRAT.
>> YES.
>> ARE YOU NOT SURE THAT YOUR
POLICIES ARE STRONG ENOUGH TO
RUN AS A DEMOCRAT?
>> WELL, I THINK I WOULD HAVE TO
BE DISINGENUOUS TO RUN AS A
DEMOCRAT TODAY BUT I THINK THE
QUESTION THAT I'M ASKING MYSELF
AND I THINK MANY OF US ARE
ASKING OURSELVES IS WHAT KIND OF
COUNTRY DO WE WANT TO LIVE IN
AND RIGHT NOW I THINK IT'S CLEAR
THAT THE COUNTRY WE ARE LIVING
IN NEEDS SIGNIFICANT CHANGE, NOT
ONLY CHANGE BECAUSE OF THIS
PRESIDENT, BUT CHANGE BECAUSE OF
THE TOXICITY AND THE LACK OF
COMPROMISE OF BOTH PARTIES AND
WE CERTAINLY SAW THAT.
>> RIGHT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WE CERTAINLY SAW THAT OVER
THE LAST MONTH, THE PRESIDENT
WAS RESPONSIBLE FOR CLOSING THE
GOVERNMENT.
BUT 800,000 PEOPLE AND THEIR
FAMILIES WERE DOING EVERYTHING
POSSIBLE JUST TO EAT AND THE
DEMOCRATS AS WELL AS THE
REPUBLICANS ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR
THAT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> WELL, I WANT TO ASK WHAT ARE
THE DEMS LEFT --
>> I DON'T KNOW SENATOR HARRIS
BUT LISTENING TO HER LAST NIGHT
SAY WE SHOULD ABOLISH THE
INSURANCE INDUSTRY AS A WAY TO
GO FORWARD ON HEALTH CARE, THAT
ALONE WOULD WIPE OUT MILLIONS OF
JOBS OF AMERICANS AND THAT IS
THE KIND OF EXTREME POLICY THAT
IS NOT A POLICY THAT I AGREE
WITH AND IF YOU TAKE IMMIGRATION
AND HEALTH CARE WE HAVE EXTREMES
ON BOTH SIDES NOT REPRESENTING
THE LARGE MAJORITY OF AMERICANS
WHO DON'T HAVE A VOICE AND WHAT
I'M SAYING IS, LET'S GIVE THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE A CHOICE AND
WHAT BETTER EXPRESSION OF
DEMOCRACY THAN WHY SHOULD WE
ONLY RELY ON REPUBLICANS AND
DEMOCRATS THAT HAVE DISPLAYED
NOT ONLY THE LAST TWO YEARS BUT
FOR DECADES AN INABILITY TO DO
THE PEOPLE'S WORK.
>> I'LL TELL YOU WHY IN A SECOND
BUT --
>> OKAY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> I WANT TO TELL PEOPLE ABOUT
YOU.
WHEN I HAD A SHOW AT CNN I RAN
INTO HOWARD AND THE ELEVATOR AND
I SAID TO HIM, HOWARD, GET ME A
LATTE.
HE'S A STARBUCKS GUY AND I WAS
TEASING YOU AND I WENT BACK TO
MY OFFICE AND HE SHOWS UP, I
HAVE A PICTURE OF IT, HE SHOWS
UP WITH A LATTE.
NOW, THAT'S A GREAT GUY.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
THAT THE CEO OF STARBUCKS
DELIVERS A LATTE TO ME.
VERY NICE.
AND I ALSO LIKE THE FACT THAT
YOU GAVE INSURANCE TO YOUR
PART-TIME EMPLOYEES.
THAT WAS REALLY SWEET.
THAT'S ABOVE AND BEYOND.
BUT, BUT AND HERE'S THE BIG BUT,
MICHAEL BLOOMBERG HAS SAID TO
YOU DON'T RUN AND HE WAS
THINKING OF RUNNING BUT THEN HE
DID THE RESEARCH AND FOUND OUT
HE COULDN'T WIN SO HE GOT OUT OF
THE RACE.
THE MAIN THING THAT SCARES ME IS
THAT YOUR ENTRY INTO THE RACE
WILL GUARANTEE TRUMP ANOTHER
FOUR YEARS AND WE CANNOT HAVE
THAT.
YOU TALK ABOUT THE DEMOCRATS NOT
WANTING TO NEGOTIATE.
THEY CANNOT NEGOTIATE WITH A
TODDLER AND YOU GIVE HIM THE
COOKIE ONE DAY THE NEXT DAY HE
WANTS ANOTHER COOKIE SO IT'S NOT
EQUAL ON BOTH SIDES.
THEY HAD TO PLAY TOUGH, THE
DEMOCRATS WITH HIM OTHERWISE HE
WILL RUN AMOK.
NOW YOUR ENTRY INTO THE RACE
PRETTY MUCH GUARANTEES A
REPUBLICAN IS GOING TO WIN AND I
KNOW YOU'RE --
>> I DON'T AGREE WITH YOU.
>> I DON'T YOU KNOW.
>> IN FACT, NOT ONLY DO I NOT
AGREE WITH YOU BUT I THINK IF
PRESIDENT TRUMP RUNS AGAINST A
FAR LEFT PROGRESSIVE LIBERAL
DEMOCRAT --
>> WHAT IF HE RUNS AGAINST
BIDEN.
>> BIDEN HASN'T COME INTO THE
RACE YET.
LET'S FINISH.
IF HE RUNS AGAINST A FAR LEFT
PROGRESSIVE PERSON, WHO IS
SUGGESTING 60%, 70% TAX
INCREASES ON THE RICH AND A
HEALTH CARE SYSTEM WE CAN'T PAY
FOR, PRESIDENT TRUMP IS GOING TO
GET RE-ELECTED AND ALL I'M
SAYING IS LET ME GO OUT TO THE
COUNTRY AND LET THE PEOPLE HEAR
MY STORY, I GREW UP IN THE
PROJECTS OF BROOKLYN, I GAVE MY
COMPANY COMPREHENSIVE HEALTH
INSURANCE, EQUITY AND FREE
COLLEGE TUITION FOR EVERY
EMPLOYEE --
>> YOU CAN'T DO THAT WITH THE
COUNTRY.
>> YOU CAN'T.
>> LISTEN, YOU -- WHEN YOU --
BECAUSE THIS IS THE SAME PROBLEM
YOU KNOW WHO HAS.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT -- WHEN YOU OWN
YOUR COMPANY, YOU CAN MAKE THESE
CHANGES AS YOU WANT THEM TO BE.
WHEN YOU HAVE TO REPORT TO THE
SENATE AND THE CONGRESS AND ALL
THE 50 MILLION PEOPLE THAT COME
IN THE MIDDLE, THAT'S A LITTLE
BIT DIFFERENT AND SO, YOU KNOW,
MY BIG PROBLEM IS I WANT PEOPLE
TO STAND UP FOR WHAT THEY
BELIEVE IN AND I THINK YOU
ARE -- YOU'RE SAYING TO PEOPLE,
I DON'T THINK YOU'LL HEAR ME
UNLESS I SPEAK TO YOU AS AN
INDEPENDENT.
I THINK IF YOU BELIEVE IN WHAT
YOU BELIEVE IN THEN STAND UP FOR
THAT AS A DEMOCRAT AND THEN
CHANGE THE PARTY IF YOU FEEL
LIKE THAT AS OPPOSED TO GOING
ELSEWHERE.
THAT'S WHAT I WANTED TO FINISH
WITH.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
CAN I ASK YOU ALL ONE QUESTION?
AND MAYBE EVEN THE AUDIENCE.
DOES ANYONE BELIEVE THE CURRENT
SYSTEM, NOT ONLY THE PRESIDENT,
BUT THE CURRENT POLITICAL SYSTEM
AND OUR GOVERNMENT IS WORKING
WELL ON BEHALF OF THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE?
>> NOT SINCE OBAMA WAS ELECTED,
NO.
>> NO.
>> I THINK JUST IT'S THE BEST
THING WE HAVE.
>> MONEY AND CAMPAIGNS AND MONEY
AND POLITICS AND YOU'RE A
GLARING EXAMPLE AS LONG AS
YOU'RE A BILLIONAIRE YOU CAN RUN
FOR ANYTHING.
MY PROBLEM WITH POLITICS RIGHT
NOW IS THE INFLUENCE OF MONEY
AND NO SHADE TO YOU BUT YOU DO
HAVE TO BE A BILLIONAIRE TO RUN
AS AN INDEPENDENT THAT'S WHY
MICHAEL BLOOMBERG IS AN --
>> YOU CAN'T BUY THE PRESIDENCY.
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE WILL DECIDE.
LET ME MAKE ONE POINT.
CAN I MAKE ONE POINT?
IN THE LAST THREE OR FOUR
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTIONS,
BASICALLY EIGHT BATTLEGROUND
STATES DECIDED THE ELECTION.
THAT'S A FACT.
>> YEAH.
>> NOW, IF AN INDEPENDENT PERSON
WERE TO RUN FOR PRESIDENT AND
GET ON THE BALLOT OF ALL 50
STATES, WHICH IF I DECIDE TO RUN
WE WILL BE ON THE BALLOT OF ALL
50 STATES, FOR THE FIRST TIME --
>> HOW?
>> ALMOST 40 YEARS --
>> I'LL GET THERE.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN ALMOST 40
YEARS EVERY STATE, EVERY
PERSON'S VOTE WILL MATTER.
IT WON'T BE EIGHT STATES, IT'LL
BE A 50-STATE RACE.
>> AS OPPOSED TO THE ELECTORAL
COLLEGE SO A WAY OF
CIRCUMVENTING IT.
>> NO, WE COULD GET TO 270
BECAUSE EVERY STATE WILL MATTER
BUT THE ISSUE THAT --
>> IT DOES MATTER, THAT'S WHY
THE ELECTORAL COLLEGE EXIST.
I LOVE THE PRIMARY.
I LOVE PRIMARY POLITICS.
NO DISRESPECT TO YOU.
YOU JUST WENT ON GWYNETH
PALTROW'S PODCAST.
YOU'RE HERE ON "THE VIEW."
ALL POLITICS SHOULD START LOCAL.
WHY AREN'T YOU IN NEW HAMPSHIRE
OR IOWA RIGHT NOW.
>> WHAT A WANT TO ASK NOW --
>> HE'S SELLING A BOOK.
>> IF YOU'RE RUNNING FOR
PRESIDENT WHICH I BELIEVE YOU
ARE, I STILL BELIEVE -- SORRY,
SUNNY, TO INTERRUPT YOU.
I TRULY BELIEVE IN IT AND I
ACTUALLY THINK THAT LIKE IF YOU
GO TO NEW HAMPSHIRE, WHICH I'VE
DONE AS ABBY, THEY TAKE THEIR
FIRST IN THE NATION SERIOUSLY.
THE IDEA THAT YOU NEGATE THEIR
CHOICE AND I'M NOT GOING TO
CONCEDE THAT.
I STILL AM FINE WITH THE
ELECTORAL COLLEGE.
>> I THINK YOU'RE
MISUNDERSTANDING ME.
WHAT I'M SAYING IF IT'S A
50-STATE RACE, YOU CAN GET TO
270 ELECTORAL COLLEGE APPLIES.
WITH REGARD TO NEW HAMPSHIRE AND
IOWA, WATCH EVERY DEMOCRAT GO TO
THOSE STATES AND HAVE TO BE
DISINGENUOUS AND PROBABLY MAKE A
FALSE PROMISE ABOUT THINGS JUST
TO GET ELECTED.
I WOULD HAVE TO BE DISINGENUOUS
AS A DEMOCRAT IF I RAN AS A
DEMOCRAT BECAUSE IN ORDER TO RUN
AS A DEMOCRAT TODAY YOU HAVE TO
FALL IN LINE WITH FREE MEDICARE
FOR EVERYBODY, FREE, FREE
COLLEGE FOR EVERYBODY, A FREE
JOB FOR EVERYBODY.
LET ME FINISH --
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU SAID --
THAT'S JUST --
>> NOT FREE FOR THE GOVERNMENT.
AND THAT TOTALS $40 TRILLION ON
TOP OF THE FACT THAT WE ARE
SITTING ON A $21 TRILLION DEBT
IN THE COUNTRY TODAY.
WE CAN'T AFFORD TO DO IT FREE SO
IT HAS TO BE A DIFFERENT WAY AND
THE DIFFERENT WAY IS CORPORATE
RESPONSIBILITY HAS TO FALL IN
LINE AND DO MORE FOR THEIR
PEOPLE AND THE COMMUNES WE SERVE
LIKE STARBUCKS DID AND
PHARMACEUTICAL COMPANIES AND
LOBBYISTS THAT HAVE BEEN PAYING
THESE POLITICIANS, DEMOCRATS AND
REPUBLICANS HAVE TO STOP AND CAN
YOU IMAGINE, JUST IMAGINE FOR
ONE MINUTE IF AN INDEPENDENT
PERSON COULD HAVE A MANDATE FROM
THE COUNTRY, FROM THE PEOPLE,
THE FIRST ONE SINCE GEORGE
WASHINGTON TO FINALLY SAY TO THE
SYSTEM AND THE SPECIAL INTERESTS
IT NO LONGER APPLIES THAT AN
INDEPENDENT PERSON CAN BREAK THE
LOGJAM OF THIS TOXICITY THAT
EXISTS IN --
>> HOLD ON ONE SECOND.
WE'RE GOING TO BE TALKING MORE
WITH HOWARD SCHULTZ WHEN WE COME
BACK.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I CAN DO MORE TO LOWER MY A1C.
BECAUSE MY BODY CAN STILL
MAKE ITS OWN INSULIN.
AND I TAKE TRULICITY ONCE A WEEK
TO ACTIVATE MY BODY
TO RELEASE IT,
LIKE IT'S
SUPPOSED TO.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT STARTS ACTING IN MY
BODY FROM THE FIRST DOSE
AND CONTINUES TO WORK
WHEN I NEED IT, 24/7.
TRULICITY IS AN INJECTION
TO IMPROVE BLOOD SUGAR IN
ADULTS WITH TYPE 2 DIABETES
WHEN USED WITH
DIET AND EXERCISE.
DON'T USE IT AS THE FIRST
MEDICINE TO TREAT DIABETES,
OR IF YOU HAVE TYPE 1 DIABETES
OR DIABETIC KETOACIDOSIS.
DON'T TAKE TRULICITY
IF YOU OR YOUR FAMILY
HAVE MEDULLARY THYROID CANCER,
YOU'RE ALLERGIC TO TRULICITY,
OR HAVE MULTIPLE ENDOCRINE
NEOPLASIA SYNDROME TYPE 2.
STOP TRULICITY AND CALL
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE SYMPTOMS OF A
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTION,
A LUMP OR SWELLING IN YOUR NECK,
OR SEVERE STOMACH PAIN.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS MAY
INCLUDE PANCREATITIS.
TAKING TRULICITY WITH A
SULFONYLUREA OR INSULIN
INCREASES YOUR LOW
BLOOD SUGAR RISK.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
NAUSEA, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
ABDOMINAL PAIN, AND
DECREASED APPETITE.
THESE CAN LEAD TO DEHYDRATION,
WHICH MAY WORSEN
KIDNEY PROBLEMS.
I CHOOSE ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY
TO ACTIVATE MY WITHIN.
IF YOU NEED HELP
LOWERING YOUR A1C,
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
60% of women wear
the wrong size pad
and can experience leaks.
You don't have to.
With Always My Fit,
try the next size up
and get up to 20% better
coverage day or night.
Because better coverage
means better protection.
Always
(James)
I can't believe it could take
weeks to get our tax refund.
(Lisa)
At H&R Block, you could get an
Advance Refund up to
$3,000 the day you file.
(James)
We can get a pool table.
(Cori)
Or we can get the car fixed.
(Lisa VO) ♪
Up to $3,000 the day
you file at H&R Block.
Block has your back.
SURPRISE!
(VO) Living with Ammonia odor?
Not a pretty picture.
(VO) Tidy Cats LightWeight
with Ammonia Blocker
tackles tough odor.
Now 100% dust free!
So long Stankface!
(VO) Bye bye dust!
There's a Tidy Cats for that.
Alice loves the smell
of Gain so much,
she wished it came in
a fabric softener too.
[throat clears]
Say hello to your fairy
godmother, Alice.
Oh and look they got Gain scent
beads and dryer sheets too!
Emerge Restored,
Replenished,
Fortified.
Emerge everyday with Emergen-C.
Packed with B vitamins,
Electrolytes, Antioxidants,
Plus more vitamin C than
10 oranges.
Why not feel this good
every day?
Emerge and See.
>>> THANK YOU.
WE ARE BACK WITH HOWARD SCHULTZ.
WE'RE BACK WITH YOU HOWARD.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> I WANT TO CLEAR ONE THING UP
WHEN YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT
CANDIDATES RUNNING, YOU WERE NOT
SAYING THAT KAMALA WAS
DISINGENUOUS OR THE FOLKS THAT
ARE RUNNING ARE DISINGENUOUS.
>> I DON'T AGREE WITH THE
POLICIES SHE STATED BY WIPING
OUT THE INSURANCE INDUSTRY WHICH
WOULD LOSE MILLIONS OF JOBS.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S THE RIGHT
APPROACH.
>> I JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE
THAT EVERYBODY UNDERSTOOD WHAT
HE WAS SAYING.
>> WE'RE JUST WARMING YOU UP FOR
A CAMPAIGN.
BY THE WAY YOUR SON IS ONE OF MY
CLOSEST FRIENDS AND OUR DOGS ARE
COUSINS.
>> YOU HAVE ONE OF MY DOGS.
>> I DO.
ONE OF HIS GOLDEN -- ON
INSTAGRAM.
I WANT TO GET YOUR RESPONSE FROM
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
NO SURPRISE HE TWEETED AT YOU
ONCE YOU DID "60 MINUTES" ON
SUNDAY AND SAID HOWARD SCHULTZ
DOESN'T HAVE THE GUTS TO WATCH
FOR PRESIDENT.
WATCHED HIM ON "60 MINUTES" LAST
NIGHT AND I AGREE WITH HIM THAT
HE IS NOT THE SMARTEST PERSON.
BESIDES AMERICA ALREADY HAS
THAT.
I ONLY HOPE THAT STARBUCKS IS
STILL PAYING ME THEIR RENT IN
TRUMP TOWER.
HOW DO YOU RESPOND AND IF IT IS
YOU VERSUS --
>> HE HASN'T HEARD OF THE
EMOLUMENTS CLAUSE.
>> HOW ARE YOU SUCCESSFUL
AGAINST THAT?
>> I AM NOT RESPONDING TO THAT
CHILDISH BEHAVIOR.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> GOOD.
CLEARLY THE SMARTEST GUY IN THE
ROOM GOT US INTO A BIG BILLION
DOLLAR -- WHAT DID IT COST THE
SHUTDOWN.
>> 11 BILLION.
THAT'S WHAT THE SMARTEST GUY IN
THE ROOM GOT YOU.
>> NO ONE WANTS TO SEE HIM FIRED
MORE THAN ME.
>> AND NO ONE WANTS TO SEE YOU
RUN MORE THAN HIM.
>> YEP.
>> WELL, I THINK -- WE'LL SEE
ABOUT THAT.
I THINK THERE ARE LIFELONG
DEMOCRATS AND LIFELONG
REPUBLICANS WHO I BELIEVE ARE
LOOKING FOR A HOME AND PERHAPS
AFTER THE NEXT FEW MONTHS I CAN
PROVIDE THEM ONE.
>> ALL I KNOW IS RALPH NADER,
ROSS PEROT, THEY DESTROYED -- I
HAVE TO ASK YOU ANOTHER
QUESTION.
YEAH, SO THIS IS ABOUT YOUR BOOK
REALLY.
I KNOW THAT YOU GREW UP IN THE
PROJECTS IN BROOKLYN.
>> YES.
>> AND YOU REALLY FROM THE
GROUND UP AS YOU SAY, YOU CAME
FROM AN ABUSIVE FAMILY.
YOUR FATHER WAS ABUSIVE TO YOU.
YOUR MOTHER WAS IN A DEPRESSION
AND YET MY FRIEND ALDA ALDA SAYS
SOME KIDS CAN SURVIVE THAT
BECAUSE THEY HAVE SOME
TEMPERAMENT OR SOME CHEMISTRY,
SOMETHING ABOUT THEM THEY JUST
CAN DO IT.
IS THAT -- HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN
THAT?
>> I THINK MY WHOLE LIFE I'VE
BEEN TRYING TO MAKE MY PARENTS
PROUD.
UNFORTUNATELY BOTH MY PARENTS
DID NOT SEE MY SUCCESS.
EVERYTHING I TRIED TO DO AT
STARBUCKS IS ABOUT DIGNITY OF
WORK, MY FATHER DIDN'T
APPRECIATE THAT AS A LABORER AND
EVERY POLICY WE PUT IN STARBUCKS
WAS IN A WAY TO TRY AND MAKE
THINGS RIGHT FOR MY FAMILY AND A
LITTLE BIT OF FEAR OF FAILURE,
YOU KNOW.
JEWISH KID FROM BROOKLYN, YOU
CAN RELATE TO THAT.
>> I'M ITALIAN BUT SICILIAN.
>> ME, AND, YES, I CAN.
>> I'M A FAN.
I WATCHED YOU WITH OPRAH ON
SUPER SOUL SUNDAY AND I'M A KID
FROM THE PROJECTS AND ALWAYS
WANT TO MAKE MY FAMILY PROUD AND
I THINK YOU'VE BEEN SUCH AN
ETHICAL BUSINESSMAN GIVING YOUR
EMPLOYEES HEALTH CARE AND I LOVE
YOUR STORY.
BECAUSE YOU WORKED HARD FROM THE
GROUND UP AS JOY MENTIONED.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I WOULD NEVER COMPARE YOU TO
DONALD TRUMP AS A BUSINESS
PERSON.
HOWEVER, I SAID THIS ON THE
SHOW.
YOU HAVE NO POLITICAL EXPERIENCE
AND WE HAVE A BUSINESS PERSON
NOT LIKE YOU IN THE WHITE HOUSE
AND WE SEE WHAT THAT HAS DONE.
WHY NOT TAKE BABY STEPS, WHICH
IS NOT YOUR WAY CLEARLY.
BUT RUN FOR MAYOR.
RUN FOR GOVERNOR.
THE SENATE, CONGRESS.
GET SOME OTHER POLITICAL
EXPERIENCE AND THEN RUN FOR THE
WHITE HOUSE.
>> YEAH, WELL, I THINK -- I
RESPECT THE QUESTION BUT I THINK
THE WORD I WOULD THROW INTO THAT
MIX IS WHAT WE HAVE IS A VOID OF
LEADERSHIP, A VOID OF TRUST.
NO DIGNITY, NO HONOR, NO RESPECT
IN THE OVAL OFFICE AND IN
GOVERNMENT TODAY.
AND WHAT I THINK I CAN BRING IS
A LEVEL OF SERVANT LEADERSHIP
THAT I HAVE ACQUIRED OVER ALMOST
40 YEARS AND WHAT I'VE LEARNED
ALONG THE WAY AND THAT IS
SHARING SUCCESS WITH PEOPLE,
BRINGING PEOPLE ALONG WITH ME.
WE'VE BUILT A GLOBAL BUSINESS IN
77 COUNTRIES, IT'S NOT THE
SUCCESS I'VE AND ENJOYED AT
STARBUCKS BUT THE LEADERSHIP AND
UNDERSTANDING ALL DIFFERENT
KINDS OF PEOPLE.
HAVING GOVERNMENT EXPERIENCE I
THINK IS NOT A DISQUALIFIER.
I THINK WHAT THE QUALIFIER IS,
CAN YOU BRING THE COUNTRY
TOGETHER?
DID YOU LEAD PEOPLE?
AND I THINK CAN WE RESTORE A
SENSE OF VALUES AND COMPASSION
AND EMPATHY BACK INTO THE
AMERICAN SPIRIT AND OUR STANDING
IN THE WORLD.
THAT'S WHAT I BELIEVE I CAN.
>> THERE'S A CULTURE WAR.
DID YOU SUPPORT BRETT KAVANAUGH?
>> I WOULD HAVE NOT.
>> WHAT TYPE OF PERSON WOULD YOU
PUT ON THE SUPREME COURT.
>> SOMEBODY WHO HAS --
PARDON?
I'M A PRO-CHOICE PERSON.
>> THESE ARE CULTURE -- LIKE YOU
ALREADY LOST ME.
I'M PRO-LIFE.
>> I SHOULDN'T LOSE YOU.
>> WE SHOULD BE ABLE -- THIS IS
THE PROBLEM.
I MEAN, WE SHOULD BE ABLE TO
DISAGREE ON THOSE KINDS OF
ISSUES AND YET COME TOGETHER ON
WHAT'S MOST IMPORTANT FOR THE
COUNTRY.
AND WHAT'S --
>> BEING CONSERVATIVE AND MY
CONSERVATIVE PRO-LIFE VALUES ARE
VERY IMPORTANT TO ME AND YOU'RE
TRYING TO WIN OVER A LOT OF
REPUBLICANS AND THERE ARE JUST
SOME ISSUES WE WON'T MEET ON THE
MIDDLE ON.
WHY IT'S BEEN A TWO-PARTY SYSTEM
SINCE 1865 SINCE THE WIGS.
IF YOU CAN LIVE WITH THE
HYPOTHETICAL SITUATION YOU GET
TRUMP EE ELECTED THAT'S FINE BUT
NO ONE SEEMS TERRIBLY CONVINCED
THIS IS A POSSIBLE --
>> YOU'RE PUTTING WORDS IN MY
MOUTH.
I WON'T LIVE WITH PRESIDENT
TRUMP BEING RE-ELECTED BECAUSE
THAT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN AND
I'M GOING TO DO EVERYTHING I
CAN --
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> HOWARD, HOWARD, WHAT'S
ULTIMATELY GOING TO MAKE YOUR
DECISION?
>> CAN I JUST SAY ONE THING REAL
QUICK?
>> OKAY.
>> I THINK THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING FACING THE COUNTRY IS NOT
THE ISSUE OF ABORTION OR THE
CULTURAL ISSUES THAT DIVIDE US.
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING FACING
THE COUNTRY RIGHT NOW IS
ANSWERING THE QUESTION IN THE
AFFIRMATIVE AND THAT IS DO WE
BELIEVE THAT OUR CHILDREN AND
OUR GRANDCHILDREN ARE GOING TO
HAVE A BETTER LIFE THAN WE DO
AND MOST AMERICANS BELIEVE THAT
IS NOT THE CASE AND THAT IS --
THAT IS UNACCEPTABLE TO ME.
SO I WANT TO DO EVERYTHING I CAN
TO RESTORE A SENSE OF FINANCIAL
SECURITY AND A REAL BELIEF IN
THE PROMISE OF THE COUNTRY.
>> YOU'D BE GREAT IN THE
CABINET.
>> NO, BUT --
>> HOWARD, YOUR PROCEEDS ARE
GOING WHERE?
>> WHEN I GREW UP IN CANARSIE,
WE HAD BOOK MOBILES SO THEY'RE
GOING TO BOOK MOBILES IN
IMPOVERISHED NEIGHBORHOODS
AROUND BROOKLYN.
>> MAKE SURE YOU ADD AUDIO BOOKS
TO THAT BECAUSE NOT EVERYBODY
CAN --
>> WE'VE DONE THEM.
THANK YOU --
>> THANKS TO HOWARD SCHULTZ,
MEMBERS OF OUR AUDIENCE, YOU
KNOW YOU'RE EACH GOING HOME WITH
A BOOK.
>> THANK YOU.
>> "FROM THE GROUND UP."
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Introducing NEW
Theraflu PowerPods.
The cold and flu
fighting machine.
You put in your machine.
Press the button
and it gets to work.
♪♪
Activating the powerful pain
reliever, fever reducer,
nasal decongestant,
and cough suppressant,
in a warm, soothing liquid.
♪♪
NEW Theraflu PowerPods.
The cold and flu fighting
machine
you put in your machine.
Press. Sip. Relief.
When I created
Knorr Selects,
I looked for real
ingredients for real taste.
Absolutely no artificial
flavors or preservatives.
Knorr Selects
real ingredients for real taste.
Give your eyes some love, honey!
New Age Perfect
Hydra Nutrition Honey Eye Gel
with manuka honey extract
and a cooling rollerball wand
to visibly de-puff
and reduce bags.
Eyes look younger
and refreshed.
New Age Perfect
Hydra Nutrition Honey Eye Gel
from L'Oreal Paris.
Woman:
This is your wake-up call.
If you have moderate to
severe rheumatoid arthritis,
month after month,
the clock is ticking
on irreversible joint damage.
Ongoing pain and stiffness
are signs of joint erosion.
HUMIRA can help stop the clock.
Prescribed for 15 years,
HUMIRA targets and blocks
a source of inflammation
that contributes
to joint pain
and irreversible damage.
VO: HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes
fatal infections
including tuberculosis,
and cancers, including
lymphoma, have happened,
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal
infections are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Woman:
Help stop the clock
on further irreversible
joint damage.
Talk to your rheumatologist.
Right here. Right now.
HUMIRA.
(Alert chime)
Hiyeeeeeee!
Oh! We all just
got new smartphones
at Cricket!
(Alert chime)
Hiyeeeeeee!
!Holaaaaa!
OK, bye-eeeee!
All: Bye-eeeeee!
(Chime)
♪
Oats have a soluble fiber
called beta-glucan,
which can help lower cholesterol
when part of a
heart-healthy diet.
What's more, these oats
have no artificial flavors,
preservatives or added colors.
Now that's something
to celebrate.
From the first loving touch
Everything that touches your
baby should be this comforting
Pampers Swaddlers, the #1 Choice
of Hospitals,
is 2x softer
and wraps your baby in our
most premium protection
So every touch is as comforting
as the first
Pampers
The #1 Choice of Hospitals,
Nurses & Parents
>> Announcer: TOMORROW, CHRIS
CHRISTIE TAKES YOU BEHIND CLOSED
DOORS OF THE POWER STRUGGLE IN
THE WHITE HOUSE.
HIS 15-YEAR FRIENDSHIP WITH
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND WHY HE SAYS
JARED KUSHNER GOT HIM FIRED FROM
TRUMP'S TRANSITION TEAM.
>> THAT'S TOMORROW?
>> YEAH, THAT'S TOMORROW.
>> SEE YOU TOMORROW.
>> SO THANK YOU FOR COMING.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING AND
COMING.
EVERYBODY, TAKE A LITTLE TIME
AND ENJOY "THE VIEW."
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> COMING UP ON ABC7 NEWS AT
NOON.
>> NOW ABC7 NEWS AT NOON.
ON YOUR SIDE.
>>Adrianna: AS WE COME ON THE
AIR AT NOON WE ARE ON WEATHER
ALERT WITH A MIX OF RAIN, SLEET
AND SNOW TARGETING OUR AREA.
HE WEATHER CAUSING BIG
CONCERNS FOR THE EVENING
COMMUTE.
ALREADY, WE ARE ALREADY SEEING
CLOSURES BUT THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT CLOSING TWO HOURS
EARLY AS LONG AS --ALONG WITH A
BUNCH OF SCHOOLS WITH STEVE IS
TRACKING THE LATEST.
>>Steve: AS WE LOOK OUTSIDE
OVERLOOKING REAGAN NATIONAL
AIRPORT, THE CLOUDS ARE WITH
US.
WE ARE DRY, AT LEAST IN THE
DISTRICT AND CLOSE INTO THE
CITY.
ATTEMPTERS WILL ABOVE FREEZING
AT 40 DEGREES WITH TEMPERATURE
WISE WE ARE ALREADY AT THE
FREEZING MARK OVER AT
WINCHESTER, 34 IN HAGERSTOWN
AND AIR IS OFF TO THE WEST OF
US WILL LIKELY SEE THE WINTRY
MIX CHANGEOVER TO ALL SNOW
BEFORE YOU SEE THAT HAPPEN
AROUND THE IMMEDIATE METRO
AREA.
STORM WATCH 7 SATELLITE AND
RADAR IT A LOT IS NOT REACHING
THE GROUND, AT LEAST RIGHT NOW.
OVER THE NEXT COUPLE OF HOURS
PEOPLE LOOK FOR THE RAIN AND
WINTRY MIX TO OVERSPREAD THE
REGION.
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY WILL GO
INTO EFFECT LATER THIS
AFTERNOON THROUGH THE EVENING
HOURS AND IT DOES INCLUDE ALL
THE AREAS SHADED IN PURPLE.
FAIRFAX, PRINCE WILLIAM AND
COMMUNITY SURROUNDING THE
BELTWAY.
BRING YOUR RAINGEAR WITH YOU IN
THE BE ON THE LOOKOUT FOR
SNOWFLAKES.
AS WE MOVE TOWARD LATER THIS
EVENING AND THEN EVERYTHING
FINALLY BEGINS TO CLEAR ON IT.
HERE IS A SNEAK PEEK AT HER
FUTURECAST, 12 NOON WHERE WE
ARE RIGHT NOW.
IT DOES WANT TO SHOW A LITTLE
SNOW ACTIVITY OFF TO THE NORTH
AND WEST OF US.
IN ABOUT THREE HOURS OR SO,
THIS MAP WILL LOOK A LOT
DIFFERENT WITH RAIN, WINTRY MIX
WITH SLEET AND THEN ALL SNOW.
COMING UP WE WILL CHECK IT FOR
YOU HOUR BY HOUR AND BEHIND
THIS WE HAVE A BRUTAL COLD.
THE COOLEST AIR WE HAVE SEEN
AROUND HERE IAN LONG LONG TIME.
IME THAT UP FOR YOU ALSO
COMING UP.>Adrianna: ROAD
CREWS ARE OUT AND READY TO
TACKLE THE SNOW ONCE IT STARTS
FALLING.
THE.TELLS US THAT 1200 TRUCKS
WILL BE ON THE ROAD BY 1:00.
REAL ESTATE HOW WE
DEMONSTRATION SAYS IT'S MORE
THAN 1600 TRUCKS ARE NOW
TREATING ROADS ACROSS THE
STATION.700 ARE IN
MONTGOMERY AND PRINCE GEORGE'S
COUNTY.
THE DISTRICT SAYS MORE THAN 300
TRUCKS ARE ON THE ROAD RIGHT
NOW.
THEY WILL NOT DROP MUCH SALT OR
SAND UNTIL THE RAIN TRANSITIONS
INTO SNOW.
>>> AS HE MENTIONED MANY SCHOOL
DISTRICT ARE CLOSING EARLY
TODAY BECAUSE OF THE BAD
WEATHER.
HERE IS WHAT WE HAVE SO FAR.
ALEXANDRIA, ARLINGTON, FAIRFAX
WERE PRINCE WILLIAM AND PRINCE
GEORGE'S COUNTY SCHOOLS ARE ALL
CLOSING TWO HOURS EARLY.
MONTGOMERY COUNTY SCHOOLS
CLOSING 2 AND A HALF HOURS
EARLY.
THEY ARE ALSO DISMISSING EARLY
BUT THE TIMES VARY BY SCHOOL.
HOPEFULLY, TONIGHT 'S COMMUTE
WILL NOT BE ANYTHING LIKE THE
ONE ON JANUARY 20 OF 2016.
IF YOU REMEMBER IT WAS A SMALL
RUSH HOUR STORM THAT STRUCK
DAYS BEFORE THE BLIZZARD THAT
YEAR.THE ROADS AND MANY HAD
DISSIPATED THEIR CARS AND HAD
TO START WALKING.
SOME DID NOT GET HOME UNTIL
SHORTLY BEFORE SUNRISE THE NEXT
DAY.
IT WAS KNOWN AS KARMA GET IN
2.0 BECAUSE IT WAS SO SIMILAR
TO ANOTHER RUSH HOUR SNOWFALL
THAT HAPPENED BACK IN 2011.
WE ARE NOT THE ONLY ONE FEELING
THE BREATH OF MOTHER NATURE
RIGHT NOW.
CHICAGO'S HIGH TEMPERATURE
TODAY IS SIX DEGREES BUT WITH
WIND CHILLS BETWEEN -15 AND 22.
EXPERTS CALL THIS THE COOLEST
AIR IN A GENERATION.
WE HAVE MORE ON THE ARTICLE
THAT IS THREATENING MILLIONS.
>> THE DEEP FREEZE IS
TIGHTENING ITS GRIP ACROSS THE
CHICAGO LAND AREA.
LOOK BEHIND ME HERE AND HE
MIGHT BE ABLE TO SEE ALL THE
STEAM RISING FROM THE BUILDING
.
JUST ONE SIGN OF HOW COOL IT IS
HERE.
OFFICIALS SAY THIS IS A
DANGEROUS COLD.
YOU CAN PROBABLY HEAR THE
CRACKING BEHIND THEM THE -- AND
IT IS THE ICE.
THE ICE IS GROWING AS IT
FREEZES ALONG THE SHORELINE
HERE.HIS KIND OF COLD IS NO
JOKE AND IT COULD BE THE
COLDEST WEATHER WE HAVE SEEN IN
MORE THAN A DECADE.CHOOLS
ACROSS THE AREA WILL BE CLOSED
AND MANY BUSINESSES SAY THEY
ALSO PLAN TO SHUT DOWN OR HAVE
EMPLOYEES WORK FROM HOME.
OFFICIALS SAY THE BOTTOM LINE
IS, IF YOU DO NOT HAVE TO
ABSOLUTELY BE OUTSIDE IN THIS
KIND OF WEATHER, STAY INSIDE.
>>Adrianna: GOOD MORNING
WASHINGTON'S TEAM WILL BE
STARTED LIVE AT 4:00 A.M.
TOMORROW WITH THE LATEST
WEATHER, CLOSINGS AND ROAD
CONDITIONS TO HELP YOU GET ON
YOUR WAY.
IT MAYBE CALLED UP AND MANY ARE
STILL CHECKING OUT SMITHSONIAN
MUSEUMS IN THE NATIONAL ZOO
AFTER THERE ARE OPEN AFTER THE
END OF THE GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN.
WE DO HAVE TEAM COVERAGE AND
JUNGLES IS AT THE NATIONAL ZOO
BUT WE START AT THE AIR AND
SPACE MUSEUM'S REOPENING EVENT.
>> IT HAS BEEN A LONG 24 DAYS
FOR PEOPLE HERE AT THE
SMITHSONIAN AIR AND SPACE
MUSEUM.
THEY BEEN SHUT DOWN AND CLOSING
THEIR DOORS TO MORE THAN 8000
PEOPLE A DAY.
AS YOU CAN SEE, THE DOORS ARE
NOW BACK OPEN AND THE LINES
STARTED BEFORE THE 10:00 OPEN.
THE DIRECTOR, SOME OF THE
SENIOR STAFF COMING OUT TO
WELCOME GUESTS BACK FOR THE
FIRST TIME.HE UNCERTAINTY,
THEY TELL ME, WAS THE WORST
PART OF THIS AND NOT KNOWING
WHEN THEY WOULD REOPEN.
THERE WAS A SILVER LINING.
THERE WAS A MAJOR CONSTRUCTION
PROJECT AT THE SMITHSONIAN AND
THEY WERE ABLE TO MAKE A LOT OF
PROGRESS ON THAT AS THE MUSEUM
WAS CLOSED.
IT WAS ALREADY FUNDED SO THE
CONSTRUCTION WORKERS WERE
ALLOWED TO WORK AROUND THE
CLOCK.
HE WANTED TO TALK TO THE PEOPLE
WHO FIRST CAME OUT THIS
MORNING.
>> IT IS GREAT TO BE BACK AND I
HOPE IT STAYS OPEN LONGER THAN
THE NEXT TWO OR THREE WEEKS.
>> I WOKE UP THIS MORNING AND
MY SON WANTED TO CHECK OUT THE
MUSEUM AND WE LOVE ROCKETS.
>> WE ARE DOING EXACTLY WHAT WE
ARE SUPPOSED TO BE DOING.
OPEN TO THE PUBLIC ENSURING
AMERICA'S GREATEST ICONIC
ARTIFACTS OF THE PUBLIC.
LOOKS AS YOU CAN SEE, THE
CROWDS CONTINUE TO FILL IN HERE
FOR THE FIRST TIME, AGAIN, IN
24 DAYS BUT THE GOVERNMENT
SHUTDOWN WAS OBSOLETE 35 DAYS
BUT THE MUSEUM WAS ABLE TO STAY
OPEN LATER BECAUSE THEY HAD
SOME MONEY SET AWAY ON THE
SIDE.
THIS HAS BEEN A ROUGH TIME FOR
THE SMITHSONIAN'S AS THEY HAVE
LOST MORE THAN $1 MILLION A DAY
ACROSS ALL OF THE MUSEUMS HERE
IN THE NATION'S CAPITAL.
YOU WANT TO COME OUT AND VISIT
THERE OPEN UNTIL 5:30 P.M.
TONIGHT.
IN THE DISTRICT I AM SAM
SWEENEY WITH ABC7 NEWS.
>> SOME 45,000 VISITORS A DAY
WERE NOT ABLE TO ACCESS THE 90S
FACILITY IN MUSEUMS IN THE
NATIONAL ZOO DURING THE
SHUTDOWN.
THAT CHANGED TODAY AT 8:00 A.M.
SHARP OFFENSES AND DOORS OPENED
AND THE CAM TURNED ON.
>> WE MISS THEM THE EVERYDAY
AND THE ANIMALS GET OLDER.
EACH OF THE PANDAS ENJOYED THE
SNOW FROM WHAT WE HEAR AND IT
WAS HARD NOT TO BE HERE FOR IT.
>> HOW SPECIAL TO BE BACK
TODAY?
>> I WAS THE FIRST ONE THROUGH
THE DOOR SO YES,.
>> MORE THAN 4000 EMPLOYEES
WERE FURLOUGHED AND DID NOT GET
PAYCHECKS FROM THE 45 DAY SHUT
DOWN.
THE SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTION
LOST $1 MILLION A WEEK IN
REVENUE.
THE CAMERAS WERE ALSO HERE
FIRST THING IN THE MORNING.
>> WE WORRY SO MUCH.
>> THE ANIMALS ARE ENJOYING THE
EXTRA ATTENTION TODAY.
WHILE THE SHUTDOWN WAS GOING ON
OUT THERE, AND HERE IT WAS LIFE
AS USUAL.
IN FACT, THE ZOO WELCOMED SOME
NEW ANIMALS.
THREE NEW NORTH AMERICAN RIVER
OTTER PUPS WERE BORN AS WELL AS
THE ARRIVAL OF A NEW MAIL
CHEETAH.
>> ANIMAL CARE, WE WERE ALMOST
AT HUNDRED PERCENT.
ALMOST EVERYONE ON GROUND HAS
SOME THING TO DO WITH THE
ANIMAL CARE AT THE ZOO.
WE DID OUR NORMAL JOBS AND WE
DID IT WITHOUT OUR VISITORS
HERE.
>> DURING THE SHUTDOWN,
BEHAVIORAL RESEARCH CONTINUED
ON ANIMALS LIKE APES AND
ZOOKEEPERS TELL US TODAY THAT
THEY COULD TELL THAT THE
ANIMAL'S BEHAVIOR CHANGED.
THEY WERE HYPERSENSITIVE
BECAUSE OF THE LACK OF
VISITORS.
AT THE NATIONAL ZOO, JOHN
GONZALEZ ABC7 NEWS.
>>Adrianna: JUST IN.
WATERSTONE PLEADING NOT GUILTY
IN THIS A FEDERAL COURT ON
CHARGES BROUGHT BY SPECIAL
COUNSEL ROBERT MUELLER'S
RUSSIAN PROBE.
THE FRONT AND LONGTIME ADVISOR
OF PRESIDENT TRUMP IS ACCUSED
OF LYING, OBSTRUCTION AND
WITNESS TAMPERING.
HIS EIGHT CENTERS ON HIS
ALLEGED EFFORTS TO LEARN WITH
POTENTIALLY DAMAGING EMAILS BY
THE CLINTON CAMPAIGN WOULD BE
RELEASED BY WIKILEAKS.
HE DENIES BUT IF CONVICTED HE
FACES UP TO 20 YEARS IN PRISON.
>>> MEANWHILE FORMER TRUMP
ATTORNEY, MICHAEL COHEN IS
SCHEDULED TO TESTIFY.
THAT IS THE WORD FROM THE
COMMITTEE CHAIRMAN.EMOCRAT
ADAM SHIFT.
HE SAYS HE WILL TESTIFY BEHIND
CLOSED DOORS AND HE WAS
INITIALLY SUPPOSED TO TESTIFY
DURING AN OPEN SESSION BEFORE
THE HOUSE OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE.
HOWEVER, HE CANCELED THE
APPEARANCE CITING THREATS MADE
AGAINST HIS FAMILY.IKE
ACTING ATTORNEY GENERAL MATT
WHITAKER SAYS ROBERT MUELLER'S
RUSSIAN PROBE IS NEARING ITS
COMPLETION.
THIS IS THE FIRST OFFICIAL ON
THE RECORD CONFIRMATION THAT
THE TWO-YEAR PROBE IS COMING TO
AN END.
WHITAKER SAYS HE HAS BEEN FULLY
BRIEFED ON THE INVESTIGATION
AND HE SAYS HE LOOKS FORWARD TO
ROBERT MUELLER DELIVERING THE
FINAL REPORT.
>>> COMING UP NEXT AT NOON.
NEW FOLLOW-UP FROM THE FAILED
CARIBBEAN GETAWAY.
A MUSIC FESTIVAL THAT PROMISED
SO MUCH AND DELIVERED NOTHING.
AND AT THE MODELS AT THE CENTER
OF THE WJLA PROMOTION PHASE
POSSIBLY BEING SUBPOENAED.
MORE ON THE MILLIONS THEY MIGHT
HAVE TO PAY BACK.
PLUS A LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE.
NOTHING COMING DOWN YET BUT WE
ARE BRACING FOR A MIX OF WINTER
WEATHER THAT COULD MAKE THINGS
SLIPPERY FOR YOUR IN COMMUTE.
STEPHEN BACK AFTER THE BREAK.
FIRST A CHECK OF THE ROADS WITH
ERIC SMITH.
>>Eric: GOOD AFTERNOON AND SO
FAR SO GOOD.
WINGS ARE FAIRLY QUIET AROUND
THE MAIN ROADWAYS BUT WE DO
HAVE A SLOWDOWN ON I-66 INSIDE
THE BELTWAY INTO ARLINGTON.
IT IS AN EASTBOUND WORKS IN
BETWEEN FAIRFAX DRIVE AND IT IS
SLOW MOVING MAINTENANCE
VEHICLES FOR POTHOLE REPAIR.
THAT IS WHY THINGS WILL BE
QUITE HEAVY FOR A SHORTER
SEARCH IN THIS WAY TO
ARLINGTON.
YOU EXPECT A SHORT RIDE.
IT IS A RIGHT ON 395 TODAY AND
OVER 14TH STREET BRIDGE THAT
WILL BE A GOOD RIDE.
NORTH AND
>>Adrianna: DEVELOPING RIGHT
NOW.
THE LATEST ON THE FOUR HOUSTON
POLICE OFFICERS THAT WERE ALL
SHOT WHILE TRYING TO SERVE A
WARRANT.
TWO ARE IN CRITICAL BUT STABLE
CONDITION.
ANOTHER IS HOSPITAL IS IN GOOD
CONDITION AND THE OTHER OFFICER
HAS BEEN RELEASED FROM THE
HOSPITAL.
THEY WERE TRYING TO ENTER A
HOME USUALLY WEAR BLACK TAR
HEROIN WAS ALLEGEDLY BEING SOLD
FOR TWO SUSPECTS SHOT THEM AND
THE OFFICERS RETURNED FIRE
KILLING BOTH SUSPECTS.
>> OH MY GOSH.
>> YOU ARE GOOD MAN.
>>Adrianna: TRAPPED AND 34
>> OH MY GOSH.
DEGREE WATER SURROUNDED BY ICE
>>Adrianna: TRAPPED AND 34
ON SUNDAY.
DEGREE WATER SURROUNDED BY ICE
A 33-YEAR-OLD CHICAGO MAN WAS
ON SUNDAY.
RESCUED AFTER TRYING TO SAVE
A 33-YEAR-OLD CHICAGO MAN WAS
HIS NINE MONTH OLD DOG THAT HAD
RESCUED AFTER TRYING TO SAVE
FALLEN INTO THE LAKE.
HIS NINE MONTH OLD DOG THAT HAD
THE DOG RAN FROM ITS OWN AND
FALLEN INTO THE LAKE.
THEN FELL THROUGH THE ICE
THE DOG RAN FROM ITS OWN AND
THERE.
THEN FELL THROUGH THE ICE
THE MAN MANAGED TO GET HIS DOG
THERE.
OUT BUT THEN HE WAS TRAPPED
THE MAN MANAGED TO GET HIS DOG
HIMSELF.
OUT BUT THEN HE WAS TRAPPED
HE CALLED 9-1-1 ALONG WITH A
HIMSELF.
PASSERBY.
HE CALLED 9-1-1 ALONG WITH A
>> WE SAW THE DOG, FOR THE RICH
PASSERBY.
BUT AT THAT POINT, THERE IS A
>> WE SAW THE DOG, FOR THE RICH
DOG WE MUST BE OVER THERE AND I
BUT AT THAT POINT, THERE IS A
THINK THAT IS WHEN HE HEARD US.
DOG WE MUST BE OVER THERE AND I
HE STARTED YELLING TO HELP ME.
THINK THAT IS WHEN HE HEARD US.
>>Adrianna: PUT THE OFFICERS
HE STARTED YELLING TO HELP ME.
THROUGHOUT THE DOG'S LEASH AND
>>Adrianna: PUT THE OFFICERS
HE AND OTHER OFFICERS ANCHORED
THROUGHOUT THE DOG'S LEASH AND
THEMSELVES FORMING A HUMAN
HE AND OTHER OFFICERS ANCHORED
CHAIN AND RESCUED THE MAN.
THEMSELVES FORMING A HUMAN
>> THEY WERE IN THE ELEVATOR
CHAIN AND RESCUED THE MAN.
SINCE FRIDAY.
>> THEY WERE IN THE ELEVATOR
>> THEY WERE IN THE ALBERTSONS
SINCE FRIDAY.
PARTY?
>> THEY WERE IN THE ALBERTSONS
>>Adrianna: THREE WHOLE DAYS
PARTY?
TRAPPED IN A NEW YORK CITY
>>Adrianna: THREE WHOLE DAYS
ELEVATOR WITH NO FOOD OR WATER.
TRAPPED IN A NEW YORK CITY
POLICE SAY 33-YEAR-OLD WOMAN
ELEVATOR WITH NO FOOD OR WATER.
WAS CLEANING ELECTRIC TOWNHOUSE
POLICE SAY 33-YEAR-OLD WOMAN
AND GOT STUCK BETWEEN THE
WAS CLEANING ELECTRIC TOWNHOUSE
SECOND AND THIRD FLOORS ON
AND GOT STUCK BETWEEN THE
FRIDAY.
SECOND AND THIRD FLOORS ON
IT WAS NOT UNTIL YESTERDAY WITH
FRIDAY.
THE HOMEOWNERS RETURNED AND
IT WAS NOT UNTIL YESTERDAY WITH
FOUND HER STILL INSIDE THE
THE HOMEOWNERS RETURNED AND
ELEVATOR.
FOUND HER STILL INSIDE THE
FIREFIGHTERS MANAGED TO OPEN
ELEVATOR.
THE DOOR AND GET HER OUT.
FIREFIGHTERS MANAGED TO OPEN
THE LAST INSPECTION OF THAT
THE DOOR AND GET HER OUT.
BUILDING HAD NO VIOLATIONS.
THE LAST INSPECTION OF THAT
>>> A FEDERAL JUDGE RULED
BUILDING HAD NO VIOLATIONS.
SEVERAL PROMINENT MODELS THAT
>>> A FEDERAL JUDGE RULED
PROMOTED THE FAILED FYRE FEST
SEVERAL PROMINENT MODELS THAT
CAN BE SUBPOENAED.
PROMOTED THE FAILED FYRE FEST
THAT INCLUDES DINNER AND OTHERS
CAN BE SUBPOENAED.
BUT ALL OF THEM WERE PAID BY
THAT INCLUDES DINNER AND OTHERS
BILLY McFARLAND TO PROMOTE THE
BUT ALL OF THEM WERE PAID BY
FESTIVAL WHICH TURNED INTO A
BILLY McFARLAND TO PROMOTE THE
DISASTER AND WAS CANCELED.
FESTIVAL WHICH TURNED INTO A
McFARLAND WAS SENTENCED TO SIX
DISASTER AND WAS CANCELED.
YEARS IN PRISON FOR FRAUD.
McFARLAND WAS SENTENCED TO SIX
FYRE FEST IS BACK IN THE
YEARS IN PRISON FOR FRAUD.
SPOTLIGHT BECAUSE OF DARKNESS
FYRE FEST IS BACK IN THE
DONE BY NETFLIX AND HULU.
SPOTLIGHT BECAUSE OF DARKNESS
>>> NOW TO A CONSUMER ALERT FOR
DONE BY NETFLIX AND HULU.
YOU IPHONE USERS YOU WANT TO
>>> NOW TO A CONSUMER ALERT FOR
HOLD OFF FOR USING BASED ON FOR
YOU IPHONE USERS YOU WANT TO
THE TIME BEING BECAUSE APPLE
HOLD OFF FOR USING BASED ON FOR
DISCOVERED A GLITCH RAISING
THE TIME BEING BECAUSE APPLE
PRIVACY CONCERNS.
DISCOVERED A GLITCH RAISING
MORE NOW FOR MAGGIE RULLI.
PRIVACY CONCERNS.
>> IT IS A CREEPY INVASION OF
MORE NOW FOR MAGGIE RULLI.
PRIVACY THAT MIGHT HAVE BEEN
>> IT IS A CREEPY INVASION OF
GOING ON FOR MONTHS.
PRIVACY THAT MIGHT HAVE BEEN
>> THERE ARE POTENTIALLY
GOING ON FOR MONTHS.
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE AT RISK FOR
>> THERE ARE POTENTIALLY
THIS.
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE AT RISK FOR
>> TURNING YOUR CELL PHONE INTO
THIS.
A HOT MIC. THE MAJOR GLITCH
>> TURNING YOUR CELL PHONE INTO
UNCOVERED LAST NIGHT, LET'S
A HOT MIC. THE MAJOR GLITCH
SOMEONE CALLING YOU ON FACEBOOK
UNCOVERED LAST NIGHT, LET'S
MERELY HEAR THE AUDIO FROM YOUR
SOMEONE CALLING YOU ON FACEBOOK
PHONE BEFORE YOU EVEN HAVE TIME
MERELY HEAR THE AUDIO FROM YOUR
TO ACCEPT OR REJECT AND IN SOME
PHONE BEFORE YOU EVEN HAVE TIME
CASES, EVEN GIVING THEM ACCESS
TO ACCEPT OR REJECT AND IN SOME
TO YOUR PHONE'S CAMERA.
CASES, EVEN GIVING THEM ACCESS
BRAD MULKEY WAS HERE OVERNIGHT
TO YOUR PHONE'S CAMERA.
AND WAS ABLE TO USE THE GLITCH
BRAD MULKEY WAS HERE OVERNIGHT
TO OVERHEAR A COWORKER.
AND WAS ABLE TO USE THE GLITCH
>> I WAS THE ONLY JUST HEARING
TO OVERHEAR A COWORKER.
MY VOICE BUT IS THERE ANYTHING
>> I WAS THE ONLY JUST HEARING
GOING INTO DAVID'S MICROPHONE.
MY VOICE BUT IS THERE ANYTHING
HE HAD NOT EVEN TOUCHED THE
GOING INTO DAVID'S MICROPHONE.
SCREEN YET.
HE HAD NOT EVEN TOUCHED THE
>> IT IS ALL TRACE BACK TO
SCREEN YET.
APPLE STORE .1 OH AS SOFTWARE.
>> IT IS ALL TRACE BACK TO
SOMETHING THAT APPLE HAS NOW
APPLE STORE .1 OH AS SOFTWARE.
DISABLED.
SOMETHING THAT APPLE HAS NOW
IF YOU HAVE UPDATED YOUR PHONE
DISABLED.
IN THE LAST COUPLE OF MONTHS,
IF YOU HAVE UPDATED YOUR PHONE
IT IS VERY LIKELY IT COULD BE
IN THE LAST COUPLE OF MONTHS,
IMPACTED.
IT IS VERY LIKELY IT COULD BE
HERE'S SOMETHING YOU CAN DO.
IMPACTED.
OPEN UP YOUR SETTINGS, GO TO
HERE'S SOMETHING YOU CAN DO.
BASE TIME AND TURN IT OFF.
OPEN UP YOUR SETTINGS, GO TO
>> APPLE PROMISES THERE WILL BE
BASE TIME AND TURN IT OFF.
A LONG-TERM FIX FOR THIS AND
>> APPLE PROMISES THERE WILL BE
THEY SAY THEY ARE AWARE OF THE
A LONG-TERM FIX FOR THIS AND
ISSUE.
THEY SAY THEY ARE AWARE OF THE
THEY HAVE IDENTIFIED A RISK
ISSUE.
THAT THE FIX THAT WILL BE
THEY HAVE IDENTIFIED A RISK
UPDATED.
THAT THE FIX THAT WILL BE
>>Adrianna: HAVE YOU TURNED OFF
UPDATED.
YOUR FACE TIME?
>>Adrianna: HAVE YOU TURNED OFF
I HAVE.
YOUR FACE TIME?
>>Steve: NOT YET.
I HAVE.
>>Adrianna: DO NOT FACETIME ME.
>>Steve: NOT YET.
>>Steve: WINTER WEATHER
>>Adrianna: DO NOT FACETIME ME.
ADVISORY AND FOR THE DISTRICT
>>Steve: WINTER WEATHER
IN ARLINGTON AND ALEXANDRIA,
ADVISORY AND FOR THE DISTRICT
3:00 P.M. THIS AFTERNOON.
IN ARLINGTON AND ALEXANDRIA,
ANYWAY YOU LOOK AT IT, IF YOU
3:00 P.M. THIS AFTERNOON.
ARE GOING TO BE OUT AND ABOUT
ANYWAY YOU LOOK AT IT, IF YOU
AT 2:00 TO 4:00, CONDITIONS
ARE GOING TO BE OUT AND ABOUT
WILL RAPIDLY DETERIORATE.
AT 2:00 TO 4:00, CONDITIONS
THIS OUR LOOKING OVER TOWARD
WILL RAPIDLY DETERIORATE.
THE PENTAGON AND OVER TOWARD
THIS OUR LOOKING OVER TOWARD
THE GONE CITY, NO PROBLEMS AT
THE PENTAGON AND OVER TOWARD
ALL.