[brassy big band music plays]
[♪♪♪]
[sighing]
Well, lookie here.
Didn't expect
to ever clap eyes on you again.
Seems you weren't the only one
who read the message.
Relax, Eddie boy.
We're just a couple old friends
grabbing coffee.
[scoffs] "Old friends."
Though, by the way
you're jittering
like a bag of junebugs,
you already drank too much.
I'm out of the habit.
I'll say.
Figured
you'd turn yellow,
walked away from the group.
I told myself
it was too risky,
being involved
in the organization.
But then you remembered
what you believe in.
[♪♪♪]
So who's our man?
I think he lost his nerve,
didn't show.
Nah...
When a fellow takes time
to reach out the way he did?
He means business.
[♪♪♪]
Look, Mommy.
Homework's done.
And I wrote
Daddy a letter.
Good job!
And quickly, too.
I have my reasons.
Do you now?
Dory down the hall
got a new toy.
You stick face-parts
on a potato
and call it "Mr. Potatohead".
Sounds like
a waste of good food.
Hey.
Ooh. You look smart.
Going someplace?
It's Friday night,
hitting the town.
"Hitting"
where, exactly?
Dennis has a date...
with a girl.
Can it, squirt!
A date?
Well, what's her name?
Miriam Lincoln.
The girl who works
weekends at the bakery?
Yeah.
Oh.
Well...
speaking of dough...
Here's a dollar.
Home by 10:30.
Thanks, Mom.
[smooch]
You sure you don't
want me to stay home
and play with you?
I'll be fine,
sweetheart.
Go on and see Dory.
Can I take a potato?
Please?
Whatcha gonna do
here all alone?
Gonna enjoy
some peace and quiet.
Now scram.
[chuckles softly]
[door opens]
[contented sigh]
[door shuts]
[♪♪♪]
[exhales deeply]
[grunts]
Oh!
[thug grunting,
redhead groaning]
[Millie]: I found all those in
this darling shop.
And then...
there's this,
which I'm not too sure about.
Oh, Millie,
it'll look great on you.
Do you think so?
A whole new you.
Though all this must've
cost a pretty penny.
If I'm gonna
snag a job here,
I'm gonna need
to look the part.
And then...
there's this.
[gasping deeply] Oh...
Oh, she's a beaut.
I'm glad
you think so.
It's yours.
Oh! Oh, Millie, no.
No way can I pull that off.
You also can't keep living
out of your old trunk.
I've got plenty wear in
the clothes I brought with me.
Oh, come on, Jean.
There's a reason
they call this the New World.
It's a chance
to reinvent yourself.
I'm perfectly
satisfied
with the current model,
thank you very much.
Just in case.
[banging on door]
[man]: Edward!
Edward!
Please!
Open up!
If you're looking
for Edward Harcourt,
he hasn't lived here
in over a year.
[man]: I need help.
Please!
Oh! I'll call
the police.
No police!
Edward.
Oh, my God! Oh.
Good Lord.
[♪♪♪]
Sounds like
it was a terrible fright.
It was.
We'd no idea
who the man was,
he just kept
saying your name.
A lanky ginger fellow,
sporting
a great mop of hair.
He was under
the impression
you still
lived in the flat.
Redhead? I've no idea.
[chuckles]
Well, you will
in a minute--
he's in here.
[exhaling deeply]
Or he was.
They must've
taken him somewhere.
Without his gown?
I'll get a locksmith
on that front door.
You can't have riff-raff
staggering in off the street.
No, the man
knew you, Edward.
I don't think so.
You can't just leave.
Why not? He did.
What's he hiding?
My question precisely.
[yawning deeply]
[bangs toolkit down]
Rough night?
We had this fellow
Ginsberg over.
He read from
this long poem of his
while the rest of us
played strip poker
till the heater
caught fire.
What a hoot! [laughs]
Hailey. You're in
a flea-infested rat-trap.
Sarge, it's my home.
And living with those men--
well, it's lowered
your standards
and raised some eyebrows.
You can
do better.
Yeah, and you were never young.
All right.
So how's about
I fix whatever
you called me here for?
Closet door
giving you trouble?
I told Marcus he screwed
the hinges hinky,
but would he listen?
The closet door's
fine, Hailey.
Toaster!
That damn thing burned
my biscuits last week.
Good thing that guy of yours
is off to Vietnam.
I can finally fix things up
around here.
It's not
the toaster.
I'll say.
That your old
cryptogram machine?
It still work?
I was hoping
you could tell me.
I thought
the government
wouldn't let you
do anything with it.
They might now.
I did get the patent.
What are you
thinking?
Market it.
There's a demand for
simple encryption devices--
embassies, businesses,
newspaper cables.
Folks all looking for a way
to whisper their secrets
in plain sight.
I was thinking
we'd do a partnership.
Sarge, she's yours.
And she'll need a lot of work
to be a viable prototype.
But... if it sells?
[sighs deeply]
Could mean income.
For both of us.
[Hailey]:
Maybe I can do better.
Thank you.
His personal effects.
the nurse didn't know
what to do with them.
Cigarettes, wallet, socks.
He left
without his socks?
What on Earth
was he running from?
What I want to know
is what we do with them.
Well, sure as eggs,
my cousin knows how to get
this man's stuff back to him.
Maybe what's in there
can tell us why he came
and bloodied up our doorstep.
You sure you know
how to put this all
back together again?
Yup.
Good.
Sure are using
a lot of oil there.
That's 'cause
the parts are dirty.
Well, then shouldn't
you use soap?
I'll just charge you
parts and labour.
No. No, no,
you're right.
Just do your thing.
It's just that,
next to my babies,
this is the best thing
I ever dreamt up.
Yeah, and if
we're gonna succeed,
the machine needs to be as solid
as the ideas behind it.
[snap]
I think
it's kinda like sausage.
Sausage?
Yeah, like
we made on the farm.
We knew, if folks were
gonna enjoy the end-product...
Oh. They couldn't
see it getting made.
Bingo.
So, how's about I take this baby
of yours back to my place?
Sure.
[Jean]: I'll put the kettle on
and we can get started.
There must be
something in here
that's a way
to identify him.
Millie.
-I say we start with the wallet.
-Millie, look.
[Millie]: Oh, my God.
Whoever our man's
running from...
...Is now after us.
[phone line ringing]
[sighing]
[Jean]: Sorry
to come by like this,
but we didn't know
who else to call.
[Iris]: No, of course.
You were smart to get out fast.
[Hailey]:
They could've come back.
Heck, they still could've
been there.
[Jean]: From what I could see,
nothing was stolen,
which makes it
even more chilling.
Edward still isn't answering.
[Jean]: Well, what,
do we call the police?
That's the one thing
the redhead begged us not to do.
Either he's
into something bad,
or the cops are.
In this town,
it's a toss-up.
This is what the nurses
gave us,
everything we know
of the man.
See if we can
make sense of it all.
There was nothing
in his wallet--
just a couple of
dollars, and this...
Holy doodle.
Looks like
a marijuana cigarette.
Not that I'd know
anything about it.
I don't want
that in here.
Got it, Sarge.
Consider it unloaded.
Yes.
Into the garbage.
[muttering]:
Seems a waste.
[Jean]:
So he knew he was in danger
and decided
to make himself scarce.
[Millie]:
Whoever smashed us up
must've followed
this red-headed mystery man
to our flat.
[Iris]: And then waited
for you to clear out
and ransacked the place.
[♪♪♪]
[Jean]: He didn't want
anyone knowing who he was,
even if he got hurt.
[Iris]:
Especially if he got hurt.
Maybe because
that was no reefer.
[Millie gasping]
Oh, my!
It's like
miniature ticker-tape.
[Hailey]: Except just try
making sense of it.
It's some kind of code.
[Millie]:
And no drugs?
None that you'd smoke.
That's heroin.
[gasps]
I'd say that's...
more than
a hundred grams.
[Hailey]:
Hot damn.
What's that worth?
My guess is...
[sighs] ...maybe $4,000?
That's more
than I make in a year!
I've seen this stuff
hollow out a person,
whole communities.
I hate this stuff
with a passion.
I can flush it right now.
No, we won't.
We won't?
Oh...
Because we can't.
Someone is willing
to beat a man almost to death
in order to get it back.
If we get rid of it,
we could be
sealing his fate.
And ours as well.
So what do we do?
Well... work out
a way to return it.
Otherwise we're signing
the man's death warrant.
How do we know
he wasn't just a dealer,
and got in trouble?
Mommy, what are you doing?
Cadence. To your room.
Now.
I'll be in after
these ladies leave.
[♪♪♪]
[troubled sigh]
[Jean]: Did you know,
when one has illicit drugs
burning a hole
in one's handbag,
it looks like everyone's
giving you the fish-eye?
The bottom
of your handbag, Jean,
is possibly
the safest place on Earth.
[knocking on door]
[Jean]: Well, let's not
test that theory
against a police detective.
Stash it.
[Bryce]: Ladies!
There you are!
Just who I was
looking for.
I'm guessing
you've something to tell me.
You've been shopping?
Oh! [laughs] Yes.
Yes, we've been
buying up the town.
[chuckles] I'll, um...
I'll leave you two to chinwag.
Detective.
Take as long as you like!
She's a funny one.
Oh! Hysterical.
You said we had
something to tell you?
Yeah!
When am I
taking you out again?
[laughing]
Oh! Is that all?
Well, that's
not nothing.
I'll take that
as a yes, then.
A drink on Monday.
I'd suggest one now,
but I fear you'd
get the wrong idea.
I've got a better one.
How about I pick you up
when I finish work?
Very well, then.
But we've got
one problem.
A problem?
I noticed the lock
on that door is broken.
Oh, yes. Oh.
No, we're well aware.
My cousin is,
in fact, the landlord,
and he's going
to fix it.
Well, it
better be soon.
Because you never know
who might just walk
right on in there.
In fact...
why don't I go upstairs
and check on your digs?
If there were
marauding invaders,
we'd have heard
shrieks from above.
[chuckles] Jean doesn't
seem the shrieking type.
You'd be surprised.
[rock music blaring]
What the hell
are you boys doing?
You know you can
turn this thing
into a stereophonic
turntable?
Sure I know that, Ray,
I just don't want to.
My records aren't stereo
and mono increases the decibels
without sacrificing
sound quality.
Cut the gas now!
Get ready for
another Hail-storm.
We're just trying
to make it better.
You want better?
Wash the dishes.
Scrub the toilet.
Pick up your socks!
Or even better?
Pay your damn rent.
You know what
Nietzsche said?
"What doesn't kill us
makes us stronger."
Wrong one.
"Women were
God's second error."
Sure,
but he also said
"Without music,
life would be a mistake."
Yeah, the same goes
for living with you two.
I could do a whole lot better
here, you know.
I want my hi-fi back
the way it was.
You hear me?
-Man...
-Whoa.
[clicking]
You wanna try
my new toy?
I just got
a three-reel set
of the Grand Canyon!
Maybe after
I speak with your mother.
[footsteps]
Cadence, honey,
why don't you take yourself
into the courtyard?
The light's better
out there.
Thank you.
Thank you for making
the trip over.
You said
it was important.
I need to get home
to my family, though.
I don't have much time.
Um, Olivia,
I value your opinion
as a police employee.
[deep breath]
If someone I knew
came across
a quantity of, uh...
illicit drugs...
Like what?
120 grams of heroin?
Oh, dear...
Well, this person
should share the fact--
and the drugs--
with the police, yes?
Hypothetically? Yes.
That's what I thought.
But in this city,
at this time?
I wouldn't dream of it.
Why not?
The new Chief is trying
to stand up to the graft,
but between criminals
on the street
and crooked politicians
at City Hall?
It's a steep
climb.
So who can you trust?
No one.
The patrol division
is swimming with corruption,
and in cahoots
with other divisions.
So this person...
what should
she do?
Iris, you make damn sure
that whatever cop you speak with
is a straight-shooter.
I-It's not me, Olivia.
Of course, it isn't.
And not every cop
is crooked,
but... be careful.
In this town,
that's a toe dipped in trouble.
[♪♪♪]
[Olivia]: She's a sweetheart.
[chuckles]
How old
are yours now?
Four and six.
Oh, that's
a great age.
They still think
their mothers
know everything.
[chuckles]
[knocking at door]
[relieved sigh] Oh...
You've cleaned it up well.
Nothing
quite so motivating
as the spectre
of a detective's visit.
I was afraid Millie
was gonna invite him up
for a tumbler of rum.
[laughs]
-Did you flush the drugs?
-Despite the close call...
...I decided they'd
be more use to us
on this side
of the sewage system.
Heroin does real
damage to our city.
I don't want to just find out
who these men are,
I want to put them in jail.
Good thing we've got
what they're after.
Not only that, looks like
they're expecting us.
[Iris]: "You know the place,
you know the time."
-But we don't.
-Bastards!
That was
my best shade.
The redhead may know
who's behind this.
Well, if Hansel
left a trail...
I'd say
these are the breadcrumbs.
[Iris]: At least we can crack
the ticker tape code.
What are these?
Could they be
phone numbers?
[Iris]: Perhaps...
if the exchange
were enciphered as numbers,
but not in San Francisco.
What about
a reverse cipher?
We could try dialing
them backwards.
Ooh!
[rock music begins blaring]
[♪♪♪]
[power clunk]
[thumps desk]
It was just a fuse.
You're an idiot.
Hey, it's back to mono,
like you wanted.
When two signals
equal in level but uncorrelated
are added together,
the sum of the two is--
I want you to hear me,
loud and clear.
Where's your rent, Murray?
[blows air]
As Karl Marx says,
the interests
of the landlord
are not
those of society.
[Hailey]:
Except I'm society.
I'm damn well interested,
and sick of playing
this song and dance every month.
Hailey.
We're poets.
I don't care
if the goddamn muse
of inspiration's
whispering in your ear.
You're two weeks late.
If you don't have this
by tomorrow...
What? You'll move out?
No, Murray.
You will.
It's my name on the lease,
remember?
And I'm done
living with men.
I'll bet you are.
Murray... don't.
No. I-I wanna know.
What nice, tidy
lady-girl's
gonna wanna
move in here?
They all went
and got married.
But not our little
Hail-Storm, no.
And if you managed
to sucker in
some sweet-faced gal,
well, one up-close look
at who you are...
what you are?
Poor gal'd
run off screaming.
Murray!
Shut up, will you?
[♪♪♪]
[phone line ringing]
[man's voice]: Hello?
Oh, hello, sir.
My name's Jean McBrian.
I'm an acquaintance
of someone who was
recently assaulted--
a tall, lanky
red-headed--
-What are you telling me for?
-[announcement crackles]
I believe you may
know the man.
I've no idea
who you are talking about.
You've got the wrong number.
Please don't call again.
Well, certainly.
But could you just--
-[dial tone buzzing]
-[Jean sighs]
[Jean]: That's the second
friendly Franciscan--
"I've no idea
who you're talking about--"
"You've got the wrong number.
Please don't call again."
It's a word-for-word repeat
of what the first fellow said
on the telephone.
At the Presidio,
when we'd ask
higher-ups for intel,
sometimes, no matter
who we'd asked,
the denial
would be the same.
[Jean]: Same here.
We would get
the exact same response.
We knew that not only
did they know the answers--
[Iris]: But they'd worked out
the exact same way
to cover up the fact.
[Jean]: Well, thank goodness,
that's not all I heard.
What else did he say?
He didn't say anything, but...
in the background,
I could hear,
"End of the line for 59."
59? That-That's
the, uh, Powell-Mason cable car.
I did hear
a screeching of brakes.
Well, that's
the cable car turner
at one end or the other.
So two possibilities,
at either end of the city.
I heard seagulls.
One of the turnarounds
is near the water,
so that's the north end
of the Powell-Mason line.
So we're just gonna show up
at an intersection?
It's all
we have, Millie.
Well, you two try
and give it a shot tomorrow.
I'll tackle that cipher
First... I'm off
for a family reunion.
[♪♪♪]
[bell dings]
[cook]: Order up!
He goes by "Rusty."
Appropriate.
Why not tell us before?
He's a private person.
As am I.
What the hell
was that doing in his wallet?
You would know better
than me, Edward.
You can rest assured
I haven't told a soul.
I went two years
without seeing him, Camilla.
I wouldn't know
how to find him now.
[hushed]: We are sitting on
a hot box of drugs
worth thousands of dollars.
Your friend
is at risk,
and so are we.
[Edward sighs]
It was two years ago...
until two days ago.
This very diner.
We were both...
...sent here
for a rendezvous,
but when the man
we were expecting
failed to show,
I left.
And... he stayed?
I guess, for a while.
To move drugs?
No! It had nothing
to do with that.
I told you
what I know, Camilla.
Stop twisting this
into something else.
Your friend
was found
with drugs on him.
Are you seriously telling me
that that's a coincidence?
He's not my friend.
Now kindly get the hell
out of
my business.
He's half-dead
and running for his life,
and you
are our only link.
Then consider yourself lucky.
[weary sigh]
[♪♪♪]
[brakeman]:
End of the line for 59.
[bell dings]
[♪♪♪]
Well, here we are.
"End of the line
for 59."
The conductor,
the screeching car wheels,
seagulls...
[Iris]: Well, those apartments
look promising.
[Jean]: There's only
so many places
where you could hear
all those noises from.
[Iris, sighing]:
"So many," indeed.
[Jean]: Well, I see
two windows open,
so let's try them.
You think it's
enough to go on?
I've gotten
more from less.
Hmm. Well,
let's get knocking.
[knocking]
Sorry to bother.
We're looking for
someone who may have
come here injured
the other night.
No idea
what you're talking about.
Well, he came
to us for help.
We've got
his belongings here.
Paul!
Just let 'em in.
How did you find me?
Ciphers and seagulls.
We're here about
the night you were beaten,
and a meeting you had
with your friend,
Edward Harcourt.
I wouldn't call Edward
a "friend."
I barely know the guy.
Then why come
banging down his door?
I'd been mugged.
He was the closest
I could think of.
Yet no calling
the police.
What's the point?
Precisely what
we're trying to figure out.
Well, don't.
I don't need your help!
Just walk out and forget me!
There are some
dangerous people after you,
and now they're
after us as well.
Rusty, I'm your friend,
but this is crossing the line.
Do you
recognize these?
Haymakers.
Not my brand.
They were on you the night
you were attacked.
I met up with a man.
Friendly enough.
Offered 'em to me.
Started asking
about drop-offs and payments,
I told him
I had no clue what he meant,
so I walked away.
Only he started following,
asking if I was the right guy.
I told him
it didn't seem I was,
then he started chasing me,
and I'm running for my life,
and I couldn't get free,
and he caught me,
and...
It took everything I had
to get away.
So you never knew
what was in them?
What?
Heroin.
[shaken]: Definitely
not my brand.
Well, it's not
ours, either,
but here we are.
Just throw
the drugs away!
Rusty, someone out there
is after these drugs,
and they'll do anything
to get them back.
Now, who did
you meet with?
[loudly]:
I don't know!
I think it's time
you two left.
Then how did you
arrange the meeting?
I thought it would be
someone else.
I thought it would be a friend.
He's safe now.
We're gonna keep it that way.
Take your junk
and get out.
Now!
Tell Edward...
tell him...
don't go near the papers.
What? "The papers"?
What do you mean by the papers?
[door bangs]
[♪♪♪]
[Jean sighs]
Who fixed the lock?
Yours truly.
Any luck?
I've tried everything
from Gronsfeld
to Playfair,
but nothing cracks it.
How's about you?
You find your man?
We did,
but he's keeping mum.
Though he did leave us
a parting gift.
Told Edward--
"Don't go near
the papers."
Ticker-tape paper?
Cigarette papers?
[Millie]: No idea.
For this code,
I'm inclined
to use lex parsimoniae.
Lex what?
"Law of Parsimony."
According
to William of Ockham,
the hypothesis requiring
the fewest assumptions
should be selected.
If this is street code,
it can't be complex.
Otherwise you wouldn't be
able to write it on one end,
and then read it
on the other.
[Hailey]: So think simple
instead of complicated.
Wrap it.
What are you
talking about?
A possible scytale code.
Try this.
[Iris]: Scytale is a simple
transposition cipher,
used by the ancient Greeks
and Spartans.
It's how military commanders
would communicate
with their front lines
during battle.
[Jean]: First,
a band of parchment
gets wrapped around a rod,
then the message gets written.
[Iris]: And when
the band of paper is unrolled,
it becomes ciphertext.
[Jean]: The trick then
is to have a baton
in the battlefield
that matches the sender's.
[Iris]:
Wrap the parchment right,
and boom,
there's your message.
[Jean]:
This has the advantage
of being fast to make
and not prone to mistakes--
helpful things
when you're at war.
"H"...
A-N-D...
O-F-F...
"Hand-off."
C-E-D-A-R...
M-I-L-L...
"Cedar Mill..."
4-2...
S... U-N...
7... P... M.
"Hand-off--
Cedar Mill 42,
Sun, 7 p.m."
Jean, you're a genius.
We've got it--
a time and a place.
Brava, ladies.
What's 42?
I don't know, but...
but the meeting's tonight.
We really should
call the police.
[Iris]: There's too many
police on the take,
but if we can smoke out
these buyers,
we give them hard facts
that they can't deny--
their names,
their game plan.
Let's go hand off
some drugs.
[Jean]:
You two find the dealer.
We'll keep a lookout.
[Iris]:
Everyone off for the weekend.
Our gents
must've known that.
[Hailey]:
The sheds are numbered.
There's our 42.
That way.
Good luck.
Just keep an eye out.
Come on.
[♪♪♪]
[Hailey]: Hang on.
We're here.
I don't think you ladies
got the right place.
Oh, we do...
and we come
bearing gifts.
Not the kind
I usually pick up from.
Takes all kinds
in this world.
And what's
on offer should be
of no less
interest to you.
[clang]
[man]: That's for sure.
I was staring down hot water
if you didn't show.
How long
has it been?
Oh, it's been
minutes, Iris.
They'll be fine.
Oh, no.
Oh, the guard's headed
toward the girls.
What happens if
he sees them dealing?
Oh, let's not
find out.
Hey! Hello?
Yoo-hoo! Excuse me.
Well, sir...
it's been a pleasure
doing business.
Tell your bosses
to ease up
on the beatings now.
Hey!
Someone tampered
with the goods.
Just a bit
of quality control.
It's all there,
guaranteed.
Back.
[Jean]: Uh, sir!
Can you help us?
Our car.
It broke down.
[Iris]:
Just over there, see?
We thought
we were out of gas,
but, um, we're
not out of gas.
[Iris]:
It could be the starter.
Or the battery.
Or the muffler.
Well, probably
not the muffler.
What're you
ladies doing here?
Well, we took
a wrong turn.
And then another,
looking for help.
For our poor
busted-up car...
And then it just
finally up and died.
Do you know
a thing or two?
[Iris]: Our friends
went looking for help,
but there seems to be
no one around.
[guard]: Okay, I'll have a look.
You know, we can
leave you to this...
You can stay put
until I'm finished
my inventory here.
I got fellows to answer to,
just like you.
[car engine starts]
Oh, it must've just
needed a rest.
And of course,
your expert touch.
Well...
best be on
your way, ladies.
[door bangs]
Uh, sir!
If we could
just get your name,
so we could recommend you,
to your superiors.
Better not.
I got a schedule
to keep.
I'd get in trouble
if they knew I stopped it
to do stuff like this.
Come on, Brutus.
[♪♪♪]
[Brutus barks]
What do ya got there, Brutus?
Huh? What do ya got?
[barks]
Evening, sir.
You with
the broken-down ladies?
Oh, come on.
There's a bit of life
left in them yet.
Charming place
you've got here.
Hope you can
enjoy it.
[♪♪♪]
Come on.
Come on, Brutus.
Drugs are off our hands
and onto theirs.
I'd say that's
the last trouble we'll see--
Rusty and co. as well.
Right. Let's
get out of here.
Well, you
certainly know
how to show a girl
a good time.
[laughing]
You tired already?
This is
more fresh air
than my lungs have
previously encountered.
[chuckles]
That, and I had
a late night.
Oh?
So I've got
competition.
You're not even
on the race-track,
my friend!
[chuckles]
It's my cousin,
Edward.
I'm worried he's got
into some trouble.
Such as?
Oh, come on...
It's not like
I'll go arrest him.
Unless he went
and killed somebody.
Still, it would
compromise you,
and I'm sure
you steer clear of that.
Well, I've got
to admit,
I spend a lot of time
scratching the underbelly
of this fair city.
And if you lie with dogs,
you wake up with fleas.
That's why a walk
like this is nice--
reminds me that there's
more to this city
than its darkest corners.
I'd be tempted to stay
in those dark corners,
to take bribes,
withhold evidence...
[chuckles]
Well, you work
a beat long enough,
anything you need,
eventually, you know a guy
who can get it for you.
And have you ever
needed something?
No.
[♪♪♪]
Oh.
Oh, will you
look at that?
Mm-hmm.
How's this?
"Cozy room available
in a fun, breezy
warehouse space."
A good start.
What do you
mean "start"?
That's my tenth
kick at the can.
Hailey, it's great
that you're looking
for better roommates,
but when you write "fun,"
a girl will read that
as another word for "noisy."
And, uh, "cozy,"
she'll think "small."
"Breezy..."
Sounds like a hurricane
comes through every night.
-Mm.
-I got it--
Oh...
Plus, the papers
will charge a buck
for that magnum opus.
Abbreviate.
"The papers..."
That's what this guy, Edward,
wasn't supposed go near.
Maybe it's got
nothing to do
with cigarette papers.
Want me to phone
it in for you?
Sarge.
Maybe it's newspapers.
As in
"Don't do anything
that'll get you written
about in the news"?
Or "don't go putting
anything in there yourself."
But what do I know?
Bottom to top?
How do you
read that way?
I'm not reading.
I'm detecting anomaly,
which the eye does faster
when the mind isn't trying
to make sense of the words.
"Think less,
do more." Huh.
There.
Look.
A cipher.
This may get us
closer to those dealers.
[♪♪♪]
Cracked it.
Didn't take long.
Well, it's just
a simple Caesar cipher--
every letter transposed
three letters ahead--
"A" is "D,"
"B" is "E."
Smart.
Gaius Julius thought so.
It's one of the oldest
ciphers in history,
simple enough for
the average person to use.
What's it say?
The tough part
is the abbreviations,
but essentially,
it's a warning--
telling
"all able men"
to beware
of someone else's messages
in the "Help Wanted" section.
To "Stay out
of the papers,"
or else.
Jean! Jean?
Millie!
Oh, God.
What happened?
Who would do this to him?
It doesn't
make sense.
We delivered
the package
to the men
who wanted it.
That was not
what they were after.
We haven't stopped
the beatings.
There's another reason
for these attacks.
[Jean]: And one
we've seen before...
[Edward takes a deeper breath]
Tell me
you're not Saint Peter.
That'd be
your lucky day.
I'd let anyone through
those pearly gates.
[weak chuckle]
[sighs] Last
thing I remember,
I was locking
my front door
on the way
to the bank.
You were found
beaten up in an alley.
Just like Rusty.
It was a mugging.
Welcome to America.
Oh, come on,
Edward.
I don't care
what you're up to,
but if we don't know
why these attacks
are taking place,
we can't stop them.
If you won't talk to me,
please talk
to the police.
Oh, Camilla,
for God's sake...
There's a detective
outside,
he's a good man.
Except in
the eyes of the law,
I'm also breaking one.
And what
have you done?
It's not
what I've done.
It's who I am.
You've no idea
why I left home.
I believe I do.
"The heart
is a lonely hunter,"
as the book puts it.
You came here to be
the man you need to be.
I understand.
[sighs] You don't.
You may have once
ran off with a man...
but at least...
he was a man.
They weren't all men.
Really, the only
difference is
when it comes
to the hunt,
I enjoy it.
[both chuckling quietly]
[Iris]: There's
a whole series of them--
encrypted messages in the, uh,
"help wanted" section
of the newspaper.
Folks talking
to each other,
right under our noses.
Sounds like a latter-day
agony column.
What's an agony column?
Oh, they've been around
since Victorian times.
Secret messages encrypted
in the classifieds,
so to arrange
a rendezvous.
For people too afraid
to pick up the phone
or write a letter.
Yes. Only...
This time, I think
it's a for group of men,
to... connect.
How would you know this?
[Jean]: I worked for a man
who kept me on
for a few years after the war.
A brilliant cryptographer.
He'd cracked the Enigma code,
invented computing devices...
and...
and he loved men.
Here, that's a crime.
Well, yes, it is
back in Britain, too.
Like the codes he cracked,
he was hidden in plain sight,
until the police found out.
He'd called them
because he'd been robbed
by one of his, um,
visiting gentleman.
When the world saw him
for what he was...
...they destroyed him.
So you think our men are like
this man that you worked for?
Mm.
And they feel
that they're in danger--
and clearly, with good reason.
Edward Harcourt,
meet Detective Bryce.
I can see why
you chose him.
Because he's
a fine investigator--
Mr. Harcourt.
I hear you may have
a thing or two
to tell me.
I'll take my leave.
Gentlemen.
As I told Camilla,
I've no recollection--
I'm not interested
in today.
It's the weeks before
I wanna know about.
I understand
there are some bad people
you'd like to catch...
But if you don't,
and I've shared the truth
about myself...
I still have to pay the price.
In the eyes of the law,
I'm a criminal, too,
as bad as the man who beat me.
Well, I doubt he's as clever
and good.
Detective,
you're muddying waters.
And flirting.
That's not cricket.
Whatever you tell me,
I will take it
to the right people.
You will see justice done.
I sure hope so.
[knocking at door]
Good morning, Sarge.
Oh, it's a quiet morning here,
for once.
[Hailey]: The boys are off
to some coffee shop.
I tell you, next
to hearing themselves squawk,
the next best thing
is listening to someone else.
Don't worry, Sarge.
I know how to put it
back together again.
Good.
Oh, I went by the newspaper
offices this morning
and picked up what's come up
on your "for rent" listing.
Already?
Oh, I wrote you a good ad.
Oh, this is
gonna be good.
Just think...
one of these gals could
end up living here.
So be careful
who you let in.
Look at this one--
"loves to converse."
Uh, that means
"insufferably opinionated."
Or this one...
"easy-going."
That means
"slovenly as hell."
I wonder
what I'd put down
if I had
to describe myself.
You know... my code.
You don't need one.
What else
you got there?
Um... likes to cook--
-Oh!
-...Crochet--
Mm-hmm.
That's good. I don't
know how to cook very well.
[Edward]: Ladies, you don't
have to do this.
[Millie]:
Just a few days.
Just to have someone
to change your dressings
and feed you,
you know, soup.
Tell me, Jean,
when was the last time
my cousin made soup?
I picked up a ham hock
this morning.
I'll have pea soup
on the go in no time.
More coppers?
What do you mean "more"?
What kind of tenants
have I been renting to?
Edward Harcourt?
Yes?
You're under arrest
for suspicion
of communist conspiracy.
Don't be
ridiculous.
Officer,
I'm no communist.
The charges can be
explained at the station.
This is rubbish.
My cousin has just come
back from hospital,
and he is not
going anywhere.
You'll keep
your distance, ma'am.
He's coming with me.
I would like
to see you try.
Millie!
I'll be fine.
Now, you listen to me.
You know,
that's a great idea.
Why don't we do that
down at the station?
You two are coming with me.
She's got nothing
to do with this!
She does now.
You know who this is down to,
don't you?
Bill Bryce.
I trusted that bastard
and he betrayed us.
[door slams]
ANNOUNCER: FOR ALMOST
40 YEARS,
DUMBARTON UNITED
METHODIST CHURCH
HAS HOSTED THE DUMBARTON
CONCERT SERIES.
WOMAN: WE'RE LOCATED
IN GEORGETOWN,
IN WASHINGTON, D.C.
NEAR THE EMBASSIES,
NEAR THE UNIVERSITIES.
AND, UM, IT REALLY BECOMES
A MELTING POT FOR CULTURE.
ANNOUNCER: DUMBARTON
CONCERTS SHINE A LIGHT
ON WORLD-CLASS MUSICIANS
AND EMERGING ARTISTS ALIKE.
WOMAN: WE LOOK FOR
OPPORTUNITIES TO PRESENT
PEOPLE INTERNATIONALLY
WHO HAPPEN TO BE IN THE AREA.
WE ALSO PRESENT
SOME LOCAL MUSICIANS,
BUT REALLY ALWAYS HAVE
NATIONAL AND INTERNATIONALLY
EXCELLENT ARTISTS.
[SINGING SLOW TUNE]
MAN: I HAVE BEEN PERFORMING
AT DUMBARTON CONCERTS
PROBABLY FOR ABOUT 15 YEARS.
ANNOUNCER: EDGAR ALLEN POE'S
HAUNTING POEM "THE RAVEN"
INSPIRED NICHOLAS WHITE
TO COMPOSE AN 8-PART CANTATA,
MUSIC FOR VOICE WITH
INSTRUMENTAL ACCOMPANIMENT.
WHITE:
"THE RAVEN" WAS COMMISSIONED
BY DUMBARTON CONCERTS IN 2011
AND PERFORMED HERE FOR THE FIRST
TIME IN FEBRUARY OF 2013.
AND THIS WEEKEND WILL MARK
THE SECOND PERFORMANCE
OF "THE RAVEN"
HERE AT DUMBARTON CONCERTS.
ANNOUNCER: CANDLELIGHT AND
PRISTINE ACOUSTICS MAKE FOR
AN INTIMATE SETTING.
WOMAN: THIS CHURCH
DATES TO THE 1880s.
THERE'S A GRANDNESS
TO THE SANCTUARY,
ALONG WITH THE GREAT
ACOUSTIC, THERE'S A SENSE
OF BEING TOGETHER.
WHITE: THIS IS
A VERY SPECIAL SPACE.
YES. IT'S--IT'S WONDERFUL
FOR CHAMBER MUSIC.
[WOMAN SINGING]
I LOVE COMING BACK TO D.C.
IT'S A CITY THAT HAS
SUCH GREAT HISTORY,
SUCH A WONDERFUL ARTS SCENE,
AND SPECIFICALLY
A CHORAL MUSIC SCENE.
SO I THINK I FEEL VERY DRAWN
TO THIS PLACE.
[SINGING]
IT'S ALWAYS MY GOAL AS A
COMPOSER TO ENHANCE THE WORDS,
AND THIS IS A WONDERFUL SET OF
WORDS TO BE GIVEN AS A PALETTE.
I HOPE THAT WHAT THE
AUDIENCES REALIZE IS
HOW MUCH MUSIC CAN GIVE.
[SINGING]
IT GIVES YOU COMMUNITY,
IT GIVES YOU TRANSCENDENCE.
IT GIVES YOU BEAUTY
IN YOUR LIFE.
A CONCERT CAN JUST
FILL YOUR HEART.
[APPLAUSE]
WOMAN: CHRISTIAN HEURICH
WAS A GERMAN IMMIGRANT.
HE EMIGRATED TO
THE UNITED STATES IN 1866.
HE SETTLED HERE IN
WASHINGTON, D.C.
AND ESTABLISHED THE CHRISTIAN
HEURICH BREWERY IN 1873.
AND HE QUICKLY BECAME ONE OF
THE LARGEST BREWERY OWNERS
IN WASHINGTON, D.C.
CHRISTIAN ACQUIRED THE
PROPERTY FOR THIS HOUSE
IN THE EARLY 1870s,
AND IT WAS SOON AFTER THAT
THAT DUPONT CIRCLE
REALLY BECAME THE FASHIONABLE
NEIGHBORHOOD FOR THE WEALTHY
AND THE POWERFUL.
THE HEURICHS, WHEN THEY
DESIGNED THE HOUSE,
REALLY HAD THE INTENTION
OF BUILDING IT TO LOOK LIKE
A GERMAN CASTLE.
WHEN HE BUILT HIS MANSION HERE
IN THE EARLY 1890s,
HE MADE SURE TO INCLUDE
HIS OWN GERMAN-STYLE TAVERN
IN HIS BASEMENT.
[OOM-PA MUSIC PLAYING]
THE ROOM IS DECORATED
WITH GERMAN MURALS
THAT ALL DEPICT THESE FUNNY
DRINKING PHRASES.
AND THEY SAY THINGS LIKE,
"A GOOD DRINK MAKES
THE OLD YOUNG"
OR, UM, "A HAPPY GUEST
IS NO ONE'S BURDEN."
TONIGHT AT THE HEURICH HOUSE,
WE'LL BE HOSTING OUR MONTHLY
EVENT CALLED HISTORY & HOPS,
WHERE WE PARTNER WITH LOCAL
CRAFT BREWERIES FROM D.C.,
MARYLAND, AND VIRGINIA.
VISITORS CAN COME IN
AND TALK WITH THE BREWERS,
TASTE THE BEERS,
AND THEN WE ALSO DO HOUSE TOURS
THROUGHOUT THE EVENING
AND TALK MORE ABOUT THE HEURICH
BREWERY HISTORY.
JEROME: WHEN THE HOUSE
WAS CONSTRUCTED,
IT WAS THE FIRST
FIREPROOF RESIDENCE
IN WASHINGTON, D.C.
YOU'RE WALKING UNDERNEATH
THE MUSICIAN'S BALCONY.
TONIGHT'S HISTORY & HOPS
FEATURES BLUE MOUNTAIN BREWERY
FROM AFTON, VIRGINIA.
IF YOU'VE EVER BEEN
TO THE BREWERY, WE ACTUALLY
HAVE 2 BREWERIES.
WE HAVE ONE RIGHT OUTSIDE
CHARLOTTESVILLE
IN AFTON, VIRGINIA,
UM, WITH OUR BREW PUB
AND WE HAVE A BIG
RESTAURANT THERE.
WE ALWAYS HAVE 10 BEERS ON TAP.
WE BROUGHT, UM, KOELSCH,
WHICH IS PROBABLY OUR
LIGHTEST BEER,
EASY-DRINKING--GERMAN HOPS,
GERMAN MALTS.
AND WE ALSO BROUGHT
OUR DOUBLE IPA,
WHICH IS OUR--OUR REAL BIG
HOPPY PALE ALE.
UM, WE USE ALL-AMERICAN
HOPS IN IT.
[BEER FLOWING]
AND THEN THE LAST ONE HERE
IS LOCAL SPECIES,
WHICH, UM, WAS
A BRONZE MEDAL WINNER
AT THE GREAT AMERICAN
BEER FESTIVAL A COUPLE
YEARS AGO IN DENVER.
JEROME: HISTORY & HOPS
IS A REALLY GREAT WAY
TO COME AND VISIT
THE HEURICH HOUSE.
YOU GET TO COME AND VISIT
THE HOUSE, DRINK BEER,
EAT FOOD, LISTEN TO MUSIC
IN THE HOUSE,
UM, AND IT REALLY IS
A DIFFERENT EXPERIENCE THAN
COMING FOR A PUBLIC TOUR.
ANNOUNCER: WASHINGTON'S
OLDEST COMMERCIAL DISTRICT,
KNOWN AS BARRACKS ROW,
IS TUCKED AWAY IN THE SOUTHERN
HALF OF CAPITOL HILL
NEAR EASTERN MARKET.
A SHORT ALLEYWAY OFF 8th STREET
LEADS DIRECTLY TO THE FRIDGE,
A UNIQUE ART GALLERY
THAT OPENED IN 2009.
MAN: THE FRIDGE IS MY BABY.
IT'S MY LIFE'S WORK.
IT IS AN ART SPACE
THAT I FOUNDED
TO REALLY HELP UNCOVER
YOUNGER ARTISTS--
ARTISTS WHO HAVE NOT NECESSARILY
EXHIBITED OTHER PLACES.
ANNOUNCER: THE FRIDGE IS
DEDICATED TO SHOWING THE WORK
OF STREET ARTISTS,
INCLUDING GRAFFITI
AND STICKER ARTISTS.
GOLDSTEIN: A LOT OF THE ARTISTS
THAT I'VE WORKED WITH
HAVE DONE WORK
OUT ON THE STREET,
MEANING LEGALLY
OR ILLEGALLY,
AS GRAFFITI ARTISTS
OR OTHER TYPES OF VANDALS
AND TAGGERS EVEN
WHO--WHO HAVE DEVELOPED
INTO INDOOR ARTISTS.
ANNOUNCER: IN ADDITION TO BEING
THE GALLERY'S OWNER,
ALEX GOLDSTEIN IS ALSO
AN ARTIST HIMSELF.
HE RECENTLY COMPLETED
HIS SECOND SOLO SHOW
AT THE FRIDGE,
WHICH FEATURED IMAGES
OF JOHN LENNON SPRAY-PAINTED
ON THE BACKS OF STREET SIGNS.
GOLDSTEIN: I'VE HAD THE BAD
HABIT OF PAINTING ON THE
BACKS OF STREET SIGNS
FOR MANY, MANY DECADES.
EVERYTHING IN MODERATION,
INCLUDING MODERATION.
SO, FOR THIS SHOW,
I DECIDED TO BRING THE
STREET INTO THE GALLERY.
ANNOUNCER: THE SHOW ALSO
GAVE HIM THE OPPORTUNITY
TO SHOWCASE WORK
BY HIS LATE FATHER.
GOLDSTEIN: MY DAD WAS A SCULPTOR
FOR A PERIOD OF HIS LIFE,
AND I'M GONNA BE DISPLAYING FOR
THE FIRST TIME EVER IN PUBLIC
SOME SCULPTURES THAT HE MADE.
AND SO THAT'S KIND OF,
I THINK, A TRIBUTE TO HIM
AND MY MOM, TOO.
STREET ART, YOU KNOW,
WHEN I WAS YOUNGER,
WASN'T CALLED THAT.
IT WAS JUST VANDALISM.
A LOT OF ARTISTS WERE PUTTING
UP ARTWORK ON THE STREET
AS A WAY TO GET IT SHOWN,
JUST TO SHOW TO EACH OTHER.
NOW THE BUILDING DEVELOPERS
HAVE BOUGHT ALL THOSE
BUILDINGS IN D.C.,
AND THEY ACTUALLY HIRE US-TYPE
STREET ARTISTS
TO ACTUALLY COME IN
AND DECORATE THE NEW PROPERTY,
WHICH IS REALLY AN
INTERESTING EVOLUTION.
I LIKE SEEING GRAFFITI.
IT'S A SIGN OF LIFE.
IT'S A SIGN OF PEOPLE TAKING
OWNERSHIP OF THEIR OWN SPACE.
AND WHILE I'M A BUILDING OWNER
AND I'D BE MAD
IF SOMEONE TAGGED
THE FRONT OF MY BUILDING--
WHATEVER. I CAN JUST
PAINT OVER IT
AND KNOW, ULTIMATELY,
IT'S NOT REALLY HARMFUL.
ANNOUNCER: THE FRIDGE IS OPEN
THURSDAY THROUGH SUNDAY
AND IS FREE TO THE PUBLIC.
ANNOUNCER: CRUMBS & WHISKERS
OPENED IN JUNE 2015
AS WASHINGTON D.C.'S
FIRST CAT CAFE.
IT'S A PLACE
WHERE YOU COME IN
AND YOU CAN HANG OUT WITH
ABOUT 20 ADOPTABLE CATS
AND ALSO GET COFFEE, TEA,
CAKES, THINGS LIKE THAT.
I THINK GEORGETOWN IS A GREAT
PLACE FOR A CAT CAFE
BECAUSE IT KIND OF HAS
THE SAME PERSONALITY THAT
A CAT CAFE WOULD HAVE,
WHICH IS QUIRKY AND ECLECTIC
AND ALSO A DESTINATION.
MAN: WE DO HAVE SOME CUSTOMERS
THAT COME FROM OUT OF STATE.
WE'VE HAD PEOPLE FROM DALLAS,
FROM MASSACHUSETTS,
FROM KENTUCKY,
UM, ALL OVER.
ANNOUNCER: CRUMBS &
WHISKERS IS FOSTER HOME
FOR ADOPTABLE CATS
FROM THE LOST DOG AND CAT
RESCUE FOUNDATION.
CRUMPLER: OUR GOAL IS TO JUST
OFFER A PLACE WHERE CATS CAN
BE OUTSIDE OF CAGES AND LIVE
IN AN OPEN ENVIRONMENT.
WE LIKE TO JOKE THAT WE HAVE
ORGANIC, FREE-RANGE CATS.
SINGH: CATS THAT ARE SOCIALS
ARE THE ONLY KIND OF CATS
WE PUT HERE.
AND IT'S GREAT BECAUSE THEY'RE
THE ONES THAT STRUGGLE MOST
IN A SHELTER ENVIRONMENT
BECAUSE THE ISOLATION
HITS THEM THE HARDEST.
CRUMPLER: EACH CAT DEFINITELY
HAS ITS OWN PERSONALITY.
ALL OF THEM ARE SO DIFFERENT.
SINGH: IS IT A SASSY CAT?
IS IT A CHILL CAT?
IS IT A PLAYFUL CAT?
IS IT A SLEEPY CAT?
IS IT A DIVA CAT?
WE'VE HAD 42 ADOPTIONS,
AND RIGHT NOW, WE HAVE
ANOTHER 4 IN PROCESS.
ANNOUNCER: DUE TO ITS
OVERWHELMING POPULARITY WITH
LOCALS AND TOURISTS ALIKE,
CRUMBS & WHISKERS STRONGLY
SUGGESTS MAKING RESERVATIONS.
CRUMPLER: WE'VE BEEN
VERY BUSY SO FAR.
SINGH: OUR WEEKENDS
ARE ALWAYS SOLD OUT.
ANNOUNCER: CUSTOMERS VISIT THE
CAFE TO GET THEIR CAT FIX.
I USED TO HAVE A CAT
FOR A LONG TIME,
AND THEN HE PASSED
AWAY A FEW YEARS AGO.
SO I WAS KIND OF--
WHEN I FOUND OUT THAT
THEY HAD THEM,
HAD THIS HERE,
I HAD TO GO.
YOU SEEM LIKE YOU COULD BE
A GOOD MOUSER.
HA HA HA HA!
I THINK BEING ABLE TO, LIKE,
INTERACT WITH ANIMALS,
EVEN FOR A SHORT
AMOUNT OF TIME.
HELPS BOTH ANIMALS AND HUMANS.
IT'S BEEN PROVEN THAT, LIKE,
SPENDING TIME WITH ANIMALS
CAN, LIKE, IMPROVE MOODS
AND DECREASE STRESS.
WOMAN: IT'S VERY COZY
AND VERY WARM AND WELCOMING.
IT'S JUST REALLY NICE TO
BE ABLE TO SPEND TIME
WITH THESE VERY--VERY
WELL-TRAINED CATS
WHO ARE VERY USED TO
PEOPLE--HA HA!
SINGH: SOME PEOPLE COME HERE
BECAUSE THEY ACTUALLY
WANT TO ADOPT.
AND FOR THOSE PEOPLE, I REALLY,
REALLY HOPE THAT THEY FIND,
LIKE, THAT PERFECT CAT HERE.
UM, FOR OTHER PEOPLE, THEY COME
HERE TO, LIKE, DE-STRESS.
HA HA HA!
YOU CAN WALK OUT OF HERE
FEELING VERY RELAXED
OR VERY ENERGIZED.
[REOWW]
ODS,"
YOU CAN WALK OUT OF HERE
FEELING VERY RELAXED
OR VERY ENERGIZED.
FIND US ON FACEBOOK
AND AT WETA.ORG.
ODS,"
YOU CAN WALK OUT OF HERE
FEELING VERY RELAXED
OR VERY E Previously...