>> ACTOR TARAJI P. HENSON.
TARAJI: YOU MIGHT WANT TO SAY
THAT BEFORE I GO STICKING MY
FINGER IN THERE.
>> REVEALS HER PERSONAL HEALTH
SCARE.
TARAJI: I'M PASSED OUT ON THE
FLOOR.
>> AND HER RAPID WEIGHT GAIN
TURNED OUT TO BE A 50 POUND
TUMOR.
DR. OZ: A MASS THAT WEIGHS AS
MUCH AS A SIX-YEAR-OLD.
>> PLUS, DR. PIMPLE POPPER
WEIGHS IN.
COMING UP NEXT.
♪
DR. OZ: ARE YOU READY FOR SEASON
10?
>> YEAH!
>> I LOVE YOU, DR. OZ.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: TARAJI P. HENSON IS ONE
OF HOLLYWOOD'S BIGGEST STARS.
FROM HER HIT TV SHOW EMPIRE TO
HER NEW FUNNY MOVIE, WHAT MEN
WANT.
TARAJI, SHE CAN DO IT ALL.
RECENTLY, TARAJI OPENED UP ABOUT
A HEALTH SCARE THAT CAUSED HER
TO MAKE BIG CHANGES TO SAVE HER
LIFE.
SHE IS HEALTHY, SHE IS HAPPY,
AND SHE IS HERE.
TARAJI, COME ON OUT.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: I TELL YOU -- THEY LOVE
YOU.
TARAJI: THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
HI!
[LAUGHTER]
DR. OZ: I DON'T GET THAT KIND OF
APPLAUSE.
TARAJI: YES YOU DO.
DR. OZ: I'M SO HAPPY YOU ARE
HERE.
TARAJI: THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
DR. OZ: WE WERE AT THE WOMEN'S
FINALS OF THE U.S. OPEN,
EXPERIENCING ONE OF THOSE MOMENT
IN U.S. HISTORY, SERENA WILLIAMS
AND NAOMI OSAKA IN AN
UNFORGETTABLE MATCH.
TARAJI: WE WERE THERE FOR THE
BIG MOMENT.
DR. OZ: WE WERE STARING AT EACH
OTHER, TRYING TO MAKE SENSE OF
WHAT WAS HAPPENING.
WHAT MEN WANT IS A NEW MOVIE
THAT EVERYBODY IS GOING TO LOVE.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: JUSSIE SMOLLETT, WHO HAS
BEEN ON THE SHOW, WAS RECENTLY
INJURED.
IT IS BEING CALLED A HATE CRIME.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'VE BEEN ABLE
TO SPEAK TO HIM.
TARAJI: YOU KNEW I HAD TO CHECK
ON MY BABY.
DR. OZ: CASTMATE FROM EMPIRE AND
GOOD FRIEND.
TARAJI: HE IS RESILIENT AND HIS
MOTHER RAISED HIM RIGHT.
HE IS AT HIS VERY CORE, HE IS
LOVE.
THAT IS WHO HE IS.
[APPLAUSE]
TARAJI: LOVE IS ALWAYS GOING TO
WIN.
THE DEVIL TRIED, BUT NOT THIS
TIME.
DR. OZ: ALL OF US ARE SAYING, WE
LOVE YOU VERY MUCH.
[APPLAUSE]
TARAJI: YES, THANK YOU.
DR. OZ: I ADORE YOU FOR A LOT OF
REASONS.
I THINK IT IS PROBABLY WHY A LOT
OF PEOPLE LIKE YOU.
YOU ARE REAL AND AUTHENTIC.
YOU'VE HAD TWO HEALTH ISSUES IN
YOUR LIFE THAT WE ARE GOING TO
DISCUSS TODAY.
THE FIRST HAS TO DO WITH YOUR
STOMACH.
TARAJI: DR. OZ: YES.
YOU HAD A RECENT WARNING FROM A
DR. ABOUT STOMACH CANCER.
TARAJI: I WAS FILMING A MOVIE I
DID CALLED BEST OF ENEMIES WITH
SAM ROCKWELL.
I GOT REALLY SICK ONSET AND I
COULDN'T HOLD WATER DOWN.
IT HAPPENED ONCE BEFORE WHEN I
WAS IN MONTE CARLO.
I WAS STUCK IN A HOSPITAL AND
THEY ARE SPEAKING FRENCH AND I'M
SICK.
I THINK I'M DYING AND NO ONE
UNDERSTANDS WHAT I'M SAYING.
ANYWAY, I'M IN GEORGIA AND I
HAVE THIS BOUT OF THROWING UP.
I COULDN'T HOLD DOWN WATER.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW, I'M PASSED
OUT ON THE FLOOR.
WE GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
LONG STORY SHORT, IT IS BAD
GASTRITIS.
THE DOCTOR SAID TO ME, IF I
DON'T CHANGE MY WAYS, I WAS
GOING TO GET STOMACH ULCERS,
WHICH WOULD LEAD TO STOMACH
CANCER.
I WAS LIKE, YOU HAVE MY
ATTENTION.
SO IT WAS DUE TO DRINKING COFFEE
FOR SO MANY YEARS, SO MANY
WARNINGS -- FROM COLLEGE, THAT
WAS JUST HAVE IT.
THEN I USED TO GET REALLY BAD
CRAMPS ON MY CYCLE.
SO I WOULD TAKE IBUPROFEN.
ANY MODEL OF IBUPROFEN, IT SAYS
DO NOT TAKE ON AN EMPTY STOMACH.
THAT, WITH THE COFFEE, WINE ALL
OF THAT WAS EATING THROUGH MY
STOMACH.
I HAD TO CUT ALL OF THAT.
I DON'T DRINK COFFEE ANYMORE.
DR. OZ: AT ALL?
TARAJI: I HAVE TO BE REALLY
TIRED.
I HAVE OTHER ALTERNATIVES.
DR. OZ: CAN I SHOW YOU WHAT WAS
HAPPENING INSIDE YOUR BODY?
TARAJI: CAN YOU, PLEASE?
ONCE I SAW IT FOR MYSELF, THAT
IS WHEN I WAS LIKE, I HAVE TO
MAKE A CHANGE.
DR. OZ: I BROUGHT YOU A PRESENT.
TARAJI: I ALWAYS WANTED TO DO
THIS.
DR. OZ: YOU HAVE TO PUT THE
PURPLE GLOVES ON.
IF YOU REALLY SEE WHAT IT LOOKS
LIKE INSIDE, IT WILL REINFORCE
SOME OF THESE DECISIONS.
ARE YOU READY, EVERYBODY?
THIS IS WHAT A HEALTHY STOMACH
LOOKS LIKE.
THE SWALLOWING TUBE COMES IN
HERE.
THERE'S A BIG MUSCLE HERE THAT
REGULATES HOW MUCH OF THIS ACID
GOES TO THE REST OF YOUR BODY.
PUT YOUR FINGER INTO THAT HOLE.
FEEL HOW TYPE THAT IS.
DR. OZ: TARAJI: IS THIS A REAL
STOMACH?
DR. OZ: THAT IS A REAL STOMACH.
[LAUGHTER]
TARAJI: OK.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO SAY THAT
BEFORE I GO STICKING MY FINGER
IN THERE.
DR. OZ: WE GOT THESE FROM THE
MEDICAL SCHOOL.
TARAJI: I AM ON DR. OZ.
DUH.
[LAUGHTER]
DR. OZ: I WANT YOU TO FEEL HOW
HARD THESE ARE.
PUSH THROUGH THAT IF YOU CAN.
TARAJI: I TRUST YOU.
DR. OZ: SOME OF THE THINGS WE
EAT MESS WITH THAT.
THESE ARE STRONG MUSCLES.
I CAN HOLD IT LIKE THIS.
THAT IS HOW TIGHT THAT IS.
IT IS DESIGNED TO PROTECT US SO
WE DON'T HAVE THE ACID GOING IN
THE WRONG PLACE.
YOU DON'T WANT IT GOING WHERE IT
IS NOT SUPPOSED TO GO.
INSIDE THE STOMACH, THERE'S THE
INSIDE.
CAN YOU ALL SEE THAT?
JUST FEEL THE OUTSIDE.
TARAJI: IT LOOKS LIKE A
CHANNELING.
NO THANK YOU.
DR. OZ: YOU SEE THESE FOLDS.
THEY ARE NORMAL.
WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU DON'T TAKE
CARE OF YOURSELF IS THIS.
TARAJI: OOH!
THAT IS REAL.
DR. OZ: WHAT IF I SAID IT WASN'T
REAL?
TARAJI: SOMETHING ABOUT THAT
FELT TOO REAL.
THAT IS WHY I THOUGHT I WOULD
ASK.
DR. OZ: THE THING ABOUT SEEING
THE REAL BODY IS YOU CAN
APPRECIATE HOW SIGRID YOUR BODY
IS.
IF YOU RECOGNIZE HOW REMARKABLE
THIS IS, YOU SEE HOW THIS IS A
VERY DIFFERENT APPEARANCE.
THIS STOMACH IS THE STOMACH OF
SOMEONE WHO MADE SOME MISTAKES.
THERE ARE DIFFERENT KINDS OF
FOLDS AND LAYERING.
YOU SEE THIS LITTLE THING HERE.
I DO WANT YOU TO FEEL THAT.
TARAJI: ARE THOSE ULCERS?
DR. OZ: KICKSTART IT AS ONE,
PROBABLY, BUT THIS IS WHAT
CANCER LOOKS LIKE.
SEE HOW IT IS INVADING THE
TISSUE?
SHOW PEOPLE WHAT YOUR HANDS LOOK
LIKE.
TARAJI: YOU SENT ME UP.
DR. OZ: IT IS REAL.
IT IS A DR.'S SHOW.
TARAJI: IT DAWNED ON ME AFTER A
WHILE.
DR. OZ: HER HANDS ARE LIKE THIS.
SO THESE FOLDS ARE VERY
DIFFERENT.
IF YOU CAN PREVENT THIS FROM
HAPPENING, YOU WILL DO THAT.
TARAJI: SO THE GREEN IS THE
CANCER.
DR. OZ: ACTUALLY, THIS IS THE
THE INSIDE OF THE CANCER WILL
SOMETIMES DEVELOP AN ULCER
ITSELF.
TARAJI: DON'T DRINK COFFEE ON AN
EMPTY STOMACH, AMONG OTHER
THINGS.
DR. OZ: I THINK YOU ARE ABOUT AS
SQUEAMISH AS ANYONE HAS BEEN UP
HERE.
I'M TAKING TARAJI TO THE
OPERATING ROOM NEXT TIME.
HAVE YOU SEEN AN OPERATION?
TARAJI: I DON'T WANT TO.
MY STEPFATHER IS A DENTIST.
HE ALWAYS WATCHES THOSE SURGERY
SHOWS.
JUST LIKE WITH POPCORN AND
PEANUTS, SOMEBODY'S BODY IS OPEN
AND BLOOD IS EVERYWHERE AND HE'S
WATCHING IT.
THAT IS WHY I'M AN ACTRESS.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: SO YOU MENTIONED YOU
GAVE UP COFFEE.
ALCOHOL?
TARAJI: I DON'T DRINK HARD
ALCOHOL.
I JUST CAN'T DO IT ANYMORE.
I GO TO SLEEP.
I STILL LIKE WINE.
I JUST DON'T DRINK IT AS
CASUALLY AS I DID.
DR. OZ: AND FATTY FOODS ARE A
PROBLEM.
TARAJI: BECAUSE I DON'T THINK WE
HAVE ENOUGH TO BREAK IT DOWN,
RIGHT?
I KNOW A LITTLE SOMETHING.
DR. OZ: SHE KNOWS.
WHAT DO YOU EAT NOW?
TARAJI: I EAT VEGAN,
PLANT-BASED.
THE CHICKPEA IS MY FRIEND.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: ARE YOU VEGAN?
TARAJI: I'M TOTALLY VEGAN.
DR. OZ: THAT IS TOUGH TO DO.
TARAJI: I DON'T DO ANY DAIRY,
CHEESE.
IF I DO MILK, I HAVE A NUT MILK
MAKER.
I DRINK A LOT OF ALMOND MILK.
DR. OZ: I'M SO IMPRESSED.
[APPLAUSE]
TARAJI: YOU DO WHAT YOU'VE GOT
TO DO IF YOU WANT TO LIVE.
DR. OZ: AND YOUR FIANCE, IS HE
INTO THIS?
TARAJI: HE'S MORE OF A GASKET
AREA, BUT HE STILL LIKES
CHICKEN.
[APPLAUSE]
TARAJI: THEY KNOW.
HE LIKES THE SAUCE -- ANYBODY OF
CARIBBEAN DISSENT?
SOUS.
IT IS A SOUP FROM THE CARIBBEAN,
RIGHT?
WHEN WE WENT TO TURKS AND CAICOS
ON VACATION, WE HAD SOME.
I LEARNED HOW TO MAKE IT.
I WILL MAKE HIM THAT AND I WILL
MAKE ME A VEGAN VERSION WITH
MUSHROOMS.
DR. OZ: DO YOU FEEL DIFFERENT?
TARAJI: I HAVE A LOT MORE
ENERGY, FOR SURE.
DR. OZ: WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK
Who said olive oil is the only
heart-healthy cooking oil?
Mazola corn oil has more
cholesterol-blocking
plant sterols than olive oil.
And a clinical study showed
it can help
lower cholesterol 2X more.
When it comes to heart-health,
Mazola is a smart choice.
Is your dry skin cream not doing
enough?
Try Eucerin Advanced Repair
cream.
For 48hour dry skin relief...
Goes beyond ceramides with
moisturizing factors
naturally found in skin...
Eucerin Advanced Repair Cream
For healthier looking skin.
Lash Paradise Mascara
from L'Oréal Paris.
Voluptuous Volume.
Intense Length.
Feathery-Soft Lashes.
This is what
paradise looks like.
Lash Paradise Mascara
from L'Oréal Paris.
Take your lashes to paradise.
Listen moms, Hot Pockets are
exactly what hungry kids
want in a snack.
Premium pepperoni.
Real Cheese.
And that buttery garlic crust.
They're literally stuffed
full of deliciousness.
Nothing satisfies
like 100% real cheese
and 10 grams of protein.
(Ding!)
♪Hot Pockets!♪
-Ah, the old crew!
Remember when we all used to go
to the cafeteria
and just chow down midday?
-You mean, like, lunch?
-Come on. Voted
"Most Likely to Help People
Save $668 When They Switch."
-At this school?
-Didn't you get caught
in the laminating machine?
-Ha. [ Sighs ]
-"Box, have a great summer.
Danielle."
Ooh.
Danielle, control yourself.
I'd like to slow it down here
with a special discount
for a special girl.
Danielle, this one's for you.
with a special discount
for a special girl.
When you eat a bowl
of oatmeal,
you're getting beta-glucan.
That's a soluble fiber
that slows the breakdown
of carbohydrates.
And that provides energy
that lasts.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE ARE BACK WITH TARAJI
P HENSON.
CAN I ASK YOU ABOUT THE WORK
YOU'VE DONE AROUND MENTAL
HEALTH?
THE STIGMA AROUND MENTAL HEALTH
IS REALLY HURTING THIS COUNTRY.
NOT ENOUGH PEOPLE SPEAK OUT
ABOUT IT.
WHAT GOT THIS ISSUE ON YOUR
RADAR?
TARAJI: IT IS IMPORTANT TO ME
BECAUSE, ACTUALLY I FOUND MY
FOUNDATION, NAMED AFTER MY
FATHER, OUT OF NECESSITY.
THERE HE IS.
HI, DADDY.
I MISS YOU.
I SUFFERED TRAUMA IN MY LIFE AND
SO DID MY SON.
WHEN IT CAME TIME TO TALK ABOUT
IT, IT BECAME AN ISSUE.
YOU HAVE TO BE CULTURALLY
COMPETENT IN ORDER FOR ME TO
FEEL SAFE SHARING MY DEEPEST
SECRETS AND FEARS AND BEING
VULNERABLE.
WHEN IT CAME TIME TO LOOK FOR A
THERAPIST, THERE WERE NONE.
IT WAS LIKE LOOKING FOR A
UNICORN.
I'M NOT SAYING THEY DON'T EXIST,
BUT IT WASN'T EASILY ACCESSIBLE.
I DISCUSSED IT WITH MY BEST
FRIEND WHO ALSO HAD HER BOUTS
WITH ANXIETY.
WE DECIDED TO DO SOMETHING ABOUT
IT.
IN THE AFRICAN-AMERICAN
COMMUNITY, IT HAS BEEN SUCH A
TABOO.
WE DON'T TAKE CARE OF OUR MENTAL
HEALTH AND WE SHOULD.
WE SUPPRESS A LOT.
IT COMES OFF, AND WHEN WE DO
EXPRESS OURSELVES, IT COMES OFF
AS RAGE.
WE HAVE A LOT TO BE UPSET ABOUT.
[APPLAUSE]
TARAJI: AND NOT TO SHUN THOSE
FEELINGS, BUT THEY NEED TO BE
CHANNELED OR EXPRESSED IN A
HEALTHY WAY.
WE CAN TALK ABOUT OUR THYROID.
I CAN TALK ABOUT MY GASTRITIS.
BUT WHEN IT COMES TO OUR MENTAL,
WHICH IS PART OF TOTAL HEALTH
CARE, WE MISS THAT.
FOR SO LONG, WE'VE BEEN TOLD TO
PRAY OUR PROBLEMS AWAY.
WE'VE BEEN DEMONIZED.
WE'VE BEEN MISDIAGNOSED.
THERE'S A LOT OF TRUST ISSUES.
I DECIDED TO DO SOMETHING ABOUT
IT.
THE MISCONCEPTIONS WITH
CELEBRITIES AND PEOPLE YOU LOOK
UP TO IS THAT, SOMEHOW WE GOT IT
ALL TOGETHER BECAUSE WE HAVE
MONEY.
MONEY DOESN'T MAKE YOUR ISSUES
GO AWAY.
WHEN I TAKE THIS WIG OFF AND
THESE LASHES -- HE LOOKED AT MY
HAIR LIKE, THAT IS A WIG?
WHEN TARAJI IN THE LIMELIGHT
COMES OFF, I GO HOME TO REAL
PROBLEMS JUST LIKE EVERYBODY
ELSE.
DR. OZ: WHY DID YOU NAME IT
AFTER YOUR DAD?
TARAJI: MY DAD WAS A VIETNAM VET
AND HE SUFFERED FROM HIS OWN
ISSUES.
HE WAS VOCAL ABOUT IT.
IT MADE AN IMPRESSION ON ME.
I WOULD HANG OUT WITH MY WHITE
FRIENDS AND THEY WOULD BE LIKE,
I HAVE MY APPOINTMENT WITH MY
THERAPIST.
I WAS LIKE, I NEED ONE.
I NEED ONE OF THOSE.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: THAT IS SO IMPORTANT.
I ALWAYS WONDER, WHY ARE WE ALL
COMPLETELY PARALYZED BY FEAR,
ANXIETY, ALL THE STUFF THAT
HAPPENS?
HOW DOES THAT AFFECT YOU?
TARAJI: I THINK I HAD TO DEAL
WITH A LOT OF MY THINGS WHEN I'M
PREPARING TO PORTRAY A
CHARACTER.
IF I'M LYING TO THE GIRL IN THE
MIRROR, HOW CAN I TELL THIS
CHARACTER CINCO TRUTH?
ACTING TO ME HAS BECOME VERY
THERAPEUTIC.
NOT TO SAY I DON'T NEED A
THERAPIST, BUT I'M JUST VERY
AWARE OF WHO I AM BECAUSE THIS
IS MY INSTRUMENT.
SO I HAVE TO BE.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: I RESPECT YOUR HONESTY
ABOUT THIS.
I SEE THAT ACTING IS THERAPEUTIC
FOR YOU.
WHAT NEEDS TO HAPPEN IN THE
AFRICAN-AMERICAN COMMUNITY FOR
FOLKS TO EMBRACE THIS MORE?
TARAJI: WE NEED TO START TALKING
ABOUT IT MORE.
JUST BY ME LAUNCHING AND GOING
PUBLIC WITH MY FOUNDATION, I'M
STARTING TO SEE CHATTER AND
PEOPLE TALKING ABOUT IT BECAUSE
YOU PUT A FACE TO IT.
MY FANS, YOU GUYS TRUST ME,
RIGHT?
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: THEY DO.
TARAJI: AND WHEN YOU SEE SOMEONE
THAT YOU TRUST AND LOOK UP TO
SAY, IT'S OK, THEN IT MAKES IT
LIKE A SIGH OF RELIEF, LIKE I'M
NOT THE ONLY ONE.
DR. OZ: YOU ARE RIGHT.
WE ASK OUR AUDIENCE -- THE
REASON WE DO THESE SURVEYS IS TO
FIND OUT WHAT IS BOTHERING
AMERICA.
THE BIGGEST EPIDEMIC IS
LONELINESS.
PEOPLE DON'T FEEL CONNECTED.
THEY DON'T HAVE THE USUAL
TACTICS LIKE TALKING TO YOUR MOM
OR BEST FRIEND.
WHAT IS A TACTIC YOU USED TO GET
PAST IT?
TARAJI: I MAKE SURE I KEEP IN
TOUCH WITH MY FRIENDS.
I HAVE SUCH A GREAT CORE OF
FRIENDS THAT CHECK ON ME.
IT IS ALL ABOUT THE PEOPLE YOU
HAVE AROUND YOU.
GET OFF THE INTERNET.
GET OFF THE SOCIAL MEDIA.
RECONNECT.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: YOU ARE A BEAUTIFUL
PERSON.
ON THE OUTSIDE AND ON THE
INSIDE.
TARAJI: THANK YOU.
DR. OZ: COMING UP, YOU KNOW WHAT
MEN WANT.
WHAT AM I THINKING RIGHT NOW?
WE ARE ABOUT TO FIND OUT.
STICK AROUND.
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
>> I FEEL WEIRD AFTER LAST
NIGHT.
>> THAT IS WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
TEQUILA MEANS DESPERATION.
>> STOP DOING THAT.
>> STOP DOING WHAT?
>> TALKING WITHOUT MOVING YOUR
MOUTH AND SAYING THINGS YOU
SHOULDN'T BE SAYING TO YOUR
BOSS.
>> I WOULD NEVER SAY ANYTHING
DISRESPECTFUL OR INAPPROPRIATE
TO YOU.
>> RIGHT THERE, YOU JUST DID IT.
I HEARD YOU SAY IT.
>> CAN YOU HEAR MY INNER
THOUGHTS?
>> I CAN HEAR YOUR INNER
THOUGHTS!
STOP DOING THAT!
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: THAT IS A SCENE FROM
TARAJI P. HENSON'S HILARIOUS NEW
MOVIE, WHAT MEN WANT.
IT IS FUNNY.
IT IS ACTUALLY ROMANTIC.
THE IDEA THAT YOU COULD READ OUR
MINDS, A TAKEOFF FROM WOMEN,
BECAUSE I WISH WE COULD READ
YOUR MINDS AS WELL, BUT WHAT
DOES THE MOVIE MEAN TO YOU?
TARAJI: FOR ME IT IS A
CELEBRATION OF JUST BEING
YOURSELF.
THAT IS THE THE WE MISS.
IF YOU ARE HONEST FROM THE
BEGINNING AND YOU PUT IT ALL ON
THE TABLE, IT IS NOT THAT
COMPLICATED.
IT REALLY ISN'T.
[APPLAUSE]
TARAJI: WE MAKE IT MORE
COMPLICATED.
THAT IS WHAT THE MOVIE IS
SAYING.
WE WANT THE SAME THINGS.
DR. OZ: MOVIE DIRECTOR ADAM
SHANKMAN IS HERE.
YOU MAY RECOGNIZE ADAM AS A
JUDGE ON SO YOU THINK YOU CAN
DANCE.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: DANCE YOUR WAY UP HERE.
[LAUGHTER]
ADAM: GOOD TO SEE YOU.
DR. OZ: ESPECIALLY IN THE ERA OF
ME TOO, SO MUCH ANGER AND
FRUSTRATION, IT IS DIFFICULT TO
PREDICT WHAT MEN ARE THINKING,
OR WOMEN, ACROSS GENDERS.
WHAT IS A WAY WE CAN TAKE THIS
AND -- WITHOUT BEING ABLE TO
READ MINDS?
ADAM: FIRST I WANT TO SAY THANK
YOU FOR HAVING US.
NOTHING SAYS COME SEE OUR COMEDY
LIKE POKING THROUGH A
DISEMBODIED DISEASED STOMACH.
[LAUGHTER]
DR. OZ: A UNIQUE PROMOTIONAL
TOOL.
ADAM: THAT IS AMAZING.
NOTHING IN THE MOVIE IS AS FUNNY
AS WATCHING YOU DEAL WITH THAT
STOMACH.
[LAUGHTER]
ADAM: THE MOVIE, TO ME, IS ABOUT
THE IMPORTANCE OF LISTENING TO
EACH OTHER, NOT MAKING
ASSUMPTIONS.
AS TARAJI SAID, MEN AND WOMEN
BOTH WANT THE SAME THING, TO
FEEL SAFE AND APPRECIATED AND
ULTIMATELY RESPECTED.
THIS IS NOT A MAN BASHING MOVIE
IN ANY WAY.
BOTH OF US SIGNED ON TO THIS
MOVIE SAYING THAT WE WILL NOT
MAKING MOVIE ABOUT A WOMAN WHO
IS MADE WHOLE BY THE LOVE OF A
MAN.
[APPLAUSE]
ADAM: IT IS ABOUT A WOMAN WHO
BECOMES OPEN TO OUR RELATIONSHIP
BECAUSE SHE SORT OF REALIZES --
HAVING A WOMAN LIKE HER --
[APPLAUSE]
ADAM: THAT WAS THE ONLY REASON
TO MAKE THE MOVIE FOR ME.
TARAJI: I'LL PAY YOU LATER.
DR. OZ: WE ALL KNOW WHAT WE
WANT, WHICH IS LOVE, BUT THERE'S
OTHER THINGS WE WANT, INCLUDING
GOOD HEALTH.
WE'RE GOING TO PLAY A GAME.
WHAT MEN AND WOMEN DON'T WANT.
ARE YOU READY?
[APPLAUSE]
TARAJI: OK.
DR. OZ: MALE ON ONE SIDE, FEMALE
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
I'M GOING TO SAY A HEALTH
CONDITION THAT NONE OF US WANT.
TELL ME IF MEN OR WOMEN GET IT
MORE OFTEN.
FOR EXAMPLE, NAIL FUNGUS.
DO MEN GET THAT MORE OFTEN OR
WOMEN?
AUDIENCE, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> MEN.
DR. OZ: WE HAVE THE SMARTEST
AUDIENCE IN AMERICA.
TARAJI: I CHANGE THAT.
THE ONLY REASON I SAY WOMEN IS
BECAUSE OF THE NAIL SHOPS.
DR. OZ: I SHOULD CLARIFY,
TOENAIL FUNGUS.
TARAJI: TOENAILS, MEN.
[LAUGHTER]
DR. OZ: SHE GOT IT RIGHT.
HIGH FIVE.
IT IS MEN.
WOMEN, ONCE IN A WHILE, LET
THEIR TOES BREATHE.
MEN DON'T.
OK, WE GOING TO MOVE UP THE
LADDER.
SECOND TOPIC.
WHO GETS HEMORRHOIDS MORE OFTEN?
AUDIENCE?
A LITTLE MORE MIXED HERE.
TARAJI: I'M JUST GOING TO LISTEN
TO THEM.
[LAUGHTER]
DR. OZ: I'M NOT ASKING THE
AUDIENCE ANYMORE.
WOMEN GET MORE HEMORRHOIDS WHEN
THEY GET PREGNANT, BUT MEN CATCH
UP.
GO LIKE THIS.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU NOTICED, BUT
THIS TISSUE IS THE SAME AS YOUR
ANUS.
ADAM: SO I'VE BEEN KISSING HER
-- FOR SO LONG.
[LAUGHTER]
TARAJI: OK.
DR. OZ: AT THE END OF THE DAY,
--
[LAUGHTER]
DR. OZ: WHAT IS A TRUE STORY?
ADAM: I'VE BEEN KISSING HER --
[LAUGHTER]
ADAM: SINCE THE DAY I TOOK THIS
JOB.
[LAUGHTER]
TARAJI: YOU SEE WHY WE HAD HIM,
OUR FEARLESS LEADER?
HE KNOWS COMEDY AND TIMING.
DR. OZ: WE WILL CALL THAT A
TIME.
LAST ONE, AUDIENCE, DON'T SAY
ANYTHING.
BAD BREATH.
IS IT MORE WITH MEN OR WOMEN?
WHO GETS IT MORE?
TARAJI: I'M NOT CLAIMING THAT
FOR US.
WOMEN?
DR. OZ: THE ANSWER IS WOMEN.
TARAJI: HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT?
ADAM: THAT IS WHY I'M GAY.
[LAUGHTER]
DR. OZ: TARAJI AND ADAM'S NEW
MOVIE OPENS TODAY.
IT IS FANTASTIC.
GOT BLESS YOU.
GO SEE IT.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: DR. OZ: WEIGHT GAIN, WE
ALL EXPERIENCE IT AT SOME POINT,
Switch to Fios and get
entertainment delivered
to your home like no one else.
Because Fios is a 100%
fiber-optic network.
That means you'll get the
fastest internet available
and Fios TV One with amazing
4K capability,
and an advanced voice remote.
And now we'll give you a Netflix
premium plan for a full year.
So you can stream your favorite
Netflix shows
and movies in 4K on 4
devices at once.
Already have Netflix?
We'll cover the cost for one
year.
Just switch for 79.99 a month
with a two-year agreement
and get Fios Gigabit Connection
with TV and phone
with a 2-year price guarantee.
And not only will you get a
Netflix premium plan on us for a
year,
you'll be able to find Netflix
in the Fios Channel guide
and use the advanced voice
remote to launch Netflix
and easily find all the
channels,movies and shows
you love.
When you think about it,
there are so many entertaining
reasons to switch to Fios.
100% fiber-optic network.
100% phenomenal.
Go to getfios.com today.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE'VE ALL BEEN THERE,
YOU PUT ON A FEW POUNDS AND THEN
A FEW MORE, UNTIL ONE DAY YOU
LOOK AT YOUR BODY AND IT DOESN'T
LOOK LIKE IT DID LAST YEAR OR
EVEN LAST MONTH.
BUT WHAT IF A BULGE WASN'T
WEIGHT GAIN AT ALL?
WHAT IF IT WAS SOMETHING GROWING
INSIDE OF YOU THAT COULD KILL
YOU?
THAT IS WHAT HAPPENED TO BRENDA.
IT IS AN OUTRAGEOUS STORY AND A
MEDICAL MYSTERY SOLVED JUST IN
TIME.
>> ABOUT TWO YEARS AGO, I
NOTICED I WAS PUTTING ON WEIGHT.
I JUST THOUGHT IT WAS MENOPAUSE.
I STARTED WALKING A LITTLE BIT
MORE AND EATING LESS.
IT GOT TO A POINT WHERE I WAS
NOT EATING AT ALL AND I WASN'T
LOSING WEIGHT.
I LOOKED IN THE MIRROR AND I WAS
STUNNED.
IT WAS A DIFFERENT PERSON.
REALITY HIT AND I REALIZED THAT
THIS EXTRA WEIGHT COULD ACTUALLY
KILL ME.
DR. OZ: IT COULD HAVE COST HER
HER LIFE, BUT BRENDA DIDN'T JUST
HAVE NORMAL WEIGHT GAIN.
SHE HAD A 50 POUND TUMOR.
SHE IS JOINING US NOW TO SHARE
HER STORY.
YOU DIDN'T GO TO THE DOCTOR FOR
MONTHS.
WHY?
BRENDA: I JUST THOUGHT IT WAS
MENOPAUSE.
I DIDN'T HAVE ANY IDEA IT WAS A
TUMOR GROWING.
I JUST CHALKED IT UP TO GAINING
WEIGHT BECAUSE I HAD ALL THE
SYMPTOMS OF MENOPAUSE.
DR. OZ: IF YOUR SYMPTOMS GOT
WORSE AND YOUR HEALTH DECLINED
RAPIDLY, WHAT HAPPENED?
BRENDA: I COULDN'T WALK VERY
FAR.
I COULDN'T BREATHE.
I COULDN'T EAT.
I WOULD TAKE ONE BITE OF FOOD
AND IT FELT LIKE IT WAS IN MY
THROAT.
THE BIG PART WAS I WASN'T
SLEEPING.
JUST GETTING UP FROM THE COUCH
TO WALK TO THE BATHROOM TOOK THE
BREATH RIGHT OUT OF ME.
DR. OZ: BRENDA MADE THE
APPOINTMENT WITH A DOCTOR.
SHE HAD A CAT SCAN DONE.
WHAT HE FOUND WAS SHOCKING.
IT WAS A 50 POUND TUMOR.
IT WAS A POTENTIAL CAUSE FOR
LIMITING BLOOD SUPPLY TO HER
MAJOR ORGANS, WHICH IS WHY SHE
WAS HAVING THOSE SYMPTOMS.
A MASS THAT WEIGHS ABOUT AS MUCH
AS A SIX-YEAR-OLD GROWING INSIDE
OF YOU.
I'M SURE YOU ARE ALL NERVOUS.
LET ME SHOW EVERYONE WHY
BRENDA'S SURGERY WAS SO
DANGEROUS.
THESE ARE THE LUNGS.
THIS BIG CIRCULAR STRUCTURE IS A
MASS IN THE MIDDLE OF THE BELLY.
THAT IS THE UTERUS.
THESE ARE THE INTESTINES.
KIDNEYS ARE CRUSHED ON THE SIDE.
THE LIVER IS PUSHED AWAY.
EVERYTHING MOVED OUT OF THE WAY.
BECAUSE YOUR STOMACH SHRUNK,
THERE WASN'T ROOM FOR FOOD.
IT PROBABLY AFFECTED EVERYTHING
ELSE.
LET ME SHOW YOU A CAT SCAN.
THERE'S HER SPINE.
THIS WHOLE MASS IS NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE THERE.
IT WEIGHS WHAT A SIX-YEAR-OLD
WAYS.
THERE'S THE LIVER AND INTESTINES
CRUSHED.
IT WAS SERIOUS.
THEY NEEDED TO OPERATE
IMMEDIATELY.
AFTER TWO HOURS OF SURGERY, THEY
REMOVED THE TUMOR WITH NO
COMPLICATIONS.
THEY FOUND THAT IT WAS THE NINE.
AFTER THE SURGERY, YOU SAY YOUR
HUSBAND BARELY RECOGNIZED YOU.
HOW MUCH WEIGHT DID YOU LOSE?
BRENDA: I WEIGHED 229 WHEN I
WENT IN.
I CAME OUT, POST SURGERY, I
WEIGHED 182.
THEY SAID I WASN'T DONE LOSING
WEIGHT YET.
I DON'T KNOW THE EXACT AMOUNT.
BUT IT WAS CLOSE TO 50 POUNDS
WHEN I WENT TO THE DOCTOR.
DR. OZ: THEY FOUND OUT THERE WAS
SOMETHING ELSE THAT WAS
WORRISOME.
AN ESTIMATED 200 MILLION WOMEN
HAVE THIS.
ONE IN 10 WOMEN IN THIS COUNTRY.
I'M GOING TO WISH YOU WELL.
GOD BLESS YOU.
I'M GOING TO HELP EVERYONE
UNDERSTAND WHAT THEY FOUND.
BRENDA, HER PROBLEM IS BROUGHT
ABOUT BY SOMETHING CALLED
ENDOMETRIOSIS.
I BROUGHT IN OB/GYN
EXTRAORDINAIRE DR. JESSICA
SHEPHERD.
FIRST, WHY DOES IT GO
UNDIAGNOSED SO OFTEN?
SHE DIDN'T REALIZE SHE HAD
ENDOMETRIOSIS.
DR. SHEPHERD: ENDOMETRIOSIS IS
ONE OF THOSE DISEASES AND
CONDITIONS THAT IS OFTEN
OVERLOOKED.
IT TAKES SEVEN TO 10 YEARS TO
DIAGNOSE.
IT IS ONE OF THOSE DISEASES THAT
MIMICS SOMETHING ELSE.
YOU COULD HAVE NORMAL MENSTRUAL
PAIN, BUT IF IT IS SEVERE, THAT
COULD BE A CLUE.
IT CAN AFFECT THE BOWELS, THE
BLADDER.
YOU MAY HAVE ISSUES THAT AFFECT
THOSE ORGANS, NOT REALIZING IT
IS ENDOMETRIOSIS, WHEN THE
TISSUE THAT IS SUPPOSED TO STAY
INSIDE THE UTERUS HAS GONE
OUTSIDE OF THE UTERUS.
DR. OZ: FOLKS WILL OFTEN
COMPLAIN ABOUT PAIN, WHEN YOU
ARE TRYING TO BE INTIMATE, YOU
GET DISCOMFORT.
BRENDA: MANY WOMEN DON'T GO TO
THE GYNECOLOGIST AND COMPLAINED
OF THAT ISSUE.
DR. OZ: PEOPLE FEEL AWKWARD
ABOUT IT.
DON'T BE EMBARRASSED ABOUT
LIFE-THREATENING PROBLEMS.
BOWEL MOVEMENTS CAN BE PAINFUL.
BRENDA: AND SOMETIMES WE'VE SEEN
PATIENTS WHERE WE DIAGNOSE IT
AND IT CAN INVADE THE BOWEL.
THAT IS WHY THEY WILL HAVE
PAINFUL BOWEL MOVEMENTS DURING
THEIR PERIOD AND ALL THE TIME.
DR. OZ: THANK YOU.
APPRECIATE THE KNOWLEDGE.
WHEN WE COME BACK, DR. PIMPLE
POPPER IS IN THE HOUSE AND WE
ARE
MONDAY.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: BOILS, BUMPS, BULGING
LUMPS.
AS WE AGE, WE SEE OUR BODIES
CHANGE IN SHOCKING WAYS.
TODAY I HAVE A PIMPLE POPPING
PROFESSIONAL.
PLEASE WELCOME DR. PIMPLE POPPER
HERSELF, DR. SANDRA LEE.
SHE'S SEEN ALL KINDS OF BUMPS
AND LUMPS.
WHAT IS THE BIBIGGEST MISTAKE YU
SEE FOLKS MAKING?
DR. LEE: THEY DON'T COME IN SOON
ENOUGH.
I SEE SOME REALLY BIG ONES.
DR. OZ: LET'S LOOK AT SOME OF
THESE DIFFERENT BUMPS AND LUMPS
THAT WE FIND IN OUR SKIN.
WE'RE GOING TO START WITH ONE.
DR. PIMPLE POPPER HERSELF IS
HERE TO HELP FIGURE OUT THE
ANSWERS.
THIS IS A PRETTY TYPICAL IMAGE.
DR. LEE: THIS IS WHAT I CALL AN
ABSCESS, THAT A LOT OF PEOPLE
KNOW AS A BOIL.
THE PROBLEM IS THAT THERE'S THIS
PRESSURE UNDERNEATH AND WE
NEEDED TO BE RELEASED.
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING TO DO
AT HOME IS TO REALLY APPLY WARM
COMPRESSES TO THIS.
DR. OZ: IF YOU PUSH HERE, IT IS
STILL SORT OF HARD.
DR. LEE: THAT IS STARTING TO
COME TO A HEAD, BUT WE NEED MORE
OF IT TO COME TO A HEAD.
WE WANTED TO GET SO SUPERFICIAL
THAT IT RUPTURES ON ITS OWN.
THE WARMTH DRAWS THIS TO THE
SERVICE -- THE SURFACE.
DR. OZ: I MADE THIS FOR YOU.
THE FIRST THING YOU SAID,
THERE'S ALL THE LAYERS TO THE
SKIN.
YOU CAN GO PRETTY DEEP.
YOU SAID, PUT A WARM COMPRESS ON
THERE.
HOW LONG?
DR. LEE: MAYBE 15, 20 MINUTES.
A HOT SHOWER HELPS.
THAT HELPS TO BRING IT TO THE
SURFACE.
YOU WANT IT TO BECOME MORE
SUPERFICIAL.
THE MORE SUPERFICIAL SOMETHING
IS, THE LESS LIKELY IT IS TO
CAUSE A SCAR.
YOU WANT TO GET RID OF THAT
PRESSURE.
THAT IS WHAT MAKES US SO
UNCOMFORTABLE.
DR. OZ: I'M GOING TO PUT THE
GLOVES ON.
LET'S SAY I PUT THAT ON THERE.
READY TO GO.
THERE'S A FLAT PART THERE.
YOU ALSO HAVE A LITTLE HAIR
STUCK IN YOUR PIMPLE.
AS YOU PUT THE WARM SOAPS ON
THERE, YOU GET A LITTLE WEAKNESS
THERE.
YOU START TO GET A LITTLE BIT OF
THIS.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU EVER DO
A STERILE NEEDLE.
I'LL GO A LITTLE HORIZONTAL AND
PUNCTURE IT.
OFTENTIMES, ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS CONTINUE TO PUT THAT WARM
COMPRESS.
WITH TIME, IT WILL GENTLY, MORE
AND MORE, AND HERE'S THE BEST
PART.
ONCE YOU'VE DRAINED THAT OUT,
GET YOUR TWEEZERS, YOU CAN DO IT
, GO IN AND GET THAT HAIR.
THIS IS GOING TO FEEL SO GOOD.
DOES THAT FEEL GOOD?
YOU PAY TO BE ABLE TO DO THIS.
ONCE THIS IS OUT, ALL THIS
INFLAMMATION GOES AWAY.
EVERYONE IS HAPPY.
DR. LEE: THAT'S RIGHT.
I NEED THOSE VIDEOS.
THAT WAS GREAT.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: LET'S GO OVER ONE MORE
PICTURE.
THIS IS A PRETTY TYPICAL ONE
THAT GUYS COMPLAIN ABOUT.
THIS IS MAGNIFIED A LOT.
DR. LEE: THIS IS A SKIN TAG.
THIS IS NORMAL.
THESE ARE COMMON ON PEOPLE.
THEY OCCUR WHERE THERE'S A LOT
OF FRICTION.
THEY ARE COMMON.
THEY ARE PART OF LIVING.
SOMETIMES YOU GET SOME PRETTY
BIG ONES.
DR. OZ: HERE'S ONE, A REAL
VIDEO.
DR. LEE: I THINK THIS ONE WAS
HANGING OFF THIS GENTLEMAN'S
KNEE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW HE LIVED WITH
THIS.
WE KNOW MET.
I USE A SCISSOR HERE, A SERRATED
SCISSOR.
THAT DIDN'T ACTUALLY DO IT ALL.
I HAD TO USE A BLADE AND REALLY
GET IN THERE.
IT IS HANGING OFF OF A SMALL
STOCK.
TRIMMING IT, AND I'M GOING TO
CAUTERIZE THE BASE, AND THAT IS
IT.
HE DOESN'T HAVE ANY MORE SKIN
TAG THERE.
DR. OZ: IT WAS BEHIND HIS KNEE.
COULDN'T BEND HIS KNEE ALL THE
WAY.
OLIVIA HAS ONE OF THESE.
DOESN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
YOU ARE ABOUT TO SHOW US
SOMETHING.
HOW DOES IT AFFECT YOUR LIFE?
>> IT IS A SKIN TAG AND IT WILL
DEFINITELY AFFECT MY LIFE
GREATLY.
IT SNAGS ON MY BRAS AND IT IS
REALLY ANNOYING.
I'M REALLY HAPPY THAT IT IS
GOING TO BE REMOVED.
DR. LEE: IT IS ON YOUR BACK?
>> THE RIGHT SIDE OF MY BACK.
DR. LEE: I'M GOING TO HAVE YOU
CLIMB UP HERE AND PUT MY GLOVES
ON LIKE I DO IN MY OFFICE.
DR. OZ: LITTLE MARK SO WE ALL
CAN SEE IT.
ARE YOU COMFORTABLE?
IT IS PROBABLY THERE BECAUSE OF
THE BRA RUBBING ON IT.
I'M GOING TO MAKE A LITTLE MARK
HERE.
CAN YOU ALL SEE THAT?
DR. LEE: I PUT A LITTLE
ANESTHESIA JUST UNDER IT.
ALL I DO IS I USE THESE SPECIAL
SCISSORS THAT HAVE SERRATIONS ON
THEM.
THANK YOU.
DR. OZ: THAT IS FAST.
DR. LEE: THAT IS IT.
DR. OZ: LOOK AT THAT.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. LEE: ISN'T THAT NICE?
IT WILL BE NICE AND FLAT AND IT
WILL HEAL GREAT.
DR. OZ: ENJOY.
DR. PIMPLE POPPER, YOU CAN CHECK
OUT MORE HELPFUL TIPS.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS THE CHANGES
ARE GOING TO BE THERE, BUT IF
YOU ARE NOT SURE, CALL YOUR
DERMATOLOGIST.
MAKE SURE YOU DON'T MAKE ANY
MORE MISTAKES.
YOU ARE ALL GOING HOME WITH A
When you feed yourself
some oats,
the oats feed your body fiber.
Fiber helps keep things
moving through your system.
Which is great.
Because when you're good
to your system,
it'll be good to you.
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE ARE BACK WITH DR.
PIMPLE POPPER, SANDRA LEE, WHO
SAYS THINGS WE FIND IN OUR SKIN
CAN BE A PAIN, BUT CAN ALSO BE A
SIGN OF SOMETHING DEADLY.
LILY IS WITH US.
I'VE GOT A LITTLE QUIZ FOR YOU.
I'VE GOT THREE IMAGES APPEAR
THAT ARE TYPICAL TO FIND ON THE
BODY.
TELL ME WHICH ONE IS THE MOST
DANGEROUS.
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS ONE.
THAT IS A BOIL.
>> THEY ALL LOOK SCARY.
DR. OZ: DR. LEE, WHICH IS THE
MOST LIFE-THREATENING?
DR. LEE: THE LAST ONE IS THE
MOST LIFE-THREATENING.
THAT LOOKS LIKE IT COULD BE A
MELANOMA.
JUST BECAUSE THEY LOOK REALLY
UGLY DOESN'T MEAN IT IS THE MOST
DANGEROUS.
DR. OZ: IF YOU SEE SOMETHING
LIKE THIS, PLEASE GET IT CHECKED
OUT.
TAKE IT AWAY.
DR. LEE: A STANDS FOR ASYMMETRY.
IF YOU HAVE A MALL AND YOU CUT
IT IN THE MIDDLE AND THE SIDES
DON'T MATCH, THAT IS A POTENTIAL
BAD SIGN.
B IS BORDER.
IF THE BORDER IS IN REGULAR,
SCALLOPED OR JAGGED, THOSE ARE
ALL POTENTIAL BAD SIGNS THAT YOU
WANT TO BE AWARE OF.
C IS COLOR.
IF IT IS MULTIPLE COLORS, IF IT
IS WHITE AND BLUE AND RED AND
GREEN, THAT IS POTENTIALLY
CONCERNING.
D IS DIAMETER.
IT IS BIGGER THAN THE HEAD OF A
PENCIL ERASER, THAT IS SOMETHING
WIKI ATTENTION TO.
E IS EVOLVING.
IF YOU FEEL LIKE YOU ARE GETTING
SOMETHING NEW OR ONE OF YOUR
MOLES ARE CHANGING DRAMATICALLY,
THAT IS SOMETHING TO BRING TO
THE ATTENTION OF YOUR
DERMATOLOGIST.
DR. OZ: THE GOOD NEWS IS THOSE
AREN'T TRUE FOR A MOLE YOU HAVE
ON YOUR BODY.
CAN YOU GET A LITTLE COMFORT
THERE?
>> YES.
DR. OZ: KEEP TRACK OVER HERE.
DR. LEE, I HAVE A CHALLENGE.
WE ARE BOTH SORT OF COMPETITIVE.
I WANT TO GO HEAD TO HEAD TO SEE
WHO POPS PIMPLES THE BEST.
THERE IT IS.
THESE ARE THE RULES.
I WILL BEAT YOU.
DR. LEE: SO YOU SPIN AND IT
DETERMINES WHERE ON YOUR FACE
YOU NEED TO POP A PIMPLE.
HERE IT IS ON HIS RIGHT CHEEK.
YOU WANT TO POP THE CORRECT WAY
WITHOUT GETTING SPLASHED.
DR. OZ: SO, VERY GENTLY.
I GOT IT.
YES.
LOOK AT THAT.
THAT FELT GOOD.
NOW YOU ARE UP.
DR. LEE: MY TURN.
I'M GOING TO GET ONE RIGHT HERE.
DR. OZ: THAT IS PROBABLY AN EASY
ONE.
DR. LEE: SOME OF THEM ARE HARDER
THAN OTHERS.
DR. OZ: SHE'S A NATURAL TALENT.
YOU PRACTICE ALL DAY LONG IN
YOUR OFFICE.
DR. LEE: THAT WAS REALLY LUCKY.
DR. OZ: ALL THE MARBLES.
HERE I GO.
LET ME TAKE THIS ONE OFF.
OH!
DR. LEE: AT LEAST IT WENT THAT
WAY AND NOT ON YOUR SHIRT.
DR. OZ: DID I LOSE?
DR. LEE: WE WILL DO A REMATCH
NEXT TIME.
DR. OZ: I LOVE HAVING YOU HERE.
GO TO DOCTOROZ.COM FOR A CHANCE
TO WIN ONE OF THES FOR A CHANCE
TO WIN ONE OF THESE GAMES.
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
Who said olive oil is the only
heart-healthy cooking oil?
Mazola corn oil has more
cholesterol-blocking
plant sterols than olive oil.
And a clinical study showed
it can help
lower cholesterol 2X more.
When it comes to heart-health,
Mazola is a smart choice.
t' dingmiThs
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
heu(Daughter)ot'vav oks  .. sk
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: DO YOU DREAM OF A
FLATTER STOMACH WITHOUT HAVING
TO EXERCISE?
THERE'S A BRAND-NEW PROCEDURE
THAT PROMISES TO BUILD MUSCLE
AND BURN FAT WHILE YOU ARE
LAYING DOWN.
I'M ALWAYS SKEPTICAL OF
TREATMENTS LIKE THIS.
I ASKED DR. DENDY ENGELMAN TO BE
HERE.
SHE'S PART OF A GROUNDBREAKING
STUDY TO FIND OUT ONCE AND FOR
ALL, CAN YOU GET ABS WITHOUT
EXERCISE?
>> DR. ENGELMAN: THIS, WHAT IT
IS DOING TO MY PATIENT IS THE
EQUIVALENT OF 20,000 CRUNCHES IN
ONE SESSION.
DR. OZ: I SEE YOUR STOMACH
COMING TOGETHER.
IS IT UNCOMFORTABLE?
>> A LITTLE UNCOMFORTABLE, BUT
IT IS NOT UNBEARABLE.
DR. OZ: HOW LONG DOES THIS TAKE
TO SEE RESULTS?
DR. ENGELMAN: YOU CAN SEE
RESULTS -- SHE WILL HAVE MORE
DEFINITION, BUT THE RESULTS
CONTINUE TO IMPROVE.
DR. OZ: THIS IS LEO'S ABDOMINAL
AREA BEFORE.
AND THERE SHE IS NOW.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THOSE
RESULTS?
>> I'M REALLY HAPPY WITH THE
RESULTS.
THIS HAS BEEN AN AREA THAT HAS
BEEN STUBBORN NO MATTER HOW MUCH
I GO TO THE GYM.
DR. OZ: ARE YOU SORE AFTERWARDS?
DR. ENGELMAN: YES.
DR. OZ: LIKE YOU DID A BUNCH OF
CRUNCHES.
YOU TAKE CARE OF A LOT OF
PEOPLE.
BUT IT DOESN'T REALLY REPLACE
ACTUALLY DOING CRUNCHES.
DR. ENGELMAN: THAT'S RIGHT.
WE WANT TO MAINTAIN A HEALTHY
LIFESTYLE.
BUT THERE ARE CERTAIN AREAS THAT
ARE STUBBORN.
EVEN IN A REAL SELF INTERVIEW,
90% OF PATIENTS SAID THIS WAS A
GREAT WAY TO GO.
BUT IT IS NOT GOING TO REPLACE A
HEALTHY LIFESTYLE.
DR. OZ: WHO IS NEXT?
I THOUGHT SO.
THANK YOU BOTH VERY MUCH.
TOGETHER, CHANGE IS HAPPENING.
OUR JOURNEY IS JUST BEGINNING.
I'LL SEE YOU ALL NEXT TIME.
[CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY THE
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE,
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTION CONTENT AND ACCURACY.
VISIT NCICAP.ORG
I use this
every day
CAPTION CONTENT AND ACCURACY.
VISIT N But is Beth's soap
as clean rinsing as Dove?
My soap's still leaving
plenty of things behind
But Dove is cleaner rinsing
My soap,
...Dove.
Made with 1/4
moisturizing cream...
Dove cleans and cares
beautifully.
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
>>> RIGHT NOW ON