DR. OZ:  THE NORMAL SIGNS OF
PREGNANCY NOT THERE.
ANY MORNING SICKNESS?
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
>> I DIDN'T GAIN ANY WEIGHT.
DR. OZ:  BIRTH PLAN, NO TIME FOR
ONE.
THE UNBELIEVABLE TRUE STORIES OF
WOMEN WHO DID NOT KNOW THEY WERE
PREGNANT.
>> WHEN THEY DID THE ULTRASOUND
ON MY KIDNEY STONES, THAT'S WHEN
THEY FOUND OLIVER.
DR. OZ:  PLUS IT'S THE DISH,
THIS WEEK, HEALTHIER BACON
DISHES.
>> IT SMELLS SO GOOD.
DR. OZ:  COMING UP NEXT!
ARE YOU ALL READY FOR SEASON 10?
>> YEAH!
>> I LOVE YOU DR. OZ!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  TODAY, REAL LIFE
STORIES OF WOMEN WHO ARE NO
IDEA, NO IDEA THEY WERE PREGNANT
UNTIL MOMENTS BEFORE THEY GAVE
BIRTH.
ONE MOM SAYS AFTER A MEAL OF
CHINESE TAKEOUT, WHICH WE ALL
LOVE, SHE THOUGHT HER
INDIGESTION WAS BECAUSE OF A
FOOD BABY, YOU HEARD OF THOSE
FOOD BABIES, RIGHT, A LITTLE
POOCH AFTER A BIG MEAL.
IT TURNED OUT IT WAS A 37-WEEK
BABY BOY.
THERE HE IS.
ANOTHER MOM WAS EXPECTING TO SEE
KIDNEY STONES ON HER ULTRASOUND,
NOT A BABY THAT WAS ABOUT TO BE
DELIVERED.
CUTE, CUTE, CUTE.
CAN YOU IMAGINE?
IT TURNS OUT IT ACTUALLY HAPPENS
MORE OFTEN THAN YOU THINK.
>> I WENT TO THE HOSPITAL FOR
EXTREME STOMACH PAIN.
AFTER BEING THERE ALL DAY, I
WENT IN FOR AN ULTRASOUND, I HAD
A BIRTH AT 11:06.
>> THEY ASKED ME IF THERE WAS A
CHANCE I WAS PREGNANT?
WENT TO ULTRASOUND, 36 WEEKS,
TWO DAYS.
>> MY WATER BROKE.
DR. OZ:  OVER THE YEARS, THE
UNBELIEVABLE STORIES HAVE POURED
IN, WOMEN WHO HAD NO IDEA THEY
WERE PREGNANT UNTIL MOMENTS
BEFORE THEY DELIVERED AND THEY
SAW NO WARNING SIGNS FOR NINE
MONTHS.
DEBATE YOU HAVE NAUSEA OR
VOMITING OR INTESTINAL ISSUES AT
ALL?
>> I GOT SICK ONE TIME, I
THOUGHT I HAD BAD BARBECUE.
>> I HAD MY PERIOD EVERY MONTH.
>> I THOUGHT I WAS COP AT THIS
UPDATED.
>> ONE BIG PUSH, MY BABY CAME
OUT.
DR. OZ:  SOME STORIES DEFIED THE
ODDS.
>> WHY WOULD I BE PREGNANT WHEN
I WAS MARRIED FOR 22 YEARS, I'M
47.
DR. OZ:  AND THE LATEST, A
SURPRISE DELIVERY AFTER A NIGHT
OF INDIGESTION OF WHAT SHE
THOUGHT WAS BAD CHINESE FOOD,
CRYSTAL GOT THE SHOCK OF HER
LIFE.
DR. OZ:  LET'S START WITH
CRYSTAL WHOSE BABY, FOOD BABIES
TURNED OUT TO BE A REAL BABY.
YOU SAY YOU HAVE NO IDEA THAT
YOU WERE PREGNANT.
YOU HADN'T KNOWN AT THE TIME.
FOLKS RIGHT NOW WATCHING WOULD
SAY IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO BE NINE
MONTHS PREGNANT AND NOT HAVE
SOME SYMPTOMS.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
I DID NOT GAIN ANY WEIGHT, HAD
NO BACK PAIN OR ANYTHING, IT'S
CRAZY.
DR. OZ:  YOU HAVE BEEN PREGNANT
BEFORE YOU KNOW THE STORY.
>> EXACTLY.
DR. OZ:  I HAVE A PICTURE OF YOU
HOLDING YOUR OLDER CHILD, ONE
IT'SINGLY SHE WAS ACTUALLY
PREGNANT WITH HER SECOND CHILD
IN THIS PICTURE.
YOU TELL ME DO YOU SEE THE
SECOND CHILD IN THERE?
WERE YOU TRYING TO GET PREGNANT
AT THE TIME?
>> NO, WE WERE NOT.
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
I WAS ON BIRTH CONTROL AND WE
WERE NOT ACTIVELY TRYING AT ALL.
DR. OZ:  TAKE US BACK TO THAT
FATEFUL NIGHT WHEN YOU ORDERED
CHINESE, WHAT DID YOU ORDER?
>> GENERAL CHICKEN.
DR. OZ:  YOU ENJOY IT, WHAT
HAPPENS?
>> I GO TO ASLEEP.
I WAKE UP IN A COUPLE HOURS.
THAT DAY, MY WHOLE LIFE WAS
CHANGED DRAMATICALLY.
SO I THOUGHT MAYBE I HAD FOOD
POISONING OR SOMETHING LIKE,
THAT BUT THAT WAS NOT THE CASE.
IT DID NOT GET BETTER.
THE LONGER THAT I WAITED, THE
WORSE IT GOT.
SO EVENTUALLY I HAD TO CALL 911
AND THAT WAS IT.
DR. OZ:  YOU CALLED 911 BECAUSE
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT IS
HAPPENING.
YOU THINK MAYBE YOUR APPENDIX
RUPTURED.
THE AMBULANCE COMES, WHAT DID
THEY SAY?
>> I WAS IN SO MUCH PAIN AT THAT
TIME I COULD BARELY ANSWER
QUESTIONS.
THEY GOT ME FROM THE BED AND PUT
ME ON THE STRETCHER.
AS SOON AS I GOT IN THE
AMBULANCE, I WAS IN ACTIVE LABOR
LIKE I WAS HAVING THAT CHILD IN
MY FRONT YARD.
RUSHED TO THE HOSPITAL ABOUT
FIVE MINUTES LATER WHILE STILL
IN THE AMBULANCE, THEY CALLED
AND SAID CONGRATULATIONS, YOU'RE
A NEW DADDY AGAIN, ANOTHER BABY.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  SO WHAT WAS YOUR FIRST
THOUGHT WHEN YOU LOOKED DOWN AND
YOU REALIZED THERE IS A LITTLE
BABY BOY, A MIRACLE THERE?
>> I WAS TOTALLY SCARED.
WE LOVED HIM THE MOMENT WE SAW
HIM.
HE WAS SUPER SMALL, FIVE POUND
BABY.
>> JUST PERFECT.
DR. OZ:  DOES HE LIKE CHINESE
FOOD YET, TOO YOUNG?
>> I DON'T WANT TO THINK ABOUT
CHINESE FOOD.
DR. OZ:  YOUR BABY BOY IS 10
MONTHS OLD.
BABY OLIVER, COME JOIN US!
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  OH, MY GOODNESS.
COME JOIN US.
SIT DOWN, OF COURSE.
OH, MY GOODNESS, HOW CUTE.
WHAT IS IT LIKE LOOKING AT HIM
NOW?
>> IT'S GREAT, IT'S GREAT NOW.
HE IS SUCH A GOOD BABY.
DR. OZ:  TALK ABOUT GOOD.
HAVE YOU HAD CHINESE FOOD?
>> NO.
TRAUMATIZED.
I DON'T WANT TO DO IT.
DR. OZ:  I DIDN'T WANT TO PUT
FOOD IN HERE, I DON'T WANT TO
ADD INSULT TO INJURY, I HAVE A
LITTLE BABY, THIS MAY COME IN
HANDY.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
DR. OZ:  VERY PROUD OF BOTH OF
YOU.
CONGRATULATIONS.
UP NEXT ANOTHER WOMAN WHO HAD NO
IDEA SHE WAS PREGNANT WHAT SHE
THOUGHT WAS AN EXTREMELY PAINFUL
KIDNEY STONE ENDED UP BEING HER
FIRST CHILD, STICK AROUND.
Is your dry skin cream not doing
enough?
Try Eucerin Advanced Repair
cream.
For 48hour dry skin relief...
Goes beyond ceramides with
moisturizing factors
naturally found in skin...
Eucerin Advanced Repair Cream
For healthier looking skin.
Alright, I brought in
Ensure Max Protein...
To give you
the Protein you need
with less of
the sugar you don't.
(Straining)
I'll take that.
(Cheers)
30 grams of protein
and 1 gram of sugar.
Ensure Max Protein.
In two great flavors.
Dave, Dave!
There's a world of possibilities
out there.
Perhaps Tic Tac Mints can help
you open up a bit
You played a mean recorder when
you were seven, Dave.
Offer them a Tic Tac and you
could be jamming in no time.
Isn't that Shirley from the
office?
It's freaking Friday, Dave.
What about this young lady?
I think she's had her eyes on
those Tic Tacs for a while now.
Everyone loves a Tic Tac Dave!
It's time to open up.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  WE ARE BACK WITH REAL
LIFE STORIES OF WOMEN WHO DIDN'T
KNOW THEY WERE PREGNANT UNTIL
THEY WERE ABOUT TO DELIVER.
OUR NEXT GUEST WENT IN FOR AN
ULTRASOUND FOR HER STOMACH PAIN,
EXPECTING TO SEE KIDNEY STONES,
SHE GOT JUST THIS AND OH, NO,
THAT'S WHAT CHILDREN DO TO YOU.
HE HAD SHE HAD THE SHOCK OF HER
LIFE WHEN THE KIDNEY STONES
REVEALED A BABY.
SHE HAD BEEN IN LABOR 40 HOURS
AND WAS ABOUT TO BECOME A MOTHER
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
ALLEY IS HERE WITH HER SON
OLIVER.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  BEFORE THE SURPRISE
BIRTH, YOU ACTUALLY HAD MISSED A
PERIOD AND DONE A HOME PREGNANCY
TEST.
>> YES.
DR. OZ:  WHICH CAME BACK?
>> NEGATIVE, TWICE.
DR. OZ:  TWO NEGATIVE  TESTS.
>> YES.
DR. OZ:  ANY OTHER CHANGES?
>> I DIDN'T GAIN ANY WEIGHT.
I GAINED A LITTLE BIT OF WEIGHT.
I THOUGHT I WASN'T EATING
HEALTHY AND WORKING OUT AS MUCH
AS I USED TO.
I NEVER HAD MORNING SICKNESS.
I NEVER HAD LOWER ENERGY LEVELS.
THERE WAS JUST NOTHING ABNORMAL,
I FELT GREAT.
DR. OZ:  YOU STARTED TO FEEL
ABDOMINAL PAIN, LITTLE OLIVER IS
STILL THERE IN THERE.
YOU ARE THINKING KIDNEY STONES.
>> THAT'S WHAT THE DOCTOR AND
E.R. THOUGHT, TOO.
WHEN THEY DID THE ULTRASOUND ON
MY KIDNEY STONES, THAT'S WHEN
THEY FOUND OLIVER.
DR. OZ:  A BIG BOMBSHELL.
WHAT IS GOING THROUGH YOUR MIND
AT THIS POINT, HOW CRAZY IS
THIS?
>> WHEN THEY TOLD ME THAT I WAS
GIVING BIRTH, I WAS SHOCKED AND
I DID NOT KNOW HOW I WAS GOING
TO DO IT.
I WAS NOT PREPARED.
DR. OZ:  I HAVE BEEN THROUGH
THIS.
>> I HAD NOTHING FOR HIM.
I DIDN'T HAVE A CAR SEAT.
I JUST WAS NOT PREPARED TO HAVE
A BABY, BUT LUCKILY MY MOM IS
ABSOLUTELY AMAZING AND MY WHOLE
FAMILY HAS BEEN THERE FOR ME.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  I'M GROWING TO BRING IN
A DOCTOR TO HELP EXPLAIN THE
PREGNANCY PHENOMENON.
WE GOT TWO OLIVERS.
I HAVE AN OLIVER, TOO.
MUST BE A POPULAR NAME.
WE JUST HEARD BOTH OF THESE
STORIES, OH, NO, IS RIGHT!
NOT KNOWING THEY'RE PREGNANT,
HOW DOES SOMEBODY, NOT JUST GET
PREGNANT WHICH I CAN SEE THAT
HAPPENING WITHOUT YOU REALLY
BEING AWARE OF IT, BUT GO
THROUGH AN ENTIRE PREGNANCY
WITHOUT ANY IDEA?
>> BOTH CRYSTAL AND ALLEY ARE
GREAT EXAMPLING OF NO TWO PEOPLE
ARE THE SAME, NO TWO PREGNANCIES
ARE THE SAME.
SOME HAVE INCREDIBLE AMOUNT OF
SYMPTOMS AND SOME VERY FEW.
SOMETIMES WHEN THE PREGNANCY IS
NOT ON YOUR MIND, YOU CAN
ATTRIBUTE THE SIGNS AND SYMPTOMS
TO PREGNANTS SO OTHER THINGS,
YOUR BELLY IS GETTING BIGGER,
YOU'RE GAINING WEIGHT.
THE BABY IS MOVING, IT'S
INDIGESTION.
DR. OZ:  YOU'RE THE EXPERT,
PREGNANT TEST, THEY'RE SUPPOSED
TO WORK.
ONE AT THE BEGINNING, TWO AT THE
END, AT NO POINT DOES IT SHOW
SHE WAS PREGNANT.
OLIVER WAS IN THERE.
>> A COUPLE OF THINGS COULD BE
AN ISSUE.
ONE, THE HORMONE OF PREGNANCY
DECLINES AS THE END OF PREGNANCY
IS ENSUING AND MAYBE THE URINE
WAS VERY DILUTE THAT IT WASN'T
DETECTED IN THE URINE.
HOWEVER, WHENEVER I'M IN
QUESTION ON A URINE PREGNANCY
TEST, I WILL FOLLOW THAT UP WITH
A BLOOD PREGNANCY TEST.
DR. OZ:  WOMEN AT HOME WATCHING,
WE DON'T WANT SURPRISE
DELIVERIES FROM NOW, BUT AT THE
MOMENT THEY CAN BE PROBLEMATIC.
THEY DO HAPPEN MUCH MORE
FREQUENTLY THAN WE APPRECIATE.
WHAT DO WOMEN DO NOW TO MAKE
SURE?
>> WHEN WE DO HAVE SYMPTOMS, ANY
SYMPTOMS, IRREGULAR PERIODS,
BREAST TENDERNESS, INDIGESTION,
THESE ARE ALL REALLY GOOD
REASONS TO SEEK MEDICAL ADVICE,
GET CARE.
DR. OZ:  KNOW YOUR BODY,
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
DR. OZ:  WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  HOW IS ARSENIC SHOWING
UP IN OUR FRUIT JUICES?
Listen moms, Hot Pockets are
CO
exactly what hungry kids
want in a snack.
Premium pepperoni.
Real Cheese.
And that buttery garlic crust.
They're literally stuffed
full of deliciousness.
Nothing satisfies
like 100% real cheese
and 10 grams of protein.
(Ding!)
♪Hot Pockets!♪
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
and (Daughter)f protein.
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  WHAT'S IN AMERICA'S
APPLE JUICE.
NEARLY EIGHT YEARS AGO, WE ASKED
THAT VERY QUESTION.
WHAT WE FOUND GOT EVERYONE'S
ATTENTION.
LEVELS OF ARSENIC IN APPLE
JUICES AND A NEW REPORT REVEALS
ELEVATED LEVELS OF METALS IN
POPULAR FRUIT JUICES, AND MANY
ARE MARKETED FOR CHILDREN.
TODAY WE INVESTIGATE, HOW IS
ARSENIC STILL SHOWING UP IN OUR
JUICE?
IT SHOULD BE ONE OF THE MOST
WHOLESOME DRINKS FOR YOU AND
YOUR KIDS, APPLE JUICE, BUT WE
HAVE DISCOVERED THAT APPLE JUICE
CAN CONTAIN ARSENIC.
WHEN WE FIRST DECIDED TO
INVESTIGATE ARSENIC IN APPLE
JUICE, THE REACTION WAS
IMMEDIATE AND OVERWHELMING.
>> NOT GOING TO HAPPEN TO ME, IN
MY OWN HOME, NO, THIS IS
RIDICULOUS.
>> HOW COULD I BE STANDING HERE
IN AMERICA TALKING ABOUT ARSENIC
IN APPLE JUICE?
10 OF THOSE SAMPLES CAME BACK
WITH HIGHER LIMITS OF ARSENIC
THAN WE ARE ALLOWING IN OUR
DRINKING WATER IN AMERICA.
>> LOOK AT 88 SAMPLES OF APPLE
AND GRAPE JUICE, WE FOUND 10% OF
THOSE SAMPLES EXCEEDED THE
DRINKING LEVELS FOR ARSENIC.
DR. OZ:  IN RESPONSE TO THE
INVESTIGATIONS, NEARLY 1 MILLION
OF YOU WENT TO OUR WEBSITE TO
FIND OUT MORE AND MAKE YOUR
VOICES HEARD.
>> HOW COULD THEY DO THIS TO OUR
CHILDREN?
>> I PERSONALLY WILL BE
CONTACTING ALL OF THE COMPANIES
AND SAYING WHAT ARE YOU DOING
ABOUT IT AND THEY GOT TO HEAR
FROM EVERYBODY ON THE PLANET.
DR. OZ:  THAT'S RIGHT, THAT'S
RIGHT.
NEARLY TWO YEARS AFTER OUR
INITIAL INVESTIGATION, THE
F.D.A. PROPOSED A NEW LIMIT FOR
ARSENIC IN APPLE JUICE.
BACK IN 2013, BUT NEVER MADE IT
FINAL.
AND TODAY MANY STILL ARE LEFT
WONDERING WHAT IS THE DEAL WITH
AMERICA'S JUICE, SHOULD YOU
STILL BE CONCERNED?
I'M STILL PUZZLED AS TO WHY THE
F.D.A. HAS YET MAKE THAT LIMIT
FINAL.
WE'LL HEAR HOW THEY RESPONDED IN
A MOMENT.
WITH THE LATEST FINDINGS IS THE
CHIVE SCIENTIFIC OFFICER AT
CONSUMER REPORTS.
I LIKE TO THANK THEM FOR
SUPPORTING OUR WORK IN 2011 AND
INDEPENDENTLY VALIDATING OUR
EFFORTS.
WE CONTINUE TO TEST OTHER FOODS
FOR ARSENIC.
WHAT MADE CONSUMER REPORTS
RETURN TO FRUIT BEVERAGES, WHAT
MADE YOU CONCERNED ABOUT
ARSENIC?
>> CONSUMER REPORTS INITIALLY
INVESTIGATED BACK IN 2011 HEAVY
METALS IN JUICE.
AND THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR YOUR
SUPPORT AND ALL OF WORK THAT YOU
HAVE DONE SINCE THEN.
NOW WE WANTED TO DO A SPOT CHECK
ON THE MARKETPLACE TO SEE
WHETHER THINGS HAVE IMPROVED.
DR. OZ:  SO IT'S NOT JUST APPLE
JUICE THIS TIME, IT'S IMPORTANT.
WHAT KIND OF JUICES DID YOUR
TEAM TEST?
>> SO CONSUMER REPORTS
INVESTIGATED 45 JUICES AROUND
THE COUNTRY FROM BOTTLED JUICES
AS WELL AS JUICE BOXES.
AND THEN WE LOOKED AT FOUR
DIFFERENT FLAVORS OF JUICE,
APPLE JUICE, GRAPE JUICE, PEAR
JUICE, JUICE BLENDS, THEY ARE
MIX TOURS OF DIFFERENT TYPES OF
JUICE.
DR. OZ:  GIVE THE RESULTS HERE.
I WANT TO FIND OUT HOW MANY
TYPES OF JUICES HAVE LEVELS THAT
WERE CONCERNING TO CONSUMER
REPORTS.
>> SO EVERY SINGLE SAMPLE WE
MEASURED OR INVESTIGATED HAD
MEASURABLE LEVELS OF HEAVY
METALS.
DR. OZ:  EVERYONE?
>> EVERYONE AND NEARLY HALF OF
THOSE JUICES THAT WE
INVESTIGATED INCLUDING THOSE
MARKETED TO CHILDREN HAVE LEVELS
THAT WERE CONCERNING FOR US.
DR. OZ:  EVERY PRODUCT I SHOULD
POINT OUT BUT ONE WAS BELOW THE
F.D.A.'S PROPOSED LIMIT, YOU'RE
STILL CONCERNED.
I TRUST CONSUMER REPORTS.
I WANT TO UNDERSTAND WHY YOUR
LEVELS WOULD BE DIFFERENT FAN
THE F.D.A.S?
>> THE F.D.A. HAS PENDING
PROPOSED STANDARDS FOR HEAVY
METALS AND JUICE AT ROUGHLY 10
PARTS BETTER BILLION LEVELS FOR
YEAR.
NOW, IF YOU LOOK AT OUR STUDY,
NEARLY HALF OF THOSE JUICES WE
INVESTIGATED HAD LEVELS AT THREE
PARTS PER BILLION, MUCH LOWER
THAN THAT.
SO WE BELIEVE THAT IT'S FULLY
REASONABLE AND FULLY FEASIBLE
FOR THE F.D.A. TO SET VERY
STRICT, VERY AGGRESSIVE LEVELS
AT THE THREE PARTS PER BILLION
LEVEL RATHER THAN WAITING ON
HIGHER LESS PROTECTIVE LEVELS.
DR. OZ:  HALF OF THE COMPANIES
ARE DOING IT ALREADY, WHY NOT
REWARD THE GOOD GUYS?
IT'S NOT JUST ABOUT MAKING MORE
RULES.
IF SOME COMPANY IS DOING A
BETTER JOB THAN OTHER COMPANIES,
HAVE THE GOOD COMPANIES GET SOME
BUFF FROM DOING A BETTER JOB.
>> THE THING IS WE WANT TO
PROTECT PEOPLE.
THAT'S THE BOTTOM LINE.
DR. OZ:  WHICH JUICES, YOU
SHOWED US FOUR, HAD THE HIGHEST
MEASURABLE LEVEL OF HEAVY
METALS?
>> INTERESTINGLY GRAPE AND THEN
FRUIT BLENDS AND THEN FIVE JUICE
BOXES THAT WE INVESTIGATED HAD
LEVELS THAT WERE CONCERNING.
DR. OZ:  WHAT ABOUT THOSE
ORGANIC JUICE?
>> THAT WAS REALLY SURPRISING.
ORGANIC JUICE PERFORMED EXACTLY
THE SAME REGARDING HEAVY METALS
AS CONVENTIONAL JUICE, REALLY
SURPRISING.
DR. OZ:  SO YOU CAN'T GET AWAY
FROM THIS REALLY.
YOU HAVE TO MAKE A RULE SO WE
ALL KNOW WHAT IT IS.
>> STRICT AGGRESSIVE STANDARDS.
DR. OZ:  LINDA IS JOINING US,
YOU'RE HEARING THIS FOR THE
FIRST TIME, THIS IS NEW
INFORMATION.
HOW DO YOU REACT TO THESE
FINDINGS?
>> I'M COMPLETELY UNSETTLED.
ESPECIALLY WITH THE JUICE BOXES,
I STILL PACK MY DAUGHTER'S LUNCH
EVERY DAY.
I THROW IN AN ORGANIC JUICE BOX.
I'M LIKE I'M APPALLED BECAUSE
YOU HAD THIS ON THE SHOW AND
IT'S SCARY.
DR. OZ:  SO LET ME SHOW YOU
SOMETHING THAT YOU MAY FIND
INTERESTING, I'LL SAY, BECAUSE
IT MIGHT WORRY YOU AS WELL.
YOU SHOWED US THE AMOUNT OF
JUICE THAT A CHILD WOULD HAVE TO
DRINK REGULARLY TO RAISE
CONCERNS FOR CONSUMER REPORTS.
>> WE FOUND SEVEN JUICES THAT
ENDED UP HAVING RISK LEVELS AT
JUST FOUR OUNCES OF JUICE PER
DAY.
NOW, THIS IS WHAT FOUR OUNCES
IS.
MOST PEOPLE DON'T REALLY HAVE A
GOOD IDEA OF HOW MUCH FOUR
OUNCES ACTUALLY IS.
FOUR OUNCES.
DR. OZ:  LINDA, IF YOU WENT TO A
RESTAURANT AND ORDERED JUICE FOR
YOURSELF OR YOUR CHILDREN, WOULD
THAT BE WHAT YOU EXPECT?
>> PROBABLY MORE.
IT LOOKS LIKE IT DOESN'T TAKE
MUCH.
DR. OZ:  IT SEEMS LIKE A PRETTY
NORMAL -- THAT'S A SERVING SIZE.
>> THAT'S EIGHT OUNCES.
WE FOUND NINE JUICES POSE A RISK
AT A DAILY CONSUMPTION OF JUST
ONE CUP OR EIGHT OUNCES PER DAY.
DR. OZ:  WHAT ABOUT FOR ADULTS,
LINDA OR ME?
>> WE FOUND 10 JUICES, FIVE OF
WHICH HAD CONCERNING LEVELS THAT
POSED RISK TO HEALTH AT JUST
FOUR OUNCES A DAY --
DR. OZ:  FOR ADULTS.
>> FOR ADULTS AND THEN ANOTHER
FIVE THAT POSE A RISK AT EIGHT
OUNCES PER DAY FOR ADULTS.
DR. OZ:  IT'S STRANGE, ISN'T IT.
SO NOW WE'RE LOOKING AT A
SCENARIO WHERE THE GOVERNMENT
HAS A RULE THAT IT'S NOT MADE
FIRM YET TO LIMIT, BUT IF IT IS
THE LIMIT, THE REASON THEY MAY
HAVE PICKED IT, IT'S A LEVEL
THAT WE TOLERATE IN OUR DRINKING
WATER.
DRINKING WATER IS FREE.
YOU'RE PAYING FOR JUICES, SO YOU
THINK THEY COULD DO A LITTLE
BETTER THAN DRINKING WATER.
WE ALSO WANT TO POINT OUT, THIS
IS IMPORTANT TO RECOGNIZE, WE'RE
NOT TALKING ABOUT LARGE AMOUNTS
OF ARSENIC, THESE ARE VERY SMALL
AMOUNTS, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
DROP FROM THESE THINGS.
THESE SMALL AMOUNTS CONSUMED
REGULARLY CAN INCREASE THE RISK
OF DEVELOPMENTAL PROBLEMS, HEART
DISEASE, BLADDER, LUNG, SKIN
CANCERS, A LOT OF THINGS.
IT'S HARD TO TELL HOW MUCH IS
TOO MUCH.
WHY NOT PICK A NUMBER THAT WE
KNOW IS ACHIEVABLE.
>> PLEASE.
DR. OZ:  PLEASE.
DR. OZ:  MAKE OURSELVES MORE
COMFORTABLE.
WHAT ABOUT LEAD, WE TALKED ABOUT
THE PAINT.
IS THERE LEAD IN OUR JUICES?
>> LEAD IS OF A CONCERN
CERTAINLY BECAUSE OF THE EFFECTS
THAT IT CAN HAVE ON DEVELOPMENT,
PARTICULARLY FOR CHILDREN, THEIR
BRAIN DEVELOPMENT AS WELL AS THE
BEHAVIOR AMONG OTHER THINGS.
THE THING THAT WAS INTERESTING
IS THAT HALF OF THE JUICES THAT
WE FOUND HAD LEVELS OF LEAD THAT
WERE CONCERNING TO US.
MOST EXPERTS SAY THERE ARE
ABSOLUTELY NO TOLERABLE LEVELS
OF LEAD FOR CONSUMPTION.
SO THIS IS A CONCERN INDEED.
DR. OZ:  WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
THAT?
>> LEAD, ARSENIC, IT'S LIKE WHAT
DO WE DRINK NOW?
DR. OZ:  I THINK WE CAN DRINK
JUICES.
WE HAVE TO PUSH THE JUICE
COMPANIES DOING A GOOD JOB TO
MAKE THE ENTIRE INDUSTRY FOLLOW
THE SAME GUIDELINES, WE CAN SIT
HERE COMFORTABLY A SAY DRINK THE
JUICE.
WE ARE STRUGGLING.
WHY ARE THERE HEAVY METAL IN THE
DRINKS AND WHEN IS THE F.
GOING TO DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT?
THAT IS NEXT.
When you combine
Ancestry's DNA test
with its historical records...
...you could learn
you're from Ireland...
...Donegal, Ireland...
...and your ancestor
was a fisherman.
With blue eyes.
Just like you.
Begin your journey
at Ancestry.com.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  WE ARE BACK
INVESTIGATING ARSENIC IN FRUIT
JUICES.
HOW ARE HEAVY METALS STILL
SHOWING UP IN OUR JUICES.
LET'S START WITH HOW DO THEY GET
IN THE JUICES IN THE FIRST
PLACE.
IT DOESN'T GET ADDED IN, NOBODY
IS PUTTING IT IN THERE.
IT STARTS WITH THE FRUIT.
THEY ARE NATURALLY IN THE AIR,
WATER AND SOIL, IT'S THERE.
WE ALSO HAVE CONTAMINATED THE
ENVIRONMENT WITH HEAVY METALS.
THEY'RE FOUND IN POLLUTANTS, IN
PESTICIDES THAT WE USE AND WE
TRIED TO CHANGE ALL OF THESE
THINGS, THERE IS STILL STUFF
AROUND.
THE PLANTS GROW IN THIS SOIL AND
SOME OF THE FRUITS ABSORB MORE
ARSENIC THAN OTHERS, THE APPLE
ABSORBS SOME, BUT THE GRAPES
ABSORB EVEN MORE.
WE BRING IN DR. JAMES DICKERSON
FROM CONSUMER REPORTS.
WE HAVE BEEN RAISING CONCERNS
FOR YEARS.
WHY DO YOU THINK THE F.D.A. WITH
WHOM YOU SPEAK FREQUENTLY
DOESN'T FINALIZE THE LIMIT OF
ARSENIC IN PARTICULAR IN OUR
APPLE JUICE?
>> THAT'S A GREAT QUESTION.
WE REALLY DON'T KNOW WHY.
THAT'S WHY WE WENT TO THEM
DIRECTLY AND SAID, LOOK, WHAT'S
GOING ON?
PLEASE, PLEASE OH, PLEASE SET
STRICT LIMITS, TAKE THE LIMITS
THAT YOU ALREADY HAVE THAT ARE
PENDING THAT I MENTIONED, GO
AHEAD AND FINALIZE THEM BUT WE
DON'T KNOW WHY THEY HAVEN'T DONE
ANYTHING YET.
DR. OZ:  WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE THE
JUICE COMPANIES TO DO?
THEY'RE PROBABLY BETTER OFF
GETTING AHEAD OF THIS ANYWAY.
>> THERE ARE A COUPLE OF THINGS
WE THINK THEY CAN ADDRESS.
ONE IS BETTER SOURCING.
BETTER SOURCING CAN GO A LONG
WAY TO REDUCING THE AMOUNTS OF
HEAVY METALS THAT YOU FIND IN
JUICE.
DR. OZ:  BUY CLEAR FRUITS AND
VEGETABLES.
>> BE VIGILANT IN THAT RESPECT.
THE SECOND PART IS LOOKING AT
THE MANUFACTURING PROCESS AND
LOOKING AT WAYS TO MINIMIZE
POTENTIAL CONTAMINATION PATHWAYS
THERE.
IT'S SOMETHING THAT IF YOU LOOK
AT OUR JUICES THAT WE
INVESTIGATED, HALF OF THEM DO
NOT HAVE CONCERNING LEVELS, SO
CLEARLY INDUSTRY IS DOING
SOMETHING ABOUT IT AND CAN
ACHIEVE IT.
IT CAN BE DONE.
DR. OZ:  LET ME ASK DR. GAIL
CHARLIE TO JOIN US FROM THE
JUICE PRODUCT ASSOCIATION.
THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US.
WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF CONSUMER
REPORTS FINDINGS?
>> CONSUMERS SHOULD BE REASSURED
BY THESE FINDINGS, FRANKLY, THEY
SHOW THAT THE JUICE PRODUCERS
ARE COMPLYING WITH THE SAFETY
STANDARDS THAT THE FOOD AND DRUG
ADMINISTRATION HAS SET TO
PROTECT PUBLIC HEALTH.
SO A JUICE IS SAFE AND I HAVE
HEARD NOTHING FROM CONSUMER
REPORTS THAT SHOWS OTHERWISE.
DR. OZ:  IF HALF THE JUICE
COMPANIES ARE ALREADY BELOW THE
LOWER LIMITS THAT CONSUMER
REPORTS THINKS ARE IDEAL, WHY
JUST NOT EXPAND THAT TO
EVERYBODY?
>> WELL, THE SAFETY STANDARDS
SET BY THE SCIENTISTS AT THE
FOOD AND DRUG ADMINISTRATION ARE
CONSISTENT WITH THE LEGAL
STANDARD WHICH IS REASONABLE
CERTAINTY OF NO HARM WHICH IS
PRODUCERS COMPLYING WITH THOSE
STANDARDS.
SETTING THE STANDARDS LOWER THAN
WHAT'S ALREADY, WHAT THE
STANDARDS ARE FOR WATER ALREADY
DOESN'T MAKE A LOT OF SENSE
SCIENTIFICALLY BECAUSE WE DRINK
SO MUCH MORE WATER THAN WE DO
JUICE.
DR. OZ:  AND, GAIL, YOU HAVE
INTERACTED WITH THE F.D.A., DO
YOU THINK THEY SHOULD FINALIST
THE LIMITS OF ARSENIC IN JUICE,
JUST FINISH IT OFF AND SAY THIS
IS WHAT THE RULE IS?
>> SURE, BUT YOU SHOULD KNOW
THAT FINALIZED OR OTHERWISE THE
JUICE PRODUCERS ARE ALREADY
COMPLAINING WITH THAT LIMIT.
DR. OZ:  GAIL, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH FOR BEING WITH US.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  SO THE BIG QUESTION IS,
WHY HASN'T THE F.D.A. PASSED
FORMAL LIMITS IN EIGHT YEARS,
THE COMPANIES KNOW THE RULES,
THEY CAN PLAY BY THEM, THEY'RE
ALREADY DOING THE RIGHT THING.
WE ASKED THE F.D.A. WHY THEY
HAVE YET TO FINALIZE THE LIMIT.
THEY SAY THE FINDINGS UNDERSCORE
THE PROGRESS THAT HAS BEEN MADE
IN REDUCING THE AMOUNTS OF THESE
ELEMENTS IN FRUIT JUICES OVER
THE PAST SEVERAL YEARS.
WE ARE ENCOURAGED BY THIS
PROGRESS AND BELIEVE THE F.D.A.
OVERSIGHT INDUSTRY
RESPONSIVENESS WILL CONTINUE TO
DRIVE INNOVATION AND LEAD TO
REDUCTIONS IN EXPOSURE.
GUYS, I KNOW YOU LIKE THE JUICE,
I DO, TOO, JUICE IS STILL SAFE.
WE ALL NEED TO BE SMARTER WHEN
WE DRINK IT.
NO JUICE FOR INFANTS AND LIMIT
IT FOR KIDS BECAUSE OF THE SUGAR
CONTENT.
I SUGGEST DILUTING JUICE WITH
WATER.
I HOPE THAT IS HELPFUL.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  THIS CREW IS HERE AND
TALKING BACON.
>> THE CLASSIC TO HEALTHIER
I'M ALEX TREBEK
HERE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50-85
AND LOOKING
TO BUY LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET,
REMEMBER THE THREE P'S.
THE THREE WHAT?
THE THREE P'S?
WHAT ARE THE THREE P'S?
THE THREE P'S OF LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET
ARE PRICE, PRICE, AND PRICE.
A PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD,
A PRICE THAT CAN'T INCREASE,
AND A PRICE
THAT FITS YOUR BUDGET.
I'M 54 AND I WAS
A SMOKER BUT QUIT.
ALEX, WHAT'S MY PRICE?
YOU CAN GET COVERAGE
FOR $9.95 A MONTH.
I'M 65, RETIRED,
AND TAKE MEDICATIONS.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
ALSO $9.95 A MONTH.
I JUST TURNED 80
AND I'M ON A FIXED INCOME.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
$9.95 A MONTH FOR YOU, TOO.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85,
CALL NOW ABOUT
THE NUMBER ONE MOST POPULAR
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE PLAN
AVAILABLE THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IT HAS AN AFFORDABLE RATE
STARTING AT $9.95 A MONTH.
THAT'S LESS THAN 35 CENTS A DAY.
YOU CANNOT BE TURNED DOWN
BECAUSE OF YOUR HEALTH.
NO MEDICAL EXAM,
NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE IS GUARANTEED,
AND THIS PLAN HAS A GUARANTEED
LIFETIME RATE LOCK,
SO YOUR RATE CAN NEVER GO UP
FOR ANY REASON.
AND WITH THIS PLAN,
YOU CAN PICK YOUR PAYMENT DATE,
SO YOU CAN TIME
YOUR PREMIUM DUE DATE
TO WORK WITH YOUR BUDGET.
OPTIONS START AT $9.95 A MONTH,
PLUS, YOU GET A 30-DAY
MONEY BACK GUARANTEE.
SO CALL NOW
FOR FREE INFORMATION.
AND YOU'LL ALSO GET
THIS FREE BENEFICIARY PLANNER,
AND IT'S YOURS JUST FOR CALLING.
SO CALL NOW.
Live from the Starlite Lounge.
♪ One plus one equals
too little too late ♪
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]
WITHOUT.
DR. OZ:  IF THERE IS ONE THING
THAT BRINGS US TOGETHER IT'S
FOOD, WE'RE DISHING ON
EVERYTHING FROM THE LATEST FOOD
HACKS AND TRENDS TO EVERYDAY
RECIPES YOU CAN MAKE FOR DINNER
TONIGHT.
>> SINGING IS MY FIRST LOVE, MY
OTHER PASSION IS BAKING.
>> I'M AN IRON CHEF BUT MOSTLY
THE EXECUTIVE CHEF OF A
RESTAURANT AND MOTHER TO AN
11-YEAR-OLD.
THIS IS THE FIRST RECIPE I MADE
IN A PROFESSIONAL KITCHEN, IT IS
TERRIBLE.
>> MY COOKING IS LIKE ME.
THIS IS LIKE MY GIRLFRIEND IN
THE KITCHEN.
>> I AM AS A CHEF FIRST AND
FOREMOST ABOUT FLAVOR.
IT'S SIMPLE, IT'S CELEBRATORY
AND MOST OF ALL IT'S ABOUT
HAVING A GREAT TIME IN THE
KITCHEN.
>> I'M TRYING TO HELP.
>> LET'S DISH!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  WELCOME TO THE DISH ON
OZ!
THE  BACON CRAZE HAS TAKEN OVER
AMERICA AND IT'S TAKING OVER THE
DISH.
>> FOR YOU, IT'S THE HEART
HEALTHY SPECIAL.
>> I NEVER ORDERED THAT, ALEX,
PLEASE.
KATHY WHAT IS ON THE MENU TODAY?
>> WE'RE BRINGING YOU HEALTHIER
TWISTED ON BACON!
FROM TURKEY BACON TO NITRATEFREE
OPTIONS, WE'RE INVESTIGATING
WHAT REALLY MAKES A HEALTHIER
VERSION OF BACON, IF THERE IS
SUCH A THING.
WE INTRODUCE YOU TO THE WEDGE
SALAD BACON SKEWER, THIS IS YOUR
NEWEST OBSESSION, AND WE'RE
SHOWING YOU HOW TO TURN YOUR
VEGGIES INTO BACON, THAT'S
RIGHT, WE'RE TASTE TESTING THE
TRENDING D.Y.I. BACON RECIPES
TAKING OVER THE INTERNET.
BEFORE WE GET STARTED ON THIS
SANDWICH AND ALL OF THAT, ALEX
HAS DRINKS FOR US.
>> A NICE SODA.
DR. OZ:  OH, MY GOODNESS.
>> JUST FOR YOU, THE DR. OZ
SPECIAL, A BACON SODA.
>> WHAT?
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  IT ACTUALLY SAYS BACON
SODA.
>> THAT'S FOR YOU.
DR. OZ:  I'LL SAVE MINE FOR
LATER.
>> TAKE A PASS.
ALL RIGHT, WHAT DO WE THINK?
>> WHY?
>> THIS IS A NO.
A FIRM NO FROM ME.
>> THIS SHOULD BE OUTLAWED.
NEVER DO THAT.
>> I ACTUALLY WANT TO BE THE
BRIGHT BULB ON THIS CHRISTMAS
TREE RIGHT NOW AND SAY THAT THIS
SODA HAS A SILVER LINING.
IT KIND OF IS LIKE A CREAM SODA,
KIND OF, KIND OF.
[APPLAUSE]
>> LIKE THE AFTERTASTE.
>> NOT BUYING THIS?
>> NOT A BUYER.
>> THAT'S OK, BECAUSE LUCKY FOR
US, WE'RE IN THE BACON BOOM
WHERE EVERYTHING IS BACON, IT
FEELS, YES, THIS SODA, THERE ARE
HEALTHIER BACONS POPPING UP.
THE BIG QUESTION IS COULD THEY
BE AS GOOD AS THE REAL THING.
WE WANT TO PUT THIS TO THE TEST.
I KNOW ALEX, YOU HAVE SOME
STRONG OPINIONS ABOUT WHERE
BACON BELONGS.
>> I JUST DON'T WANT TO BE HERE
AND NOT HAVE YOU GUYS KNOW HOW I
FEEL.
>> I KNOW.
>> I LIKE TO BE REALLY CLEAR ON
SAYING IT.
>> FOOD IS LOVE AND BACON IS
JUST AT THE HEART OF THE
CONVERSATION.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  GOT THAT IN THERE.
>> THIS VALENTINE'S DAY, SAY IT
WITH BACON.
>> EXACTLY.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO TRY TO SELL
US SOME OTHER THINGS.
I'M A SERIOUS PURIST WHEN IT
COMES TO BACON.
>> I ACTUALLY, AS YOU SEE, I'M A
LITTLE BIT WITH YOU.
I FEEL THE CLASSIC BACON, IT IS
SALTY, FATTY, CRISPY, VERSATILE,
DELICIOUS JUST LIKE THIS.
WE DON'T WANT YOU GUYS TO HAVE
ANY FOOD, WE'RE GOING TO GO HOG
WILD!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> I DO LOVE THE REAL THING.
>> PASS THE BACON.
>> MY QUESTION FOR YOU, ARE
THESE HEALTHIER OPTIONS, A LOT
OF PEOPLE WILL GO ON THE MENU
AND ORDER THE TURKEY BACON,
THINKING THEY'RE DOING GOOD FOR
THEMSELVES.
IS IT WORTH PASSING THAT BAD BOY
UP?
>> ALEX --
>> LIKE AROMA THERAPY.
DR. OZ:  DO THE HOMEWORK, WE'LL
DO A HEAD-TO-HEAD COMPARISON.
YOU CAN CURE IT WITH SEWEDUM
NITRATE OR SODIUM POUR AND ADD
SUGAR TO IT.
TURKEY BACON IS DARK AND WHITE
MEAT, A LITTLE BIT OF BOTH, YOU
SPICE IT UP.
IT TASTED LIKE BACON AND THEN
YOU PRESS IT INTO A FORM SO IT
LOOKS LIKE THIS.
ADD A LITTLE SMOKE TO IT BECAUSE
IT WON'T ACTUALLY TASTE QUITE
THE SAME, PORK BELLY.
WITH CHIPS ORALLY QUID SMOKE IS
WHAT THEY USE IN THE TURKEY
BACON, A LITTLE BIT MORE
SYNTHETIC.
THEY ADD SALT TO MAKE IT TASTE
RIGHT.
>> SO IT'S MORE PROCESSED.
WE DON'T LIKE PROCESSED FOODS,
SO BACON IS THE ANSWER.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  WHAT I'M SERVING WHICH
ROUGHLY FOR THE SIZE AND SLICES
OF WHAT YOU GUYS NORMALLY EAT IS
ABOUT ONE STRIP OF BACON.
>> THIS IS NOT ONE OUNCE.
THIS IS LIKE ONE GRAM.
DR. OZ:  THIS IS AN OUNCE, IT'S
A LITTLE BIT LARGER.
THESE COMPARED HEAD-TO-HEAD, 25
LESS CALORIES PER TURKEY BACON
STRIP.
MY VOTE IS IF YOU THINK THEY
BOTH TASTE FINE TO YOU, HAVE THE
TURKEY BACON.
IF YOU PREFER THE ORIGINAL PORK
BACON, WHICH IS WHAT I WOULD DO
AND IN MY FAMILY, WE'RE PORK
PEOPLE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> TO CLARIFY, THERE ARE FEWER
CALORIES IN THE TURKEY BACON,
BUT IT'S ALSO MORE PROCESSED.
DR. OZ:  MORE SALT.
>> IN THEORY, JUST TO MAKE YOU
HAPPIER.
>> MY DAD SAYS WE ARE PORK
PEOPLE.
I THINK MY DAD, ME AND MY
BROTHER WOULD ALL CHOOSE THE
REGULAR BACON.
MY MOTHER AND MY SISTERS ARE
VEGETARIANS, SO WE HAVE LIKE ALL
KINDS OF FUN LITTLE -- THERE ARE
OTHER NONMETAL STERNATIVES ALSO.
THE SHOW IS KIND OF FULL OF
THOSE NONMETAL STERNATIVES AND
THE REAL THING.
THE INTERNET IS BLOWING UP WITH
THE NEW SOLUTIONS OF HOW DO WE
GET A HEALTHIER BACON PROBLEM.
PEOPLE ARE FOCUSED ON THIS
BECAUSE BACON IS I THINK
AMERICA'S MOST BELOVED FOOD.
FAKON ARE MADE OUT OF VEGGIES,
WE HAVE VERSIONS FOR YOU TRY.
WE HAVE AN EGGPLANT VERSION
THERE, A MUSHROOM BACON.
DR. OZ:  YOU DON'T GET ANY.
>> SEE HOW CRISPY THIS IS,
THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
THIS IS EGGPLANT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> THIS IS GOOD.
>> IT'S PRETTY GOOD.
I FEEL LIKE I'M CHEATING ON PORK
BACON BY EATING THIS.
>> DATE AROUND, YOU KNOW WHAT I
MEAN.
[APPLAUSE]
>> SHE'S GOT OPTIONS.
>> I LIKE IT.
>> I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO BE
SKEPTICAL ABOUT THIS.
I FEEL WE'RE GIVING THIS A TASTE
TEST AND WE'RE COMING OUT ON
THIS SIDE.
DR. OZ:  I LIKE THIS.
THESE DON'T LOOK LIKE BACON, BUT
I LOVE MUSHROOMS.
>> I COULD GO WITH THIS AND CALL
IT FAKON.
>> YOU WANT TO SEE HOW WE MADE
THIS TRUE BACON?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> GIVE ME A PLATE OF THIS.
♪♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> I LIKE IT.
>> I NEED A PLATE OF THIS, I
THINK.
AND YOU HAVE ONE MORE TO SHOW
US.
>> I HAVE ONE MORE FAKON HERE.
YOU'LL NEVER GUESS THE
INGREDIENTS THAT IT'S MADE OUT
OF.
>> YOU SAY YOU NEVER GUESS, I
IMMEDIATELY WANT TO KNOW.
>> LET'S ANALYZE.
>> POTATO --
>> WAIT, IT'S COMING TO ME, HOLD
ON, IT'S GOOD.
>> POTATO?
>> ANY GUESSES?
>> WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
CHICKEN SKIN?
>> ANY MORE GUESSES.
>> IT FEELS LIKE SKIN.
>> IT'S SEASONED REALLY WELL.
>> BANANAS?
>> ARE YOU READY FOR THE REVEAL?
>> A PLANTAIN OR SOMETHING?
>> ARE YOU READY?
OK, THIS IS WHAT THIS IS.
WHAT IS THAT?
>> EXCUSE ME.
>> IT'S RICE PAPER.
>> RICE PAPER BACON.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> IF YOU PUT ME HERE FOR THREE
DAYS IN A ROOM WITH THIS, I
WOULD HAVE NEVER GUESSED.
DR. OZ:  THEY CUT IT LIKE THIS?
>> WITH A SCISSOR, I GUESS.
DR. OZ:  THE BACON, THE SPICES,
THIS IS SHOCKINGLY GOOD.
>> REALLY GOOD.
>> THIS I REALLY LIKE.
>> NICE SPICES.
>> YOU TOLD ME IT WAS CHICKEN
SKIN, I BELIEVE YOU.
THIS IS HOW GOOD RICE PAPER
BACON IS.
DR. OZ:  WHEN WE COME BACK, A
LOADED BACON WEDGE SALAD
WILL HAVE YOU
OBSESSED AND I'LL PROVE IT.
STICK AROUND!
♪
Oats have a soluble fiber
called beta-glucan,
which can help lower cholesterol
when part of a
heart-healthy diet.
What's more, these oats
have no artificial flavors,
preservatives or added colors.
Now that's something
to celebrate.
t' dingmiThs
heur,sok e.d ot'vav oks  .. sk
Woman:
I've been saying, "I'm fine."
But, really
I'm struggling to keep
up this brave face
to hide my symptoms
of depression.
I'm taking my antidepressant,
like we discussed.
But, I'm still
feeling depressed.
Is it just me?
Doctor: It's not just you.
Two out of three people
on antidepressants
may still
experience symptoms.
When added to an
antidepressant,
REXULTI has been proven
to help reduce
symptoms of depression.
Woman:
So I can stay on my
current antidepressant
and help build on
the progress I've made.
Hey, guys.
(Mixed greetings)
REXULTI is not for everyone.
Call your doctor about
unusual changes in behavior,
worsening depression,
or thoughts of suicide.
Antidepressants
can increase these
in those 24 and younger.
Elderly dementia
patients taking REXULTI
have an increased risk
of death or stroke.
Call your doctor if
you have high fever,
stiff muscles, and confusion
to address a possible
life-threatening condition
or if you have uncontrollable
muscle movements,
as these may be permanent.
REXULTI has been shown
to increase blood sugar
in some people.
Other risks are increased
cholesterol; weight gain;
unusual urges
or compulsive behaviors;
decreased white blood cells,
which can be serious;
dizziness on standing;
seizures; trouble swallowing;
and impaired judgment
or motor skills.
Now, I'm glad I talked
with my doctor
about adding REXULTI.
Feel better about
facing the world.
Pay $0 for your first
REXULTI prescription.
Details at REXULTI.com.
>> I AM KNOWN AS THE CHEF OF THE
STARS WITH MY PRIVATE CATERING
BUSINESS.
I'M A TV HOST.
I COOK FOR ATHLETES AND
ENTERTAINERS, A LOT OF WELL
KNOWN CELEBRITIES.
I STARTED MY CAREER WITH A
REGULAR 9:00 TO 5:00 JOB AND I
HATED IT, SO I TRADED MY SUIT
FOR A CHEF'S COAT.
I'M BORN AND RAISED IN THE SOUTH
AND MY DAD IS JAMAICAN.
MY STYLE IS CARIBBEAN HEAT MEETS
SOUTHERN SWEET.
WE'RE ON THE BEACH AND ALL OF
THESE PEOPLE BEHIND US ARE
EATING MY JAMAICAN JERK CHICKEN
AND GOING CRAZY.
YES, I'M SERVING UP FOOD AND
HOLDING A BABY AT THE SAME TIME.
THAT'S HOW YOU DO THAT.
I HAVE BEEN A PROFESSIONAL CHEF
AND CATER FOR 12 YEARS.
I LIVE FOR A GOOD PARTY.
YOU HAVE A REASON TO CELEBRATE,
YOU HANG AROUND WITH ME, I'M
GOING TO GIVE YOU ONE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  THEY SAY THAT
EVERYTHING IS BETTER WITH BACON.
TODAY WE'RE GIVING YOU THE
HEALTHIER BACON DISHES THAT YOU
CAN INDULGE WITH.
A BACON LOVER IN HER FAMILY, YOU
GIVE A LITTLE UPGRADE, A HEALTHY
BOOST?
>> SORT OF.
WE CALL HER THE BACON ATOR, THAT
IS MY 2-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER SASHA.
I GO OUT OF TOWN, I'M TRAVELING.
I COME BACK, MY HUSBAND IS
LIKE,A, I GAVE THE BABY BACON.
SHE IS OBSESSED.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO, SHE
WAS CRYING.
EVERY DAY IS BACON, BACON, OK.
I TRY TO MIX IT IN WITH HER
VEGETABLES.
SHE PICKS IT OUT AND EATS JUST
THE BACON.
DR. OZ:  GOOD EFFORT.
SHE IS NOT ALONE, LOTS OF KIDS
ARE OBSESSED WITH BACON THESE
DAYS, TAKE A LOOK.
>> WHY ARE YOU CRYING?
>> BECAUSE I LOVE BACON.
>> THERE IS NO MORE BACON.
>> YEAH?
>> NOT TODAY.
YOU ATE ALL THE BACON.
[SCREAMING]
[LAUGHTER]
>> BACON!
>> BACON?
>> YEAH.
>> BACON!
BACON!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  THAT WAS CUTE.
>> LOOKS LIKE MY BABY.
WE ARE DOING A LITTLE BIT OF A
HEALTHY SPIN.
WE'RE DOING A SALAD FOR YOU,
YOU'LL LOVE THAT.
WE'RE DOING A WEDGE SALAD AND WE
ADD BACON.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> IT'S A WEDGE SALAD.
YOU LOVE TO ORDER A WEDGE SALAD.
I AM PUTTING THEM ON SKEWERS SO
IT'S A PARTY APPETIZER, IT'S
FUN, IT'S ALL OF THAT, RIGHT.
YOU KNOW YOU NEED A GOOD SIZE OF
ICEBERG LETTUCE, CUT IT INTO A
WEDGE AND KEEP IT IN BITE SIZE
CHUNKS, KEEP IT TOGETHER STACKED
UP, YOU PUT IT ON A SKEWER.
YOU LAY ON A COUPLE OF PIECES OF
BACON, THIS IS A HALF OF STRIP,
TWO PIECES, SOME AVOCADOS,
LADIES, JUMP IN.
>> GOT YOU.
>> LET ME GET ON THIS, THANK
YOU.
>> YOU CAN HAVE WHATEVER FUN
VEGETABLES, YOU CAN DEVIATE FROM
THE WEDGE IF YOU LIKE, KEEP IT
CLASSIC HERE.
WE LOVE THE CREAMY BLUE CHEESE
DRESSING THAT COMES WITH A WEDGE
SALAD, RIGHT, I KNOW, I KNOW, WE
DO.
DR. OZ WON'T LET US DO THAT
TODAY, LADIES SO I HAVE DONE A
BLUE CHEESE DRESSING, IF YOU
RELEASE THAT, I'LL TELL YOU GUYS
THE SECRETNESS.
YES!
DR. OZ:  GREEK YOGURT.
>> PLAIN NONFAT GREEK GO GURET,
THE CREAMINESS BUT NOT THE
CALORIES AND FAT.
GREEK YOGURT, BLACK PEPPER, BLUE
CHEESE CRUMBLES, OF COURSE.
>> GARLIC POWDER.
>> IT GOES IN AS WELL.
>> I LOVE THAT WITH BLUE CHEESE.
>> WHAT IS KEEPING THE
CONSISTENCY?
YOGURT AND BUTTERMILK.
DO A LOWFAT BUTTERMILK IN THERE.
DR. OZ:  THEY LIKE IT BECAUSE
IT'S BAD FOR THEM.
IT'S THE MOST ELEGANT WORD IN
THE ENGLISH LANGUAGE.
IT SOUNDS SO DECADENT, IT IS
REALLY GOOD.
>> YOU MAKE BUTTER, YOU HAVE
CREAM AND WHIP IT, YOU GET
LIQUID THAT COMES OFF AS YOU ARE
MAKING THE SALAD, THAT'S
BUTTERMILK.
ALL OF THE FAT, ALL OF THE CASH
MONEY GOES INTO THE BUTTER.
THE BUTTERMILK IS SURPRISING I
WILL LEAN AND GOOD FOR YOU,
RIGHT, VINEGAR OF THE COW.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> I CANNOT --
DR. OZ:  A COUPLE OF THESE.
>> YOU TAP IT OFF, KEEP THE LID
ON TIGHT, Y'ALL, IT COULD BE A
MESS.
DR. OZ:  SHAKE IT UP, SHAKE IT
UP.
>> GET YOUR EXERCISE.
THERE WE GO.
[APPLAUSE]
>> THIS FEELS LIKE A PLAY FOR
YOU TO GET US TO WORK OUT.
YOU JUST GOT US WORKING OUT.
>> DOWN HERE, LET'S CHECK IT
OUT.
AS A CATERER, WE CAN HAVE A
SALAD.
WE'LL KEEP IT LIGHT.
>> PORTION CONTROL, DR. OZ.
>> CHEERS, LADIES.
>> AND IT'S SALAD, WE FEEL GOOD
ABOUT LIFE.
DR. OZ:  WHILE THEY'RE ENJOYING
THIS, WE COMPARED THE BLUE
CHEESE DRESSING TO THE STORE
BOUGHT VERSION.
THE GREEK YOGURT VERSION THAT
SHE JUST MADE, 100 CALORIES LESS
THAN THE STORE BOUGHT STUFF.
GO AHEAD AND SLATHER UP, THE
BIGGEST BACON LOVER IN YOUR
FAMILY, WHO IS IT?
>> MY BROTHER.
I GO OVER WHEN I VISIT HIM IN
THE MORNINGS, THEY LOVE TO COOK
BREAKFAST.
I GO OVER AND NEXT -- THERE HE
IS.
NEXT TO THE STOVE HE HAS A PAN
OF BACON GREASE BECAUSE HE BAKES
IT IN THE OVEN, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HE DOES WITH IT, HE LIKES
IT AND THERE IS A JAR OF BACON
FAT AND GREASE IN THEIR PANTRY
AND THEY MAKE STUFF TO COOK
WITH.
>> WHY NOT.
>> UP NEXT, IT'S SIX DEGREES OF
FREAKY BACON, THE ONE BACON HACK
THAT WILL CHANGE BACON HACK
THAT WILL CHANGE
At last, one red that works on
everyone.
New Made for All lip color from
Maybelline New York.
Tested on 50 skin tones.
Sensational on all.
New Made for All.
Only from Maybelline New York.
I was on the fence about
changing
from a manual to an electric
toothbrush.
But my hygienist said going
electric
could lead to way cleaner teeth.
She said, get the one inspired
by dentists,
with a round brush head.
Go Pro with Oral-B. Oral-B's
gentle rounded brush head
removes more plaque along the
gum line.
For cleaner teeth and healthier
gums.
And unlike Sonicare, Oral-B
is the first electric toothbrush
brand
accepted by the ADA
for its effectiveness and
safety.
What an amazing clean!
I'll only use an Oral-B!
Oral-B.
Brush like a pro.
Is your dry skin cream not doing
enough?
Try Eucerin Advanced Repair
cream.
For 48hour dry skin relief...
Goes beyond ceramides with
moisturizing factors
naturally found in skin...
Eucerin Advanced Repair Cream
For healthier looking skin.
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  WE ARE BACK AND THIS
CREW HAS GONE BACON CRAZY WITH
HEALTHY TAKES ON YOUR FAVORITE
BACON DISHES, BUT ACCOUNT BACON
TREND GO TOO FAR.
THAT'S THE QUESTION, DAPHNE?
>> I'M GOING TO SAY YES, IT DOES
FEEL LIKE EVERY PRODUCT YOU NAME
HAS A BACON VERSION OF IT THESE
DAYS.
THEY ALL LEAD BACK TO BACON.
IT'S SIX DEGREES OF FREAKY
BACON.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  EXACTLY.
I MEAN SIX DEGREES OF KEVIN
BACON, FREAKING BACON.
SIX PRODUCTS DO LEAD BACK TO
BACON.
THE FIRST WE HAVE IS MINCE.
>> I AM ON BACON MINT.
>> IT'S ABOUT THE WORST THING I
HAVE EVER SMELLED.
THIS IS THE WORST THING I HAVE
EVER SMELLED.
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> BACON SOAP.
>> BACON SOAP FOR HANDS AND
BATH, GUYS.
THERE YOU GO.
COVER YOURSELF WITH A NICE
LAYER.
THAT'S NICE.
>> THIS IS NOT OK.
>> LIP BALM.
>> I DON'T THINK THIS IS GOING
TO LEAD TO DATE NIGHT.
>> MAYBE A FIRST AND A LAST DATE
ALL IN ONE.
BACON COLOGNE OVER THERE.
>> BACON MAYONNAISE.
>> LOOK AT YOU.
>> AND THEN THERE IS ONE OVER MY
HEART TO BANDAGE EVERY TIME I
EAT BACON, EAT TOGETHER.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ:  FOR THAT WE HAVE FIVE
AND NOT NECESSARILY ESSENTIAL,
ONE IS REALLY IMPORTANT, SHOW
THEM THE SIXTH PRODUCT.
>> ARE YOU READY FOR THIS?
DR. OZ:  CHANGE SOME LIVES
TODAY.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK IT'S GOING
TO BE, IT'S A MUFFIN TIN.
HOW DO I USE THIS FOR BACON.
JORDAN, WALK US THROUGH THE DISH
ON OZ.
>> THIS IS WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO
DO, YOU FLIP IT UPSIDE DOWN ON
THE TABLE, WRAP IT WITH ALUMINUM
FOIL AND PUT THE BACON OVER IT.
YOU'RE MAKING A BACON CUP FOR
YOUR BREAKFAST.
I LOVEMAKING A LITTLE-UP, YOU
CAN MAKE 15 OR 30 ALL AT ONCE.
DR. OZ:  PASS THE BAND AIDS.
>> ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS.
>> I LIKE THE ONES WITH NO
CALORIES.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> COME ON BACK, BACK WITH OUR
CHOCOLATE COVERED VALENTINE'S
SHOW.
WE'RE INVESTIGATING EVERYTHING
CHOCOLATE, IS IT REALLY AS
HEALTHY AS EVERYBODY WOULD SAY,
WHAT TO BUY FOR YOUR SWEETIE,
AND A FLOURLESS CHOCOLATE CAKE
RECIPE, AS DISH AS IT SOUNDS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
(CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY THE
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE,
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTION CONT
Sensitive skin?
Cetaphil Moisturizing Lotion
is a daily defense
that protects against dryness
before it starts...
with fast absorbing,
continuous hydration.
Cetaphil skin is healthy skin.
Switch to Fios and get
entertainment delivered
to your home like no one else.
Because Fios is a 100%
fiber-optic network.
That means you'll get the
fastest internet available
and Fios TV One with amazing
4K capability,
and an advanced voice remote.
And now we'll give you a Netflix
premium plan for a full year.
So you can stream your favorite
Netflix shows
and movies in 4K on 4
devices at once.
Already have Netflix?
We'll cover the cost for one
year.
Just switch for 79.99 a month
with a two-year agreement
and get Fios Gigabit Connection
with TV and phone
with a 2-year price guarantee.
And not only will you get a
Netflix premium plan on us for a
year,
you'll be able to find Netflix
in the Fios Channel guide
and use the advanced voice
remote to launch Netflix
and easily find all the
channels,movies and shows
you love.
When you think about it,
there are so many entertaining
reasons to switch to Fios.
100% fiber-optic network.
100% phenomenal.
Go to getfios.com today.
♪
Oats have a soluble fiber
called beta-glucan,
which can help lower cholesterol
when part of a
heart-healthy diet.
What's more, these oats
have no artificial flavors,
preservatives or added colors.
Now that's something
to celebrate.
>>> COMING UP RIGHT NOW ON "PAGE
SIX" TV, NICKI AND CARDI, THEIR
BEAT, WE'LL TELL YOU WHAT'S
BRINGING THE TWO SUPERSTARS
TOGETHER.
>>> IS J.LA THE