Captioning sponsored by CBS
>> BERNIE SANDERS IS BACK.
ANNOUNCING HIS BID IN THE 2020
DEMOCRATIC PRIMARY, SANDERS
JOINING A CROWDED FIELD, AT
LEAST 10 CANDIDATES SO FAR, AND,
OF COURSE, STILL COUNTING.
>> LOOK OUT!
>> NO, NO, NO.
LOCK THE DOOR!
>> THEY'RE COMING!
THEY'RE COMING!
HELP!
>> THEY CAME WITHOUT WARNING,
FROM THE SENATE, THE HOUSE, AND
EVEN FROM THAT COFFEE PLACE THAT
SELLS K-POPS.
INVASION OF THE PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES.
EVERY DAY, THEIR NUMBERS GREW
AND GREW AND GREW TO INCLUDE
EVERYONE YOU'VE EVER HEARD OF!
EVEN FIDO O'ROURKE!
INVASION OF THE PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES.
WHO WILL BE NEXT?
IT MAY EVEN BE YOU!
>> I DON'T WANT TO RUN!
AAAHHHGGHH!
>> IT'S "THE LATE SHOW WITH
STEPHEN COLBERT."
TONIGHT, SECOND DEGREE BERN.
PLUS, STEPHEN WELCOMES
ANDREW McCABE
DAN LEVY
AND MUSICAL GUEST SIGRID
FEATURING JON BATISTE AND STAY
HUMAN.
AND NOW, LIVE ON TAPE FROM THE
ED SULLIVAN THEATER IN NEW YORK
CITY, IT'S STEPHEN COLBERT!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: HEY "P."
>> Stephen: PLEASE, HAVE A
SEAT, EVERYBODY!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
WELCOME, ONE AND ALL, ALL AROUND
THE WORLD, WELCOME TO "THE LATE
SHOW."
I'M YOUR HOST, STEPHEN COLBERT.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
THANK YOU.
I FEEL IT, TOO.
THE 2020 PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION
IS HEATING UP.
IN FACT, TODAY, MANY ARE
"FEELING THE BERN," BECAUSE WE
GOT THE OFFICIAL CAMPAIGN
KICKOFF ANNOUNCEMENT FROM
VERMONT SENATOR AND MAN WHO
WANTS TO TRY A FEW MORE FROZEN
YOGURT FLAVORS BEFORE HE PLACES
HIS ORDER, BERNIE SANDERS.
NOW, BERNIE--
( APPLAUSE )
I'D LIKE TO TRY THE LEMON AGAIN,
PLEASE.
BERNIE MADE HIS CAMPAIGN
ANNOUNCEMENT THIS MORNING IN THE
MOST BERNIE WAY POSSIBLE: ON
VERMONT PUBLIC RADIO.
(  LAUGHTER  )
YEAH, YEAH.
ELECTRIC!
>> Jon: YEAH, ELECTRIC,
BOOGIE-WOOGIE-WOOGIE.
>> Stephen: IT'S A HOT
BOOKING.
AFTER THAT, HE MADE IT OFFICIAL,
BY POSTING A FLIER ON HIS LOCAL
CO-OP BULLETIN BOARD.
(  LAUGHTER  )
( APPLAUSE )
NOW, NOW, SANDERS FINISHED
SECOND OUT OF SIX IN 2016, BUT
THIS YEAR'S FIELD IS WAY LARGER.
HERE ARE ALL THE DEMOCRATS "THE
NEW YORK TIMES" SAYS ARE EITHER
RUNNING OR MIGHT RUN.
THERE YOU GO.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
THAT BETO, HE'S A SPICY TEX-MEX.
EVIDENTLY, THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY
HAS BEEN PASSING OUT A MIRROR
THAT SAYS, "2020: WHY NOT YOU?"
THE FIELD IS ALSO WAY MORE
DIVERSE, WITH MULTIPLE WOMEN,
PEOPLE OF COLOR, AND THE FIRST
OPENLY GAY MAJOR PARTY
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE.
BUT SANDERS-- PLAWZ-- FOR ALL
THAT DIVERSITY, BERNIE SANDERS
DOES NOT BELIEVE THAT HURTS HIS
CHANCES.
>> Stephen: YES, LIKE
DR. KING, I HAVE A DREAM, A
DREAM WHERE THIS DIVERSE NATION
CAN COME TOGETHER AND BE LED BY
AN OLD WHITE GUY.
WHERE DO I FIND THE COURAGE?
ALSO, WHERE DO I FIND THE
PUDDING?
I WANT PUDDING."
(  LAUGHTER  )
THE POWNT IS-- AND HERE'S THE
POINT-- BERNIE'S NOT YOUNG,
WHICH WAS POINTED OUT ON "CBS
THIS MORNING" BY JOHN DICKERSON:
>> YOU'LL BE 79 WHEN YOU'RE
INAUGURATED.
>> YES.
>> THAT'S OLD, BY THE STANDARD
OF PRESIDENTS.
>> YES.
>> SHOULD PEOPLE BE CONCERNED
ABOUT THAT?
>> I THINK, YOU KNOW, WHEN WE
LOOK AT PEOPLE, WHETHER THEY'RE
OLD OR THEY'RE YOUNG, YOU HAVE
TO LOOK AT THE TOTALITY OF THE
PERSON.
I WAS A CROSS-COUNTRY RUNNER, A
LONG-DISTANCE RUNNER WHEN I WAS
A KID, AND I'VE BEEN RUNNING
HARD, IN A SENSE, SINCE THEN.
>> Stephen: YES, BERNIE'S BEEN
RUNNING SINCE HE WAS A KID.
AND WE ACTUALLY HAVE A PICTURE
OF HIS MIDDLE SCHOOL TRACK TEAM.
(  LAUGHTER  )
STILL LOOKS GREAT.
STILL LOOK AMAZING.
INCREDIBLE.
BUT BERNIE INSISTS THAT IT
DOESN'T MATTER IF OTHER
CANDIDATES ARE MORE DIVERSE,
BECAUSE IT'S NOT ABOUT HIM.
IT'S ABOUT THE PEOPLE.
THAT'S WHY THE TAGLINE ON HIS
WEBSITE IS "NOT ME. US."
BOLD MOVE TO DO A MISDIRECT IN
THE MIDDLE OF A SLOGAN.
HIS OTHER CHOICE WAS:
BERNIE SANDERS: OLD...
FASHIONED AMERICAN VALUES.
( APPLAUSE )
BERNIE ALSO FEELS VINDICATED,
BECAUSE THE REST OF THE
DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATES ARE
JUMPING ON HIS 2016 PLATFORM.
>> ALL OF THOSE IDEAS PEOPLE
WERE SAYING, "OH, BERNIE,
THEY'RE SO RADICAL.
THEY ARE EXTREME.
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE JUST WON'T
ACCEPT THOSE IDEAS."
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT'S HAPPENED
IN OVER THREE YEARS?
ALL OF THOSE IDEAS, AND MANY
MORE, ARE NOW PART OF THE
POLITICAL MAINSTREAM.
>> SO YOU'RE SAYING THE PARTY
CAME YOUR WAY?
>> WELL, I DON'T WANNA SAY THAT.
I THINK MOST PEOPLE WOULD SAY
THAT.
(  LAUGHTER  )
>> Stephen: (AS BERNIE)
"I DON'T WANNA SAY THAT.
I THINK MOST PEOPLE WOULD SAY
THAT.
ALL I WANNA SAY IS, HOW DO YA
LIKE ME NOW?"
KISS MY VERMONT CHEESE BALLS."
BUT HE'S RIGHT.
THE POLITICAL LANDSCAPE HAS
CHANGED.
THE MAJORITY OF DEMOCRATIC
CANDIDATES THIS TIME AROUND HAVE
JOINED HIS REVOLUTION.
HE'S NOT JUST BERNIE SANDERS.
HE'S GREY GUEVARA.
( APPLAUSE )
IT'S A GOOD LOOK.
VERY SHARP LOOK.
BRACE YOURSELF.
BECAUSE IN HIS ANNOUNCEMENT,
BERNIE DID NOT HAVE KIND WORDS
FOR DONALD TRUMP.
>> WE ARE RUNNING AGAINST A
PRESIDENT WHO IS A PATHOLOGICAL
LIAR.
HE IS A PATHOLOGICAL LIAR.
AND IT GIVES ME NO PLEASURE TO
SAY THAT.
WE HAVE A PRESIDENT WHO IS A
PATHOLOGICAL LIAR, AND IT GIVES
ME NO PLEASURE TO SAY THAT.
>> Stephen: SOUNDS LIKE IT GIVES
YOU SOME PLEASURE TO SAY THAT.
I MEAN, YOU SAY IT THREE TIMES.
IT'S GETTING CLOSE TO A FETISH,
I THINK.
AND THIS AFTERNOON, THE
PRESIDENT WEIGHED IN ON BERNIE'S
RUN.
>> OH, BERNIE SANDERS IS RUNNING
AH, THAT'S RIGHT.
PERSONALLY, I THINK HE MISSED
HIS TIME.
>> Stephen: EXCUSE ME, SIR,
BERNIE SANDERS DOESN'T HAVE A
TIME.
HE EXISTS OUTSIDE OF TIME, LIKE
AN UNDATED CAN OF BEANS IN YOUR
PANTRY.
TRUMP LIKES BERNIE, BUT HE
DOESN'T LIKE BERNIE'S CHANCES.
>> YOU'VE GOT A LOT OF PEOPLE
RUNNING, BUT ONLY ONE PERSON IS
GOING TO WIN.
I HOPE YOU KNOW WHO THAT
PERSON IS.
>> Stephen: I DO.
JOHN OLIVER.
HE ALWAYS WINS.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
CONGRATULATIONS, BUDDY.
WELL DESERVED, YOU AND YOUR
WHOLE TEAM.
A HUGE NEW STORY IN "THE NEW
YOUR TIMES" CAME OUT JUST THIS
AFTERNOON, RIGHT.
TODAY HAS FOUND THAT "TRUMP HAS
PUBLICLY ATTACKED THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION MORE THAN 1,100
TIMES."
1,100-- ALMOST AS MANY TIMES AS
HIS CAMPAIGN MET WITH RUSSIANS.
( APPLAUSE )
CLOSE, DAMN CLOSE.
AND WE'RE LEARNING MORE ABOUT
TRUMP'S ATTEMPTS TO UNDERMINE
U.S. ATTORNEYS' INVESTIGATIONS.
THIS ONE INVOLVES ONE-TIME
ACTING ATTORNEY GENERAL AND
CINDERBLOCK-AMERICAN, MATTHEW
WHITAKER.
NOW, BEFORE WE MOVE ON, IT WOULD
BE AN ABDICATION OF MY SOLEMN
RESPONSIBILITY AS A LATE-SHOW
HOST IF I DID NOT REMIND YOU
THAT WHITAKER WAS ONCE ON THE
BOARD OF A COMPANY THAT CLAIMED
IT HAD D.N.A. EVIDENCE THAT
BIGFOOT DOES EXIST, AND
MARKETED AN EXTRA-DEEP MASCULINE
TOILET FOR WELL-ENDOWED MEN.
(  LAUGHTER  )
OF COURSE, BEST PLACE TO FIND
BIGFOOT D.N.A.?
HIS MASCULINE TOILET.
NOW, LATE LAST YEAR, TRUMP ASKED
WHITAKER WHETHER
GEOFFREY S. BERMAN, A TRUMP
ALLY, COULD BE PUT IN CHARGE OF
THE WIDENING INVESTIGATION OF
MICHAEL COHEN BY THE SOUTHERN
DISTRICT OF NEW YORK.
(AS TRUMP):
"NUMBER-ONE CHOICE,
GEOFFREY S. BERMAN.
IF HE'S NOT AVAILABLE, LET'S GO
WITH JARED T. SON-IN-LAW.
THIRD CHOICE: U.S. ATTORNEY
BURGER, CHEESE."
(  LAUGHTER  )
EVEN WHITAKER, EVEN WHITAKER
KNEW THAT HE COULD NOT PUT MR.
BERMAN IN CHARGE, SINCE MR.
BERMAN HAD ALREADY RECUSED
HIMSELF FROM THE INVESTIGATION.
HE DID, HOWEVER, TELL SOME
ASSOCIATES AT THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT THAT THE PROSECUTORS
IN NEW YORK REQUIRED, "ADULT
SUPERVISION."
THAT IS TRUE.
YOU GOTTA HAVE ADULT
SUPERVISION.
THIS CASE IS RATED NC-17, FOR
EXPLICIT PORN STAR PAYOFF,
GRAPHIC TAX EVASION, AND
HARDCORE REGRET.
(  LAUGHTER  )
( APPLAUSE )
( CHEERS )
THIS, FULL FRONTAL.
♪ ♪ ♪
THIS COULD GET KIND OF
ILLEGAL-ISH FOR WHITAKER,
BECAUSE "EARLIER THIS MONTH, HE
TOLD A CONGRESSIONAL COMMITTEE
THAT MR. TRUMP HAD NEVER
PRESSURED HIM OVER THE VARIOUS
INVESTIGATIONS," WHICH IS WHY HE
"IS NOW UNDER SCRUTINY BY HOUSE
DEMOCRATS FOR POSSIBLE PERJURY."
OH, HE'S GOING TO NEED THAT
MASCULINE TOILET, BECAUSE
MATTHEW WHITAKER IS IN SOME DEEP
DOO-DOO.
SPEAKING OF--
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
SPEAKING OF-- THEY THOUGHT I WAS
DONE.
I'M NOT.
SPEAKING OF TRUMP'S LEGAL
PROBLEMS, IT'S DAY FIVE OF HIS
NATIONAL EMERGENCY, THAT SOME
ARE CALLING "CRISIS ON THE
SOUTHERN BORDER: PRESS ONE FOR
ENGLISH.
PRESS TWO FOR MURDER."
YESTERDAY, 16 STATES SUED THE
PRESIDENT OVER HIS EMERGENCY
DECLARATION TO BUILD THE BORDER
WALL.
16 STATES.
THAT'S TWO MORE THAN HILLARY
CAMPAIGNED IN.
(  LAUGHTER  )
THE LAWSUIT-- GOTAB READY.
GOTTA BE READY.
THE LAWSUIT WAS ANNOUNCED BY
CALIFORNIA'S ATTORNEY GENERAL,
WHO NOTED THE SIGNIFICANCE OF
THE DAY, SAYING, "YOU WOULDN'T
EXPECT TO CELEBRATE PRESIDENTS'
DAY THIS WAY."
ACTUALLY, I WOULD.
(  LAUGHTER  )
I ASSUME TRUMP IS GOING TO
RUIN EVERY HOLIDAY FROM NOW ON.
I AM PREPARED TO SPEND ARBOR DAY
TALKING ABOUT HOW HE GROPED A
FICUS.
(  LAUGHTER  )
( APPLAUSE )
THOUGH-- YEAH.
THOUGH, SUING HIM ON PRESIDENTS'
DAY DOES SHOW HOW DIVIDED OUR
COUNTRY IS.
I MEAN, FOR PETE'S SAKE, WE
CAN'T EVEN ALLOW HIM ONE DAY TO
BUY A NEW MATTRESS AT AN
UNBEATABLE PRICE.
AND RUMOR IS HE GOES THROUGH
MATTRESSES.
WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
FORMER ACTING F.B.I. DIRECTOR
ANDREW McCABE IS HERE.
STICK AROUND.
I can't tell you who I
am or what I witnessed,
but I can tell you
Liberty Mutual customized
my car insurance so I
only pay for what I need.
Oh no, no, no,
no, no, no, no...
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
♪ Ho! ♪
♪
♪ With imagination
yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ With imagination ♪
♪
[zip]
SC Johnson.
♪ ♪
Hi.
Oh, your cute.
Oh.
You guys hungry?
(dinosaurs screeching)
♪ ♪
For mild-to-moderate eczema,
EUCRISA can be...
...used almost everywhere on
almost everybody.
Like the arm of an angel.
Or the leg of this little guy.
For ages 2 and up,
prescription EUCRISA works at
and below the surface
of the skin.
It blocks overactive
PDE4 enzymes
which is believed
to reduce inflammation.
And it's steroid-free.
Do not use if you are allergic
to EUCRISA or its ingredients.
Allergic reactions may occur
at or near the application site.
The most common side effect
is application site pain.
Ask your doctor about EUCRISA.
All right, man.
-All right.
Son: College, I'll be
three whole states away.
Mom: He'll only be
three states away.
Son: I can do whatever I want.
Mom: I can drive up
here anytime I want.
Mom: He's going to
be so homesick.
Son: This is gonna be so sick.
No matter if your
journey takes six years...
or 72,000 miles...
your Volkswagen is covered with
America's Best Bumper-to-Bumper
Limited Warranty.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: HEY, EVERYBODY!
WELCOME BACK TO THE SHOW!
>> Stephen: LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN, MY FIRST GUEST IS THE
FORMER DEPUTY DIRECTOR
OF THE F.B.I. WHO WAS FIRED
AFTER LAUNCHING
INVESTIGATIONS INTO PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S TIES TO RUSSIA.
HIS NEW BOOK IS "THE THREAT."
PLEASE WELCOME, FORMER DEPUTY
DIRECTOR OF THE F.B.I. ANDREW
McCABE!
♪ ♪ ♪
( APPLAUSE )
HAVE A SEAT.
WELCOME TO THE SHOW.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Stephen: I-- I IMAGINE YOU
NEVER THOUGHT THAT YOU WOULD BE
ON A LATE-NIGHT TALK SHOW.
>> NEVER IN MY WILDEST DREAMS,
YEAH, OR NIGHTMARES.
>> Stephen: BECAUSE YOU MOSTLY
HAVE WORKED ON THINGS YOU REALLY
CAN'T DISCUSS WITH THE REST OF
US.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
LIKE EVERYONE WHO WORKS FOR THE
F.B.I., YOU LIVE A VERY PRIVATE
LIFE.
THE WORK THAT WE DO IS
OFTENTIMES-- IT'S ALWAYS
SENSITIVE.
IT'S OFTEN CLASSIFIED.
IT'S THINGS WE DON'T TALK ABOUT.
>> Stephen: LEGALLY, DO YOU
HAVE TO LOOK AND DRESS LIKE AN
EXTRA FROM "DRAGNET" TO BE IN
THE F.B.I.
>> OF COURSE,.
>> Stephen: IT'S A GOOD LOOK.
I TRY TO ROCK IT WHEN I CAN.
>> GOT IT.
>> Stephen: NOW, YOUR NEW BOOK
IS CALLED "THE THREAT," AS I
SAID BEFORE "HOW THE F.B.I.
PROTECTS AMERICA IN THE AGE OF
TERROR AND TRUMP."
( APPLAUSE )
YOU HAVE TO GIVE THIS TO DONALD
TRUMP.
HE IS SINGLEHANDEDLY SAVING THE
PUBLISHING INDUSTRY IN AMERICA
BECAUSE EVERYONE WHO EVER SPENT
FIVE MINUTES IN A ROOM WITH HIM
IS JUST STAMPEDING A PUBLISHER
TO SAY, "YOU WON'T BELIEVE WHAT
THIS GUY SAID!"
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S A SERIES OF
AMAZING INCIDENTS WHEN YOU HAVE
TO INTERACT WITH THE PRESIDENT.
SO IT'S GREAT FODDER FOR STORY
S.
>> Stephen:  AT ALL-- AT ALL
TIMES, BUT THIS PRESIDENT IN
PARTICULAR.
YOU-- AS I SAID, YOU WERE ACTING
DIRECTOR AFTER COMEY WAS FIRED.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> Stephen: AND OPENED TWO
INVESTIGATIONS INTO THE
PRESIDENT, IF I'M CORRECT.
>> IT'S ACTUALLY ONE
INVESTIGATION WITH A DUAL
PURPOSE.
SO THERE'S A CRIMINAL CONCERN.
WE THOUGHT THAT THERE MAY HAVE
BEEN A FEDERAL CRIME COMMITTED
-- THAT BEING OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE.
>> Stephen: WHEN HE FIRED
COMEY.
>> THAT'S CORRECT.
THAT'S CORRECT.
AND WE ALSO FELT LIKE THERE WAS
A POSSIBILITY THAT A THREAT TO
NATIONAL SECURITY MIGHT EXISTED.
>> Stephen: BECAUSE HE MIGHT
BE COLLUDING OR CONSPIRING WITH
THE RUSSIANS, OR THEY MIGHT HAVE
SOME COMPROMMATE ON HIM.
>> IT'S A LITTLE BIT MORE
GENERAL THAN THAT.
IF YOU THINK THAT THE PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES MAY HAVE
FIRED THE DIRECTOR OF THE F.B.I.
FOR THE PURPOSE OF INTERFERING
WITH OR STOPPING OUR
INVESTIGATION INTO RUSSIAN
MALIGN INFLUENCE IN THE
CAMPAIGN, THE QUESTION YOU HAVE
TO ASK YOURSELF IS, "WHY?
WHY WOULD ANY PRESIDENT DO
THAT?"
AND THAT GIVES RISE TO THE
COUNTER-INTELLIGENCE CONCERN?
WHY WOULD THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES BE TRYING TO
OBSTRUCT AN INVESTIGATION INTO
RUSSIA'S ACTIVITY?
AND WHAT-- WHAT MAKES YOU, THAT
THE PRESIDENT FIRED COMEY
BECAUSE OF THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION, OTHER THAN THE
FACT THAT HE SAID THAT OUT LOUD?
(  LAUGHTER  )
( APPLAUSE )
( CHEERS )
>> YEAH.
YEAH.
>> Stephen: IS THERE ANYTHING
OTHER THAN THAT?
IS THERE OTHER THAN, LIKE, WHAT
HE SAID TO LESTER HOLT.
>> THAT WAS A GOOD THING.
AND IT WAS SOMETHING WE WERE
AWARE OF.
>> Stephen: IT'S CALLED A LEAD
IN THE BUSINESS.
>> IT WAS AN INVESTIGATIVE LEAD.
THERE WERE A NUMBER OF THINGS
THAT CONCERNED US.
AS WE INVESTIGATED THE
POSSIBILITY OF RUSSIAN COLLUSION
WITH THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN THROUGH
THE FALL.
SO THAT'S THE INVESTIGATION THAT
JIM COMEY HAD MADE PUBLIC.
>> Stephen: WHAT IS IT LIKE TO
BE IN A ROOM WHERE PEOPLE ARE
SERIOUSLY CONSIDERING AND
EVENTUALLY DECIDE TO, WHAT'S IT
LIKE TO BE IN THAT ROOM WHEN
YOU'RE HAVING TO SERIOUSLY
CONSIDER WHETHER TO INVESTIGATE
THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES?
>> YEAH, IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
I MEAN, LOOK, WE DON'T TRAIN AT
QUANTICO FOR, "HERE'S WHAT TO DO
WHEN YOU THINK YOU NEED TO
INVESTIGATE THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES."
IT'S JUST NOT A TOPIC THAT WE
TALK ABOUT.
( LAUGHTER )
BUT WHAT WE DO TRAIN ON IS WE
SAY, "LOOK, THESE ARE THE
AUTHORITIES WE HAVE.
AND THIS IS HOW WE LAWFULLY
EXECUTE THEM."
WHEN WE HAVE INFORMATION OR
FACTS THAT INDICATE A CRIME MAY
HAVE BEEN COMMITTED OR THAT A
THREAT TO NATIONAL SECURITY MAY
EXIST, THEN WE ARE OBLIGATED AS
THE F.B.I. TO INVESTIGATE THAT
MATTER, WHETHER IT'S THE
PRESIDENT OR ANYBODY ELSE.
WE DON'T OPEN INVESTIGATIONS
BECAUSE WE LIKE SOMEONE OR DON'T
LIKE THEM OR BECAUSE THEY'RE A
REPUBLICAN OR A DEMOCRAT.
WE OPEN INVESTIGATIONS WHEN WE
HAVE THE INFORMATION THAT WOULD
PREDICATE AN INVESTIGATION.
WE HAD THAT IN THIS INSTANCE,
UNDENIABLY.
>> Stephen: ALL RIGHT, YOU
DESCRIBE THE PERIOD OF TIME
AFTER DIRECTOR COMEY WAS FIRED
AS-- AS A PERIOD OF CHAOS AND
FRENZY AT THE F.B.I.
HEADQUARTERS.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> Stephen: WHAT IS THE F.B.I.
LIKE WHEN IT'S IN A CHAOTIC
FRENZY?
THAT'S A DISCONCERTING
DESCRIPTION.
>> OUR DARK TIES ARE SLIGHTLY
ASKEW ON OUR WHITE SHIRTS.
THAT'S THE FIRST TIME.
>> Stephen: JUST, THAT OKAY?
(  LAUGHTER  )
( APPLAUSE ).
>> YOU KNOW-- KNOW --
>> Stephen: YOU'RE NOT DRAMA
QUEENS.
>> NO, NO.
THERE'S NOT A LOT OF, YOU KNOW,
PEOPLE RUNNING THROUGH THE HALLS
WITH THEIR HAIR ON FIRE.
IT WAS A VERY SERIOUS TIME.
I HAD-- YOU KNOW, I FELT THAT MY
TIME AS ACTING DIRECTOR WOULD
LIKELY BE VERY SHORT.
I KNEW THAT BECAUSE THE
PRESIDENT TOLD ME THAT WAS THE
LIKELY RESULT.
( LAUGHTER )
AND I KNEW THERE WAS WORK WE
NEEDED TO DO TO MAKE SURE THE
INVESTIGATIONES OF ON ROCK-SOLID
GROUND.
>> Stephen: THE ASSOCIATED
PRESS SAYS THAT YOU ASKED FOR A
BACKUP PLAN TO PROTECT RUSSIA
EVIDENCE.
WHAT-- WHAT-- WHAT WAS THAT
BACKUP PLAN?
>> I CAN'T TELL YOU THE DETAILS
OF THE BACKUP PLAN, BUT I CAN
SAY THIS, STEPHEN.
WE-- THAT'S OUR JOB, RIGHT?
THAT'S OUR JOB TO PREPARE FOR
VERY WELLITY.
>> Stephen: IS IT ON, LIKE, A
THUMB DRIVE INSIDE A BRICK SOME
PLACE AT DUPONT CIRCLE?
DID YOU HAVE TO DO SPY STUFF TO
HIDE IT?
>> IT'S ON THE TAPE REELS THAT
TURN TO SMOKE AT THE BEGINNING
OF THE SHOW.
>> Stephen: YEAH, YOU JOKE,
BUT NOW I KNOW THOSE ARE REAL
BECAUSE IT'S ITS FIRST THING YOU
THOUGHT OF.
>> YEAH.
>> Stephen: OKAY--
>> NO, WE NEEDED TO DO IF
DIRECTOR MUELLER WAS SBL FIRED
AND HIS TEAM WAS DISBANDED.
AND WHAT WE NEEDED TO DO IN THAT
CIRCUMSTANCE WAS TO BE ABLE TO
TAKE OUR CASES BACK AND CONTINUE
THAT INVESTIGATION.
THAT'S KIND OF WHAT WE THOUGHT
THROUGH.
>> Stephen: YOU WORKED FOR
MUELLER, DIDN'T YOU?
>> I DID, FOR MANY YEARS.
>> Stephen: WHAT'S HE LIKE AS
A PERSON?
>> HE'S A TOUGH GUY.
HE IS-- HE IS A LOT OF WHAT
YOU'VE HEARD ABOUT HIM.
HE IS AN INVESTIGATOR AT HEART.
THAT IS WHAT HE LOVES TO DO.
HE LOVES CASES.
HE LOVES TO GET HIS HANDS ON
THEM.
HE LOVES TO HEAR THE DETAILS,
TALK TO THE INVESTIGATORS, PLAN
STRATEGY, AND MOVE
INVESTIGATIONS FORWARD.
SO I AM SURE THAT HE IS JUST AS
HAPPY AS HE CAN POSSIBLY BE IN
THE POSITION HE'S CURRENTLY IN.
>> Stephen: HE LOOKS HAPPY.
( LAUGHTER ).
>> YEAH.
>> Stephen: JUST A BIG, SILLY
GRIN ALL THE TIME ON HIS FACE.
>> THAT'S-- THAT'S ABOUT AS
HAPPY AS HE GETS.
(  LAUGHTER  ).
>> Stephen: HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
HIM IN CHAOS OR FRENZY?
WHAT'S THE MOST EXERCISED YOU'VE
SEEN ROBERT MUELLER?
>> I'VE SEEN HIM FRUSTRATED.
I'VE SEEN HIM, YOU KNOW,
DISAPPOINTED WITH THE THINGS WE
WERE TELLING HIM.
>> Stephen: WHAT DOES HE DO?
LIKE, HOW DOES HE EXPRESS
HIMSELF?
>> YOU KNOW, WHEN DIRECTOR
MUELLER WOULD GET FRUSTRATED WE
HAD THIS SIGN THAT WE WOULD
ALWAYS LOOK FOR.
IF HIS HEAD CAME DOWN INTO HIS
HAND, WE KNEW IT WAS A PROBLEM.
WE'RE OFF THE RAILS.
>> Stephen: THAT'S FAIRLY
COMMON AMONG ALL HUMANS.
>> I THINK SO.
AGAIN, YOU KNOW --
>> Stephen: EXACTLY, YOU'RE A
TOM BRADY F.B.I. MAN.
YOU SEE THOSE THINGS.
>> THIS IS A TELL.
>> Stephen: LIKE THIS.
>> IT WAS JUST LIKE THIS.
>> Stephen: NOW, IN THE BOOK,
IN THE BOOK, WHICH IS A GOOD
READ.
YOU LAY THINGS OUT-- WELL, LIKE
AN INVESTIGATOR.
YOU LAY THINGS OUT IN AN ORDERLY
WAY.
IT'S AN INTERESTING READ.
A VERY INTERESTING READ.
I RECOMMEND IT TO PEOPLE.
I HAVE TO SAY ROD ROSENSTEIN
DOES NOT COME OFF GREAT IN THIS
BOOK.
YOU MENTION HE FEELS LIKE THE
BLAME FOR FIRING COMB SEGOING TO
BE PINNED ON HIM.
HE'S AFRAID IT'S GOING TO BE
PINNED ON HIM BECAUSE HE GAVE
THE PRESIDENT A LETTER JUSTICING
THE FIRING OF JAMES COMEY.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> Stephen: DO YOU HAVE ANY
IDEA WHY HE WOULD DO THAT IF HE
DIDN'T, IT WAS ACTUALLY
JUSTIFIED?
BECAUSE YOU AND COMEY IN YOUR
BOOK AND IN HIS BOOK ARE VERY
CLEAR WHERE YOU WILL NOT ALLOW
YOURSELF TO BE PUSHED, WHERE YOU
WILL NOT GO.
AND I GET THE SENSE THAT ROD
ROSENSTEIN FEELS HE WAS PUSHED
INTO A PLACE HE DIDN'T WANT TO
BE.
>> LOOK, I CAN'T-- I CAN'T TELL
YOU WHAT'S IN ROD'S HEAD, BUT
FROM WHAT I OBSERVED, I DON'T
THINK THAT ROD REGRETTED WRITING
THE MEMO.
I'M SURE HE WOULD STILL STAND BY
THAT TO THIS DAY.
WHAT HE WAS TROUBLED BY WAS THE
ADMINISTRATION'S EFFORTS TO MAKE
IT SEEM AS IF THE ENTIRE THING
WAS HIS IDEA WHEN IN FACT, HE
KIND OF STEPPED INTO THE PROCESS
AT THE LAST SECOND AND
VOLUNTEERED TO WRITE THAT MEMO.
>> Stephen: ONE OF THE-- ONE
OF THE THINGS THAT YOU-- NOT IN
THE BOOK BUT IN INTERVIEWS, YOU
SAID THAT-- THE TWO OF YOU
DISCUSSED, ROD ROSENSTEIN
BROUGHT UP THE IDEA OF INVOKING
THE 25th AMENDMENT WHICH
ALLOWS THE VICE PRESIDENT OR THE
MAJORITY OF THE CABINET, THE
SENATE AND HOUSE LEADERS TO
REMOVE THE PRESIDENT FROM
OFFICE.
>> THAT WAS.
>> Stephen: HOW DID THAT COME
UP AGAIN?
I KNOW PELLEY ASKED YOU THIS
QUESTION.
I'M GOING TO ASK YOU AGAIN-- HOW
DID THAT SUBJECT COME UP?
>> IFT CAME UP IN THE MIDDLE OF
A CHAOTIC AND LONG CONVERSATION
ABOUT WHAT WERE WE GOING TO DO
NEXT?
AND, AGAIN, I CAN'T EVEN
DESCRIBE TO YOU HOW
HEAD-SPINNING THIS WAS TO BE THE
HIGHEST RANKING OFFICIAL IN THE
F.B.I., AND ONE OF THE HIGHEST
RANKING OFFICIALS IN THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT CONSIDERING, WE HAVE
A PRESIDENT WHO WE THINK MAY
HAVE ATTEMPTED TO OBSTRUCT
JUSTICE, MAY ALSO PRESENT A
NATIONAL SECURITY THREAT TO THE
NATION.
WHAT DO WE DO ABOUT THIS?
IN MY LANE THAT MEANS
INVESTIGATION, RIGHT.
I'M RUNNING THE INVESTIGATORS.
SO THE QUESTION FOR ME WAS DO WE
INVESTIGATE THIS?
IS IT FSO, HOW?
WHAT'S THE BEST WAY TO DO IT?
AND ROD WAS REALLY JUST KIND OF
SPIN THRIEWG A NUMBER OF
DIFFERENT TOPICS.
THAT'S ONE THICK HE MENTIONED IN
THE COURSE OF THAT CHAOTIC
CONVERSATION.
IT'S NOT SOMETHING THAT I'M
AWARE OF THAT EVER WENT ANY
FURTHER THAN THAT-- THAT BRIEF
MENTION.
>> Stephen: SO THE QUESTION
WAS IF WE HAD TO GET THE
PRESIDENT OUT OF OFFICE, HOW
WOULD I DO THAT?
>> WHAT ARE THE WAYS YOU COULD
--
>> Stephen: REMOVE A PRESIDENT
FROM OFFICE.
OKAY.
LINDSEY GRAHAM HAS CALLED THIS
A-- HE-- LET ME GET THIS RIGHT.
HE WANTS TO INVESTIGATE A
POTENTIAL COUP.
HOW COUP-YDID IT FEEL TO YOU IN
THE MOMENT?
IT'S A CONSTITUTIONAL COUP IN A
WAY, BUT IT'S A GREW.
>> I THINK THAT'S A
CONTRADICTION IN AND OF ITSELF.
>> Stephen: A CONSTITUTIONAL
COUP?
>> YEAH.
>> Stephen: LIKE JUMBO SHRIMP,
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
(  LAUGHTER  ).
>> IT WAS NOT VERY COUP-Y.
AGAIN, IT WAS A MENTION IN THE
MIDSTAVE WIDE-RANGING
CONVERSATION.
I'M NOT AWARE THAT ROD EVER TOOK
ANY EFFORTS TO PURSUE THAT.
I'M NOT AWARE OF ANY MEET
BUSINESS IT OR OTHER DISCUSSIONS
ON IT.
IT WAS FOR ME REALLY AN
INDICATOR OF JUST HOW FRENZIED
AND FRAUGHT THE SITUATION WAS
THAT WE WERE IN.
AND THOSE ARE THE KIND OF THINGS
THAT WERE BOUNCED AROUND.
>> Stephen: LET'S GET TO THE
MUELLER PROBE FOR JUST A MOMENT
HERE.
IS THERE ANYTHING IN THE LAST
TWO YEARS THAT MAKES YOU LESLESS
SUSPICIOUS OF THE PRESIDENT, OR
LESS INDICATIVE THAT HE HAD
IMPROPER RELATIONSHIPS WITH THE
RUSSIANS, POSSIBLE COLLUSION OR
CONSPIRACY?
>> NO.
( LAUGHTER )
DID I ANSWER TOO QUICKLY?
>> Stephen: NO
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
IT DOES SEEM ODD-- IT DOES SEEM
ODD IT MIGHT BE JUST SORT OF
USEFUL FOR HIM TO SAY OR DO
ANYTHING THAT PUTIN WOULDN'T
LIKE, JUST TO SORT OF TAKE OF
HEAT OFF OF HIM, MAKE HIM SEEP
LESS SUSPICIOUS, BUT HE WON'T DO
THAT.
>> THAT'S DEFINITELY TRUE.
AND I THINK ON THE-- IN ADDITION
TO THAT, AS A RESULT OF THE WORK
THAT THE MUELLER TEAM HAS DONE
AND WHAT WE KNOW OF THAT WORK
FROM WHAT'S BEEN DISCLOSED TO
THE PUBLIC, I MEAN, YOU HAVE AN
INCREDIBLE NUMBER OF PEOPLE IN
THE CAMPAIGN, CLOSE TO THE
PRESIDENT, WHO HAD NUMEROUS
CONTACTS WITH RUSSIANS, PEOPLE
CONNECTED TO RUSSIAN
INTELLIGENCE.
AND NOW WE HAVE MANY OF THOSE
SAME PEOPLE WHO ACTIVELY TRIED
TO COVER UP THOSE CONTACTS.
I MEAN, IT'S-- IT ALL SEEMS TO
GET MORE SUSPICIOUS EVERY DAY.
>> Stephen: WE HAVE TO TAKE A
BREAK.
DON'T GO AWAY.
WHEN WE COME BACK, WE'RE GOING
TO TALK MORE ABOUT THE MUELLER
INVESTIGATION.
♪
Now it's your turn to play.
I Hear it in the Background and
she's Watching too, saying
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
♪
[FRIEND]
I've never seen that before.
♪
I have...
(crunch)
HVR Dips.
You either love it or you really
love it.
Sometimes the best time
is time you make for yourself.
AVEENO® Daily
Moisturizing Lotion
improves skin hydration
in just one day.
And for twice the moisture,
try the body wash too.
AVEENO®.
Naturally
Beautiful
Results®.
After my divorce
I was looking for a companion
and we-we had a connection
Corny as it sounds, it was
love at first sight
It was kismet.
Adopt Love at our National
Adoption Event.
This weekend at your
local PetSmart®.
When nighttime
nasal congestion closes in,
Breathe Right strips
are designed to simply
open your nose right back up.
♪
Breathe better. Sleep better.
Breathe Right.
>> Stephen: WELCOME BACK,
EVERYBODY.
WE'RE HERE WITH FORMER DEPUTY
DIRECTOR OF THE F.B.I., ANDREW
McCABE, THE AUTHOR OF THE HIS
NEW BOOK "THE THREAT."
WE HAVE LEARNED A FAIR AMOUNT
OVER THE LAST COUPLE OF YEARS OF
FORMER DIRECTOR MUELLER'S
INVESTIGATION THROUGH SENTENCING
MEMOS, THROUGH COURT FILINGS.
>> RIGHT.
>> Stephen: WE'VE LEARNED SOME
OF WHAT HE'S LEARNED.
ARE THERE THINGS THAT YOU KNEW
THAT HAD ALREADY BEEN LEARNED IN
THE RUSSIA INVESTIGATION BEFORE
YOU LEFT THAT ARE SIGNIFICANT
DETAILS THAT WE HAVE NOT LEARNED
YET?
>> SURE.
THERE'S CERTAINLY INFORMATION --
>> Stephen: WHAT ARE THOSE
THINGS?
(  LAUGHTER  )
>> WELL... I, OF COURSE, CANNOT
DISCUSS THOSE THINGS.
>> Stephen: I MEAN, ARE THEY
LIKE A-RUG-A!
ON A SCALE OF EH, TO A-RUG-A.
WHERE WOULD YOU PUT THEM?
>> I DON'T KNOW THAT I CAN
ESTIMATE YOUR A-RUG-A SCALE.
>> IT GOES LIKE THIS, EH, AND
A-RUG-A.
>> SOMEWHERE IN THE MIDDLE.
>> Stephen: SOMEWHERE IN THE
MIDDLE.
OKAY.
SOME PEOPLE IN-- IN DEFENSE OF
THE PEOPLE WHO HAVE ALREADY BEEN
CHARGED, IT'S A PROCESS CRIME.
IT'S A PROCESS CRIME, ANDY.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL, ANDY.
IT'S PROCESS CRIMES.
WHAT DO YOU SAY TO PEOPLE WHO
SAY, THEY'RE PROCESS CRIMES?
YOU'RE NIT-PICKING.
>> WHEN I WAS AN INVESTIGATION,
I DON'T ANY FEDERAL INVESTIGATOR
WOULD SAY TO YOU LYING TO A
FEDERAL INVESTIGATOR DURING THE
COURSE OF AN INVESTIGATION IS A
PROCESS CRIME.
WE TAKE THAT PRETTY SERIOUSLY.
>> Stephen: OF COURSE YOU TAKE
THAT SERIOUSLY, IT'S YOUR JOB.
ARE YOU THE PROCESS.
THAT'S WHY IT'S IMPORTANT TO
YOU.
>> IF WE CAN'T COUNT ON, YOU
KNOW, THE INFORMATION WE GET WE
HAVE A HARDER TIME
INVESTIGATING.
>> Stephen: ONE OF THE THINGS
ABOUT THIS BOOK-- WHICH, AGAIN,
I ENJOYED READING IT.
I RECOMMEND IT TO PEOPLE-- WE
GOT YOUR EYEWITNESS ACCOUNT OF
MANY THINGS THAT WE ALREADY HAD
REPORTS ABOUT.
>> RIGHT.
>> Stephen: NOW, WE HEARD
RUMORS OR REPORTS, EITHER
THROUGH "THE NEW YORK TIMES" OR
"THE WALL STREET JOURNAL" OR
"BUZZ FEED" OR "THE WASHINGTON
POST," OF WHAT HAPPENED IN
MEETINGS WITH DONALD TRUMP, WHAT
HAPPENED CONSIDERING THE
25th AMENDMENT.
>> RIGHT.
>> Stephen: THE-- THE NEED TO
GET ROBERT MUELLER.
THERE ARE SO MANY THINGS IN HERE
THEY ALREADY KNEW ABOUT.
I GOT YOUR FRESH PERSPECTIVE ON
IT, AND I GOT AN IDEA OF WHAT IT
FELT LIKE TO BE IN THE ROOM.
>> SURE.
>> Stephen: WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THE REPORTING ON THE
INVESTIGATION SO FAR?
WE GET A LOT OF REPORTS FROM
"THE WASHINGTON POST," "THE NEW
YORK TIMES."
ARE THEY ACCURATE?
WHAT DO YOU THINK, IN GENERAL
BHOW FACTUAL THOSE REPORTS ARE?
BECAUSE THE PRESIDENT CALLS THEM
ALL "FAKE NEWS."
>> I THINK A LOT OF THE-- I
THINK THE REPORTING HAS BEEN
EXTRAORDINARY.
I THINK THERE'S A-- THERE'S
CLEARLY AN-- I'VE NEVER SEEN THE
LEVEL OF RESOURCES DEDICATED TO
THIS SORT OF WORK THAT YOU
CURRENTLY HAVE UNDER THIS
ADMINISTRATION, RIGHT.
SO THE NUMBER AND SCOPE OF
REALLY TALENTED REPORTERS THAT
ARE-- THAT ARE WORKING ON THIS
TOPIC DAY IN, DAY OUT.
AND THEY ARE GOING TO CONTINUE
TO PEEL BACK THE ONION ON THE
FACTS THAT THEY HAVE ACCESS TO.
SOMETIMES NOT TO THE BENEFIT OF
THE INVESTIGATION.
SO AS AN INVESTIGATOR, IT'S
SOMETHING THAT CONCERNS YOU VERY
MUCH, TO BE ABLE TO ENSURE THAT
INVESTIGATIVE SENSITIVE
INFORMATION DOES NOT MAKE IT--
>> Stephen: THIS BOOK, OF
COURSE, IS IN?
WAYS ABOUT THE INVESTIGATION, AT
LEAST THE ORIGIN OF IT.
IF YOU WERE STILL IN THE F.B.I.,
WOULD YOU WANT THIS BOOK OUT
THERE?
>> THAT'S A GREAT QUESTION.
>> Stephen: THANK YOU.
( LAUGHTER )
>> AS AN INTERVIEWER, I
APPRECIATE A GOOD QUESTION.
>> Stephen: YES, YES.
( LAUGHTER )
YOU'RE UNDER OATH, BY THE WAY.
YOU'RE UNDER OATH RIGHT NOW.
>> OKAY.
YOU KNOW I WORKED VERY CLOSELY
WITH THE F.B.I. IN THE PROCESS
OF GETTING THE BOOK PUBLISHED.
I'M REQUIRED TO SUBMIT THE
MANUSCRIPT TO THE F.B.I. FOR
WHAT THEY CALL PREPUBLICATION
REVIEW.
>> Stephen: WHY ARE YOU
REQUIRED TO?
BECAUSE YOU WERE ACTUALLY FIRED
FROM THE F.B.I.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> Stephen: WHAT DO YOU OWE
THE F.B.I. NOW THAT YOU'VE BEEN
CUT LOOSE?
WHY CAN'T YOU SAY WHAT YOU WANT.
YOU DON'T OWE THEM NOTHING.
>> I AM STILL, BY VIRTUE OF THE
CLEARANCES I HAD IN MY POSITION,
I'M STILL OBLIGATED TO PROTECT
NATIONAL SECURITY INFORMATION
AND THAT'S ONE OF THE WAYS THAT
GOVERNMENT ORGANIZATIONS ENSURE
THAT INFORMATION IS PROTECTED.
IT'S A PROCESS I RESPECT.
AND IT WAS-- IT TOOK A LONG TIME
AND A LOT OF WORK, BUT I'M
PLEASED WITH THE PRODUCT THAT
CAME OUT.
>> Stephen: WELL, AS AM I.
I ENJOYED IT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING
HERE, DIRECTOR.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> Stephen: "THE THREAT" IS
AVAILABLE NOW.
ANDREW McCABE, EVERYBODY!
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH
DAN LEVY.
will be, will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que será, será ♪
♪ What will be, will be ♪
♪ Whatever will be, will be ♪
♪ Que será, seráaaaaa ♪
That rocking chair would look
great in our new house.
Ahh, New house, eh?
Well, you should definitely see
how GEICO
could help you save on
homeowners insurance.
Nice tip. I'll give you two
bucks for the chair.
Two?! That's a Victorian
antique!
All right, how much for the
recliner, then?
Wait wait... how did that get
out here?
That is definitely not for sale!
Is this a yard sale?
If it's in the yard then it's...
for sale.
Oh, here we go.
GEICO. It's easy to switch
and save
on homeowners and renters
insurance.
Chili's 3 for $10 presents
our signature
sirloin steak.
Aged to perfection
and served with
a starter and drink
for just $10.
Dinner with mom, dad,
grandma and her friend Randy,
who seems to be a little more
than a friend.
Together We Chili's.
Why shop Marshalls?
Because...
Their prices will thrill you.
Whoo-hoo!
The brands will surprise you.
Mwah!
And every trip feels
like an instant victory.
Woman:
Marshalls.
Never boring.
Always surprising.
I'M MISSING OUT ON
OUR FAMILY OUTINGS
BECAUSE I CAN'T FIND A BLADDER
LEAKAGE PRODUCT THAT FITS.
EVERYTHING WAS TOO LOOSE.
BUT DEPEND® FIT-FLEX®
FEELS TAILORED TO ME.
WITH A RANGE OF SIZES
FOR ALL BODY TYPES.
DEPEND® FIT-FLEX® UNDERWEAR
IS GUARANTEED TO
BE YOUR BEST FIT.
DEPEND® FIT-FLEX® UNDERWEAR
(AVO)
Take Prilosec OTC and take
control of heartburn.
So you don't have to stash
antacids here....
Here...
or here.
Kick your antacid habit with
Prilosec OTC.
One pill a day, 24 hours, zero
heartburn.
♪
Cats will do anything
for the irresistible taste of
TEMPTATIONS™ treats.
What are you doing?
Oh hey, check this out.
TEMPTATIONS ™.
All
It Takes
Is A Shake™.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: HEY, EVERYBODY,
WELCOME BACK TO "THE LATE SHOW."
MY NEXT GUEST IS THE CO-CREATOR
AND STAR OF "SCHITT'S CREEK."
>> ROLAND, YOU BROUGHT A BABY
INTO THE STORE.
>> SHHH!
YEAH.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHY I HAVEN'T
BROUGHT HIM IN SOONER.
THIS PLACE IS PERFECT.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> YEAH, THEY SAY THAT BABIES
FALL ASLEEP QUICKEST WHEN
THEY'RE SURROUNDED BY AN EERIE,
ALMOST CRYPT-LIKE SILENCE.
>> WHAT CAN I DO TO SHORTEN YOUR
STAY IN MY STORE, ROLAND?
>> OH, JOSS WANTED ME TO PICK UP
SOME OF THIS, THIS ORGANIC APPLE
SAUCE.
ORGANIC.
LISTEN TO ME.
WHO AM I, GWYNETH PALTROW?
>> NO, NO, YOU'RE NOT.
>> Stephen: PLEASE WELCOME BACK
TO "THE LATE SHOW," DAN
LEVY!
♪ ♪ ♪
( APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: I HOPE THE PEOPLE
AT HOME CAN SEE HOW SPARKLY YOUR
SWEATER IS.
>> I CAME DRESSED AS MICHAEL
JACKSON'S GLOVE TONIGHT SO I
HOPE THAT'S A WONDERFUL THING.
>> Stephen: NICE TO SEE YOU
AGAIN.
>> HOW DO I FOLLOW THAT?
>> Stephen: OH, THE DIRECTOR--
>> I WAS BACKSTAGE TRYING TO GET
ANSWERS FOR ALL THE QUESTIONS HE
COULDN'T GIVE YOU ANSWERS FOR.
AND, UNFORTUNATELY, WHEN YOU'RE
THE DIRECTOR OF THE F.B.I., I
CAN'T GIVE YOU THOSE ANSWERS FOR
ME.
>> Stephen: YOU HAVE THE SAME
GLASS THOUGH.
YOU COULD BE A G-MAN.
>> HE'S MUCH, MUCH SMARTER THAN
I AM.
>> Stephen: I DON'T KNOW, I
DON'T KNOW.
>> I CAN ALMOST ASSURE YOU GLI
DON'T-- I'LL BUY IT.
I BELIEVE.
YOU'RE DUMB.
>> HE CAME OUT IN A SUIT, AND I
CAME OUT IN THIS.
>> Stephen: OKAY, OKAY.
YOU'VE BEEN HERE BEFORE.
THANKS FOR COMING BAG.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR HAVING
ME.
>> Stephen: YOU KNOW THE DRILL
WITH THE TITLE OF THIS SHOW.
CBS HAS MADE A REAL RULE WHAT WE
CANNOT SAY THE TITLE OF THIS
SHOW WITHOUT PUTTING UP A LOWER
THIRD WHEN SAYING THE TITLE OF
THE SHOW.
YOU BEING THE GUEST I WILL ALLOW
YOU TO SAY THE TITLE OF THE SHOW
FIRST.
>> THE TITLE OF THE SHOW IS
"SCHITT'S CREEK."
I HAVE COCREATED THE SHOW
THIS COULD GO ON ALL NIGHT.
"SCHITT'S CREEK."
>> Stephen: IT COULD, IT
THIS COULD GO ON ALL NIGHT.
COULD, BUT WE SHOULD PROBABLY
>> Stephen: IT COULD, IT
STOP.
COULD, BUT WE SHOULD PROBABLY
>> VERY PROVOCATIVE TITLE, I
STOP.
GUESS.
>> VERY PROVOCATIVE TITLE, I
>> Stephen: IT HAS RECENTLY
GUESS.
HAD AN EXPLOSION OF POPULARITY.
>> Stephen: IT HAS RECENTLY
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW OR WHY OR
HAD AN EXPLOSION OF POPULARITY.
WHERE, BUT I'M GLAD IT HAPPENED.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW OR WHY OR
>> Stephen: REALLY, NO, IT'S
WHERE, BUT I'M GLAD IT HAPPENED.
ALWAYS BEEN A FUNNY SHOW, BUT
>> Stephen: REALLY, NO, IT'S
THE LAST YEAR IT'S COMPLETELY
ALWAYS BEEN A FUNNY SHOW, BUT
TAKEN OFF.
THE LAST YEAR IT'S COMPLETELY
THAT MUST FEEL FANTASTIC.
TAKEN OFF.
>> IT FEELS GREAT.
THAT MUST FEEL FANTASTIC.
MOST SHEEFERS FIVE SEASONS GET
>> IT FEELS GREAT.
CANCELED, AND SOMEHOW WE'RE
MOST SHEEFERS FIVE SEASONS GET
STILL AROUND AND DOING BETTER
CANCELED, AND SOMEHOW WE'RE
THAN EAR WHICH SAY WONDERFUL,
STILL AROUND AND DOING BETTER
WONDERFUL THING.
THAN EAR WHICH SAY WONDERFUL,
THANK YOU TO THE PEOPLE WHO HAVE
WONDERFUL THING.
BEEN WATCHING AND SUPPORTING
THANK YOU TO THE PEOPLE WHO HAVE
( APPLAUSE ).
BEEN WATCHING AND SUPPORTING
>> Stephen: ONE THING THAT
( APPLAUSE ).
DEFINITELY WILL HELP, LAST
>> Stephen: ONE THING THAT
WEEK-- WAS IT LAST WEEK-- YOU
DEFINITELY WILL HELP, LAST
GOT A VERY EXCITING ENDORSEMENT.
WEEK-- WAS IT LAST WEEK-- YOU
>> YES, WE DID.
GOT A VERY EXCITING ENDORSEMENT.
>> Stephen: DO YOU WANT TO
>> YES, WE DID.
TELL THE PEOPLE?
>> Stephen: DO YOU WANT TO
>> YEAH, WELL, I ACTUALLY WAS IN
TELL THE PEOPLE?
THE CAB WHEN THIS HAPPENED.
>> YEAH, WELL, I ACTUALLY WAS IN
MA RYE MARIAH CAREY TWEETED
THE CAB WHEN THIS HAPPENED.
ABOUT THE SHOW.
MA RYE MARIAH CAREY TWEETED
YOU CAN APPLAUD MARIAH CAREY, I
ABOUT THE SHOW.
THINK.
YOU CAN APPLAUD MARIAH CAREY, I
THAT'S A WONDERFUL THING.
THINK.
WATCH "SCHITT'S CREEK."
THAT'S A WONDERFUL THING.
>> Stephen: WHAT DOES IT MEAN
WATCH "SCHITT'S CREEK."
TO YOU?
>> Stephen: WHAT DOES IT MEAN
>> IT'S A PARTICULARLY
TO YOU?
MEANINGFUL THING FOR ME BECAUSE
>> IT'S A PARTICULARLY
AS A YOUNG CHILD, SHE WAS
MEANINGFUL THING FOR ME BECAUSE
EVERYTHING TO ME.
AS A YOUNG CHILD, SHE WAS
I KNOW HER ENTIRE CATALOG.
EVERYTHING TO ME.
THERE WERE POSTERS ON THE WALL.
I KNOW HER ENTIRE CATALOG.
IT WAS A WHOLE THING.
THERE WERE POSTERS ON THE WALL.
SO THEN WHEN SOMETHING LIKE THIS
IT WAS A WHOLE THING.
HAPPENS, SOMETHING INSIDE OF ME
SO THEN WHEN SOMETHING LIKE THIS
GETS TRIGGERED, AND I-- AND I'M
HAPPENS, SOMETHING INSIDE OF ME
OFTEN-- YOU KNOW, IN THIS CASE I
GETS TRIGGERED, AND I-- AND I'M
WAS IN A CAB-- I COULDN'T SCREAM
OFTEN-- YOU KNOW, IN THIS CASE I
IN A CAB, STEPHEN.
WAS IN A CAB-- I COULDN'T SCREAM
I COULDN'T DO IT.
IN A CAB, STEPHEN.
>> Stephen: NO, THEY DON'T
I COULDN'T DO IT.
LIKE THAT.
>> Stephen: NO, THEY DON'T
IN UBER, YES.
LIKE THAT.
IN A CAB, NO.
IN UBER, YES.
IT'S EXTRA.
IN A CAB, NO.
>> THEY CHARGE ME EXTRA FOR
IT'S EXTRA.
THAT.
>> THEY CHARGE ME EXTRA FOR
>> Stephen: IT'S SURGE PRICING
THAT.
FOR THE SCREAMING.
>> Stephen: IT'S SURGE PRICING
WHAT DO YOU DO?
FOR THE SCREAMING.
THAT MUST HAVE BEEN AMAZING.
WHAT DO YOU DO?
A CHRYSANTHEMUM BLOOMING INSIDE
THAT MUST HAVE BEEN AMAZING.
OF YOU.
A CHRYSANTHEMUM BLOOMING INSIDE
>> IT WAS MORE LIKE AN
OF YOU.
ANXIETY-INDUCED PANIC BECAUSE I
>> IT WAS MORE LIKE AN
DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO PHYSICALLY
ANXIETY-INDUCED PANIC BECAUSE I
MANIFEST THE EXCITEMENT SO I WAS
DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO PHYSICALLY
SORT OF BOTTLING IT UP INSIDE,
MANIFEST THE EXCITEMENT SO I WAS
SENDING PEOPLE TEXT MESSAGES IN
SORT OF BOTTLING IT UP INSIDE,
ALL CAPS SAYING, "MARIAH."
SENDING PEOPLE TEXT MESSAGES IN
AND THEY WOULD WRITE BACK, "WHAT
ALL CAPS SAYING, "MARIAH."
ABOUT HER?"
AND THEY WOULD WRITE BACK, "WHAT
AND I WOULD FORGET THEY DIDN'T
ABOUT HER?"
SEE THE TEXT.
AND I WOULD FORGET THEY DIDN'T
NEEDLESS TO SAY, I HAVE NEVER
SEE THE TEXT.
HAD AN OUTLET FOR MY ENTHUSIASM
NEEDLESS TO SAY, I HAVE NEVER
UNTIL RIGHT NOW, WHERE I FEEL
HAD AN OUTLET FOR MY ENTHUSIASM
LIKE I'M REALLY EXCITED ABOUT
UNTIL RIGHT NOW, WHERE I FEEL
THIS.
LIKE I'M REALLY EXCITED ABOUT
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
THIS.
IT'S A FULL-CIRC EEL.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: DO YOU WANT TO
IT'S A FULL-CIRC EEL.
THANK HER?
>> Stephen: DO YOU WANT TO
DO YOU WANT TO THANK HER.
THANK HER?
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
DO YOU WANT TO THANK HER.
ENDORSING OUR LITTLE SHOW.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
IT'S A FULL-CIRCLE MOMENT FOR ME
ENDORSING OUR LITTLE SHOW.
AND I THINK, YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES
IT'S A FULL-CIRCLE MOMENT FOR ME
IN MY SHORT-LIVED CAREER, IT'S
AND I THINK, YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES
VERY WONDERFUL TO HAVE THESE
IN MY SHORT-LIVED CAREER, IT'S
FULL-CIRCLE MOMENT S.
VERY WONDERFUL TO HAVE THESE
>> Stephen:  CONGRATULATIONS.
FULL-CIRCLE MOMENT S.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> Stephen:  CONGRATULATIONS.
IT WENT FROM McCABE TO A MA
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
MARIAH CAREY FAN MOMENT.
IT WENT FROM McCABE TO A MA
>> Stephen: IN THE SHOW, THEY
MARIAH CAREY FAN MOMENT.
HAVE SOME FANTASTIC OUTFITS
>> Stephen: IN THE SHOW, THEY
BECAUSE THEY'RE, AGAIN, FORMERLY
HAVE SOME FANTASTIC OUTFITS
VERY RICH.
BECAUSE THEY'RE, AGAIN, FORMERLY
AND YOU REALLY DO A BEAUTIFUL
VERY RICH.
JOB OF SHOWING JUST HOW
AND YOU REALLY DO A BEAUTIFUL
SOMETIMES, JUST HOW DUMB LOOKING
JOB OF SHOWING JUST HOW
THE RICH CAN LOOK.
SOMETIMES, JUST HOW DUMB LOOKING
( LAUGHTER )
THE RICH CAN LOOK.
TELL ME ABOUT THIS OUTFIT.
( LAUGHTER )
>> YEAH, THAT PARTICULAR HOODED
TELL ME ABOUT THIS OUTFIT.
SWEAT SHERT, IT'S FROM HELLED
>> YEAH, THAT PARTICULAR HOODED
MET LANG, AND IT'S A MOHOCK ON A
SWEAT SHERT, IT'S FROM HELLED
CASHMERE SWEATSHIRT WITH THUMB
MET LANG, AND IT'S A MOHOCK ON A
HOLES CUT OUT FOR THE
CASHMERE SWEATSHIRT WITH THUMB
CONVENIENCE OF YOUR THUMBS.
HOLES CUT OUT FOR THE
>> Stephen: DID YOU MAKE THIS
CONVENIENCE OF YOUR THUMBS.
UP?
>> Stephen: DID YOU MAKE THIS
>> NO, I BOUGHT THAT ON eBAY.
UP?
SO THIS IS SOMETHING THAT PEOPLE
>> NO, I BOUGHT THAT ON eBAY.
OWN, I GUESS.
SO THIS IS SOMETHING THAT PEOPLE
I CERTAINLY DO NOW.
OWN, I GUESS.
(  LAUGHTER  ).
I CERTAINLY DO NOW.
>> Stephen: YOU HAVE-- YOU
(  LAUGHTER  ).
HAVE ALL THESE?
>> Stephen: YOU HAVE-- YOU
OH, YEAH, I KEEP ALL THESE
HAVE ALL THESE?
OUTFITS.
OH, YEAH, I KEEP ALL THESE
THIS WAS A NEPREEN SWEATER, AND
OUTFITS.
WE'RE SHOOTING IN THE DEFEND
THIS WAS A NEPREEN SWEATER, AND
SUMMER AND IT'S MADE OF SCUBA
WE'RE SHOOTING IN THE DEFEND
MATERIAL.
SUMMER AND IT'S MADE OF SCUBA
WHY YOU WOULD DRESS YOURSELF IN
MATERIAL.
SCUBA-- AND I'M IN CHARGE.
WHY YOU WOULD DRESS YOURSELF IN
WHY I WOULD CHOOSE TO DRESS
SCUBA-- AND I'M IN CHARGE.
MYSELF SOME SCUBA MATERIAL IS A
WHY I WOULD CHOOSE TO DRESS
TESTAMENT TO HOW LESS SMART I AM
MYSELF SOME SCUBA MATERIAL IS A
THAN McCABE.
TESTAMENT TO HOW LESS SMART I AM
>> Stephen: TALCUM POWDER FOR
THAN McCABE.
THAT DAY.
>> Stephen: TALCUM POWDER FOR
CONGRATULATIONS ON THE SHOW.
THAT DAY.
CONGRATULATIONS ON MARIAH CAREY.
CONGRATULATIONS ON THE SHOW.
>> THANK YOU.
CONGRATULATIONS ON MARIAH CAREY.
I MEAN, IT'S A WONDERFUL THING.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Stephen: YES.
I MEAN, IT'S A WONDERFUL THING.
( APPLAUSE ).
>> Stephen: YES.
>> SO NICE TO SEE YOU.
( APPLAUSE ).
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> SO NICE TO SEE YOU.
>> Stephen: "SCHITT'S CREEK"
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
AIRS WEDNESDAY NIGHTS ON
>> Stephen: "SCHITT'S CREEK"
POP TV.
AIRS WEDNESDAY NIGHTS ON
DAN LEVY, EVERYBODY!
POP TV.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH A
DAN LEVY, EVERYBODY!
PERFORMANCE BY SIGRID.
Before I had the shooting,
burning of
diabetic nerve pain
these feet raised
a bouncing boy and
climbed the ladder in
the hardware business.
But I couldn't bear my
diabetic nerve pain any longer.
So I talked to my doctor
and he prescribed LYRICA.
LYRICA may cause
serious allergic reactions,
suicidal thoughts or actions.
Tell your doctor right
away if you have these,
new or worse depression,
unusual changes in mood
or behavior, swelling,
trouble breathing,
rash, hives, blisters,
muscle pain with fever,
tired feeling,
or blurry vision.
Common side effects:
dizziness, sleepiness,
weight gain, swelling
of hands, legs, and feet.
Don't drink alcohol
while taking LYRICA.
Don't drive or use
machinery until you
know how LYRICA
affects you.
Those who've had a
drug or alcohol problem
may be more likely
to misuse LYRICA.
Now I have less
diabetic nerve pain.
Ask your doctor about LYRICA.
It's absolute confidence
in 30,000 precision parts.
Now I have less
diabetic nerve pain.
Or it isn't.
It's inspected by
Mercedes-Benz
factory-trained technicians.
Or it isn't.
It's backed by an
unlimited mileage warranty,
or it isn't.
For those who never settle,
it's either Mercedes-Benz
Certified Pre-Owned,
or it isn't.
The Mercedes-Benz Certified
Pre-Owned Sales Event.
Now through February 28th.
Only at your authorized
Mercedes-Benz dealer.
♪ ♪ ♪
♪
(Butcher)
We both know you're not just
looking for pork chops.
You're searching
for something more...
...red-blooded.
Right this way.
You thirst for adrenaline,
you hunger for raw power.
Well, you've come
to the right place.
The road is yours, dig in.
♪ ♪
Only TYLENOL® Rapid Release Gels
have laser drilled holes.
They release medicine fast,
for fast pain relief.
TYLENOL®
(SASS)
Do humans LIKE
useless pieces of cheap metal?
(SPRINTERN)
He means, you need a
much better phone.
(PAUL)
If you lease an iPhone
from Sprint
you get another one
on them.
(SPRINTERN)
And they'll give you an
Apple Watch.
(VO)
Switch today and get the amazing
iPhone XR and Apple Watch
on us.
For people with hearing loss,
They're better together.
visit Sprintrelay.com
-Their Béarnaise sauce here
is the best in town.
[ Soft piano music playing ]
Mm, uh, what do you do for fun?
-Not this.
♪
-Oh, what am I into?
Mostly Progressive's
Name Your Price Tool.
Helps people find coverage
options based on their budget.
Flo has it, I want it,
it's a whole thing,
and she's right there.
-Yeah, she's my ride.
This date's lame.
He has pics of you on his phone.
-They're very tasteful.
♪ ♪
Just gonna leave you alone.
>> Stephen: HERE PERFORMING
"DON'T FEEL LIKE CRYING" FROM
HER ANTICIPATED ALBUM, "SUCKER
PUNCH," LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
SIGRID!
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ I KNOW I SHOULD BE
ORDERING TAKEOUT
♪ SITTING ON MY COUCH
THAT'S WHAT YOU DO
♪ I KNOW I SHOULD BE
ALL IN MY FEELINGS
♪ STARING AT THE CEILING
BUT HERE'S THE TRUTH
♪ WALLOWING IN IT
WOULD BE SUCH A WASTE
♪ THAT ISN'T GONNA FIX IT ANYWAY
NO, OH
♪ OOH, YEAH
I DRY MY EYES 'CAUSE
♪ I DON'T FEEL LIKE CRYING
OOH, YEAH
♪ AT LEAST TONIGHT, NO
I DON'T FEEL LIKE CRYING, CRYING
♪ HOPE YOU DON'T BLAME ME
FOR WHAT I'M SAYING
♪ MY HEART IS ACHING
DO YOU FEEL IT TOO
♪ I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND
THAT I'M DEALING
♪ IT'S MY WAY OF HEALING
BUT HERE IS THE TRUTH
♪ WALLOWING IN IT
WOULD BE SUCH A WASTE
♪ THAT ISN'T GONNA FIX IT ANYWAY
NO, OH
♪ OOH, YEAH
I DRY MY EYES 'CAUSE
♪ I DON'T FEEL LIKE CRYING
OOH, YEAH
♪ AT LEAST TONIGHT, NO
I DON'T FEEL LIKE CRYING
♪ OOH
IT HASN'T HIT ME YET
♪ AND I KNOW IF I GO HOME
I'M GONNA GET UPSET
♪ YEAH, IT HASN'T HIT ME YET
AND I KNOW IF I GO HOME
♪ I'M GONNA GET UPSET
OOH
♪ IT HASN'T HIT ME YET
AND I KNOW IF I GO HOME
♪ I'M GONNA GET UPSET
AT LEAST TONIGHT, NO
♪ I DON'T FEEL LIKE
CRYING, CRYING
♪ WALLOWING IN IT
WOULD BE SUCH A WASTE
♪ THAT ISN'T GONNA FIX IT ANYWAY
NO, OH
♪ OOH, YEAH
I DRY MY EYES 'CAUSE
♪ I DON'T FEEL LIKE CRYING
OOH, YEAH
♪ AT LEAST TONIGHT, NO
I DON'T FEEL LIKE CRYING
♪ OOH
IT HASN'T HIT ME YET
♪ AND I KNOW IF I GO HOME
I'M GONNA GET UPSET
♪ AT LEAST TONIGHT, NO
I DON'T FEEL LIKE CRYING
♪ OOH
IT HASN'T HIT ME YET
♪ AND I KNOW IF I GO HOME
I'M GONNA GET UPSET
♪ YEAH, IT HASN'T HIT ME YET
AND I KNOW IF I GO HOME
♪ I'M GONNA GET UPSET
OOH
♪ IT HASN'T HIT ME YET
AND I KNOW IF I GO HOME
♪ I'M GONNA GET UPSET
AT LEAST TONIGHT, NO
♪ I DON'T FEEL LIKE
CRYING ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: SIGRID, EVERYBODY!
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
You.
All of you.
How you live,
what you love.
That's what inspired
us to create
America's most
advanced internet.
Internet that puts
you in charge.
That protects
what's important.
It handles everything,
and reaches everywhere.
This is beyond WiFi,
this is xFi.
Simple. Easy. Awesome.
Xfinity, the
future of awesome.
♪
It hasn't always
been easy, has it?
♪
There have been days
when you doubted yourself.
♪
And days when you
were ready to quit.
♪
But you didn't.
Because you had the courage to
venture into something powerful.
Education.
If I leave you with just
three words of advice:
never...stop...growing.
[cheering]