♪
>> Steffy: Zoe, what are you
trying to say?
>> Zoe: Just that it's
understandable, you know, Hope's
connection to Phoebe.
>> Xander: Because of when she
was born, so close to her own
daughter.
Right?
>> Zoe: Can't get much closer.
You know, when, um, she looks
at Phoebe, how can she not see
Beth?
>> Brooke: Seems like being
around Phoebe would be a
constant reminder.
>> Hope: Of my own daughter?
Yeah, exactly.
That's why it's helping.
I only got to hold my own baby
once.
Just once.
But Phoebe is here now, this
beautiful girl that Steffy has
brought into our lives, and I
can hold her.
I can sing to her, I --
And for brief moments at at
time, I can feel what it would
have been like for me...
with Beth.
>> Would Zoe do it?
Would she tell?
>> Reese: I don't know!
I would just hope that she would
take time to think it over.
>> Call her, then.
>> Reese: I did. I tried.
I texted her.
>> Try again!
She can't tell anyone what we
did, Reese.
>> Wyatt: You need my help.
>> Bill: It's been a long time
since we've felt like a family.
>> Wyatt: Yeah, for several
reasons.
>> Bill: Legitimate ones.
I'm the first to admit that.
>> Wyatt: Okay.
What -- What do you want from
me?
Why am I here?
>> Bill: You're here because I'm
gonna prove my loyalty to you.
♪
>> Reese: Straight to voicemail.
>> Well, what are we supposed to
do, then?
Are we supposed to just wait
here for the cops to show up?
God, that's probably what we
deserve, isn't it?
>> Reese: Hey, don't say that.
>> [ Sighs ] That poor woman,
the actual mother.
I --
I can't even imagine what she's
going through.
>> Reese: Hope will get better,
and my daughter is safe because
I was able to arrange this.
>> You're the one who put her in
the situation to begin with.
>> Reese: It does no one any
good for the truth to come out
now.
I pray that Zoe realizes that.
I pray that she doesn't tell
anyone what I did to Hope.
>> Steffy: I think part of Hope
does see her own daughter when
she looks at Phoebe.
>> Zoe: More than you realize.
>> Steffy: What do you mean?
Did Hope say something to you?
>> Zoe: No. Not Hope.
But there is something you
should know.
[ Phoebe crying ]
>> Steffy: Oh, that's Phoebe.
Hold that thought, I'll be right
back.
[ Door opens ]
>> Xander: Okay, what is going
on?
What were you about to tell
Steffy?
>> Zoe: That's just it.
I don't know if I should.
>> Xander: But that's why we're
here, right?
There's something you wanted to
know.
>> Steffy: Look how popular you
are!
You have so many visitors!
This is Xander and Zoe.
This is Mommy's little girl.
This is my beautiful daughter.
[ Gasps ]
[ Giggles ]
>> Zoe: She's beautiful.
The noble tortilla was created
thousands of years ago
by the ancient Mayans.
So for the love of
all things delicious,
fill this storied vessel with
Queso Fresco and Oaxaca cheese.
Topped with Cotija, a cheesy
cargo worthy of the honor.
Holy Cow.
Moo.
That means really good.
Return to real food.
Dairy products made
with California milk.
From our family
farms to your table.
Return to real.
Look for the seal.
Gentle means everything,
so we improved everything.
We used 50% fewer ingredients
Added one handed pumps
And beat the
top safety standards
The new JOHNSON'S®
Choose Gentle
♪Your hunger's so bad that this
pasta looks good.♪
♪Here comes a 90, 10, 1 crew
with a Protein One bar for you.♪
♪Protein One♪
♪For all your snack
emergencies.♪
♪Protein One♪
90 calories
10 grams of protein
1 gram of sugar
>> Bill: You liked working here.
>> Wyatt: I did, yeah.
But, I mean, I'm just -- I'm
doing really well over at
Forrester right now.
>> Bill: Oh, come on, Wyatt.
Really?
What, posting things on social
media all day?
Like, you know, tap tap.
>> Wyatt: I do a lot more than
that, thank you very much.
>> Bill: At that dress farm,
you're just wasting your talent.
Come home, Wyatt.
This is where you belong.
>> Wyatt: Do I?
>> Bill: Of course you do.
You're my son.
>> Wyatt: Because I remember a
whole other conversation we had
that would speak otherwise.
>> Bill: You know me, all right?
I lose my temper, I say things I
don't mean, and I'm not proud of
it.
I'm working on it.
>> Wyatt: You said I had no
guts.
You sure you want somebody
working here like that?
>> Bill: Yes! I mean, no!
I mean, you have guts, Wyatt.
You had enough guts to stand up
to me, to do what was right when
I wouldn't.
You're damn right I want you
working here.
>> Wyatt: You kicked me out.
>> Bill: Look, I don't know what
was happening to me back then.
I thought I didn't need you.
I was wrong, and I'll do
whatever I can to fix it.
What do you want me to say?
I mean, I'd fall on my sword if
I was still wearing it.
>> Wyatt: You said you didn't
realize what was happening at
the time.
Should I refresh your memory?
The way you pursued Steffy,
the way you bribed me into
getting Liam to believe that you
two were still together, is that
it?
>> Bill: I don't want to think
about any of that, Wyatt.
>> Wyatt: It was your son's own
pregnant wife, Dad!
Who -- Who does that?
>> Bill: I do.
I did.
I screwed up, big-time, and I
will do whatever I have to to
repair it, to make this family
right.
I used to preach "Family first."
I lived that, until I turned my
back on everyone.
But we can get it back, Wyatt.
We can have this family again.
I mean, look at my relationship
with Will, all right?
I've already proved it.
I've stepped up for him.
I'm gonna step up for you.
That's what I want.
I want to be the kind of man
that you need me to be, the kind
of father that you need me to
be.
Come back to Spencer.
This is where you belong.
>> Reese: Okay, okay.
I brought you into this.
I will testify to that if the
time comes, all right?
You were -- You were driving
into Los Angeles to help a
friend.
You didn't know what you were
being dragged into.
You don't know the birth mother.
>> Hope.
You said her name was Hope.
I know I don't know her,
but I feel like I do
I can picture her -- her guilt,
her confusion about all of this,
and we did that.
We caused her that pain.
She's a total stranger.
I don't know anything about her.
I should just be able to forget
her, but I can't.
I feel this -- this guilt,
this tremendous guilt.
about what we did to her.
>> Brooke: I think I understand.
I'm trying to, at least.
>> Hope: It's okay if you don't.
I mean, honestly, I can't fully
comprehend it, either.
All I know is that when I hold
Phoebe, something inside of me,
it just...
feels right, you know?
I feel complete.
>> Brooke: She really does bring
you peace, doesn't she?
>> Hope: Yeah.
Yeah, and I know it might sound
a bit...
but I really believe that Phoebe
was here for a reason.
And not just for Steffy.
And I know she is Steffy's
daughter and I respect that, but
when I hold her and I look down
at her...
every part of me feels it,
that Phoebe is here for me, too.
>> Steffy: I know, I know.
You're hungry, sweet pea.
There you go.
Let's fill you up before Kelly
wakes up, okay?
>> Xander: Is it difficult
juggling?
>> Steffy: Yeah, yeah, it can
be, but I wouldn't have it any
other way.
>> Zoe: So Phoebe fits right in
as if she was always yours.
>> Steffy: Yeah, always.
It's like I have to remind
myself I didn't carry Phoebe.
I know it sounds ridiculous,
but...
That's how quickly we connected.
Huh?
I don't care if I didn't
physically give birth to her,
and Phoebe doesn't care.
She's my daughter.
Just as much as Kelly.
Right?
Oh, I'm sorry, there was
something you had to tell me,
right?
>> Zoe: Uh...
>> Steffy: It was important?
>> Zoe: Yeah, um...
>> Steffy: Something you said I
needed to know?
>> Zoe: I -- I just wanted to
say how happy I am for you.
>> Steffy: Thank you, that's
very kind.
But what does this have to do
with Hope?
>> Zoe: Well, um, you know,
we've been talking about it at
work...
>> Xander: Yeah.
>> Zoe: And we just want to be
here for the both of you.
You know, Hope for her loss, and
you for this exciting new
chapter.
Happy birthday!
Let's blow out the
candles together!
Ok, let's huff and puff.
Like you do sometimes, Grandpa?
Well, when you have COPD,
it can be hard to breathe.
So my doctor said...
SYMBICORT can help
you breathe better-
starting within 5 minutes.
It doesn't replace a rescue
inhaler for sudden symptoms.
SYMBICORT helps provide
significant improvement
of your lung function.
SYMBICORT is for COPD,
including chronic bronchitis
and emphysema.
It should not be taken
more than twice a day.
It may increase your risk
of lung infections,
osteoporosis, and
some eye problems.
Tell your doctor if you
have a heart condition
or high blood pressure
before taking it.
SYMBICORT could mean a day
with better breathing.
Watch out, piggies!
Ask your doctor if SYMBICORT
is right for you.
If you can't afford
your medication,
AstraZeneca may be
able to help.
If you can't afford
your medication,
Ready for a lash lift?
L'Oréal's new Unlimited Lash
Lift Mascara.
1. Stretch it.
2. Tilt it.
3. Lift it.
Reach even smaller lashes.
Unlimited length.
Unlimited lift.
New Unlimited Mascara by L'Oréal
Paris.
Oh!
♪ Ozempic®! ♪
(announcer)
People with type 2 diabetes
are excited about
the potential
of once-weekly Ozempic®.
In a study with Ozempic®,
a majority of adults
lowered their blood sugar
and reached an A1C
of less than seven
and maintained it.
Oh!
Under seven?
And you may lose weight.
In the same
one-year study,
adults lost on average
up to 12 pounds.
Oh!
Up to 12 pounds?
A two-year study showed
that Ozempic® does not
increase the risk
of major cardiovascular events
like heart attack,
stroke, or death.
Oh!
No increased risk?
♪ Oh, oh, oh, Ozempic®! ♪
Ozempic® should not be the first
medicine for treating diabetes,
or for people with
type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Do not share needles or pens.
Don't reuse needles.
Do not take Ozempic® if you have
a personal or family history
of medullary thyroid cancer,
Multiple Endocrine Neoplasia
Syndrome type 2,
or if you are
allergic to Ozempic®.
Stop taking Ozempic®
and get medical help right away
if you get a lump or swelling
in your neck,
severe stomach pain, itching,
rash, or trouble breathing.
Serious side effects
may happen,
including pancreatitis.
Tell your doctor if you have
diabetic retinopathy
or vision changes.
Taking Ozempic® with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may increase the risk
for low blood sugar.
Common side effects are nausea,
vomiting, diarrhea,
stomach pain, and constipation.
Some side effects
can lead to dehydration,
which may worsen
kidney problems.
I discovered the potential
with Ozempic®.
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! Ozempic®! ♪
Ask your healthcare provider
if Ozempic® is right for you.
>> Brooke: Sugar?
Hope?
>> Hope: Hmm?
>> Brooke: [ Sighs ]
Lost in thought?
>> Hope: [ Sighs ] I suppose.
>> Brooke: Phoebe?
>> Hope: I need to tell you
something, and I --
I don't know how.
>> Brooke: I'm your mother.
You can tell me anything.
>> Hope: Um...
I don't -- I haven't even
admitted it to myself.
>> Brooke: Something about
Phoebe?
>> Hope: I know I was telling
you how comforting it is being
around her.
>> Brooke: Right.
>> Hope: But there's another
layer.
>> Brooke: Okay.
>> Hope: I'm trying to figure
out what it is.
It's this feeling and...
I guess it's almost like guilt
because I hold Phoebe and I look
at her, and I think about the
home that she and Kelly could
have if Liam and Steffy were
together.
You know, she has two children
in her house.
These two beautiful girls would
benefit from Liam living with
them.
>> Reese: I would have never
planned this.
I would have never taken
someone's child, but my child
was in danger.
I saw an opportunity.
And I know this doesn't make it
any better, but the baby has a
good home.
>> You're right, it doesn't make
it any better, not even a little
bit.
[ Door opens ]
>> Reese: Zoe!
>> Oh, my God. Did you do it?
Did you tell?
>> Zoe: No.
>> Reese: No?
>> Zoe: Yeah, I should have, but
I couldn't.
>> Reese: [ Sighs ] Thank you.
>> Zoe: Can I talk to my father,
please?
Alone.
>> Of course.
>> Zoe: Have I just made
a horrible mistake?
>> Bill: This company is your
legacy, Wyatt.
Come on, what's holding you
back?
>> Wyatt: Okay, the thing is,
I'm working for some really good
people over at Forrester right
now.
>> Bill: Unlike me.
>> Wyatt: One good person in
particular.
The woman I am living with, the
woman who you were extremely
cruel to.
Do you remember that?
Now, what's it say to Sally if I
come back here working for you,
the man who literally just
destroyed --
>> Bill: Bring her!
>> Wyatt: What?
>> Bill: You heard me.
>> Wyatt: [ Scoffs ]
Sally Spectra, here at Spencer.
>> Bill: Sure, why not?
>> Wyatt: Because she likes
fashion.
That's what her life is all
about, not -- I mean...
>> Bill: Wyatt, we publish
fashion magazines!
Hello?
Eye On Fashion.
We'll find a place for her.
I mean, if that's what it takes
to get you back here, that's
what we're gonna do.
I'll do anything, Wyatt.
I will do anything to get our
family back on track.
My mom washes the dishes...
...before she puts them in the
dishwasher.
So what does the dishwasher do?
Cascade Platinum does the work
for you,
prewashing and removing
stuck-on foods,
the first time.
Wow, that's clean!
Cascade Platinum.
I landed.
I saw my leg did not look right.
I was just finishing a ride.
I felt this awful pain in my
chest.
I had a PE blood clot in my
lung.
I was scared.
I had a DVT blood clot.
Having one really puts you in
danger of having another.
My doctor and I chose XARELTO®.
XARELTO®. To help keep me
protected.
XARELTO® is a latest-generation
blood thinner that's...
proven to treat and reduce the
risk of DVT
or PE blood clots from happening
again.
In clinical studies, almost 98%
of patients on
XARELTO® did not experience
another DVT or PE.
XARELTO® works differently.
Warfarin interferes with at
least 6 of your body's
natural blood-clotting factors.
XARELTO® is selective, targeting
just one critical factor.
Don't stop taking XARELTO®
without talking to your doctor,
as this may increase risk of
blood clots.
While taking, you may bruise
more easily,
or take longer for bleeding to
stop.
XARELTO® can cause serious, and
in rare cases, fatal bleeding.
It may increase your risk of
bleeding
if you take certain medicines.
Get help right away for
unexpected
bleeding or unusual bruising.
Do not take XARELTO®
if you have an artificial heart
valve or abnormal bleeding.
Before starting,
tell your doctor about all
planned medical
or dental procedures and any
kidney or liver problems.
Learn all you can...
to help protect yourself from
another DVT or PE.
Talk to your doctor about
XARELTO®.
>> Wyatt: You've given me a lot
to think about, that's for sure.
>> Bill: [ Chuckles ] Well, you
know, that's all I've been doing
the last few months --
thinking.
Thinking about what I've done,
what I've lost, what I don't
want to be --
Alone.
I want to be the kind of father
I didn't have, a father that my
boys can actually stand to be
around.
Help me, Wyatt.
Help me get there.
Help me be the kind of father
I know I can be.
>> Brooke: Hope, what are you
saying?
There is nothing to feel guilty
about, nothing at all.
>> Hope: The family I was
dreaming of, raising my daughter
with Liam...
It isn't happening.
But Liam still has a family with
Steffy -- his daughter, and now
this new little girl.
Beth is gone, and, you know,
maybe Liam needs to --
Those girls deserve to have --
>> Brooke: Look, you always
think about other people first,
and this is a good example of
how you do that.
But you have to focus on
yourself.
Your relationship with Liam
takes nothing away from those
girls.
>> Hope: They could have a
full-time father.
It would be different if we
still had our own child to
raise, but...
>> Brooke: Your marriage wasn't
based on Beth.
You and Liam, you fell in love,
you got married, and, yes, maybe
Beth would have come along, but
the core of the family, Hope,
is you and Liam.
And you need to focus on that.
You need to be there for each
other.
And stop pushing him away.
>> Hope: I understand, but...
>> Brooke: No. No "buts."
>> Hope: Why?
>> Brooke: Because he's your
husband, and you need to make
this relationship work.
You have to be there for him.
>> Hope: Why is Beth gone?
Why did I have to lose my child?
It changed everything.
>> Brooke: Oh, honey...
>> Reese: I -- I thought you
were headed straight to Hope.
>> Zoe: Yeah, I almost did.
But I -- I decided to go to
Steffy instead.
>> Reese: Steffy?
>> Zoe: I didn't know what I'd
even say to her, how the words
would come out, if they even
should.
But I just had this feeling to
go see her, that baby.
Hope's baby.
I still can't even believe that
you would do something so
horrible, telling Hope that her
child had died.
>> Reese: I would do anything to
keep you safe.
>> Zoe: Except for stop
gambling.
>> Reese: I know you probably
can't forgive what I've done.
It was awful.
>> Zoe: Most criminal acts are.
>> Reese: I know you don't
believe it, but it's true.
How much I love you.
What I would do to protect you.
>> Zoe: I believe that, which
makes it so hard for me
because the right thing is so
obvious.
The right thing for me to do is
to go running to Steffy, to
Hope, to Liam, to the police,
just shouting and screaming to
all what you did!
That's the right thing.
But you're my father, and that
baby is in good hands.
I mean, Steffy just -- she
adores her.
She is Phoebe's mother in every
sense of the word.
It just --
To take her away now, it seems
cruel.
>> Reese: So what are you
saying?
>> Zoe: I'm saying I hate what
you did.
Every bit of it.
You put me in a terrible
position.
And, you know, you said you
don't expect me to forgive you.
Yeah, I don't know yet if I
will.
I guess time will tell.
But, uh, I do know that
I love you.
That will never change.
And I don't want you to go to
prison.
So...
I won't say anything.
and I can just keep your...
ugly secret.
>> Reese: Thank you, baby.
Thank you.
Thanks to you,
Steffy will keep her daughter.
And Hope will never know
that that baby's actually hers.
The best eggs...
in so many ways.
Which cage free eggs
taste fresher and more
delicious?
Only Eggland's Best.
Which organic eggs
have more vitamins
and less saturated fat?
Only Eggland's Best.
Better taste, better
nutrition, better eggs.
With tough food, your dentures
may slip and fall.
Fixodent Ultra-Max Hold
gives you the strongest hold
ever
to lock your dentures.
So now you can eat tough food
without worry.
Fixodent and forget it.
Now, full coverage that
doesn't quit.
Super Stay Foundation...
from Maybelline New York.
With full coverage pigments...
Stays on. Stays flawless.
Up to 24-hour wear.
Super Stay Foundation
Only from Maybelline New York.
The communal feast.
Potluck.
This parade of dishes will soon
be yours to scrub.
And they're not even...
Yours.
New and improved Dawn Ultra can
finish off this buffet.
Each drop now has even more
grease-cleaning power.
So you can scrub 50% less,
and get done faster.
Next month, their place!
A drop of Dawn and grease is
gone.
.
Stronger is rebuilding
a newborn's heart...
and restoring a
father's faith.
It's standing tall
after one surgery...
not six.
Stronger is being
a typical kid...
despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding
it earlier ...
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is
seeking answers...
And not giving up,
until you find them.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.