"THE REAL" IS ON THE ROAD AT
HOWARD UNIVERSITY.
AND TODAY ON "GIRL CHAT," LAURA
HARVEY IS THINKING LIKE A MAN.
J.LO MIGHT BE PERFORMING A
HOMETOWN TRIBUTE AT THE GRAMMY.
TWITTER HAS QUESTIONS.
THEN, WE PUT THE
HOWARD UNIVERSITY STUDENTS TO
THE DESK.
A TEST.
IT'S ANTI-UP.
PLUS THE MEGA TALENTED WAYNE
BRADY IS HERE.
"THE REAL" IS LIVE.
♪ THIS IS OUR TIME ♪
♪ DON'T WASTE ANOTHER ♪
♪ MINUTE OF IT ♪
♪ THIS IS OUR TIME ♪
♪ GRAB AHOLD, IT'S TIME TO ♪
♪ LIVE IT ♪
♪ STARTING RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ IT'S OUR LIFE, WE'VE GOT ♪
♪ A CHOICE ♪
♪ IT'S OUR TIME, SO STARTING ♪
♪ RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ GRAB AHOLD, IT'S TIME TO ♪
♪ LIVE IT ♪
♪ STARTING RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ RIGHT NOW ♪
>> WELCOME TO "THE REAL"!
GOOD MORNING BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE.
OKAY, LET'S JUMP RIGHT INTO
THIS, SOMETHING SUPER EXCITING
TO ANNOUNCE.
IN HONOR OF BLACK HISTORY MONTH,
WE ARE GOING TO BE TAKING
"THE REAL" ON THE ROAD.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> THERE IT IS.
FIRST A STOP, ON THE ROAD TO
VISIT SOME OF THE NATION'S MOST
THRIVING VCU AND WE WILL MEET
WITH STUDENTS, PLAYING GAMES,
GIVING AWAY SOME SCHMONEY AND
LEARNING BY HBCUs ARE
IMPORTANT TO OUR HISTORY AND OUR
FUTURE.
WE GOT ONE RIGHT HERE.
AND TODAY, OUR "REAL" AMBASSADOR
IS LIVE IN WASHINGTON, D.C., AT
HOWARD UNIVERSITY.
[APPLAUSE]
>> THAT IS SO COOL.
WHAT'S UP, DONYA.
YOU GUYS LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> HELLO HOWARD UNIVERSITY,
HOW'S EVERYONE DOING?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> ALL RIGHT.
HOWARD, WHAT I WANT TO KNOW IS,
WHO IS READY FOR SOME LIVE GIRL
CHAT?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU SO MUCH, WE CAN'T WAIT
TO HEAR WHAT YOU HAVE TO SAY
ABOUT OUR GIRL CHAT TOPICS.
FIRST UP, IT LOOKS LIKE
22-YEAR-OLD LAURIE HARVEY HAS
ADOPTED HER STEPDAD'S "THINK
LIKE A MAN" APPROACH BY PLAYING
THE FIELD WITH MANY ELIGIBLE
BACHELORS.
LORI, AFTER CALLING OFF HER
ENGAGEMENT WAS RUMORED TO BE HIS
SEEING WRAPPER FUTURE FOR A
WHILE BUT THOSE RUMORS AND IN
ONE CLAP BACKED OUT HER AFTER
SEEING PICTURES OF HER HANGING
OUT WITH TREY SONGS.
HOWEVER, GLORY RECENTLY DELETED
PICTURES OF HER AND TREY SONGS
OFF OF INSTAGRAM AND THEN WAS
SEEN HANGING OUT WITH DIDDY'S
SON, AUSTIN COMBS.
SHE'S ALSO BEEN LINKED TO
BRITISH RACE CAR DRIVER LEWIS
HAMILTON.
AND RUMOR HAS IT, MEEK MILL
TRIED TO HOLLER AT HER BUT SHE
WASN'T INTERESTED.
PEOPLE ON TWITTER HAVE FOUND IT
EXTREMELY REFRESHING THAT LORI
IS BASICALLY DOING WHAT SO MANY
MEN DO.
LIKE USER I AM MARK LANDRY WAS
SAID, LORI HARVEY, THE FIRST
BLACK WOMAN TO SUCCESSFULLY PULL
A YOU, ON YOU.
[LAUGHS]
>> THAT'S HILARIOUS.
>> SO LADIES DO YOU RESPECT
LORI'S DATING HUSTLE?
>> FIRST OF ALL, SHE IS NOT THE
FIRST BLACK WOMAN TO DO THAT.
BUT GO AHEAD.
>> I HAVE ALWAYS THOUGHT THAT IF
YOU ARE NOT MARRIED, LADIES
ESPECIALLY, YOU SHOULD BE OUT
THERE OPENLY DATING TO GET TO
KNOW YOURSELF AND WHAT YOU LIKE.
I'M ALL ABOUT THAT.
AND HERE WE CALL IT OPENLY
DATING.
HOWEVER THATMEANS, MULTI-DATING
DOES NOT MEAN YOU ARE
MULTI-DOING IT.
AND IF YOU ARE, THAT'S YOUR
PREROGATIVE.
BUT IT'S NOT COOL TO JUST ASSUME
THAT A WOMAN IS DOING IT.
>> I ACTUALLY COINED THE PHRASE.
I WROTE A BOOK CALLED "LOVE THEM
OR LEAVE THEM BUT DON'T GET
STUCK WITH THE TAB."
AND IN IT, I WAS TALKING ABOUT
HOW WE GET CAUGHT UP WITH ALL
THESE RULES.
THERE WAS LIKE THIS 90 DAY RULE,
AND I THOUGHT, WHO WANTS TO
SPEND TIME WITH ONE PERSON FOR
90 DAYS AND I THOUGHT, THAT'S
NOT REALLY REALISTIC.
SO I APPLAUD SOMEONE LIKE LORI
BECAUSE YOU SHOULD MULTI-DATE,
AND THAT'S WHAT WE CALL IT,
MULTI-DATING BECAUSE YOU WANT TO
GET TO KNOW SOMEBODY.
WHEN I FIRST STARTED THIS SHOW,
I WAS MULTI-DATING AND PEOPLE
THOUGHT, YOU JUST DON'T WANT TO
BRING A GUY ON THE SHOW.
AND THEY SAID TO YOU JUST DON'T
WANT TO DATE A GUY WHO IS
MARRIED.
IN THAT TIME, IF YOU DATE MORE
THAN ONE GUY ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU
ARE YOUNG, YOU FIND OUT WHAT YOU
LIKE OR DON'T LIKE IN A MAN.
SO WHAT SHE'S DOING IS ACTUALLY
THE WAY DATING IS SUPPOSED TO
BE, THAT'S THE WAY IT IS.
>> IN A MATURE WAY, THE RISK
MUNICATION INVOLVED.
I'VE BEEN A VERY OPEN ABOUT
THAT.
I DON'T WANT ANYONE TO THINK
THEY ARE THE ONLY ONE.
BUT SOME PEOPLE THAT'S NOT FOR
THEM.
>> WHAT WE TALKED ABOUT YOU AND
GZ, WE ARE LIKE, YOU ARE NOT
EXCLUSIVE.
>> THAT'S SOMETHING THAT'S
OBVIOUSLY SPOKEN ABOUT BETWEEN
THESE PEOPLE AND AGAIN I THINK
IT SO IMPORTANT TO ESTABLISH
THAT WHAT YOU SEE ON
SOCIAL MEDIA, SOMEBODY TAKING A
PICTURE WITH SOMEBODY DOES NOT
MEAN THEY ARE SLEEPING TOGETHER.
>> BUT WHAT IT IS IS, MEN ARE
FEARFUL.
THEY'VE BEEN DOING THIS FOR
YEARS.
THEY WANT TO SHAME US AND SAY,
IF THEY SEE YOU OUT WITH A GUY,
SOMETHING IS WRONG WITH YOU.
NOTHING IS WRONG WITH YOU.
DON'T LET MEN CONTROL YOU.
>> THEY ARE DATING, SO WHAT DO
YOU HAVE FOR US?
>> I HAVE SIDNEY HERE.
>>   HI, LADIES.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THIS
MULTI-DATING?
>> I ABSOLUTELY AGREE WITH
LONNIE.
LONI.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH
DATING PEOPLE WHO ARE IN YOUR
SOCIAL CIRCLE OR OUTSIDE OF YOUR
SOCIAL CIRCLE.
THERE IS NOTHING BETTER TO DO
THAT THEN GOING OUT ON A MILLION
DATES IF YOU WANT TO, THREE
DATES IF YOU WANT TO.
THIS IS JUST WHAT YOU ARE DOING.
>> THERE ARE SOME FINE MEN AT
HOWARD UNIVERSITY.
I WAS TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHICH
ONE I WAS GOING TO -- [LAUGHS]
>> I'M WONDERING.
DO YOU THINK GUYS -- ACTUALLY WE
KNOW THAT GUYS CAN GET INSECURE
ABOUT THIS, KNOWING THE GIRL
THEY ARE DATING IS SEEING OTHER
GUYS, BUT I DON'T THINK THEY
SHOULD BE.
I THINK THEY SHOULD RESPECT THE
FACT THAT SHE IS BEING HONEST
AND THEN GIVE UP THEM A CHANCE.
WHEN YOU ARE YOUNG YOU HAVE TO
FIGURE OUT WHAT YOU LIKE AND
WHAT YOU DON'T LIKE, AND YOU
WILL NEVER KNOW THAT IF YOU
MARRY THE FIRST AND THEN END UP
YEARS LATER DOWN THE ROAD GOING,
I WISH I WOULD HAVE EXPERIENCED
SOMETHING ELSE OR SEEN SOMETHING
ELSE.
>> I DO THINK IT'S IMPORTANT TO
SAY, DIFFERENT STROKES FOR
DIFFERENT FOLKS.
THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE WHO LOVE
TO MULTI-DATE.
COOL.
THEN THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE WHO
GET EXHAUSTED DOING THAT.
>> DID YOU MULTI-DATE?
>> NO I DIDN'T, AND I DID TURN
OUT OKAY.
SO I WANT TO LET PEOPLE KNOW,
IT'S OKAY TO DO THAT AS WELL.
IT'S NOT OKAY TO JUDGE A PERSON
WHO MULTI-DATES AND IT'S NOT
OKAY TO JUDGE A PERSON WHO
CHOOSES NOT TO.
>> I ALSO WANT TO SAY, WHEN YOU
DATE ONE PERSON, YOUR MIND AND
YOUR ASPIRATIONS ARE LIMITED TO
WHATEVER THAT PERSON BRINGS INTO
YOUR LIFE.
THEY ARE LIKE, WE GO AND DO
THESE THINGS, WE TALK ABOUT
THESE THINGS.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHERE YOU CAN
GROW AND MATURE TO UNTIL YOU
OPEN THAT UP TO SOMEBODY WHO MAY
BE CHALLENGES YOU IN AREAS THAT
YOU NEED TO.
THAT'S WHY MULTI-DATING ALLOWS
YOU TO LEARN MORE ABOUT
YOURSELF, WHAT YOU NEED VERSUS
WHAT YOU WANT.
AND THE SECOND PART I WANT TO
SAY IS, THE COOL THING ABOUT
MULTI-DATING IS, ONCE YOU SEE
AND GET TO KNOW YOUR OPTIONS, IT
WILL BE REALLY CLEAR WHEN THAT
ONE PERSON MOVES YOU IN SUCH A
WAY WHERE YOU THINK, I'M NOT
INTERESTED IN MULTI-DATING
ANYMORE BECAUSE YOU ARE WHO I
WANT TO.
>> ANOTHER WOMAN WHO IS DATING A
HIGH-PROFILE MAN IS JENNIFER
LOPEZ AND YESTERDAY TWITTER
MELTED DOWN AFTER A RUMOR
SURFACED THAT J.LO WOULD BE
PERFORMING A MOTOWN TRIBUTE AT
THIS SUNDAY'S GRAMMY AWARDS IN
HONOR OF THE LABELS 60TH
ANNIVERSARY.
AMONG THE NEWS, JAMAIL HILL
TWEETED "I HAVE QUESTIONS."
CAN WE JUST CANCEL BLACK HISTORY
MONTH?
REBOOT FOR 2020?
WE ARE IN WEEK ONE AND I CAN'T
TAKE MUCH MORE.
THIS IS -- THIS IS THE GRAMMYS
ASKING J.LO TO DO THIS.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE THAT CLEAR.
THIS IS A CLEAR RUMOR, AND THE
THING ABOUT THE GRAMMYS, EVERY
TIME THEY NEED ATTRIBUTE FOR A
BLACK PERSON, THEY GO TO
MADONNA.
AS MADONNA NOT THIS TIME?
IT'S LIKE -- I GUESS MAYBE
MADONNA IS LIKE, LOOK.
I'M TIRED OF THIS ALL RIGHT?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> FOR ME JUST AS A FAN OF THAT
MUSIC COME UP WITH ALL THOSE
GREATS THAT WE JUST LISTED AND
SO MANY MORE, I LIKE THE OG.
I'D LIKE TO HEAR ON ENSEMBLE OF
THE GREATEST.
I WOULD LOVE THAT, TOO.
BUT MOST OF THE TIME WHEN IT'S
ATTRIBUTE IT'S USUALLY OTHER
ARTISTS DOING IT.
THEY GET TO SIT IN THE AUDIENCE
AND BE LIKE, I KILLED THAT ONE.
DO WE KNOW IF J.LO IS THE ONLY
PERSON DOING -- >> THIS WAS ALL
A RUMOR, AND IT ALL HAPPENED
YESTERDAY.
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH THEIR
ETHNICITY.
MOTOWN IS A SOUL SONG, IT'S A
SOUL MUSIC.
TOTALLY DIFFERENT FROM POP OR
HIP-HOP.
>> THE RANGE IS LIKE -- >> WHAT
ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY?
>> NO, I'M JUST SAYING IT'S A
CERTAIN TYPE OF CATEGORY AND
MUSIC.
WHEN I THINK OF MOTOWN, I THINK
OF THAT SOULFUL VOICE THAT HAS
LIKE EIGHT DIFFERENT RANGES IN
THE BOYS.
NOW THIS IS THE BEAUTY OF MOTOW
MOTOWN.
IT INFLUENCES SO MANY PEOPLE AN
AND, IT INFLUENCES JENNIFER
LOPEZ AND INFLUENCED ME.
I WOULD LIKE TO SEE THE
PERFORMANCE BROUGHT END.
HAVE A DELL SING A SONG, I HAVE
JENNIFER HUDSON SANG A SONG.
"FANTASIA" SING A SONG OR ALICIA
KEYS.
>> I THINK WHOEVER DOES THE BET
TRIBUTES NEEDS TO PRODUCE THIS
ONE BECAUSE THEY WILL GET THE
RIGHT SINGERS.
THEY WILL GET THE FANTASIAS, THE
JILL SCOTT'S, -- >> SO
REALISTICALLY, I KNOW WE JUST
SAID THAT THEY ARE ALL ALIVE,
BUT USUALLY FOR TRIBUTES THEY
HAVE SOMEONE ELSE PERFORM THE
SONGS.
BUT I AGREE, IT WOULD BE
INCREDIBLE TO SEE THEM COVER
THEIR OWN SONG SINCE THEY ARE
STILL HERE.
I COMPLETELY AGREE WITH THAT.
NOW YOU SAID IT'S NOT A RACIAL
THING, YOU SAID, WOULD IT BE
OKAY IF ADELE SING THE SONG OR
JUST A DAY?
>> IS CONSIDERED AN R&B ARTIST.
SAM SMITH IS CONSIDERED -- SO WE
ARE NOT TALKING ABOUT THE COLOR
HERE.
LET'S BE REALISTIC.
>> I THINK IT THAT WOULD BE
AMAZING IN AN ENSEMBLE BECAUSE I
ACTUALLY THINK SHE COULD DO
DIANA ROSS VOCALS.
NO?
>> I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
EVERY TIME IT'S US, YOU ALL ARE
GOING SOMEPLACE ELSE.
THAT IS ABOUT ETHNICITY.
THERE ARE PEOPLE THAT CAN SING,
AND, I'M PRETTY SURE KNOWING
J.LO BEING THE SMART BUSINESS
WOMAN SHE IS SHE WOULD STEER THE
SHARE THE STAGE.
SHE COULD DO ONE SONG, AND THAT
WOULD BE THE WAY TO DO IT.
BUT TO NOT -- >> BECAUSE MOTOWN
HAD SUCH AN IMPACT ON BLACK
MUSIC AND BLACK HISTORY, AND I
WANT TO KNOW WHAT
HOWARD UNIVERSITY THINKS ABOUT
THIS.
DONYA?
>> I HAVE MARAN.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I THINK JUST BECAUSE J.LO HAS
BEEN IN THE INDUSTRY FOR SO
LONG, SHE WILL KILL IT EITHER
WAY.
>> OKAY.
WE THOUGHT ABOUT THIS, AND WE
HAVE AT ALEXIS G AT ONE OH
EIGHT, SHE SAID HER PERFORMANCES
ARE AMAZING.
THEN WE HAD THE BALL MOM SAID,
J.LO IS AN AMAZING PERFORMER AN
AND, AND I GUESS IN THIS CASE
THAT WOULD BE THE BEST.
>> IF YOU'RE GOING TO DO THE
GRAMMYS, DO IT RIGHT.
>> TUNE INTO "E! NEWS" AND YOU
WILL SEE ME COVERING THE FASHION
AND ALL THE FUN ARTISTS.
AND I WILL LET YOU GUYS KNOW
WHAT'S GOING TO GO DOWN.
WE HAVE TO TAKE A BREAK BUT
THERE IS SO MUCH MORE LIVE
"GIRL CHAT."
STAY RIGHT THERE.
>> FROM "A MILLION LITTLE THING
THINGS."
PLUS CHICAGO, WHERE ARE YOU?
AND, CAN YOUR HAIR EVER BE TOO
MUCH TO BEAR?
DIY HAIR CARE JUST FOR YOUR HAIR
TYPE.
THAT'S ON ALL NEW "THE REAL" ."
>> WELCOME BACK TO "THE REAL."
WE ARE NOT JUST HAVING LIVE
"GIRL CHAT" TODAY, WE ARE LIVE
AT HOWARD UNIVERSITY IN
WASHINGTON, D.C.
SAY, WHAT'S UP, HOWARD?
OKAY.
THEY DID IT, I COULD HEAR IT
FROM OVER THERE.
SENATOR CORY BOOKER RECENTLY
ANNOUNCED ITS 2020 CAMPAIGN TO
RUN FOR PRESIDENT, AND HE HAS
ALREADY HIT THE GROUND RUNNING.
COREY WAS BEING INTERVIEWED ON
THE BREAKFAST CLUB WHERE
CHARLEMAGNE GRILLED HIM NOT JUST
ON HIS DATING VIEWS BUT HIS
LIFE.
HE SAID WELL HE'S NOT DATING
HER, HE'S "GOT A BOO-BOO.
NO SINGLE MAN HAS BEEN ELECTED
PRESIDENT AND HAS BEEN SINGLE
SINCE 1892.
DO YOU THINK AMERICA IS READY
FOR A BACHELOR PRESIDENT.
THAT WOULD BE AWESOME.
>> LONI IS SAYING NO.
>> YOU COULD HAVE ALL OF THESE
WOMEN SLIDING UP INTO THE
WON'T HAVE A FIRST LADY.ND WE-
>> WE MIGHT HAVE A WHITE HOUSE
WEDDING.
WOULDN'T THAT BE COOL?
>> WOULDN'T THAT BE NICE?
>> A WHITE HOUSE WEDDING.
>> STAY SINGLE, INSTEAD OF, I
DON'T WANT YOUR MARRIAGE TO BE
PART OF YOUR CAMPAIGN.
>> THINK ABOUT DATING.
YOU HAVE LOTS OF SECRET SERVICE
AROUND THEM, SO -- >> IT COULD
BE LIKE AMERICAN PRESIDENT OF
MICHAEL DOUGLAS, AND TAKE YOU
UP.
>> I'D RATHER THAT YOUR POLICY
BE WHAT WE FOCUS ON.
>> I DO WHENEVER A PRESIDENT
STEP SIN, AND THE FIRST LADY IS
REALLY SOMEONE THAT I LOOK
FORWARD TO.
I THINK A WOMAN IS GOING TO HAVE
A DIFFERENT LENS THAT IS
NECESSARY ON SOCIETY THEN A MAN.
SO I WILL BE MISSING OUT ON THAT
AND I WONDER, IF THERE WAS A
SINGLE PRESIDENT, WHAT WOULD HE
DO TO SUPPLEMENT THAT?
>> OR WHAT WOULD SHE DO?
>> I'M SAYING A SINGLE MALE
PRESIDENT.
THAT ROLE CAN'T BE OVERLOOKED
BECAUSE YOU DON'T HAVE SOMEBODY
TO TAKE CARE OF THAT.
WE NEED TO MAKE SURE THAT WE
HAVE SOMEONE OVERLOOKING -- >>
IF SHE HAS A SISTER OR AN AUNTIE
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT -- >>
YES.
HOLD ON, NOW I HAVE A REAL DEEP
QUESTION.
COULD A GIRL FRIEND OVER?
>> SO THEN YOU HAVE AN ANSI, A
COUSIN AT A HOME GIRL BUT A
GIRLFRIEND.
>> THE AMERICAN PRESIDENT SIDNEY
WADE DID NOT TAKE OVER AS
FIRST LADY.
SHE DIDN'T DO THAT IN THE MOVIE
SO WE CAN HAVE THAT IN REAL
LIFE.
[LAUGHTER]
>> SERIOUSLY.
AND THEY DON'T LIKE THAT EITHER.
I THINK WE GOT SPOILED WITH
MICHELLE OBAMA.
TO BE HONEST.
SHE REALLY TOOK ACTION AND SPOKE
OUT AND MADE US ALL FALL IN LOVE
WITH HER.
>> AND THAT'S GOING TO BE
INTERESTING
L'OREAL PARIS INTRODUCES
ROUGE SIGNATURE
MATTE COLORED INK
LESS TEXTURE
MORE COLOR
LESS EXCESS
MORE IMPACT
ALL DAY MATTE
BARE LIP SENSATION
ROUGE SIGNATURE
MATTE COLORED INK
BY L'OREAL PARIS
WE'RE WORTH IT
Never ending is now even better
at Olive Garden.
All new Never Ending Stuffed
Pastas starting at $12.99.
Pick your favorite stuffed
pasta, sauce and topping.
It's all never ending.
All new
Never Ending Stuffed Pastas.
Only for a limited time,
at Olive Garden.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> WELCOME BACK TO "THE REAL,"
TIME FOR MORE LIVE "GIRL CHAT."
WE ARE PAYING TRIBUTE TO OUR
NATION'S TOP HBCUs ALL MONTH
LONG AND TODAY, OUR REAL
AMBASSADOR DONYA IS AT
HOWARD UNIVERSITY IN
WASHINGTON, D.C.
RIGHT NOW, DONYA IS ACTUALLY
LIVE WITH HOWARD'S PRESIDENT,
DR. WAYNE FREDERICK.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HI!
IT'S SO GREAT TO MEET YOU,
DR. FREDERICK.
I HEAR YOU ARE A THREE-TIME
ALUMNUS OF HOWARD.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ATTRACTS
STUDENTS TO YOUR UNIVERSITY?
>> WELL YOU KNOW I THINK SOME OF
THE SAME THINGS THAT ATTRACTED
ME HERE.
THE FIRST BEING ACADEMIC
EXCELLENCE THAT OCCURS HERE.
HOWARD EPITOMIZES BLACK
EXCELLENCE AND I THINK THE
SECOND THING THAT I WOULD SAY IS
BECAUSE OF THE DIVERSITY THAT WE
HAVE.
WE HAVE DIVERSITY FROM 44 STATES
AND 71 COUNTRIES.
AND THAT THE LAST THING IS, THE
STUDENT SERVICES.
THEY ARE SOME OF THE BEST AT
GOING OUT ON SOLVING THE WORLD'S
PROBLEMS.
>> THAT'S BEAUTIFUL.
AND WHAT MAKES THE HOWARD
EXPERIENCE SO UNIQUE?
>> WELL, THE HOWARD EXPERIENCE
IS UNIQUE FOR SEVERAL REASONS.
AS SMART AS ALL STUDENTS ARE,
THEY ARE ALSO IN THE MIDDLE OF
POP CULTURE AT ANY GIVEN TIME
WHEN THEY COME ON THE CAMPUS.
YOU LOOK AT OUR ALUM AS WELL AND
THEY GET A REALLY GREAT EXAMPLE
OF WHO THEY SHOULD BE AND WHAT
THEY SHOULD BE DOING AS THEY GO
OUT INTO THE WORLD.
SO YOU HAVE AN ALUMNUS RUNNING
FOR PRESIDENT BUT ANY NIGHT OF
THE WEEK YOU COULD TURN ON YOUR
TELEVISION SET AND THERE IS A
HOWARD ALUM.
PEOPLE LIKE FELICIA BECHARD, WE
HAVE MIRRORS AND STATES PEOPLE
AND A WIDE VARIETY OF GREAT
THINGS THAT I THINK CONTINUED TO
BE EPITOMIZED IN OUR STUDENTS AS
WELL.
>> YOU ARE PULLING UP RECEIPTS,
I SEE.
>> AND YOU GUYS HAVE TO TAKE A
BREAK, BUT THERE IS MORE OF
"THE REAL" ON THE WAY RIGHT
AFTER THIS.
>> THIS FRI-YAY, THE PARTY
DOESN'T STOP.
WE CELEBRATE BLACK HISTORY MONTH
BY THINKING OF BLACK INVENTOR.
AND WE SEND ONE UNSUSPECTING MOM
ON A TRIP OF A LIFETIME.
PLUS, WE ARE T
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
♪ ♪
>> WELCOME BACK.
I BET OUR GIRL DONYA IS HAVING A
BLAST.
ARE YOU PUMPED TO PLAY ONE OF
OUR SIGNATURE GAMES, OR WHAT?
>> I'M SO EXCITED, LONI!
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL, IT'S GAME ON BECAUSE WE
ARE GOING TO PLAY SOME ANTI-UP
WITH EVERYBODY AT
HOWARD UNIVERSITY.
THIS IS GOING TO BE GREAT.
ALL RIGHT, HOWARD, HERE'S THE
DEAL.
DONYA WILL ASK US SOME POP
CULTURE TRIVIA QUESTIONS ABOUT
YOUR HOME, AT HOWARD.
EVERY ANSWER I MAY BE ASKING --
EVERY ANSWER WILL BE IN THE FORM
OF A YEAR.
SO STUDENTS, YOUR JOB IS TO TELL
ME WHETHER YOU THINK THE REAL
ANSWER IS HIGHER, LOWER OR SPOT
ON TO THE ANSWER THAT THEY GIVE.
IF YOU ARE RIGHT, YOU WILL WIN
$500 FOR YOUR STUDENT
ORGANIZATION.
SO WHO OUT THERE -- I'VE GOT TO
FEEL SOME LOVE.
>> THEY ARE READY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I'M LOOKING FOR KAYLA WAY SOME.
WHERE ARE YOU, KAYLA?
>> OKAY, ARE YOU MS. HOWARD?
>> [LAUGHS]
>> OKAY.
WHAT YEAR ARE YOU AND WHAT
ORGANIZATION ARE YOU PLAYING FOR
>> I'M A SENIOR IN COMPUTERS
INFORMATION.
>> ALL RIGHT.
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
HERE'S YOUR FIRST QUESTION.
THE FIRST QUESTION IS FOR A TIME
ERA.
WHAT YEAR DID U.S. SENATOR AND
2020 PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE
KAMALA HARRIS GRADUATE FROM
HOWARD?
YOU GOT THIS.
>> OKAY, I'M GOING TO SAY, 1988?
>> OKAY, THAT SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
SHE SAID 1988.
FOR $500 FOR YOUR STUDENT GROUP,
DO YOU THINK THE REAL ANSWER
THAT SHE GRADUATED WAS HIGHER,
LOWER OR SPOT ON?
>> EVERYONE SAYS LOWER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I THINK IT'S LOWER.
AND I LOVE IT.
>> GRADUATED IN 1986, I'M
LOOKING FOR THE NEXT HOWARD
STUDENT.
LAUREN MYERS, WHERE ARE YOU?
♪ ♪
LAUREN, WHAT YEAR ARE YOU AND
WHAT STUDENT ORGANIZATION ARE
YOU PLAYING FOR?
>> I'M PLAYING FOR THE FRESHMAN
LEADERSHIP ACADEMY.
>> WHAT YEAR DID BARACK OBAMA,
PRESIDENT BARACK OBAMA DELIVER
THE GRADUATE COMMENCEMENT SPEECH
AT HOWARD UNIVERSITY?
WHAT YEAR?
>> I WOULD SAY 2015.
>> SO IS THE REAL ANSWER HIGHER,
LOWER OR SPOT ON?
>> EVERYBODY HERE KNOWS.
>> THEY ARE CONFIDENT.
>> THEY DELIVERED THE
COMMENCEMENT SPEECH TO THE
GRADUATING CLASS IN 2016.
THAT'S THE BEST $500.
>> SO CLOSE.
GET IT GIRL, MAKE THAT MONEY.
I'M LOOKING FOR NIGER JEFFRIES.
>> COME ON UP HERE.
WHAT STUDENT ORGANIZATION ARE
YOU PLAYING FOR AND WHAT YEAR
ARE YOU?
>> I AM A JUNIOR AND I'M
REPRESENTING THE FRESHMAN
LEADERSHIP ACADEMY.
>> AND WHO GRADUATED WITH A BFA
IN DIRECTING FROM HOWARD?
>> THIS IS SO HARD BUT I'M GOING
TO GO WITH 2,000.
>> IS SHE HIGHER, LOWER OR SPOT
ON?
>> MAYBE A LITTLE -- >> BUT HE
LOOKS SO YOUNG.
>> I WOULD SAY SPOT ON.
>> IS HE RIGHT?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> $400.
THANK YOU GUYS FOR PLAYING
AUNTIE UP.
AND THANKS FOR PLAYING WITH US.
WE HAVE TO TAKE A QUICK BREAK,
BUT WE HAVE A W
Ordinary tissues left Dakota's
nose sore and red.
So Dad slayed the problem with
Puffs Plus Lotion, instead.
With lotion to soothe and
softness to please.
A nose in need deserves
Puffs, indeed.
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
Does removing makeup
feel like this?
Your skin deserves better.
Garnier Micellar Cleansing Water
with micelles that
work like a magnet.
It's a pure way to remove
stubborn makeup
without harsh rubbing.
Cleansing, reinvented.
Micellar Water.
By Garnier,
Naturally!
>> WELCOME BACK.
WE'VE BEEN HANGING OUT WITH
HOWARD UNIVERSITY TODAY AND WE
ARE ABOUT TO CALL ONE OF YOU TO
BE PART OF "THE REAL" HOTLINE
BLING.
SO IF YOUR PHONE RINGS, IT UP
THERE WITH DONYA.
ARE YOU GUYS READY?
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
>> I HEAR A PHONE.
>> WE ARE DIALING.
>> SOMEBODY'S PHONE IS RINGING.
>> YOU ARE READY, YOU HAD YOUR
HAND ON THE BUTTON.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME AND WHERE ARE
YOU FROM?
>> MY NAME IS BRANDON ALLEN, I'M
A JUNIOR FROM DETROIT, MICHIGAN.
>> WHAT YEAR AND WHAT ARE YOU
STUDYING?
>> >> STUDYING LEGAL
COMMUNICATION >> WHAT IS WHAT
YOU HAVE ON YOUR HEAD.
>> I SERVE AS THE MR. 42ND
HOWARD UNIVERSITY.
>> ALL RIGHT, WE ARE GOING TO
GIVE YOU THE CHANCE TO WIN SOME
MONEY FOR THE HOWARD UNIVERSITY
ROYAL COURT WITH OUR IMO G
PADDLE GAME.
ADRIENNE HAS FOUR BATTLES WITH
THE EMOJIS, AND, EACH EMOJI
ADRIENNE GUESSES CORRECTLY WILL
WIN YOU $100.
HOW DOES THAT SOUND?
>> THAT SOUNDS GOOD, I'M READY.
>> ALL RIGHT, WORK TOGETHER,
BRANDON.
ADRIENNE, LET'S SEE YOUR FIRST
PADDLE.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS, LOOK AT HIM.
>> DANCING GIRL.
>> YES.
ADRIENNE, LOOK HERE.
>> OKAY.
YES.
>> BRANDON, GET THIS ONE.
>> IS THAT RIGHT?
>> THAT'S THE FOURTH ONE.
AND WE WILL DO IT BIG FOR
HOWARD UNIVERSITY ROYAL COURT
AND GIVE THEM $500.
CONGRATULATIONS BRANDON.
WE WILL BE BACK WITH MORE
"THE REAL" RIGHT AFTER THIS
PERIOD OF ♪ ♪
>> UP NEXT, MAKE A TALENTED
WAYNE BRADY IS IN THE HOUSE.
>> WELCOME BACK.
OUR GUEST IS A TRIPLE THREAT.
HE SINGS, HE ASKED AND HE IS THE
HOST OF "LET'S MAKE A DEAL."
HE'S A SIX TIME AWARD WINNER AND
A GRAMMY NOMINEE WHO AFTER 30
YEARS IN THIS BUSINESS IS NOT
SLOWING DOWN.
PLEASE WELCOME, WAYNE BRADY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
MUSICA PHYSICAL
>> I'M HAPPY TO
BE HERE.
>> SOME EXCITING THINGS ARE
HAPPENING.
FIRST OF ALL, I'D TALK ABOUT YOU
AND AL PACINO.
>> I MET AL AT A SCHOOL PLAY,
OUR KIDS GO TO SCHOOL TOGETHER.
I HAVE SEEN HIM A FEW TIMES BUT
I'M NOT ONE TO BOTHER PEOPLE.
ESPECIALLY AT SCHOOL.
LIKE, I FEEL THERE ARE CERTAIN
PLACES THAT SHOULD BE KIND OF
SACRED, BUT SO MANY PEOPLE GO TO
THE SAME SCHOOL, AND IT'S LIKE,
THEY ARE GREAT, HERE'S THE
SCRIPT.
SO IF YOU ARE MEANT TO SPEAK
THEN YOU ARE WILL SPEAK.
I WAS TRAPPED IN A LINE OF
CHAIRS AND HE WAS COMING TOWARD
ME.
I HAD A LITTLE FREAK OUT MOMENT.
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN, HE GOES,
WAYNE?
AND, HE GIVES ME A HUG, IT'S ONE
OF THE SWEETEST GUYS AND,
GROWING UP WATCHING AL, AND
ESPECIALLY EVERYBODY HAS ON
AL PACINO IMPRESSION WHICH I
WOULD NEVER DO FOR HIM TO HIS
FACE.
HE MIGHT BE WATCHING THIS, TOO.
>> YOU HAVE TO GIVE ME A LITTLE
OWL.
>> NO, MINE PROBABLY SUCKS.
LIKE, SAY HELLO TO MY LITTLE
FRIEND.
EVERYBODY DOES THAT.
[LAUGHTER]
>> SO YOU ARE RUBBING ELBOWS
WITH AL PACINO AND YOU ALSO
RECENTLY SANG WITH JOHN
BON JOVI?
>> I'M NOT BRAGGING ABOUT STUFF.
>> TELL US WHAT IT WAS LIKE.
>> AND OUR KIDS THE SAME
SCHOOL -- NO.
I WAS DOING A CORPORATE GIG, A
CORPORATION THAT CALLED AND
BOOKED US FOR THE SHOW.
IT'S A WEIRD LINEUP, BECAUSE IT
WAS ME AND A GROUP CALLED THE
ILLUSIONIST.
AND THEN WE WERE OPENING UP FOR
JOHN BON JOVI WHICH IS SUCH A
COOL, WEIRD LITTLE THING.
THE COMPANY WAS AMAZING AND TO
BE ABLE TO SING WITH JOHN, HE
BROUGHT ME UP ON STAGE.
THERE IS ON THE OTHER GUY AND, I
WAS LIVING THE ROCK STAR
FANTASY.
>> SPEAKING OF, YOU'VE TEASED US
AND SAID YOU ARE WORKING ON NEW
MUSIC.
SO, ANY UPDATES?
>> YEAH.
I HAVE A SINGLE THAT MY BUDDY
JAMIE JONES AND JACK AND ANOTHER
GUY CALLED THE HEAVY WEIGHT.
SO SHOUT OUT TO THOSE GUYS.
THEY HAVE WRITTEN A SONG THAT'S
CALLED A FLIRTING WITH FOREVER
AND WE ARE PROBABLY GOING TO
RELEASE IT IN THE NEXT COUPLE
WEEKS.
JUST A SINGLE.
>> AND IT'S CALLED "FLIRTING
WITH FOREVER?
?"
>> YES.
NOW SOME OF YOU SAID -- MOST OF
MY COMEDY IS MUSIC BUT IF YOU
DON'T KNOW, GO TO iTUNES AND
CHECK IT OUT, I RELEASED A
RECORD CALLED "LONG TIME
COMING."
IT WAS GREAT, I GOT A GRAMMY
AWARD NOMINATION.
BUT FOLKS HAVE BEEN SAYING THAT
I AM THE MONSTER ON THE MASKED
SINGER.
IT'S NOT ME.
BUT IT'S MY WAY OF SAYING, GO
LISTEN TO THE MUSIC AND YOU
COULD SEE IT WASN'T ME SO YOU
CAN SEE WHEN MY SINGLE COMES OUT
THAT IT'S NOT ME.
BUT THE MONSTER IS DOPE.
I SOUND NOTHING LIKE THAT.
>> I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
>> WOULD YOU DO THE MASKED
SINGER?
>> IT'S WEIRD, BECAUSE I HAVE --
THE THINGS THAT I'M DOING, I
WANT TO BRING TO THE LIGHT, SO I
DON'T NECESSARILY WANT TO BE --
I LOVE THE FACT THAT THE SHOW
GIVES LIGHT TO THOSE STARS THAT
CAN SING AND THEY HAVEN'T HAD
THAT SHINED TO BE ABLE TO DO
THAT.
BUT I'M LUCKY ENOUGH THAT, EVEN
ON "LET'S MAKE A DEAL, IT'S A
MUSICAL VARIETY.
>> GOING BACK TO BROADWAY, -- >>
ARE YOU GOING BACK TO BROADWAY?
>> THAT'S MY INTENT.
I'VE BEEN IN "BOOTS" AND
"HAMILTON."
BROADWAY IS MY FIRST LOVE.
>> YOU ARE ALWAYS WORKING,
WAYNE.
LAST YEAR YOU JOINED THE COST OF
"THE BOLD AND THE BEAUTIFUL" AS
AN OB-GYN.
WHY DID YOU DECIDE TO JOIN THE
SHOW?
>> A FEW REASONS.
REASON ONE, MY GRANDMA.
WE USE TO WATCH THE BOLD AND THE
BEAUTIFUL AND THE YOUNG AND THE
RESTLESS, HER STORIES.
AND I WAS I DECIDED TO DO THIS
BECAUSE I KNOW THAT SHE LOVES
THOSE STORIES.
AND MY DAUGHTER BOOKED A ROLE ON
THERE AND SHE IS A RECURRING ON
THAT SHOW.
SO I GET A CHANCE TO WORK WITH
HER.
AND, I LOVE TO MAKE PEOPLE MAD
AND MAKE FOLKS TALK.
EITHER IS DON'T LOOK DOWN OR
STAY IN YOUR LANE.
HE'S AMAZING AND SMART, MAKES
REALLY BOLD CHOICES, AND AND
FOLKS LIKE TO CONNECT.
AND, CHECK THIS OUT.
>> YOU CAN TELL ME HONESTLY, ARE
YOU HAVING A GOOD TIME WITH THE
SHOW AND WHAT DO YOU THINK I
COULD DO TO IMPROVE WHAT I'M
DOING?
>> YOU ARE VERY TALENTED AND YOU
MAKE ME LAUGH VERY MUCH.
AND I HAVE NO IMPROVEMENTS THAT
I WOULD GIVE YOU.
PROFESSIONALLY.
>> INCORPORATED YOU VERY MUCH
MA'AM, I APPRECIATE YOUR INPUT.
I WILL TALK TO YOU AT THE NEXT
QUARTERLY REVIEW.
[LAUGHTER]
>> NOW, BUY ME A CAR, DADDY.
>> RIGHT.
SHE'S JUST TRYING TO BE NICE SO
I GET HER A CAR.
[LAUGHS]
>> WE LOVE IT WHEN YOU STOP BY.
YOU ARE SO MUCH FUN.
BE SURE TO CATCH "LET'S MAKE A
DEAL."
HERE'S THE DEAL.
WE WILL HAVE TO TAKE A QUICK
BREAK BUT WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK,
YOU ARE WATCHING "THE REAL."
♪ ♪
>> IF YO
Now, eyeliner goes NYC-proof.
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil
from Maybelline New York.
Smudge resistant.
Sweat resistant.
Waterproof.
Up to 36-hour wear.
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil.
Only from Maybelline New York.
♪ ♪
>> CLOSED CAPTIONING AND OTHER
CONSIDERATION FOR "THE REAL"
PROVIDED BY:
♪ ♪
>> WELCOME BACK AND HAPPY
WEDNESDAY LADIES.
HOW FUN WAS TODAY SHOW?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
AND UP AT HOWARD UNIVERSITY,
EVERYBODY WAS A LIT, IT WAS SO
MUCH FUN.
NEXT WEEK WE ARE GOING TO LONI'S
ALMA MATER, PRAIRIE VIEW.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> PREE FIELD, THIS IS A CALL
OUT TO YOU ALL, WE WILL BE AT
THE MEMORIAL STUDENT UNION.
MAKE SURE YOU ALL COME OUT.
>> WE ALSO HAVE TO GIVE A SUPER
SPECIAL SHOUT OUT TO WAYNE
BRADY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COMING BY
TODAY WITH YOUR AL PACINO
IMPRESSION AND, LET'S TAKE A
MINUTE TO SHOW LOVE TO HOWARD IN
D.C.
WE WILL SEE YOU NEXT TIME ON
WHAT, LADIES?
"THE REAL"!
♪ THIS IS OUR TIME ♪
♪ DON'T WASTE ANOTHER ♪
♪ MINUTE OF IT ♪
♪ THIS IS OUR TIME ♪
♪ GRAB AHOLD, IT'S TIME TO ♪
♪ LIVE IT ♪
♪ STARTING RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ ♪
DR. OZ:  THE NORMAL SIGNS OF
PREGNANCY NOT THERE.