>> CHICKA-CHICKA-WALKA.
♪ ARE YOU READY Y'ALL
TO HAVE SOME FUN
♪ FEEL THE LOVE TONIGHT
DON'T YOU WORRY
♪ WHERE IT IS YOU COME FROM
IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT
♪ IT'S THE LATE LATE SHOW ♪
>> Reggie: LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
ALL THE WAY FROM INSIDE A
LEOTARD, GIVE IT UP FOR YOUR
HOST: THE ONE... THE ONLY...
JAMES CORDEN!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
( BAND PLAYING )
THANK YOU SO MUCH CHEESIER.
WELCOME TO THE "LATE, LATE
SHOW," THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
THANK YOU VERY, VERY MUCH.
I HOPE YOU HAD A GREAT DAY,
LET'S GET INTO IT I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU SAW THIS BUT THE AMERICAN
KEN EL CLUB HAS RECENTLY A
ANNOUNCED THAT THEY WILL BE
OPENING A DOG MUSEUM IN NEW YORK
CITY, YEAH.
BECAUSE YOU KNOW, WHAT IS THERE
TO DO IN NEW YORK.
(LAUGHTER)
A DOG MUSEUM IN NEW YORK CITY.
MEANWHILE THE CAT MUSEUM
CONTINUES TO BE YOUR AUNT JUDY'S
CONDO IN TAMPA.
THAT'S RIGHT.
ADMISSION FOR THE DOG MUSEUM IS
GOING TO BE $20 OR $15 FOR
STUDENTS AND SENIORS FOR $10 FOR
GOOD BOYS, GOOD BOYS.
GOO BOY GOOD BOY.
MOVING ON.
THERE'S BEEN A BIG BREAKTHROUGH
IN THE WORLD OF SCIENCE.
ACCORDING TO A RESEARCHER IN
ENGLAND WHEN YOU COUGH EATING A
BAR OF MILK CHOCOLATE IS
ACTUALLY A BETTER CURE FOR YOU
THAN OVER-THE-COUNTER MEDICINE.
NOW I KNOW WE HAVE A LOT OF
SCIENTISTS WHO WATCH THIS SHOW,
WE'RE BIG IN THE SCIENCE
COMMUNITY.
AND I JUST WANT TO TALK TO THEM
FOR AIR MINUTE AND GO HEY,
SCIENTISTS, IT'S OKAY JUST TO
SAY YOU LIKE CHOCOLATE.
(LAUGHTER)
YOU DON'T HAVE TO MAKE UP SOME
EXCUSE.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I GUESS NOW WE CAN ALL PUT OUR
CHOCOLATE IN THE MEDICINE
CABINET INSTEAD OF UNDER THE
STAIRS WITH OUR CIGARETTES, JUG
WINE AND RYAN GOSLING NUDES.
IT'S FINE.
MILK CHOCOLATE WORKS BETTER THAN
OVER THE COUNTER MEDICINE, YOU
KNOW WHAT THIS MEANS IN IT
TECHNICALLY MEANS THAT THIS IS A
BOTTLE OF COUGH SYRUP.
(LAUGHTER)
YOU'RE WELCOME.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
IN OTHER NEWS, AGE ENGLISH
FAMILY RETURNING FROM VACATION
RECENTLY SHOWED UP TO THEIR
FLIGHT WITH A COMPANY CALLED TUI
AIRLINES, ONLY TO FIND OUT THAT
THEIR ASSIGNED SEATS DID NOT
EXIST.
SO THEY HAD TO SPEND THE ENTIRE
FLIGHT SITTING ON THE FLOOR.
SPIRIT ANNE LINES ARE LIKE THIS
AND WERE LIKE WAIT, WE DON'T
HAVE TO GIVE OUR CUSTOMERS
SEATS?
WE'RE ALLOWED TO DO THIS?
THE FAMILY'S SEAT ASSIGNMENTS
WERE FOR SEATS THAT DIDN'T EXIST
OR AS THE AIRLINE IS NOW CALLING
IT ECONOMY MINUS.
(LAUGHTER)
THEY WERE SQUEEZED ON TO THE
FLOOR OF THE PLANE LIKE BAGGAGE
WHICH EXPLAINS THE IRE LINE'S
SLOGAN, KEEP CALM, YOU'RE A
CARRY ON.
AND--
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
AND WE HAD TO TELL BUT THIS.
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE HAVE NOW
SIGNED AN ON LINE PETITION TO
MERGE NORTH DAKOTA AND SOUTH
DAKOTA INTO A BRAND NEW STATE
CALLED, I PROMTION I'M NOT
KIDDING MERE, MEGAKOTA.
(LAUGHTER)
IT'S TRUE.
IT'S COMPLETELY TRUE.
BECAUSE IF THERE IS ONE THING
YOU WANT YOUR STATE TO SOUND
LIKE, IT IS A MONSTER TRUCK
RALLY.
NOW A MAN STARTED THIS
COMPETITION PURELY BECAUSE HE
THOUGHT IT WOULD, QUOTE, BE
PRETTY COOL TO HAVE A STATE
CALLED MEGAKOTA.
THEN THE MAN WENT ON TO SAY MOM,
ARE YOU BRINGING ME MY SANDWICH
OR NOT.
MOM!
(LAUGHTER)
MEGAKOTA SOUNDS LESS LICK AN
AMERICAN STATE AND MORE LIKE A
GIANT ROBOT MADE OUT OF DAKOTA
FANNING AND DAKOTA JOHNSON.
MOM!
AN FINALLY, THE VATICAN RECENTLY
LAUNCHED AN OFFICIAL TRACK TEAM
MADE UP ENTIRELY OF PRIESTS AND
NUNS WITH THE ULTIMATE DPOAL OF
COMPETING IN THE OLYMPICS.
YEAH.
YOU THOUGHT GOLD MEDAL WINNERS
THANKED GOD BEFORE.
NOW THIS IS EXCITING BECAUSE WE
ACTUALLY HAVE AN EXCLUSIVE HERE.
WE HAVE THE FIRST PHOTO OF THE
VATICAN TRACK TEAM IN TRAINING.
RIGHT, HERE THEY ARE PRACTICING
THE BATON HANDOFF.
(LAUGHTER)
SHALL WE HAVE A LOOK AND SEE WHO
OUR GUESTS ARE ON THE SHOW
TONIGHT.
IN THE RED ROOM HE IS ONE OF THE
MOST SUCCESSFUL COME ED WRANS IN
THE WORLD, YOU KNOW HIM FROM
NIGHT SCHOOL, RIDE ALONG AND THE
RECENT BOX OFFICE SMASH THE
OUTSIDE, THE ONE, THE ONLY KEVIN
HART IS HERE.
>> YES.
>> James: THERE IS HE.
>> HOW ARE YOU DOING.
>> James: HOW ARE YOU, KEV,
YOU GOOD.
>> I'M GOOD, I'M BUSY.
>> James: WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
WHAT ARE YOU SO BUSY DOING, MAN.
>> WE ARE HAVING AN INTENSE GAME
OF ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS RIGHT
NOW.
>> James: LET US WATCH S IT A
FINAL ROUND.
>> YEAH, BUT I DON'T WANT TO
LOSE AND THEN YOU SEE IT I WOULD
RATHER LIE AND SAY I WON.
>> James: DO YOU KNOW WHAT,
WE'LL FIX IT IN THE EDIT.
I THINK IT WOULD BE WEIRD IF HE
WITH DON'T SEE IT.
>> OKAY, FINE.
>> James: THIS IS IT, CAN WE
GET A DRUM ROLL.
CAN WE GET A DRUM ROLL.
>> COME ON, ASH, LET'S G FINISH
THE GAME, LET'S, GO, READY.
>> NO, I WON,.
>> James: HANG ON WHAT
HAPPENED THERE, DO IT AGAIN.
>> NO.
>> James: ARE YOU DOING IT ON
THREE OR ONE, TWO, THREE, GO.
>> I GOT A CONFESSION, HAVE I
TROUBLE GETTING TO THREE
SOMETIMES.
>> James: OKAY.
>> SOR HEE.
>> James: LET'S GO AGAIN.
ONE, TWO, THREE, GO.
>> DON'T TELL ME HOW TO PLAY THE
GAME.
DON'T-- ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS,
SHOOT.
>> I WON IN REAL LIFE.
>> James: KEVIN HART,
EVERYONE.
AND IN THE ORANGE ROOM A
FANTASTIC ACTOR, HE IS HAVING
THE MOST EXTRAORDINARY YEAR
STARRING IN THE SERIES
HOMECOMING AND INCREDIBLE FILM,
MY FAVORITE OF THE YEAR, IF
BEALE STREET COULD TALK, THE
MIGHTY, THE INCREDIBLE, STEPHAN
JAMES IS HERE TONIGHT.
>> HEY, JAMES, WHAT'S UP MAN.
>> James: ARE YOU GOOD.
>> I'M GOOD, MAN, HOW ARE YOU
DOING?
>> James: HOW IS EVERYTHING.
>> I'M HAVING A DRINK, MAN,
WHERE YOU AT.
I TECHED YOU, I TOLD YOU TO MEET
ME IN THE ROOM.
>> James: THAT WAS YOU?
>> THAT WAS ME.
YOU DIDN'T SAVE MIE NUMBER.
>> James: THAT MEANS IT IS
WEIRD BECAUSE WE HAVE A GUY ON
OUR SHOW WHO WORKS IN THE EDIT
DEPARTMENT CALLED STEPHAN AN I
WENT IN AND SAID STEPHAN WHY
AREN'T WE HAVING A DRINK AND HE
LOOKED AT ME REALLY WEIRD AND
NOW I KNOW THAT IT WAS YOU.
>> THAT WAS ME.
>> James: DO YOU WANT TO VEY
QUICK GAME OF ROCK, PAPER,
SCISSORS.
>> YEAH, COME ON IN.
>> James: ME AND YOU, ONE,
THROO, THREE, GO.
READY, ONE, TWO, THREE, GO.
OH, TRY AGAIN.
ONE, TWO, THREE, GO.
>> OH MY WORD.
>> OKAY, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
>> James: ONE, TWO, THREE, GO.
NO WAY!
ONCE ONE MORE TIME, ONE MORE
TIME, ONE MORE TIME.
>> James: DUDE, I ALWAYS KNEW
WE WERE LIKE THE SAME MIND, YOU
KNOW.
>> SAME WAVELENGTH.
>> James: OKAY.
ONE, TWO, THREE, GO.
OH!
STEPHAN JAMES, EVERYBODY.
PHOSPHORESCENT ARE HERE WITH
MUSIC.
YOU DON'T WHAT TO NIS IT.
ARE YOU READY, REG, HE'S REGGIE
WATTS, THIS IS THE "LATE, LATE
SHOW," ROLL THEM.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
♪ THE LATE LATE SHOW, OH, OH
THE LATE LATE SHOW, OOH
THE LATE LATE SHOW
♪ THE LATE LATE SHOW, OH, OH
♪ OH, OH
THE LATE LATE SHOW
IT'S THE LATE LATE SHOW ♪
>> James: IT'S THAT TIME AGAIN.
IT'S THAT TIME FOR... "EMOJI
NEWS"!
>> Reggie: ♪ EMOJI NEWS ♪
I WILL SHOW YOU A NEWS STORY
WRITTEN ONLY IN EMOJIS, YOU WILL
TELL ME WHAT YOU THINK THAT NEWS
STORY IS ALL ABOUT.
WHO HERE THINKS THAT THEY KNOW
THEIR EMOJIS.
SHOW YOURSELF TO ME, WHO KNOWS
THEIR EMOJIS?
WHO WOULD LIKE TO PLAY?
ANYBODY, ANYONE AT ALL.
YOU WANT TO PLAY?
COME ON, COME, COME, HERE, COME
IN HERE, COME IN HERE.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M GOOD, HOW ARE YOU.
>> I'M VERY WELL, WHAT IS YOUR
NAME, WHERE ARE YOU FROM.
>> BRIANA FROM COLTON.
>> YEAH.
>> WHERE IS COLTON.
>> SAN BERNARDINO.
>> James: WHERE IS SAN
BERNARDINO.
>> NEAR RIVER 150EUD.
>> James: ARE IS RIVERSIDE.
>> JUST EAST, THAT WAY.
>> James: IT'S OVER THERE,
OKAY, GOOD.
NOW WHAT, TALK US THROUGH THIS,
THIS IS-- SO THIS IS THIS
WEATHER WE'RE HAVING CURRENTLY.
>> I HAD TO LOOK GOOD FOR YOU.
>> James: OH, I LOVE YOU FOR
THAT.
WONDERFUL.
NOW WHAT DO YOU DO IN YOUR LIFE.
>> I WORK AT DISNEYLAND.
>> James: NO, YOU DON'T.
>> I DO.
>> James: SHUT THE FRONT DOOR.
>> WE HAVE TO GO TOGETHER.
>> James: WHAT DO YOU DO.
>> I'M AN ATTRACTIONS HOST JNS.
>> James: AN ATTRACTIONS HOST.
I LIKE TO THINK OF MYSELF AS AN
ATTRACTIONS HOST.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN WHAT IS YOUR
JOB ENTAIL.
>> I PRESS BUTTONS.
>> James: SHUT UP, YOU PRESS
THE BUTTONS.
YOU HOLD ALL THE POWER.
SO WHAT RIDE DO YOU WORK ON?
>> SPLASH MOUNTAIN.
>> James: NO WAY!
NO, THIS IS SO EXCITING.
WHAT THE WORST THING YOU HAVE
EVER SEEN AT DISNEYLAND.
>> OH, A LOT OF THINGS.
>> James: THAT YOU CAN TELL US
ABOUT.
>> I CAN'T MAKE IT UP.
>> James: THAT YOU CONDITION
BE FIRED FOR.
>> CAN'T MAKE IT UP I'VE SEEN
BOOBS A LOT.
>> James: ON SPLASH MOUNTAIN.
>> YEAH.
>> James: PEOPLE WANTING TO
SHOW IT OR THEY DO IT FOR THE IF
THE OWE.
>> THEY DO IT FOR THE PHOTO BUT
IT DOESN'T SHOW UP.
>> James: REALLY.
>> IT WASHES AWAY.
>> James: OH, DO YOU.
>> HANG ON, SO YOU WILL ADD A
DISHAL SPLARNS TO COVER UP THE
BOOB.
>> IT'S GONE, YEAH.
>> James: JOW WOW, THAT IS
SENSATIONAL.
I GET IT BECAUSE THERE ARE OFTEN
FOUR PEOPLE IN A PHOTO.
>> YEAH.
>> James: SO IF I GET A IF THE
OWE AND I'M WITH MY 7 YEAR OLD
SON AND BEHIND ME A WOMAN IS
FLASHING HER TA TAS, THAT IS A
DIFFICULT CONVERSATION WITH ME
AND MY SON.
SO I THINK YOU ARE DOING THE
RIGHT THING.
>> THANK YOU.
>> James: WELL, THIS IS
SENSATIONAL.
ALL RIGHT, NOW DO YOU USE EMOJIS
A LOT IN YOUR LIFE.
>> A LOT.
>> James: WHAT IS YOUR GO TOO
EMOJI.
>> PROBABLY THE LIKE GIRL THAT
IS LIKE THIS.
SHE'S LIKE, I GOT THIS.
>> James: NOW WHAT DO YOU
THINK SHE IS SAYING.
>> SHE IS SAYING I GOT T I'M IN
CHARGE.
>> James: OH, YOU THINK.
>> I THINK SO.
>> James: BECAUSE I ALWAYS
THINK SHE'S GOING-- I THINK
SHE'S GOING WHERE DID THAT TRAY
GO THAT I WAS HOLDING DRINKS.
(LAUGHTER)
JUST HAD A TRAY OF DRINKS, WHERE
DID THEY-- THAT IS WHAT I DO.
ALL RIGHT WHAT DO WE DO TAKE A
LOOK AT THIS NEWS STORY AND TELL
ME WHAT YOU THINK IS GOING ON
HERE.
>> MAN STABS ICE CREAM TRUCK,
COPS TAKE MAN.
WAYNE: LET'S VEY LOOK AND SEE IF
YOU ARE RIGHT, THIS SAY MAN IN
ENGLAND WAS ARRESTED FOR
ATTACKING AN ICE CREAM VAN AND
THREATENING ITS OWNER WITH A
THREE FOOT LONG SAMURAI SWORD.
(LAUGHTER)
I MEAN IN MY DEFENSE, I HAVE
BEEN STRUGGLING WITH MY NEW
YEAR'S DIET.
WELL DONE, YOU GOT IT ABSOLUTELY
RIGHT.
>> I DID IT.
>> James: WELL DONE.
WE'LL SEE YOU SOON, THANK YOU SO
MUCH.
WHO ELSE HERE THINKS THAT THEY
KNOW THEIR EMOJIS?
LET'S HAVE A LOOK.
THIS MAN.
COME ON AND JOIN ME.
COME OUT HERE, COME OUT HERE,
YOU HANDSOME DEVIL.
DON'T STAND ON A HIGHER STEP
DON'T STAND ON A LOWER STEP, YOU
DON'T THINK I KNOW YOUR GAME,
YOU WENT-- OH, HEY, HOW ARE YOU.
>> GOOD, HOW ARE YOU.
>> James: I'M GOOD WHAT IS
YOUR NAME WHERE ARE FROM YOU.
>> I'M FROM BRADEN, FROM LONDON,
BE TAN-- ONTARIO, CONDITION DA.
>> James: HEY, WHAT IS
HAPPENING IN YOUR LIFE, TELL ME
EVERYTHING.
>> NOT MUCH.
SURFING SERVING FULL TIME,
BASICALLY.
>> James: SERVING.
>> LIKE AT A RESTAURANT.
>> James: OH, I THOUGHT YOU
MEANT IN THE MILITARY.
>> NO, NO, NO.
>> James: WHEN YOU-- CAN I BE
HONEST, WHEN YOU PUT IT LIKE
THAT, THAT SAY GOOD WAY TO GO TO
A BAR THOUGH, MAN, I'M SO SICK
OF SERVING.
I'VE BEEN SERVING NOW FOR 25
YEARS.
I JUST NEED SOMEONE TO HELP ME
RELAX.
SO WHAT KIND OF RESTAURANT DO
YOU WORK IN?
>> IT'S A BARISH KIND OF LIKE
FAMILY, CALLED CRABBY JOES.
>> James: CRAPPY JOES.
>> CRABBY JOES, NO THE CRAPPY
JOES YZ WHY IS JOE TOO CRABBY.
>> I'M NOT TOO SURE, IS HE NOT A
VERY HAPPY GUY.
>> James: WHAT DO YOU DO AT
CRABBY JOE.
>> I'M JUST A SERVER.
>> James: YOU TAKE ORDERS.
>> TAKE ORDER, BRING THE FOOD,
THAT IS IT.
>> James: I WILL REPEAT THE
QUESTION I ASKED EARLIER, WHAT
IS THE WORST THING YOU HAVE SEEN
AT CRABBY JOES, TO PUT THIS IN
PERSPECTIVE, I ONCE WAS A
SERVER.
I ONCE DROPPED A STEAK ON A
FLOOR AND SERVED IT.
>> I HAVEN'T DONE THAT.
>> James: LIKE I GIVE A
[BLEEP] NOW.
(LAUGHTER)
>> PROBABLY SOMEONE PUKED UNDER
THE THE TABLE AND THEN STAYED
THERE FOR LIKE A HALF HOUR.
>> James: SHUT THE FRONT DOOR.
NO WONDER JOE'S CRABBY.
I WOULD BE FURIOUS.
>> HE WASN'T A HAPPY TBIE.
>> James: NOW DO YOU USE, WHAT
DO YOU THINK OF THESE I HAVE
HERE, YOU HAVE SEEN THIS FULL
SHOT, I AM ABSOLUTELY LOVING IT.
TALK TO ME, ARE YOU A BIG EMOJI
USER, DO YOU USE EMOJIS, ARE
THEY PART OF YR LIFE.
>> THEY ARE PART OF MY LIFE.
>> James: HOW OFTEN DID -- DO
YOU EVER, HERE IS MY QUESTION,
WHEN YOU ARE GOING TO WORK, DO
YOU JUST NOT TYPE THE WORD
CRABBY, DO YOU JUST PUT A CRAB
AND THEN JOE.
>> NO, I HAVEN'T.
>> James: WHAT?
>> NO.
>> James: DUDE.
>> I AM MISSING OUT.
>> James: THINK OF THE TIME,
YOU PROBABLY SAVED YOURSELF
HOURS OF YOUR LIFE.
>> CRABBY APOSTROPHE S, ONE HE
MOJ, GONE, WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE
GO TO EMOJI.
>> I LIKE THE ONE WHERE THE FACE
IS KIND OF LIKE, LIKE THE
SURPRISE FACE.
>> James: IS THAT YOUR
SURPRISE FACE?
>> IT, YEAH.
>> James: THAT IS YOUR
SURPRISE FACE.
>> MY SURPRISE FACE.
>> James: SO WHEN THAT MERN
THREW UP UNDER THE TABLE AND
THEN STAYED, YOU WERE LIKE--
(LAUGHTER)
OH MY GOD.
THIS IS A SURPRISE FACE.
>> I CONDITION DID THAT.
>> James: YEAH, YOU CAN.
YOU GOT TO PUT IT IN THE EYES,
PUT IN THE EYES.
LISTEN, HERE IS THE TRICK.
HERE IS THE TRICK FOR A GOOD
SURPRISE.
SURPRISE THE EYE.
SURPRISE THE EYES.
>> I DON'T THINK IT IS WORKING,
I DON'T THINK IT IS WORKING.
>> James: SURPRISE THE EYES,
IMAGINE SO LIKE WHEN YOU
SURPRISE, ARE YOU-- YOU HAVE TO
PUT THE SUR VICE-- SURPRISE IN
YOUR EYES, READY, ONE, TWO,
THREE SURPRISE!
YOU GOT IT!
YOU ABSOLUTELY GOT IT.
>> GOT IT, YEAH, YEAH.
>> James: ALL RIGHT.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS NEWS STORY.
TELL ME WHAT YOU THINK THIS
MIGHT BE.
>> OH, HMMMM.
UM, MAN TAKES AMBULANCE TO A
HOTEL-- LAF
(LAUGHTER)
ING J DO YOU WANT TO TELL HIM OR
SHALL I?
>> ABOUT THE BUILDING.
>> James: YEAH.
>> I BELIEVE IT'S A HOSPITAL.
>> James: YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> IT'S A HOSPITAL.
>> MAN IS TAKEN TO HOSPITAL FOR
PENIS TO BE CUT OFF.
>> James: FOR HIS PENIS TO BE
CUT OFF.
>> YEAH, TO CUT OFF-- .
>> James: NO, NO, SOMETHING
HAPPENED TO HIS PENIS.
>> I DONE KNOW WHAT HAPPENS.
>> James: LOOK, TAKE A GUESS,
THERE IS A BONE SNAPPING.
>> OH, HIS PENIS GOT BROKEN.
>> James: AND IT LOOKED LIKE.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> James: YOU KNOW WHAT THAT
LAST EMOJI S IT LOOKED LIKE A.
>> SAXOPHONE.
>> James: LET'S LOOK, A TIE
WANT EASE MAN FRACTURED HIS PENI
IN TWO PLACES WHILE HAVING SEX
IN A HOTEL AND BY THE TIME HE
GOT TO THE HOSPITALNESS, SEE
BOTH RIGHT.
>> YEAH.
>> James: BIT TIME HE GOT TO
THE HOSPITAL THE DOCTOR SAID IT
RESEMBLED A SAXOPHONE.
GOING TO BE AWHILE BEFORE HE HAS
SAX AGAIN.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR PLAYING, A
LOVELY MAN.
THAT WAS EMOJI NEW, KEVIN HART
AND STEPHAN JAMES ARE HERE WHEN
WE COME BACK.
(APPLAUSE).
♪
( BAND PLAYING )
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: WELCOME BACK.
NOW LET'S MEET OUR GUESTS
TONIGHT!
HE STARS IN "IF BEALE STREET
COULD TALK."
PLEASE WELCOME, STEPHAN JAMES!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
( BAND PLAYING )
HE STARS IN AND EXECUTIVE
PRODUCES "WHAT THE FIT."
IT'S KEVIN HART!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ CORDEN! ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
( BAND PLAYING )
HEY.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE, THANK
YOU FOR COMING TO SEE US.
I'M SO THRILLED.
I REALLY, REALLY AM, STEPHAN,
YOU HAVE A CERTAIN FAMILY MEMBER
WITHIN YOUR FAMILY WHO IS VERY
HAPPY THAT YOU ARE ON A COUCH
WITH KEVIN HART.
>> YES, YES, I DO SHUTOUT TO
AUNTIE PEA, I'M HERE WITH YOUR
MAN KEVIN   KEVIN HART.
I TOLD TU WAS GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> James: AUNTIE PEA.
>> HELLO, AUNTIE P WHAT DOES P
STAND FOR.
>> PAULETTE.
>> WHY DIDN'T YOU WANT TO STAY
PAULETTE.
>> I JUST WANTED TO PERSONALIZE
IT.
>> OKAY, I WILL SAY SHOUT OUT TO
AUNTEE PAULETTE, HELLOMENT I
HEAR ARE YOU A FAN, I'M A FAN
BACK.
I LOVE THE NICKNAME, SHOUT OUT
TO YOU.
>> James: THIS IS A LOVELY
THING, BUT THIS ISN'T THE FIRST
TIME I MED YOU TWO, I YOU HAVE A
LITTLE HISTORY TOGETHER.
YOU PLAYED BAGS KET BALL IN THE
NBA ALL-STAR GAMES.
CAN DARKS IT WAS CANADA VERSUS
URGES-- U.S.A., WHO WON THAT
IMGA.
>> I ASSUME THE U.S.A.
>> I DON'T REMEMBER.
>> I KNOW, CANADA WON, I DUST
WANTED TO LIE.
>> WHO WAS ON YOUR TEAM.
>> LET'S SEE, WE HAD KEVIN
HART,-- .
>> James: ANDERSON WAS ON THE
TEAM.
>> YEAH, BUT IT GETS THIN AFTER
ME.
>> James: WHO WAS BE OT
CANADIAN TEAM.
>> DRAKE WAS THE COACH.
>> James: DRAKE WAS THE COACH.
>> JUSTIN BIEBER WAS ON THE
TEAM.
>> James: WOW.
>> YOU, J BIEBS, DRAKE AS THE
COACH, AND THEN LIKE THE
PROPERTY BROTHER, RIGHT.
>> YEAH, YEAH, WE NEEDED THEM,
BECAUSE THEY ARE TALL.
>> I DIDN'T START OUT PLAYING IN
THE GAME, I WAS A COACH.
I REMEMBER, I REMEMBER IT VERY
WELL.
YOU KNOW, BASICALLY THIS IS WHEN
I WAS RETIRED FROM THE ALL-STAR
GAME, YOU KNOW, AS A THREE-TIME
MVP AT THE TIME, I'M SORRY, FOUR
TIME IT YOU KNOW, MY KNEES, MY
KNEES ARE BAD, YOU KNOW.
>> James: RIGHT.
>> MY CHEST HURT FROM TIME TO
TIME, I CHOSE TO PUTTED THE GAME
BEHIND ME BUT ON THIS PARTICULAR
DAY I REMEMBER GETTING A TEXT
SAYING THE U.S.A. NEEDS YOU.
AND THAT IS WHEN I WENT AND TOOK
IT UPON MYSELF TO SUIT UP AND
COME BACK OUT AND PLAY.
IT WAS-- .
>> James: WE HAVE A PICTURE OF
THE TWO OF YOU HERE, KEVIN, THIS
YOU AND STEPHAN, THIS IS YOU.
DID YOU YOU MAKE THAT, DID YOU
GET THE BALL, DID YOU BLOCK THAT
SHOT.
>> THAT WAS A BLOCK RIGHT THERE
KEVIN WAS GOING UP FOR A LAYUP
AND I BLOCKED YOU.
>> BECAUSE I'M NOT BIG ON CALLS
BUT THAT DEFINITELY LOOKS LIKE
IT'S NOT LEGAL.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE ON BOARD TO ME.
CAN WE BRING IT CLOSER.
>> James: YEAH, SURE.
>> YEAH, NO, WHEN I LOOK AT THIS
HERE, I LOOK AT AN INNOCENT MAN
BEING ATTACKED FROM THE BACK.
(LAUGHTER)
I ALSO, I ALSO LOOK AT MY
VERTICAL.  AND I MEAN, I DON'T
KNOW WHEN HE JUMPED AND WHEN I
JUMPED, BUT LOOK AT HIS FOOT AND
LOOK AT THE FLOOR.
LOOK AT MY FEET.
SOMEBODY DID SOMETHING WRONG
HERE.
>> OH, YEAH, STEPHAN, MAYBE YOU
SHOULDN'T PLAY BASKETBALL.
>> WE'RE BOTH RETIRED.
>> James: WHAT WAS DRAKE LIKE
AS A COACH?
WHAT IS HIS TEAM TALK LIKE IN
THE LOCKER ROOM.
>> HE WAS PRETTY MUCH MAN, Y'ALL
GO OUT THERE, KEEP DOING WHAT
Y'ALL ARE DOING, THE GOLDEN
STATE OFFENSE, SHOOT A BUNCH OF
3-S, EMBARRASS KEVIN.
HE REALLY WANTED IT GET THIS ONE
ON KEVIN.
>> SOUNDS LIKE A STUPID COACH,
YEAH.
>> James: BUT KEVIN, YOU HAVE
QUITE A SPORT MEM BEEL WHERE
PROBLEM, RIGHT.
>> YES.
>> James: YOU CLEBLGHT A LOT
OF STUFF WHAT KIND OF THINGS
HAVE YOU GOT.
>> I GOT A LOT OF STUFF, YOU
KNOW.
I THINK THE BENEFIT OF HAVING
GOOD RELATIONSHIPS THAT I HAVE,
GETTING THINGS THAT OTHER PEOPLE
CAN'T.
I GOT A LOT OF JERSEYS, SIGNED
JERSEYS.
YOU KNOW, I GOT HEADBANDS.
YOU KNOW, A COUPLE PLAYERS HAVE
ACTUALLY GEOFF INME THEIR
SNEAKERS-- GIVEN ME THEIR
SNEAKERS, KNEE BRACES, YOU KNOW,
ALSO I MEAN THINGS THAT YOU
WOULDN'T EXPECT.
I WENT TO THE SUPER BOWL AND THE
EAGLES WON AND-- YEAH, WELL, IT
WASN'T THIS YEAR.
SO WE'RE TALKING ABOUT PASTTIME
BUT CONFETTI, CONFETTI WAS BEING
DROPPED FROM THE CEILING.
I GRABBED SOME CONFETTI AND I
CUT A LITTLE HART OUT THE TURF,
WASN'T SUPPOSED TO DO T BUT I
DID IT CUZ I'M A THUG, YEAH, GOT
THAT.
>> James: HANG ON, YOU CUT A
HEART OUT OF THE TURF.
>> YEAH.
>> James: IN THE STADIUM.
>> YEAH, I WAS DRUNK.
THOSE ARE THINGS THAT
I'M-- AREN'T THINGS I'M TELLING
PEOPLE TO DO BUT IT WAS A GOOD
IDEA AT THE TIME.
>> James: AT THE TIME.
SO STEPHAN, AS WE HAVE
ASCERTAINED, YOU ARE FROM CAN
DARKS THERE ARE A LOT OF STER
WHY TYPES ABOUT CANADIANSMENT.
>> YEAH.
>> James: AND I WANT TO FIND
OUT JUST HOW CANADIAN YOU ARE.
IS THAT OKAY.
>> OKAYS I GUESS SO.
>> James: SO STEPHAN, DO YOU
LIKE MAPLE SYRUP.
>> DEFINITELY LOVE MAPLE SYRUP,
THAT SAY CHECK.
>> James: CANADIAN.
>> THAT IS A CHECK.
>> James: DO YOU LIKE CANADIAN
BACON.
>> CANADIAN BACON HAD TO BE
ANOTHER CHECK, ANOTHER CHECK.
>> James: DO YOU PLAY HOCKEY.
>> THAT I DO NOT DO.
>> James: OH, YOU HAVE
APPEARED ON THE CANADIAN TEAM
DRAMA DEGRASSI.
>> THAT I DID DO, YEAH.
>> James: NO WAY.
>> THAT, I DID DO.
THAT WOULD BE YES, YEAH, YEAH,
YEAH.
>> James: THIS IS CLOSE.
NOW YOU HAVE ONLY GOT ONE WRONG
OUT OF THE FIVE.
YOU HAVE TO GET, YOU HAVE TO GET
FOUR RIGHT OTHERWISE ARE YOU NOT
A YOU LAKED BACK INTO CANADA.
>> OH, OKAY.
>> James: I GUESS, SOME
DRAMATIC.
>> GEE, I'M NERVOUS.
>> James: DO YOU SPEAK FRENCH.
>> OUI.
>> James: CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> James: WELL DONE.
>> James: NOW KEVIN, WE'VE GOT
>> THANK YOU.
IT CONGRAT LAW ON YOUR BRILT
>> James: NOW KEVIN, WE'VE GOT
YANT SHOW, WHAT THE FIT, YOU ARE
IT CONGRAT LAW ON YOUR BRILT
THE STAR OF THE SHOW, YOU
YANT SHOW, WHAT THE FIT, YOU ARE
EXECUTIVE PRODUCE T I HAVE KNOW
THE STAR OF THE SHOW, YOU
THE SHOW, I WAS ON THE SHOW LAST
EXECUTIVE PRODUCE T I HAVE KNOW
NIGHT, HI SUCH FUN WHEN WE TAPED
THE SHOW, I WAS ON THE SHOW LAST
THE LAST SEASON.
NIGHT, HI SUCH FUN WHEN WE TAPED
TELL EVERYONE WHO HASN'T STEEN
THE LAST SEASON.
IT TWHA IT IS ABOUT.
TELL EVERYONE WHO HASN'T STEEN
>> WHAT THE FIT IS AN AMAZING
IT TWHA IT IS ABOUT.
SHOW I DECIDED TO DO THAT
>> WHAT THE FIT IS AN AMAZING
EMBRACES HEALTH AND WELLNESS ON
SHOW I DECIDED TO DO THAT
A DIFFERENT LEVEL.
EMBRACES HEALTH AND WELLNESS ON
I WANTED TO DO SOMETHING THAT
A DIFFERENT LEVEL.
INVOLVED WORKING OUT BY PUTTING
I WANTED TO DO SOMETHING THAT
PEOPLE IN A DIFFERENT
INVOLVED WORKING OUT BY PUTTING
ENVIRONMENT.
PEOPLE IN A DIFFERENT
SO I SAID WHY NOT TAKE MY
ENVIRONMENT.
FRIENDS PERSONALITIES, CELEBRITY
SO I SAID WHY NOT TAKE MY
FRIENDS AND PUT THEM IN FISH OUT
FRIENDS PERSONALITIES, CELEBRITY
OF WATER LIKE ACTIVITIES WHERE
FRIENDS AND PUT THEM IN FISH OUT
WE CAN BOTH EMBRACE THEM AND
OF WATER LIKE ACTIVITIES WHERE
MAKE THE MOST OUT OF THEM.
WE CAN BOTH EMBRACE THEM AND
JAMES, YOU JOIN ME.
MAKE THE MOST OUT OF THEM.
>> HE WITH WENT DOWN TO MUSCLE
JAMES, YOU JOIN ME.
BEACH.
>> HE WITH WENT DOWN TO MUSCLE
WE SHOWED THOSE TBIES.
BEACH.
WE SHOWED THOSE GUYS A THING OR
WE SHOWED THOSE TBIES.
TOO.
WE SHOWED THOSE GUYS A THING OR
>> I TELL YOU WHAT, I DIDN'T
TOO.
EXPECT TO YOU EM BRACE IT AT THE
>> I TELL YOU WHAT, I DIDN'T
LEVEL YOU DID.
EXPECT TO YOU EM BRACE IT AT THE
BUT YOU DID.
LEVEL YOU DID.
>>
BUT YOU DID.
>> James: I DID.
>>
>> YOU REALLY WENT THERE.
>> James: I DID.
>> James: A LOT OF PEOPLE SAY
>> YOU REALLY WENT THERE.
WE CHANGED MUSCLE BEACH FOREVER.
>> James: A LOT OF PEOPLE SAY
I THINK WE-- A LOT OF THOSE GUYS
WE CHANGED MUSCLE BEACH FOREVER.
THEIR CONFIDENCE WAS KNOCKED FOR
I THINK WE-- A LOT OF THOSE GUYS
A LITTLE WHILE.
THEIR CONFIDENCE WAS KNOCKED FOR
>> I JUST THINK IT WAS BY THE
A LITTLE WHILE.
ACTIONS THAT YOU CHOSE TO PUT ON
>> I JUST THINK IT WAS BY THE
DISPLAY.
ACTIONS THAT YOU CHOSE TO PUT ON
THAT COULD BE THE CAUSE FOR THAT
DISPLAY.
BUT WHAT I WILL TELL SU THAT
THAT COULD BE THE CAUSE FOR THAT
JAMES NOT ONLY CAME ON THE SHOW,
BUT WHAT I WILL TELL SU THAT
YOU PARTICIPATED AT THE HIGHEST
JAMES NOT ONLY CAME ON THE SHOW,
LEVEL AND YOU SHOWED THAT
YOU PARTICIPATED AT THE HIGHEST
PHYSICAL FITNESS IS MENTAL JUST
LEVEL AND YOU SHOWED THAT
AS MUCH AS IT IS PHYSICAL AND
PHYSICAL FITNESS IS MENTAL JUST
YOU HAD A GOOD TIME DOING THE
AS MUCH AS IT IS PHYSICAL AND
STUFF THAT WE DID.
YOU HAD A GOOD TIME DOING THE
>> James: I LOVED IT.
STUFF THAT WE DID.
>> YOU HAD A BALL.
>> James: I LOVED IT.
>> James: I LOVED IT, IT WAS
>> YOU HAD A BALL.
AN ABSOLUTE BLAST.
>> James: I LOVED IT, IT WAS
>> NOT THE SMARTEST LOCATION,
AN ABSOLUTE BLAST.
THOUGH.
>> NOT THE SMARTEST LOCATION,
LIKE I THOUGHT GOING DOWN TO
THOUGH.
VENICE BEACH, YEAH, IT WILL BE
LIKE I THOUGHT GOING DOWN TO
COOL, JAMES, WE'LL GET IN AND
VENICE BEACH, YEAH, IT WILL BE
OUT AND IT WASN'T COOL.
COOL, JAMES, WE'LL GET IN AND
>> James: NO, THERE WAS QUITE
OUT AND IT WASN'T COOL.
THE FERROR.
>> James: NO, THERE WAS QUITE
>> WHAT, WHAT IS THAT.
THE FERROR.
>> James: A LOT OF PEOPLE, A
>> WHAT, WHAT IS THAT.
SCENE, IT BECAME A SCENE.
>> James: A LOT OF PEOPLE, A
>> YOU'RE SPEAKING FRENCH.
SCENE, IT BECAME A SCENE.
>> I GOT IT,.
>> YOU'RE SPEAKING FRENCH.
>> James: YEAH, I GOT IT
>> I GOT IT,.
STEPHAN, IS WORKING OUT A BIG
>> James: YEAH, I GOT IT
PART OF YOUR LIFE?
STEPHAN, IS WORKING OUT A BIG
WHAT KIND OF WORKOUTS.
PART OF YOUR LIFE?
>> I LOVE WORKING OUT.
WHAT KIND OF WORKOUTS.
YOU KNOW WHAT IS CRAZY WE'RE
>> I LOVE WORKING OUT.
TALKING ABOUT CRAZY WORKOUTS.
YOU KNOW WHAT IS CRAZY WE'RE
I TRIED HOT YOGA THE OTHER DAY
TALKING ABOUT CRAZY WORKOUTS.
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
I TRIED HOT YOGA THE OTHER DAY
>> James: REALLY.
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
>> AND THAT WAS, I MEAN, IT'S
>> James: REALLY.
HOT.
>> AND THAT WAS, I MEAN, IT'S
>> IT'S REALLY HOT.
HOT.
>> THEY DON'T SAY HOT FOR NO
>> IT'S REALLY HOT.
REASON, IT WAS REALLY HOT.
>> THEY DON'T SAY HOT FOR NO
>> I BET IT WAS A FUROR.
REASON, IT WAS REALLY HOT.
>> James.
>> I BET IT WAS A FUROR.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> James.
>> James: LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT
>> YEAH, YEAH.
WHAT THE FIT, ON THE LAUGH OUT
>> James: LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT
LOUD NETWORK ON YOUTUBE.
WHAT THE FIT, ON THE LAUGH OUT
>> IN IS WHAT I HAVE BEEN
LOUD NETWORK ON YOUTUBE.
WAITING FOR.
>> IN IS WHAT I HAVE BEEN
>> I'M COMING BANS.
WAITING FOR.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO HOLD IT FOR
>> I'M COMING BANS.
HER.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO HOLD IT FOR
>> I WILL HOLD IT.
HER.
>> THAT SAN ACTUAL BIT OF WOOD.
>> I WILL HOLD IT.
>> YOU CAN DO T.
>> THAT SAN ACTUAL BIT OF WOOD.
>> I TEND NOT TO BREAK WOOD.
>> YOU CAN DO T.
>> OKAY, READY?
>> I TEND NOT TO BREAK WOOD.
>> James: MORE WITH THESE TWO
>> OKAY, READY?
WHEN WE COME BACK.
new or worse depression,
unusual changes in mood
or behavior, swelling,
trouble breathing,
rash, hives, blisters,
muscle pain with fever,
tired feeling,
or blurry vision.
Common side effects:
dizziness, sleepiness,
weight gain, swelling
of hands, legs, and feet.
Don't drink alcohol
while taking LYRICA.
Don't drive or use
machinery until you
know how LYRICA
affects you.
Those who've had a
drug or alcohol problem
may be more likely
to misuse LYRICA.
Now I have less
diabetic nerve pain.
Ask your doctor about LYRICA.
Like leather, skin is stronger
when it's hydrated.
Now I have less
diabetic nerve pain.
But 9 out of 10 men don't get
the hydration their skin needs.
That's why
Dove Men + Care Body Wash
has a unique hydrating formula
... to keep men's skin healthier
and stronger.
Whether you were borne for more
dance-offs...
More travels...
Or more touchdowns.
Get the immune support that
gives you more.
Airborne Gummies have 50% more
vitamin-C than Emergen-C...
Plus our crafted blend of
vitamins, minerals and herbs.
Airborne.
Isn't what goes into
your soup...
Just as important as what you
get out of it?
Our Broccoli Cheddar is
made with aged melted
cheddar, simmered broccoli,
and no artificial flavors.
Enjoy 100% clean soup today.
Panera. Food as it should be.
Dove gives you
fashion ready underarms
so you can wear anything.
From athletic tops
to zebra dresses,
and everything in between.
Enjoy 48 hour protection
and softer, smoother underarms.
With Dove antiperspirants.
YOU ARE WORKING IT AT THE
DEPARTMENT STORE, AND YOUR DADDY
IS WORKING AT THE WATER.
>> YOU NEED TO LISTEN.
>> LISTEN WHAT?
YOU DON'T GIVE A [BLEEP] ABOUT
ME, YOU DON'T GIVE A [BLEEP]
ABOUT NOBODY, YOU WITHIN ME TO
DIE IN HERE YOU KNOW WHAT IS
HAPPENING TO ME?
TO ME IN HERE?
(APPLAUSE).
>> James: THAT WAS A CLIP FROM
THE BEALE STREET IN THEATERS
RIGHT NOW.
THE FILM IS BRILLIANT AND ARE
YOU TERRIFIC IN IT.
IT IS SO GREAT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> James: IT IS SO INCREDIBLE.
TELL ANYBODY WHO HASN'T SEEN IT
WHAT THE FILM IS ABOUT AND WHO
YOU PLAY.
>> WELL, THE FILM IS THE FIRST
ADAPTATION OF A JAMES BALD WIN
NOVEL EVER, IF BEALE STREET
COULD TALK, ABOUT THIS YOUNG
COUPLE IN HAR BEM IN THE 1970S
THIS BLACK COUPLE WHO FIND
THEMSELVES AT ODD WHEN THE
HUSBAND, MY CHARACTER HAS BEEN
WRONGFULLY ACCUSED OF THIS CRIME
HE DIDN'T COMMIT AND SENTENCED
TO PRISON RIGHT AT A TIME WHEN
THEY FIND OUT THEY ARE ABOUT TO
BRING THIS BABY INTO THE WORLD.
SO ESSENTIALLY THE WHOLE FILM IS
ABOUT JUST LOVE AND THE POWER OF
LOVE AND WHAT THAT CAN HELP YOU
GET THROUGH.  AND YOU KNOW, HOW
KICKI LANE WHO JUST PLAYED TISH
IN THE CLIP YOU VUS SAW, HOW SHE
TRIES TO HELP HER HUSBAND GETS
THROUGH THIS TIME.
>> ST SO BRILLIANT AND THE FILM
HAS BEEN NOMINATED FOR SO MANY
AWARDS.
ACROSS EVERY KIND.
AND YOU TOOK YOUR MOTHER AND
YOUR BROTHER HERE TO THE GOLDEN
GLOBES.
>> I DID, YEAH.
>> AND DID THEY HAVE A-- DID
THEY HAVE A GREAT TIME.
>> YEAH.
>> DID YOUR MOTHER ENJOY IT?
WAS SHE STAR STRUCK BY ANYONE IN
PARTICULAR.
>> MY MOM, HER FACE MUST STILL
BE SWOL ENFROM SMILING AS HARD
AS SHE DID BUT YEAH, SHE WAS
JUST GOING CRAZY TAKING SELFIES
WITH EVERYBODY.
SHE WAS LIKE, YEAH, THAT'S
DENZEL, MOM.
>> CAN YOU INTROA DOES ME.
>> I DON'T KNOW HIM BUT-- SO
YEAH, SHE DEFINITELY MADE
FRIENDS WITH HUGH GRANT WHO WAS
SITTING AT OUR TABLE, LIKE BEST
FRIENDS, SHE FORGOT THAT I HAD
TAKEN HER TO THE GOLDEN GLOBES.
>> SHE WAS WITH HUGH GRANT.
>> I SAID MOM, YOU ARE MY PLUS
ONE, I BROUGHT YOU, HE DIDN'T
BRING YOU.
BUT ANYWAY I WAS SO PROUD TO PUT
A SMILE.
>> HAVE THEY STAYED IN TOUCH.
>> I DON'T KNOW, THINK THEY ARE
TEXTING HER, YOU KNOW.
>> NOW KEVIN, YOU ARE NOW
OFFICIALLY A FATHER TO A
TEENAGER.
>> YES.
>> James: AS A FATHER TO THREE
YOUNG CHILDREN, I CAN FEEL THIS
DAY COMING, WITH GATHERING FACE
PACE WHAT IS IT LIKE?
>> OH MY GOD, YOU CAN'T-- YOU
CAN'T PREPARE FOR THIS, MAN.
>> James: REALLY, WHAT
HAPPENS.
>> YOU JUST CAN'T THERE IS
SOMETHING THAT HAPPENS WITH A
TEENAGER.
AND YOU KNOW, MY DAUGHTER, MY
DAUGHTER SAY LITTLE DIFFERENT
BECAUSE WE'RE SO CLOSE.
SO WHEN YOU STAFORT TO SEE YOUR
DAUGHTER TURN INTO THIS YOUNG
WOMAN AND PICK UP CADENCES THAT
YOU KNOW SHE GOT FROM YOU.
LIKE IN THE MORNING, MY DAUGHTER
HITS ME SHE WILL COME IN THE
ROOM WHAT UP, G, YOU GUCCI I'M
LIKE WHAT?
YO, MY DAUGHTER IS SO COOL IT
MAKES ME-- IT MAKES ME SO MAD.
BECAUSE I KNOW, I KNOW SHE'S
WATCHING ME.
LIKE IF I COME DOWN AND SHE
LOOKS AT MY CLOTHES SHE'S LIKE,
THAT WHAT YOU ROCKING TODAY.
EIGHT, I SEE YOU, DAD.
BUT SHE, SHE'S SO, SHE'S SUCH A
GOOD KID, SUCH A GOOD KID, SHE
HAS A GREAT HEART AND THAT IS
WHAT I LOVE THE MOST.
BUT SHE MAKES ME LAUGH,
GENUINELY, MY DAUGHTER MAKES ME
LAUGH.
I'M SERIOUS, THAT IS A BIG DEAL
FOR ME.
>> James: YEAH.
>> THAT SAY BIG DEAL FOR ME.
THERE IS AN IMPRESSION, MY
DAUGHTER CAN DO A FOK DOWN
IMPRESSION ME AND I SEE A LOT OF
PEOPLE DO IMPRETIONZS OF ME, I
HAVE JAY JAY FARRELL TRK IS
FUNNY.
I'VE SEEN DJ, DWAYNE ROCK
JOHNSON HAS A FUNNY KEVIN HART
IMPRESSION.
BRYAN CRANSTON DOES A FUNNY
KEVIN HART IMPRESSION.
MY DAUGHTER DOES AN EXACT
REPLICA OF WHO, LIKE SHE GOES
HEY, DAD WHO IS THIS.
AND SHE WILL DO AN IMPRESSION OF
ME ON STAGE, SHE WILL GO MY NAME
IS KEVIN HART, I WORK REAL HART.
SHE DOES THE FACE, SHE DOES THE
LAUGH,-- I LOOKED AT MYSELF
LAUGH AND I WAS LIKE-- IT IS SO
DOPE, MAN.
>> James: OH MAN.
>> SHE JUST, SHE IS EVERYTHING
THAT I WOULD WANT BUT SHE'S A
TEENAGER.
YOU BAT WELL TEENAGER, MAN THERE
IS NO SUCH THING AS WINNING THE
CONVERSATION WITH TEENAGERS, YZ
IS SHE STRUPY, IS THERE A MOOD.
>> I'M SORRY, IS SHE WHAT.
>> James: IS THAT NOT A WORD
HERE.
>> SPEAKING FRENCH AGAIN, HE'S
BEEN FUROR.
>> James: WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK,
EVERYBODY.
Julie! Hey...
guess what day it is??
Ah come on,
I know you can hear me.
Mike Mike Mike...Mike
what day is it Mike? Ha ha!
Leslie, guess what today is?
It's Hump Day.
Whoot Whoot!
Ronny, how happy are folks
who save hundreds of dollars
switching to GEICO?
I'd say happier than a camel
on Wednesday.
HUMP DAY!!!! YAY!!
Get happy. Get GEICO.
Fifteen minutes could save you
fifteen percent or more.
I'm not picking it up.
You pick it up.
Well, somebody's gotta pick it
up.
I'll pick it up. They're clean!
♪ Cuz my hiney's clean ♪
♪ Oh yeah, I'm Charmin clean ♪
♪ That's how I know they're
clean ♪
(VO) Charmin Ultra Strong is
woven like a wash cloth
and just cleans better.
♪ Yeah, I'm Charmin clean ♪
The kid does have a point.
(VO) Enjoy the go with Charmin.
And for an extra clean finish,
try Charmin flushable wipes.
HVR.
You either love it
or you really love it.
I think I've got a solution
for you
We get it
You got it
We're PetSmart...
For the love of pets
With Expedia,
I saved when I added
a hotel to our flight.
So even when
she grows up,
she'll never outgrow the
memory of our adventure.
Unlock savings
when you add
select hotels to your
existing trip.
Only with Expedia.
select hotels to your
existing trip.
Digestive Advantage Probiotics
have a strong natural
protein shell.
So while other brands
may have billions of probiotics
many can struggle in stomach
acid.
Ours survive 100 times better.
Let our strength
help you stay strong.
( BAND PLAYING )
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: WELCOME BACK.
REGGIE, DO YOU HAVE A QUESTION
FOR ANY OF OUR GUESTS THIS
EVENING?
>> Reggie: YES, TONIGHT'S
QUESTION GOES TO EVERYBODY ON
THE COUCH.
A LOT OF YOU GUYS ARE PROBABLY
FAMILIAR, BOTH HAD YOU ARE
PROBABLY FAMILIAR WITH CHITTY
CHITTY BANG BANG.
IN THE DAYS WHEN CHITTEDY CHIT
AYE BANG BANG WAS FIRST BEING
WRITTEN, DID YOU THINK THE
AUTHOR HAD THE INTENT FOR SUCH
AN INTENSE IMPACT ON OUR
CULTURE?
(LAUGHTER)
>> I GUESS, I GUESS I'LL TAKE
IT.
>> GO FOR IT, YEAH.
>> FIRST OF ALL, GREAT QUESTION.
YOU KNOW, THAT IS ONE OF THOSE
QUESTIONS THAT REALLY MAKES YOU
THINK ABOUT HOW FAR WE HAVE
COME.
>> Reggie: YEAH.
>> AS PEOPLE SO I WOULD SAY
AFTER DRIVING INTO THE THOUGHT
OF THE CONCEPT THAT YOU HAVE
PRESENTED TO ME, I WOULD SAY
ABSOLUTELY NOT, THERE IS NO WAY
THERE IS NO WAY HE THOUGHT IT
WOULD BE WHAT IT WAS TODAY.
BUT THE IMPACT HAS BEEN NOTHING
SHORT OF POSITIVE.
>> I WOULD AGREE.
>> Reggie: YEAH, THAT IS THE
ONLY ANSWER SO THO IS CORRECT.
>> James: IT IS ABSOLUTELY
CORRECT.
PLEASE THANK OUR INCREDIBLE
GUEST, STEPHAN JAMES, KEVIN
HART, PHOSPHORESCENT IS HERE
WITH SOME MUSIC WHEN WE COME
BACK.  BLANKER BLANK
You've tried moisturizer
after moisturizer
but one blows them
all out of the water.
Hydro Boost
from Neutrogena®.
With hyaluronic acid
to plump skin cells
so it bounces back.
Neutrogena®
Mucinex Cold & Flu All-In-One.
Fights...
...Sore throat, fever, cough,
sinus pressure,
chest congestion, headache,
nasal congestion, body  pain...
ALL IN ONE.
Did you really need the caps
lock?
Get tough on cold and flu
symptoms.
Mucinex Cold and Flu All-In-One.
♪ When you have nausea, ♪
♪ heartburn, ♪
♪ indigestion, ♪
♪ upset stomach, ♪
♪ diarrhea... ♪
Girl, Pepto ultra coating will
treat your stomach right.
♪Nausea, heartburn, ♪
♪ indigestion, upset stomach,♪
♪ diarrhea... ♪
Try Pepto with Ultra coating.
New Tide PODS 2.0
with upgraded 4-in-1 technology.
Your detergent,
Stain removers,
And odor fighters
All fit, in the palm of your
hand.
#1 stain and odor fighter, #1
trusted.
It's got to be Tide.
( BAND PLAYING )
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: HERE TO PERFORM THE
TITLE TRACK FROM HIS LATEST
ALBUM, "C'EST LA VIE," WHICH IS
OUT NOW, PLEASE WELCOME...
PHOSPHORESCENT!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ I WROTE ALL NIGHT
LIKE THE FIRE OF MY WORDS COULD
BURN A HOLE UP TO HEAVEN
♪ I DON'T WRITE ALL NIGHT
BURNING HOLES UP TO HEAVEN NO
MORE
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ I STOOD OUT IN THE RAIN
LIKE THE RAIN MIGHT COME AND
WASH MY EYES CLEAN
♪ I DON'T STAND OUT IN THE RAIN
TO HAVE MY EYES WASHED CLEAN NO
MORE
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ "C'EST LA VIE," SHE SAY
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT SHE MEANS
♪ I SAY "LOVE, EASY, HEY COME TO
ME"
♪ "C'EST LA VIE," SHE SAY
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS
♪ I SAY, "ALRIGHT, WELL
C'EST LA VIE"
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ OOO
OOO, AHH
♪ I STOOD OUT IN THE NIGHT
IN AN EMPTY FIELD AND I CALLED
YOUR NAME
♪ I DON'T STAND OUT ALL NIGHT IN
EMPTY FIELDS AND CALL YOUR NAME
NO MORE
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ AND I WAITED FOR DAYS
FOR YOUR VOICE TO ANSWER TO ME
♪ I DON'T WAIT UP FOR DAYS FOR
YOUR VOICE TO ANSWER TO ME NO
MORE
♪ "C'EST LA VIE," THEY SAY
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY MEAN
♪ I SAY, "LOVE'S EASY IF YOU LET
IT BE"
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ "C'EST LA VIE," THEY SAY
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS
♪ I SAY, "ALRIGHT, WELL
C'EST LA VIE"
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ I SAY, "ALRIGHT, HONEY
C'EST LA VIE"
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ AIN'T THAT JUST HOW IT GOES,
HONEY
♪ C'EST LA VIE ♪
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
Dove gives you
fashion ready underarms
so you can wear anything.
From athletic tops
to zebra dresses,
and everything in between.
Enjoy 48 hour protection
and softer, smoother underarms.
With Dove antiperspirants.
When did soup become this?
At Panera,
we treat soup differently.
With vine ripened tomatoes,
signature cheddar,
simmered to perfection.
With big flavors,
not artificial ones.
Enjoy 100% clean soup today.
Panera. Food as it should be.
(Burke)
Parking Splat. And we covered
it.
Enjoy 100% clean soup today.
Talk to Farmers.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
So you finally got Fios, huh?
Yep, and wanna know what the
best part about it is?
Nope.
Gaming with less lag?
Watching movies in 4K?
The best part about it is, right
now,
my mom is streaming classes...
...my dad is streaming games...
And because the fiber-optic
network gives you
insane speed and capacity...
...they don't have to ask you to
get offline.
Exactly.
You owe me so big time.
Right now is your last chance to
switch Fios Gigabit connection
and get a year of Amazon prime
on us.
Hurry, this offer ends January
30th.
( BAND PLAYING )
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: THANKS SO MUCH FOR
WATCHING.
WE'LL SEE YOU SOON.
REGGIE, TAKE US HOME!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
( BAND PLAYING )
Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> James: THANK YOU, THANKS SO
MUCH.
BYE BYE, MWAH.
My gums are irritated.
I don't have to worry about
that, do I?
Actually, you do.
Harmful bacteria lurk just below
the gum line.
New Crest Gum Detoxify works
below the gum line
to neutralize harmful plaque
bacteria
and help reverse early gum
damage.
Gum Detoxify, from Crest.
Think only specialty stores have
what's new?
Olay has the hottest debut.
New Olay Clay Stick Masks,
Hydrating Facial Mist,
And Brightening Eye Cream.
Only by Olay.