>> ♪ Ready or not, here I come ♪
♪ You can't hide ♪
♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Hyah!
♪
>> [ Roars ]
>> We've got the three best
judges in American television
history!
[ Cheers and applause ]
It's time to face the
wall of the world.
♪
Yeah!
>> Aah!
[ Crowd cheers ]
>> Ha!
Hyah!
Bang.
"What about adding a
40-year-old, chubby, British
guy?
>> [ Laughs ]
>> Yes!
♪
>> I absolutely loved it!
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪
>> Good evening, and welcome to
"The World's Best."
Tonight, some of the most
spectacular acts from around the
globe will hit this stage and
compete for the prestigious
title of The World's Best and
the grand prize of $1 million.
Let's start by meeting our
American judges.
It's Faith Hill...
>> Whoo!
>> ...Drew Barrymore...
and RuPaul.
>> Thank you.
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Behind our American judges,
we have our 50 experts from
all over the globe.
Ladies and gentlemen, it's
the wall of the world!
[ Cheers and applause ]
Our United Nations of experts.
>> I'm Lira from South Africa,
multiplatinum singer and
songwriter.
>> I'm Petra Sprecher from
Switzerland.
I am a stuntwoman.
>> Anderson Silva, MMA fighter.
>> Royal Ballet dancer.
>> Magician.
>> Australia.
>> Musical actress.
>> Armenia.
>> Record producer.
>> Karate expert.
[ Experts speaking
indistinctly ]
♪
>> Welcome to the show, guys.
Thanks for being here.
Now, to make it past tonight's
round, performers must score
at least 75 points.
Anything less, and they'll be
heading home.
Let's meet our first acts.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Ladies and gentlemen, from the
World Taekwondo Headquarters in
South Korea, Kukkiwon!
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪
>> Now, that's sync, baby.
>> Yeah.
>> Hyah!
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪
My gosh.
What?
♪
>> Hyah!
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪
>> Oh, my goodness!
>> Oho!
♪
>> Come on.
[ Crowd cheers ]
>> Hyah!
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> That's insane!
♪
>> Hyah!!
>> Wow!
♪
>> Oh, my God.
>> Wow!
♪
>> Oh, my God.
>> Hyah! Hyah!
♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Oh, my goodness!
♪
>> Oh, that was beautiful!
>> I know!
>> Hyah!
♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Wow!
>> Ladies and gentlemen, the
Kukkiwon Demonstration Team.
>> Whoo!
>> That was absolutely
incredible.
>> [ Speaking Korean ]
>> Here's the thing -- I would
like to see if I can cut the
mustard.
I'd like to see if I could join.
>> [ Speaking Korean ]
>> You think I could have a go?
>> Okay, okay, step out for me.
>> [ Speaking Korean ]
[ Crowd chanting "James!" ]
>> Okay, okay, step out for me.
Okay, let me just limber up.
[ Crowd chanting "James!" ]
Hang on. Okay.
Okay, let me just limber up.
[ Chanting continues ]
Hang on. Okay.
Guys, guys...
[ Chanting continues ]
if you know anything about
Guys, guys...
taekwondo, you know I need
if you know anything about
absolute silence.
taekwondo, you know I need
>> Yes, yes.
absolute silence.
[ Laughter ]
>> Yes, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
[ Laughter ]
>> [ Chuckles ]
Yeah, yeah.
>> Just a little down.
>> [ Chuckles ]
Just down.
>> Just a little down.
[ Laughter ]
Just down.
Just a little bit more.
[ Laughter ]
A little bit more.
Take it just.
[ Laughter ]
And then down just a tiny bit
more, just a...
There. Okay.
[ Sighs ]
[ Laughter stops ]
Hyah!
[ Laughter ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Come on, James!
>> Yeah!
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> [ Laughing ]
>> Yes!
>> Okay, American judges,
what did we think?
>> My heart wanted to jump out
of my chest.
So thrilling!
So much skill! Totally hot.
>> Ru, would you like to have a
go and try and break one of
these?
>> Absolutely not.
>> Are you sure?
>> Yeah, I mean, what do you
guys have against wood?
I mean, come on.
[ Laughter ]
>> What did you think, Drew?
>> There just wasn't a beat
missed.
There wasn't a board missed.
There wasn't a step out.
It was just so fantastic.
I could not have loved it more.
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Faith?
>> It was like a ballet.
It had a softness to it.
And I just never got bored,
ever, not one single time.
You just kept elevating.
One of the greatest things I
have ever seen in my life.
>> Wow!
That is some big comments.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Let's go to our martial-arts
expert.
Anderson, what did you think of
Kukkiwon?
>> You know, James, martial arts
complete my life.
You know, I start training
taekwondo, and taekwondo give me
everything I have in my life
now, and I need to say,
"Thank you, guys, thank you."
This is an amazing performance.
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Okay, now, to make it past
tonight's round, performers must
score at least 75 points.
It's the moment of truth.
Time for our American judges and
the world to decide your fate.
Judges, lock in your scores.
♪
>> I dare someone
not to like that.
I dare someone.
♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> The scores are locked in.
They can't change their vote.
So, out of a possible 50, how
did our American judges score
Kukkiwon?
Let's find out.
It's 48 from Drew.
48 from Ru.
Oh, look at that!
A perfect 50 from Faith.
That gives you a combined
average score of...
49 points.
[ Cheers and applause ]
So, you need at least 75
to move forward.
It's now up to our international
judges.
It's time to face the
wall of the world.
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪
Oh.
Yay!
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> No way!
>> No!
>> Goodness!
Every single expert
from around the world
gave you a yes vote.
The Kukkiwon Demonstration Team
is through to the next round.
Let's go to our Korean judge.
Alex, you must be incredibly
proud.
>> The precision,
synchronization, and dynamics
was beyond perfection, and you
guys are true ambassadors for
Korea.
[ Speaking Korean ]
>> Aww.
Ladies and gentlemen, let's hear
it once again for Kukkiwon,
everybody!
Congratulations!
>> Wow. I should have voted 50.
>> That was...worth it.
>> Yeah.
>> No, I know.
>> I don't know how someone's
gonna top that, but they're
gonna.
Let's find out who it is.
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> ♪ Just feelin' good, good,
good ♪
>> I'm Keifer.
>> I'm Mackie.
>> And I am Francis.
>> And we are the TNT Boys.
>> ♪ Just feelin' good ♪
>> We met in a local singing
competition in the Philippines.
>> We sang together, and it
became viral.
>> ♪ Feelin' good ♪
>> Everywhere we go in the
Philippines, everybody can
recognize us.
[ Children giggling ]
>> But on the stage of
"The World's Best," it's the
next level.
>> ♪ Just feelin' good ♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
[ "Listen" plays ]
>> ♪ Listen ♪
♪ To the song here in my heart ♪
♪ A melody I start
but can't complete ♪
>> ♪ Oh, I'm screamin' out,
and my dreams will be heard ♪
♪ They will not be pushed aside
or worse ♪
♪ Into your own,
all 'cause you won't
liste-e-e-n ♪
>> ♪ Listen ♪
>> What?!
>> ♪ To the song
here in my heart ♪
♪ A melody I start,
but I will complete ♪
>> ♪ Oh, now I'm done believin'
you ♪
♪ You don't know what I'm
feelin' ♪
♪ I'm more than what you
made of me ♪
♪ I followed the voice ♪
>> ♪ You ga-a-a-ve ♪
>> ♪ Now I've gotta find ♪
>> ♪ My own ♪
♪ My ow-ow-ow-ow-n ♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪ My ow-ow-ow-ow-ow-n ♪
>> Yeah!
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Thank you, thank you.
>> Yeah!
>> Thank you!
>> Thank you, thank you.
>> Ladies and gentlemen,
>> Thank you!
the TNT Boys!
>> Ladies and gentlemen,
That was incredible!
the TNT Boys!
Well done.
That was incredible!
>> Thank you.
Well done.
>> Here's the thing -- I felt,
>> Thank you.
as I was watching it, "What
>> Here's the thing -- I felt,
about adding a 40-year-old,
as I was watching it, "What
chubby, British guy?"
about adding a 40-year-old,
[ Laughter ]
chubby, British guy?"
>> You can.
[ Laughter ]
>> Just give me a chance.
>> You can.
>> Yeah!
>> Just give me a chance.
>> Are you serious?
>> Yeah!
>> That's it. We quit.
We're going on the road.
We'll see you next time, guys.
Good night.
[ Cheers and applause ]
I think we know what the whole
room felt, but let's go to our
American judges.
What did we think of these boys?
>> Okay, first of all, you have
some serious attitude.
>> Yeah, thank you.
>> I mean, you're so precious
and so sweet, but when you were
singing, you were in that song,
you were like, "Bam."
>> Yeah.
>> I could just eat you up.
[ Laughter ]
>> Drew, what did you think?
>> You know, I have a soft spot
for kids.
I was a kid performer, but I
have kids now.
This is a whole other thing.
>> Yeah.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you!
>> You possess a gift.
>> Thank you.
>> You're just that good.
>> Thank you!
>> Ru, what did we think?
>> Thank you.
>> Boys, I have one thing to
say -- "Shantay, you stay."
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Thank you, thank you!
>> Thank you!
>> [ Laughs ]
>> Dennis from Germany --
Dennis, you've actually worked
with Beyoncé.
What do you think she would
think of that performance?
>> Oh, my God.
>> So, I would like to --
>> Oh, my God! Whoo!
>> [ Laughs ]
So, I actually wouldn't be
surprised if she would call you
up after this and be like,
"Join me on the next tour."
[ Chuckles ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Thank you!
>> All right, it's the moment of
truth.
Judges, let's lock in your
scores right now.
♪
Okay, while the U.S. judges and
the world lock in their votes,
we're gonna take a quick break.
Come on back, everybody.
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪
Carla is living with metastatic
breast cancer, which is breast
cancer that has spread to other
parts of her body.
She's also taking prescription
IBRANCE with an
aromatase inhibitor, which is
for postmenopausal women with
hormone receptor-positive HER2-
metastatic breast cancer
as the first hormonal
based therapy.
IBRANCE plus letrozole was
significantly more effective at
delaying disease progression
versus letrozole.
Patients taking IBRANCE
can develop
low white blood cell
counts, which may cause
serious infections that
can lead to death.
Before taking IBRANCE,
tell your doctor if
you have fever, chills,
or other signs of infection,
liver or kidney problems,
are pregnant, breastfeeding,
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects include
low red blood cell
and low platelet counts,
infections, tiredness,
nausea, sore mouth,
abnormalities
in liver blood tests, diarrhea,
hair thinning or loss, vomiting,
rash, and loss of appetite.
Carla calls it her new normal
because a lot has changed,
but a lot hasn't.
Ask your doctor about IBRANCE.
The #1 prescribed FDA-approved
oral combination treatment
for HR+/HER2- MBC.
Seriously, what is this?
New LISTERINE® READY! TABS™
aren't gum, mints, or marbles.
If you guessed they're tabs that
turn into liquid as you chew,
so you can swish and clean your
whole mouth instantly,
then you were correct.
And that was a really good
guess.
Nice job.
♪
This Valentine's Day,
give her your heart.
♪
Or,
ask her for her hand.
♪
Love her, love her style.
During the Valentine's Day Sale.
Save on specials
like these diamond earrings
for just $59.
Only through February 14th.
At Zales. The Diamond Store.
Yes, we are twins.
When I went on to Ancestry,
I just put in the name
of my parents and
my grandparents.
I was getting
all these leaves
and I was going back
generation after generation.
You start to see
documents and you see
signatures of
people that you've never met.
I mean, you don't
know these people,
but you feel
like you do.
You get connected
to them.
I wish that I could
get into a time machine
and go back
100 years, 200 years
and just meet
these people.
Being on Ancestry
just made me feel
like I belonged
somewhere.
Discover your story.
Start searching for
free now at Ancestry.com.
TICHINA ARNOLD:
Born a slave, Sojourner Truth
spent her life
traveling the country
and fighting
for women's rights.
Celebrate her legacy and
learn more about black history.
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Welcome back to
"The World's Best."
Okay, so, out of a possible 50,
how did the American judges feel
about the TNT Boys?
50 from Drew...
>> Thank you!
>> Thank you.
>> ...50 from Faith...
48 from Ru...
>> Oh!
>> ...which gives you
an average combined score of...
49 points.
[ Cheers and applause ]
You need at least 75 to move
forward.
Now it's all up to our
international judges.
It's time to face the
wall of the world.
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪
>> Yes!
>> Oh!
>> [ Laughing ]
99 for the TNT Boys!
>> Whoo!
Where do they go from here?
I want to go to Pops.
She's from the Philippines.
What did you think of the
TNT Boys tonight.
>> Oh, my gosh, I am so proud
right now to represent the
Philippines.
On behalf of the Filipinos,
guess what?
I know for a fact that you can
be The World's Best.
>> Whoo!
>> Ladies and gentlemen,
the TNT Boys!
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> ♪ Look at me now ♪
♪
>> Next up, ladies and
gentlemen, all the way from
Australia, it's the
Space Cowboy.
>> And neon light is powered by
2,000 volts of electricity
and filled with a highly deadly
mercury-compound gas.
But to add a unique twist, when
I swallow this glass tube
all the way down my throat,
I've attached a small microphone
to the tip.
You'll hear my gag reflex
opening...
[ Audience groans ]
...my internals working,
and my heart beating.
>> Do we have to?
>> Enjoy.
>> Yeah, I-I-I'll try.
>> [ Laughs ]
>> [ Exhales sharply ]
[ Clears throat ]
♪
[ Gagging ]
[ Audience groans ]
[ Gagging continues ]
♪
[ Heartbeat ]
>> Heart beating.
Do you hear his heart?
[ Audience groans ]
>> [ Gagging ]
♪
[ Gasps ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> [ Exhales sharply ]
>> It was so beautiful, it
[ Cheers and applause ]
brought a tear to my eye.
>> It was so beautiful, it
>> I bet.
brought a tear to my eye.
>> Now, I've got here two
>> I bet.
15-gallon beer kegs
>> Now, I've got here two
attached to each end
15-gallon beer kegs
of a weight-lifting bar.
attached to each end
In the center is welded a sword.
of a weight-lifting bar.
I'm going to attempt to swallow
In the center is welded a sword.
the blade and suspend the entire
I'm going to attempt to swallow
weight from nothing more than
the blade and suspend the entire
the blade down my throat.
weight from nothing more than
>> Hmm.
the blade down my throat.
>> Oh, no.
>> Hmm.
>> The total weight for these
>> Oh, no.
two kegs?
>> The total weight for these
Just over 132 pounds.
two kegs?
So wish me luck.
Just over 132 pounds.
♪
So wish me luck.
[ Exhales sharply ]
♪
[ Audience groans ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
♪
[ Audience groans ]
>> Whoo!
♪
>> Aah.
>> Whoo!
[ Audience gasps ]
>> Aah.
Ugh.
To most, he's
Phil Mickelson...
..pro golfer.
To me, he's...
...well, Dad.
So when his
joint pain from
psoriatic arthritis
got really bad, it scared me.
And what could that pain mean?
Joint pain could
mean joint damage.
ENBREL helps
relieve joint pain...
...helps stop irreversible
joint damage...
and helps skin get clearer.
ENBREL may lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious, sometimes
fatal events...
including infections,
tuberculosis...
lymphoma, other cancers,...
nervous system and
blood disorders...
and allergic
reactions have occurred.
Tell your
doctor if you've
been some place where
fungal infections are common.
Or, if you're
prone to infections,
have cuts or sores,
have had hepatitis B,
have been treated
for heart failure...
or if you have
persistent fever...
bruising, bleeding, or paleness.
Don't start ENBREL...
if you have an
infection like the flu.
Since ENBREL...
Dad's back to being... Dad.
Visit Enbrel.com...
and use the Joint
Damage Simulator
to see how your joint
damage could be progressing.
Ask about ENBREL.
ENBREL.
FDA approved for
over 16 years.
Do I use a toothpaste that
whitens my teeth,
or one that's good for my teeth?
Now I don't have to choose.
From Crest 3D White, the
Whitening Therapy collection
with new Spearmint and
Peppermint Oil.
It gently whitens,
plus it has a fortifying formula
to protect your enamel.
Crest.
Healthy, beautiful smiles
for life.
I'll take a Coke.
Is Pepsi Ok?
Is Pepsi, OK?
Is Pepsi, OK!?
[laughter]
Are puppies, OK?
Is a shooting star, OK?
Is the laughter of
a small child, OK?
Pepsi's more than, OK!
It's
Okayyyy
Okurrrr
♪ I Like It ♪
Okay, what have
we learned today?
You want a Pepsi?
I want a Pepsi.
There you go.
Okurrr. Aaahh.
I've got to come up with
my own catch phrase.
Okayyy
(Clapping)
Every day, visionaries
are creating the future.
( ♪ )
So, every day,
we put our latest technology
and vast expertise to work.
( ♪ )
The United States
Postal Service
makes more e-commerce
deliveries to homes
than anyone else
in the country,
affordably and on-time.
(Ringing)
( ♪ )
The future only happens
with people who really
know how to deliver it.
People aren't talking
about Giant's
The future only happens
fresh grab and go
salads and sandwiches.
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Oh, hello.
At Giant, it's
the little things
that make mealtime easy,
so you have more time
with the people you love.
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.
What would she do without me?
♪
It hasn't always
been easy, has it?
♪
There have been days
when you doubted yourself.
♪
And days when you
were ready to quit.
♪
But you didn't.
Because you had the courage to
venture into something powerful.
Education.
If I leave you with just
three words of advice:
never...stop...growing.
[cheering]
People aren't talking
about Giant's
easy grab and go
chicken wings,
perfect for game day.
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Oh, hello.
At Giant, it's
the little things
that make entertaining easy,
leaving more time for
those closest to you.
♪
[ Audience groans ]
>> Whoo!
♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Whoo!
♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
Aah.
♪
>> Ugh.
Aah.
[ Chuckles ]
>> Ugh.
[ Cheers and applause ]
[ Chuckles ]
[ Clearing throat ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Wow.
[ Clearing throat ]
>> In 2008, I broke my first
>> Wow.
Guinness World Record, when I
>> In 2008, I broke my first
swallowed 17 swords at the same
Guinness World Record, when I
time.
swallowed 17 swords at the same
A couple of years later, I had
time.
magnets inserted into my chest,
A couple of years later, I had
under the flesh.
magnets inserted into my chest,
[ Audience groans ]
under the flesh.
>> Oh!
[ Audience groans ]
>> And as I suspected, it pulled
>> Oh!
the blades away from my heart,
>> And as I suspected, it pulled
held all the swords tightly
the blades away from my heart,
together.
held all the swords tightly
I managed to swallow 19 swords.
together.
It's real.
I managed to swallow 19 swords.
I can wiggle them around
It's real.
for you.
I can wiggle them around
>> Oh, God.
for you.
No, unh-unh, unh-unh, no.
>> Oh, God.
>> Don't be afraid.
No, unh-unh, unh-unh, no.
>> No.
>> Don't be afraid.
>> So now I can achieve the
>> No.
impossible.
>> So now I can achieve the
I can swallow 29 swords at the
impossible.
same time.
I can swallow 29 swords at the
>> Oh, my God.
same time.
>> But why?
>> Oh, my God.
>> Oh, my...
>> But why?
>> Oh!
>> Oh, my...
>> Oh, no, no, no.
>> Oh!
>> No.
>> Oh, no, no, no.
>> [ Laughing ] Yes!
>> No.
♪
>> [ Laughing ] Yes!
[ Audience gasps ]
♪
>> Oh, oh, oh-oh!
[ Audience gasps ]
>> No!
>> Oh, oh, oh-oh!
Oh, my God.
>> No!
>> Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my God.
[ Audience gasps ]
>> Oh, my gosh.
Oh, God, this is so painful to
[ Audience gasps ]
watch.
Oh, God, this is so painful to
>> Aah!
watch.
♪
>> Aah!
>> Ah.
♪
>> Whoa!
>> Ah.
>> I'm the Space Cowboy.
>> Whoa!
Thank you.
>> I'm the Space Cowboy.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Thank you.
♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Oh, my word!
♪
The Space Cowboy,
>> Oh, my word!
ladies and gentlemen!
The Space Cowboy,
Thank you so much!
ladies and gentlemen!
>> Thank you.
Thank you so much!
>> RuPaul still hasn't --
>> Thank you.
RuPaul's face hasn't moved since
>> RuPaul still hasn't --
you come onstage.
RuPaul's face hasn't moved since
He's been like this.
you come onstage.
>> You -- You know that that
He's been like this.
scares the heck out of us,
>> You -- You know that that
right?
scares the heck out of us,
>> I hope so, yeah.
right?
>> Yes, it does.
>> I hope so, yeah.
[ Laughter ]
>> Yes, it does.
>> What's strange to me is that
[ Laughter ]
it is very dark and intense, and
>> What's strange to me is that
then the look in your eye is
it is very dark and intense, and
just like, "Oh, my God, I'm
then the look in your eye is
having so much fun with this."
just like, "Oh, my God, I'm
[ Laughter ]
having so much fun with this."
>> Faith, is this something you
[ Laughter ]
want to see more of?
>> Faith, is this something you
[ Laughter ]
want to see more of?
>> But please remember,
[ Laughter ]
everything that I do will be
>> But please remember,
completely different.
everything that I do will be
>> I believe you. I do.
completely different.
[ Laughter ]
>> I believe you. I do.
>> All right, let's go to Stuart
[ Laughter ]
from Scotland.
>> All right, let's go to Stuart
You're a magician.
from Scotland.
What did you think of that?
>> It was sick, it was
disgusting, it was violent, and
I loved every minute of it.
>> Ha ha!
[ Cheers and applause ]
All right, well, it's
the moment of truth.
Time for our American judges and
the world to decide your fate.
Judges, let's lock in those
scores.
♪
>> You don't want to see
more of this?
>> Me? No.
>> Oh, come on.
>> I don't know, there's a part
of me that wants to see what's
next.
♪
>> Oh.
[ Applause ]
♪
>> So, how did our American
[ Applause ]
judges feel about the
>> So, how did our American
Space Cowboy?
Let's find out.
A 33 from Faith...
38 from Ru...
[ Audience gasps ]
>> I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
>> That's 25 from Drew.
That gives you an average
combined score of...
32 points.
Now, you need at least 75 to
move forward in the competition.
It's now all up to our
international judges.
It's time to face the
wall of the world.
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪
Come on. Come on.
57 points for the Space Cowboy.
You haven't made it through.
Um, Sisco, this is an act you'd
like to see more of.
What words can we give the
Space Cowboy before he leaves
tonight?
>> Space Cowboy, you might not
be everyone's cup of tea, but
you're amazing, you're
dangerous.
And good luck to you, 'cause you
deserve to be onstage.
>> Absolutely, you do.
Once again, let's hear it for
the Space Cowboy, everybody!
Thank you so much.
>> Thank you.
>> Don't ever stop.
Thank you very, very much. Wow!
It's a tough place to hit
that 75.
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Yeah, that's gonna be -- That
would be hard to watch again.
>> I couldn't watch it. Yeah.
>> I'm gonna remember that one.
[ Chuckles ]
>> I was pretty disappointed I
only got a score of 57.
I know that my next acts just
get bigger and better, so I
really was looking forward to
come back.
They're missing out.
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Our worldwide search for the
most talented acts on Earth took
us to unexpected places,
including one in Mongolia.
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪
>> [ Speaking Mongolian ]
>> He's on a really strict diet.
>> Do you know where he's gonna
>> [ Speaking Mongolian ]
stand?
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> It's Enkh-Erdene, everybody.
Thank you for coming to see us.
Is this your first time in the
United States?
>> [ Speaking Mongolian ]
>> Yeah.
This is the first time in
America, yeah.
>> It's your first time in
America.
What's the number-one thing
you're hoping to see whilst
you're in America?
>> [ Speaking Mongolian ]
>> He wants to swim at the
beach -- in the beach.
>> You want to swim at the
beach?
Well, I'm sure we can arrange
that.
Ladies and gentlemen, it's
Enkh-Erdene!
[ Cheers and applause ]
[ "Amarillo by Morning" plays ]
♪
>> ♪ And Amarillo by morning ♪
[ Crowd cheers ]
>> ♪ Up from San Antone ♪
>> Good!
>> ♪ Everything that I've got ♪
♪ Is just what I've got on ♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪ When that sun is high in the
Texas sky ♪
♪ I'll be buckin' at a county
fair ♪
♪ Amarillo by morning ♪
♪ Amarillo is on my mind ♪
>> Wow.
Oh, my God.
♪
>> ♪ Amarillo by morning ♪
>> He's really giving me
goose bumps.
>> ♪ Up from San Antone ♪
♪ Everything that I've got ♪
♪ Is just what I've got on ♪
>> But, now, he doesn't speak
any English.
Does he know what he's saying?
>> ♪ I ain't got a dime, but
what I got is mine ♪
♪ I ain't rich, but, Lord,
I'm free ♪
[ Crowd cheers ]
♪ Amarillo by morning ♪
♪ Amarillo's where I'll be ♪
♪ Amarillo's where I'll
♪ Amarillo by morning ♪
be-e-e-e ♪
♪ Amarillo's where I'll
♪
be-e-e-e ♪
>> Wow.
♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Ladies and gentlemen,
Enkh-Erdene, everybody!
Thank you so much!
Oh, my word!
[ Cheers and applause continue ]
It was an amazing moment to hear
this many people's jaws drop
to the floor as you started
singing.
[ Laughter ]
It was incredible.
I mean, Faith, can you imagine
how different your life would
have been if you'd have met Enkh
before Tim McGraw?
[ Laughter ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Um, I-I-I'm -- I-I'm really
speechless.
You picked one of the most
classic country songs by one of
the greatest country singers of
our lifetime, and you blew me
away, and I'm the biggest
George Strait fan.
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Ru, what did you think?
>> Fantastic!
>> [ Laughs ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Amarillo by morning,
Hollywood tonight!
>> [ Laughs ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> [ Speaking Mongolian ]
>> You are a soft-spoken
gentleman from Mongolia who
doesn't speak English one
moment, and the next minute, you
are a country-music star.
[ Cheers and applause ]
These are the mind-blowing
moments we're all hoping for.
Thank you.
>> Wow.
[ Cheers and applause ]
I mean, these are some
incredible comments.
Lira is a singer from
South Africa.
Lira, what did you think?
>> I was gobsmacked -- okay? --
for the fact that he does not
speak a word of English.
So I wonder, does he understand
what he's saying, because he
sounded very sincere.
>> Good question.
>> It's a very good question.
>> No.
>> No!
[ Laughter and applause ]
>> Seriously?
You don't really understand what
you're singing about?
>> [ Speaking Mongolian ]
>> No.
[ Laughter ]
>> Oh, my word.
And this is incredible.
All right, it's the moment of
truth.
Time for our American judges and
world's to decide Enkh's fate.
Judges, let's lock in your
scores.
♪
Okay, so, out of a possible 50,
how did the American judges feel
about Enkh-Erdene?
Let's find out.
Oh!
A 50 from Drew...
a 48 from Ru...
and a 45 from Faith, which gives
you an average combined score
of...48 points.
[ Cheers and applause ]
You have 48 points.
You need at least 75 to move on.
It's all up to our international
judges.
It's time to face the
wall of the world.
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪
Oh, come on.
Come on!
Yes!
Oh, my word!
>> ♪ It's a crazy town full of
neon dreams ♪
>> 97!
That is an incredible score!
Congratulations! Well done!
You go through to the next
round.
An epic score!
Everybody is on their feet.
Now, international judges.
>> ♪ In this crazy town ♪
>> Kobi?
[ Audience boos ]
>> Let me use my escape button.
[ Laughter ]
>> Tell me, how do you say,
"You don't know what you're
talking about" in Mongolian?
>> [ Speaking Mongolian ]
>> [ Speaking Mongolian ]?
>> [ Laughing ] Yeah.
>> Very good, James!
>> On 3, ready?
We'll all do it together.
1, 2, 3.
>> [ Speaking Mongolian ]
>> What he said.
That's how we feel about you,
Kobi.
[ Cheers and applause ]
97 points!
Ladies and gentlemen,
Enkh-Erdene!
What a superstar!
[ Cheers and applause ]
The voice of Mongolia.
You don't want to miss the
incredible acts we've got coming
up right after this break.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Next up, a beautiful
performance.
You will be moved to tears.
[ Cheers and applause ]
JARDIANCE asked:
When it comes to managing
your type 2 diabetes,
what matters to you?
Let's see.
Most of you say lower A1C.
But only a few of you
are thinking about your heart.
Fact is, even though
it helps to manage A1C,
type 2 diabetes still
increases your risk
of a fatal heart
attack or stroke.
JARDIANCE is the first
type 2 diabetes pill
with a lifesaving
cardiovascular benefit
for adults who have type 2
diabetes and heart disease,
JARDIANCE significantly
reduces the risk of dying
from a cardiovascular event
and lowers A1C,
with diet and exercise.
Let's give it another try.
JARDIANCE can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration.
This may cause you
to feel dizzy, faint,
or lightheaded,
or weak upon standing.
Ketoacidosis
is a serious side effect
that may be fatal.
Symptoms include nausea,
vomiting, stomach pain,
tiredness,
and trouble breathing.
A rare but life-threatening
bacterial infection
in the skin of the genital
area could also occur.
Stop taking JARDIANCE
and call your doctor right away
if you have symptoms
of this bacterial infection,
ketoacidosis
or an allergic reaction.
Symptoms of an allergic
reaction include rash,
swelling, and difficulty
breathing or swallowing.
Do not take JARDIANCE
if you are on dialysis
or have severe kidney problems.
Other side effects are
sudden kidney problems,
genital yeast infections,
increased bad cholesterol,
and urinary tract infections,
which may be serious.
Taking JARDIANCE with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may cause low blood sugar.
Tell your doctor about
all the medicines you take
and if you have any
medical conditions.
Isn't it time to rethink your
type 2 diabetes medication?
Ask your doctor about JARDIANCE
and get to the heart
of what matters.
THIS IS YOU SHOPPING.
AND THIS IS YOU
MAXIMIZING AT T.J.MAXX.
YOU SHOPPING,
YOU MAXIMIZING.
FIND THE BRANDS YOU LOVE
AND GET MORE YOU FOR
YOUR MONEY, EVERY TIME.
IT'S NOT SHOPPING,
IT'S MAXIMIZING.
START MAXIMIZING TODAY!
MAXX LIFE AT T.J.MAXX
♪ ♪
Only TYLENOL® Rapid Release Gels
have laser drilled holes.
They release medicine fast,
for fast pain relief.
TYLENOL®
EUCRISA is an FDA approved
prescription ointment
for mild-to-moderate eczema.
And it's 100% steroid free.
Eligible patients may pay as
little as $10 per prescription.
Text SAVE to 47500.
Do not use if you are allergic
to EUCRISA or its ingredients.
Allergic reactions may occur at
or near the application site.
The most common side effect
is application site pain.
Ask your doctor about EUCRISA
and visit EUCRISA.com
to learn about savings.
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Welcome back to
"The World's Best."
So, who's next to face the
wall of the world?
Let's take a trip to Japan to
find out.
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪
>> [ Speaking Japanese ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
[ Soft background music plays ]
♪
[ Violin plays ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪
>> Wow!
>> Ladies and gentlemen, the
incredible Manami Ito!
Wow! That was incredible.
I don't know if I've ever seen
anything quite like that before.
As inspiring as a performance
could ever get.
American judges, what did we
think?
>> I believe that there's
nothing stronger than the human
spirit.
When we decide we can do
something, there are no limits
whatsoever, and you've proven
that tonight, so thank you for
coming and sharing your time.
>> Drew?
>> I think, not only are you
talented but your perspective on
life is something that the world
definitely needs.
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Ru, what did we think of
Manami's performance?
>> It's absolutely beautiful,
and it really made me proud to
witness your grace and your way
of overcoming adversity.
This is a lesson that every
human alive needs to learn.
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Let's go to our international
judges.
Mak, what did you think of
tonight's performance?
>> That was absolutely
fantastic.
Just speechless.
I have said, everybody has a
mission.
And performers have a mission to
deliver the -- the hope of
living and hope of dream.
And you try to do everything
that you can do.
Fantastic.
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Let's go to Nigeria.
Kate, what did you think?
>> I was in tears.
I mean, when I saw the video,
I didn't see any disability.
And she came out here, I'm like,
"What's my excuse?
What's the excuse of anyone
in this room?"
It's -- You are an inspiration.
Thank you.
>> Okay, it's the moment of
truth -- time for our American
judges and the world to decide
your fate.
Judges, lock in your scores.
♪
>> [ Whimpers ]
>> That was too touching.&
♪
>> Okay, so, how do the American
judges feel?
Let's have a look.
You got a 40 from Faith...
a 39 from Ru...
and a 42 from Drew, which gives
you an average combined score
of...40 points.
[ Cheers and applause ]
So you need at least 75
to move on.
Time to face the
wall of the world.
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪
There we go! Wow!
>> ♪ The story of my life ♪
♪ I give her hope ♪
>> 86 points!
Absolutely incredible!
How do you feel?
>> [ Speaking Japanese ]
>> "I feel amazing."
>> ♪ The story of my life ♪
>> Thank you, thank you, thank
you for inspiring every one of
us tonight.
Manami Ito!
>> The story of my life ♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
,, We'll be right back with more
of "The World's Best."
Thank you so much.
You did incredible. Thank you.
Thank you. Cheer.
♪
♪'Cause this is already bigger♪
♪'This is already bigger
than love♪
Dare to be devoted.
Jared.
♪
Give the gift of devotion
With our incredible
selection of jewelry
Including hundreds
of pieces under $299
Dare to be devoted.
Only at Jared.
Darrell's family uses Gain
Flings now,
so their laundry smells more
amazing than ever.
[Darrell's wife] Isn't that the
dog's towel?
[Dog SFX]
Hey, mi towel, su towel.
More scent plus Oxi Boost and
Febreze in every Gain Fling.
TOUCH SHOWS HOW WE REALLY FEEL.
BUT DOES PSORIASIS
EVER GET IN THE WAY?
EMBRACE THE CHANCE OF
100% CLEAR SKIN WITH TALTZ...
THE FIRST AND ONLY TREATMENT
OF ITS KIND OFFERING PEOPLE
WITH MODERATE TO
SEVERE PSORIASIS
A CHANCE AT 100% CLEAR SKIN.
WITH TALTZ, UP TO 90%
OF PEOPLE QUICKLY SAW
A SIGNIFICANT IMPROVEMENT
OF THEIR PSORIASIS PLAQUES.
DON'T USE IF YOU'RE
ALLERGIC TO TALTZ.
BEFORE STARTING,
YOU SHOULD BE CHECKED
FOR TUBERCULOSIS.
TALTZ MAY INCREASE
RISK OF INFECTIONS
AND LOWER YOUR
ABILITY TO FIGHT THEM.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF
YOU HAVE AN INFECTION,
SYMPTOMS, OR RECEIVED
A VACCINE OR PLAN TO.
INFLAMMATORY BOWEL DISEASE
CAN HAPPEN WITH TALTZ,
INCLUDING WORSENING OF SYMPTOMS.
SERIOUS ALLERGIC
REACTIONS CAN OCCUR.
READY FOR A CHANCE
AT 100% CLEAR SKIN?
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT TALTZ.
We took lifelong pasta experts
and gave one Prego Traditional
and one Ragu Traditional.
This is what happened.
That's because even Ragu users
prefer the taste
of Prego Traditional
two-to-one.
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> Ha! Ha! Ha!
You all right?
Welcome back to the show.
You are about to meet one of the
craziest and bravest performers
on the planet.
♪
>> I am an underwater escape
artist.
What I do is very, very real and
very, very dangerous.
The reason I started doing
escapes is because my brother
has a rare genetic disease
called tuberous sclerosis.
And when my brother has a
seizure, he doesn't breathe.
I want to understand what it is
my brother deals with on a daily
basis.
And what I can do is a minute
and a half underwater, and then
I got to breathe.
My escapes are a fight, and my
life is on the line every single
time.
[ Roars ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
The tank you see behind me
contains approximately
150 gallons of water.
In a moment, I will be chained,
shackled, and locked inside the
tank.
Then, I will be picking the
locks, using a single lock pick.
That's the handcuffs and the
lock around my neck.
However, the last lock -- the
one that keeps the lid closed --
that's a little bit different.
Over here on the table, I have a
padlock.
I also have a glass.
None of the 20 keys will open
that lock.
Now, I don't want you to take my
word for it, so, ladies and
gentlemen, please welcome to the
stage Mr. James Corden.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Your job is to make sure these
20 keys don't open that lock.
Now, obviously, I'm not gonna
make you sit here for James
going through 20 keys.
James, I would like to take
three keys at random from the
pile, and please try them in the
padlock.
These keys are gonna be dumped
in the tank --
>> Sorry, if it doesn't open,
put it in the glass?
>> Are you making up your own
show, now, James, or what?
>> No, I don't.
I just want to make...
If that doesn't open it, then --
>> That's okay. I picked you.
It's my fault.
Just put it in the glass.
>> Okay.
>> As he's doing this, these
20 keys are gonna be dumped in
the tank.
It will literally be like
searching for a needle in a
haystack.
James, did you try three keys?
>> I tried three keys, and none
of them opened it.
>> Good.
Indeed, the only key that does
open the lock, ladies and
gentlemen, is this one.
James, would you try the key in
the lock now, please?
Did it open the lock?
>> It did.
>> Save that last key, and drop
it in the glass, please.
Pick up the glass, and shake up
the keys.
[ Keys rattling ]
Now, James, would you agree that
you just placed the only key
that opens the lock with the 20
that don't?
>> Yes.
>> James, you can place the
glass on the table.
We'll take it from here.
Sir, thank you so much for your
help.
We want you to retire to a safer
spot over there.
Ladies and gentlemen,
James Corden.
>> Yes, James.
Good job.
>> Now, in all seriousness, I
want you to bear a couple of
things in mind.
First of all, the escape you're
about to see is extremely
dangerous.
I'm gonna try and get out in a
minute, 30 seconds.
The safety team has no signal.
They are trained that if I stop
moving and I pass out, to
get me out.
Wish me luck.
[ Cheers and applause ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
♪
>> My gosh, this makes me so
uncomfortable.
♪
>> Man, this is scary.
>> I'm having, like,
an anxiety attack.
>> Is that good?
>> Yeah, good.
♪
>> He can't find the key!
>> No!
>> Aah!
>> Oh, my God!
Oh!
♪
>> [ Vocalizing ]
>> More exciting and talented
acts from every corner of the
globe.
>> Amazing.
>> I had tears in my eyes
the entire time.
>> That was the most incredible
display of artistry.
>> Oh, yes!
>> Aww!
>> Oh!
>> Don't do that.
You are the reason
"World's Best" was created.
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪
Captioning sponsored by CBS