S THAT HE'S IT
THE ARE FOR THE LATE SHOW,
EVERYBODY, TUNE IN TOMORROW FOR
OUR LIVE SHOW FOLLOWING THE CBS
THIS MORNING AND MR. SPIKE LEE,
NOW STICK AROUND FOR JAMES
CORDEN.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> MR. PRESIDENT, THANK YOU FOR
JOINING ME FOR THE BIG GAME.
GO LONG!
ARE YOU READY Y'ALL TO HAVE SOME
FUN.
♪ FEEL THE LOVE TONIGHT SNOATD.
♪ DON'T YOU WORRY WHERE YOU COME
FROM.
♪ IT WILL BE ALL RIGHT.
♪ IT'S THE "LATE, LATE SHOW."
♪.
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, ALL THE
WAY FROM INSIDE-- GIVE IT UP FOR
YOUR HOST, THE ONE WITH THE MOST
JAMES CORDEN!
>> James: HOW ARE YOU.
APPRECIATE IT IT.
YOU ARE A'S VERY, VERY KIND.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
HELLO, GOOD EVENING, AND WELCOME
TO THIS, THE "LATE, LATE SHOW."
I HOPE YOU HAD A GREAT WEEKEND.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, GUYS.
OF COURSE THE BIG NEWS YESTERDAY
WAS SUPER BOWL LIII,
CONGRATULATIONS TO THE NEW
ENGLAND PATRIOTS ON THEIR
6th SUPER BOWL CHAMPIONSHIP,
WELL DONE, TO ALL OF YOU GUYS.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE).
>> James: YOU DON'T HAVE TO
CLAP.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO CLAP.
WE ALL KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
THE GAME IS-- WELL, YEAH, YOU
WON, THE GAME WAS TERRIBLE!
DID YOU WATCH IT?
I DON'T KNOW-- HERE'S THE THING,
I DON'T KNOW THAT MUCH ABOUT
FOOTBALL AND EVEN I WAS LIKE
THIS HAS TO BE A BAD GAME.
ISN'T IT, THIS IS -- IT WAS THE
LOWEST SCORING SUPER BOWL IN
HISTORY AND THE LOWEST RATED IN
TEN YEARS IS IT WAS LESS THAN A
SUPER BOWL AND MORE OF A, JUST
OKAY BOWL IT WAS FINE, THERE WAS
ONLY A SINGLE TOUCHDOWN IN THE
WHOLE GAME.
NOW HERE IS THE THING, I DON'T
WANT TO HEAR ONE MORE WORD FROM
AMERICANS ABOUT HOW SOCCER IS
DUL AND NO ONE EVER SCORES THE
REST OF MY LIFE.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
BUT OF COURSE THE PATRIOTS BEAT
THE RAMS, EVERYONE HERE IN L.A.
IS DEVASTATED.
I MEAN I THINK THEY ARE.
(LAUGHTER)
IT'S-- IT'S HARD TO TELL WITH
THE LEVELS OF BOTOX IN LOS
ANGELES HOW ANYONE REALLY FEELS.
(APPLAUSE)
OH MY GOD, I'M SO UPSET.
I'M SO UPSET RIGHT NOW, I CAN'T
BELIEVE IT.
HERE'S PATRIOTS QUARTERBACK TOM
BRADY AND SUPER BOWL MVP JULIAN
EDELMAN RIGHT AFTER WINNING THE
GAME, TAKE A LOOK.
>> WE'RE GOING TO DISNEYWORLD.
WHOOO!
(LAUGHTER)
NOW THEY DO KNOW THEY CAN STILL
GO TO DISNEY WORLD EVEN IF THEY
LOST, RIGHT?
I'VE NEVER WON THE SUPER BOWL,
I'VE BEEN TO DISNEY WORLD LIKE
SIX TIMES.
LIKE WAS THAT THE MOST THAT THE
PATRIOTS NEEDED AT HALF TIME.
GUYS, COME ON, REMEMBER F WE WIN
THIS, WE GET TO RIDE THE
TEACUPS.
(LAUGHTER)
AND SO THEY WON THE SUPER BOWL
AND LO AND BEHOLD, HERE THEY ARE
TODAY.
>> THEY DID T THEY WENT TO
DISNEY WORLD.
EVERYONE SAY IT.
I DIDN'T THINK ANYONE FOLLOWS
THROUGH.
BUT THEY SEEM TO BE HAVING A FUN
TIME.
HERE THEY ARE DRESSED AS STAR
WARS CHARACTERS HERE.
THAT'S EDELMAN ON THE RIGHT, HE
HAD A GOOD TIME BUT HE KEPT
RUNNING INTO TROUBLE WITH THOSE
SIGNS THAT SAY YOU MUST BE THIS
TALL TO GO ON THE RIDE.
IT WAS ACTUALLY KIND OF
DISAPPOINTING FOR HIM, BUT THEY
WENT, THEY DRESSED LIKE A JEDI.
NOW TOM BRADY IS THE ONLY PERSON
WHO COULD WIN SIX SUPER BOWL
RINGS, BE MARRIED TO A
SUPERMODEL AND STILL SHOW MANAGE
TO LOOK LIKE A VIRGIN.
(LAUGHTER)
IT'S QUITE AN ACHIEVEMENT T
REALLY IS.
MOVING ON, SOME POLITICAL NEWS,
DURING AN INTERVIEW BEFORE THE
GAME YESTERDAY PRESIDENT TRUMP
SAID THAT HE DOESN'T ALWAYS
LISTEN TO THE ADVICE GIVEN TO
HIM IN BRIEFINGS.
AND THAT HE DOESN'T ALWAYS HAVE
TO AGREE WITH HIS INTELLIGENCE
OFFICIALS.
(LAUGHTER)
I THINK WE ALREADY KNEW TRUMP
HAS A BAD RELATIONSHIP WITH
INTELLIGENCE.
LIKE--
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
THEN TRUMP GAVE KIND OF AN ODD
EXAMPLE OF WHEN HE MIGHT GO
AGAINST HIS INTELLIGENCE TEAM,
TAKE A LOOK.
>> MY INTELLIGENCE PEOPLE, IF
THEY SAID, IN FACT, THAT IRAN IS
A WONDERFUL KINDERGARTEN, I
DISAGREE WITH THEM 100 PERCENT.
(LAUGHTER).
>> James: IRAN IS A WONDERFUL
KINDERGARTEN.
THAT'S NOT A SENTENCE, THAT'S
SOMETHING YOU SAY WHEN ARE YOU
HIGH AFTER THE DENTIST.
THIS, THIS CAN ONLY MEAN ONE OF
TWO THINGS.
EITHER TRUMP DOESN'T KNOW WHAT
IRAN IS OR HE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT
KINDERGARTEN IS.
AND FINALLY, WE HAD TO SHOW YOU
THIS, COSTCO HAS STARTED SELLING
A FIVE TIER WEDDING CAKE MADE IF
ENTIRELY OUT OF CHEESE.
THE CAKE WEIGHS 22 POUNDS AND
COSTS $440.
HERE IT IS HERE.
LOOK AT THAT.
SO IF YOUR WEDDING VOWS DON'T
BIND YOU, AT LEAST THE CAKE
WILL.
(LAUGHTER)
AND CAKE MADE OF CHEESE, IT'S A
LITTLE ODD BUT IT IT DOES MICK
MORE SENSE WHEN YOU SEE THE
BRIDE AND GROOM.
(LAUGHTER)
SHALL WE HAVE A LOOK AND SEE OUR
GUESTS ON THE SHOW TONIGHT IN
THE BLUE ROOM AN OSCAR NOMINATED
EMMY AND GOLDEN GLOBE WINNING
ACTRESS FROM BILL LITTLE LIE,
WILD, JURASSIC PARK AND SO MUCH
MORE, THE TRULY EXQUISITE LAURA
DERN IS HERE TONIGHT.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
HOW ARE YOU, LAURA.
>> GREAT, GREAT.
>> I LOVE YOU, I'M SO EXCITED TO
BE HERE.
>> James: WHAT IS HAPPENING IN
THERE YOU ARE SORT OF GUARDING
THE DOOR LIKE THERE IS SOMETHING
TERRIBLE HAPPENING BEHIND THERE.
>> EVERYTHING'S FINE.
IT'S GREAT.
>> James: SOMEONE GO AND CHECK
IMMEDIATELY, LAURA DERN,
EVERYBODY.
AND IN THE ORANGE ROOM, HE IS A
TWO-TIME ACADEMY AWARD-WINNING
FILMMAKER WHOSE MOVIES INCLUDE
GRAVITY, CHILDREN OF MEN AND THE
TEN-TIME OSCAR OM NATURED ROMA,
THE INCOMPARABLE, THE
INCREDIBLE, ALPHONSO CUARON IS
HERE TONIGHT.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT.
>> HEY, JAMES.
>> James: HI, ALPHONSO, HOW
ARE YOU.
>> I'M GOOD, HOW ARE YOU DOING.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING
HERE, YOU HAVE GOT EVERYTHING
YOU NEED?
>> YOU CAN BRING SOME WATT SNER.
>> James: WOW, THAT IS A
REQUEST WE SHOULD HAVE ALREADY
TAKEN CARE OF, IS THAT REALLY
ALL YOU NEED, SHOULDN'T YOU JUST
BE CELEBRATING ALL THE TIME,
JUST CHAMPAGNE, CHAMPAGNE,
CHAMPAGNE.
>> OH, I FINISHED.
>> James: THEN LET'S SOBER HIM
UP, GET HIM SOME WATER, ALFONS O
KAWRON AND IN THE RED ROOM, HERE
TONIGHT WITH AN INCREDIBLY
SPECIAL PERFORMANCE INSPIRED BY
THE OSCAR NOMINATED FILM ROMA
THE ALWAYS COOL, ALWAYS
BRILLIANT, WE LOVE HIM AT THIS
SHOW, BECK IS HERE TONIGHT.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
HI, BECK, HOW ARE YOU.
>> I'M GREAT.
>> James: ARE YOU GOOD?
HEY, LADIES.
>> HI.
>> James: THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR BEING HERE.
>> THANK YOU FOR HAVING US.
>> James: WE'RE SO THRILLED.
NOW YOU'VE GOT A REALLY SPECIAL
PERFORMANCE PLANNED LATER, TELL
US WHO YOU WILL BE PERFORMING
WITH LATER IN THE SHOW.
>> WELL, WITHOUT DO WE NOT V WE
HAVE GUS TAF DUDAMEL, WE HAVE
NATASHA, WE HAVE CAVALCADE OF
STARS.
>> James: AND THE L.A.
PHILHARMONIC ORCHESTRA, ALL
HERE, ALL HERE PERFORMING WITH
BECK.
I'M SO EXCITED.
IT WILL BE ABSOLUTELY BRILLIANT.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE, BECK,
EVERYBODY, ARE YOU READY.
HE'S REG YE WATT, I'M JAMES
CORDEN, THIS THIS IS THE "LATE,
LATE SHOW," ROLL THE TITLES.
COME ON.
♪ THE "LATE, LATE SHOW."
>> James: IT CERTAINLY IS.
LAST NIGHT, LAST NIGHT WAS THE
PREMIER OF A NEW SHOW THAT I'M
HOSTING CALLED "THE WORLD'S
BEST," RIGHT AFTER THE SUPER
BOWL.
DID YOU SEE IT?
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING, IF
YOU MISSED IT, THE EPISODE ENDED
ON A MAJOR CLIFFHANGER WITH A
MASTER ESCAPE ARTIST LOCKED IN A
TANK OF WATER, LOOK AT THIS.
>> HE'S RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
>> James: AND THAT IS HOW THE
SHOW ENDED.
WE RAN OUT OF TIME.
WE RAN OUT OF TIME, AT THAT VERY
CRUCIAL MOMENT, THE SHOW IS ONLY
AN HOUR LONG, THERE WAS NOTHING
WE COULD DO ANYWAY EVERYBODY HAS
BEEN ASKING, SENDING ME MESSAGES
ASKING IF MATT MAKES IT OUT OF
THE TANK ALIVE.
AND THE TRUTH IS WE WON'T KNOW
UNTIL WEDNESDAY'S ALL-NEW
EPISODE OF THE WORLD'S BEST.
THE GOOD NEWS IS MATT IS HERE
TONIGHT.
LET'S BRING HIM OUT AND SEE HOW
HE'S GETTING ON.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, PLEASE
WELCOME MASTER ESCAPE ARTIST
MATT JOHNSON.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
HEY MLT, HOW ARE YOU DG, THANK
YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING HERE,
PEOPLE WERE GOING CRAZY FOR YOU
ON TWITTER LAST NIGHT, WHAT IS
THE RESPONSE BEEN LIKE FOR YOU
PERSONALLY SINCE THE SHOW AIRED?
(LAUGHTER)
I GUESS COULD YOU SAY YOU'RE THE
SHOW'S BREAK OUT STAR.
GET IT?
BREAK OUT-- YOU GET IT, CUZ OF
THE CHAINS AND YOU'RE IN A BOX,
YOU GET IT, RIGHT, YOU GET IT,
YEAH, YEAH, A GOOD ONE.
NOW ON LAST NIGHT'S EPISODE YOU
SAID YOU COULD SURVIVE
UNDERWATER FOR LIKE A MINUTE AND
A HALF, TWO MINUTES TOPS AND
EVERYONE IS PULLING FOR YOU.
THE QUESTION IS ARE YOU GOING TO
BE OKAY UNTIL WEDNESDAY?
(LAUGHTER)
RIGHT, WELL WE-- WE QUNT-- WE
CAN'T GET YOU OUT OF HERE NOW.
THIS ISN'T THE SHOW THAT YOU
WERE LOCKED-- IT'S THE WRONG
SHOW, YOU CAN'T-- I MEAN ARE YOU
GOING TO-- ARE YOU GOING TO BE
OKAY?
KNOCK ON THE GLASS ONCE IF YOU
WILL BE OKAY.
AND TWICE IF YOU WON'T BE OKAY
OKAY.
RIGHT, THAT WAS UNCLEAR TO ME.
I COULDN'T TELL IF IF THAT
WAS-- WELL, LISTEN, BUDDY, YOU
HANG IN THERE UNTIL WEDNESDAY,
OKAY.
IT WOULD BE A REAL DOWNER, IF
YOU DON'T, YOU KNOW, SO EXCITING
TO SEE MATT ESCAPE FROM THE TANK
AND HOPEFULLY SO MUCH MORE.
I CAN'T-- I'M DOING THE LING,
I'M HOSTING THE SHOW.
OKAY, I'VE GOT TO GO TO BREAK,
ALL RIGHT, YOU CAN'T-- YEAH, YOU
REALLY ARE MAKING THIS ABOUT YOU
AND NOT ABOUT ME, OKAY.
SO YOU JUST HANG IN THERE BUD,
WE'VE GOT IT, OKAY, WE'VE GOT.
THIS DON'T MISS THE NEXT EPISODE
OF THE WORLD'S BEST-- DO YOU
MIND?
WE'RE TAKE-- YOU'RE TAKING THE
FOCUS FROM ME ON THE SHOW, OKAY
SO THAT'S THE WORLD'S BEST THIS
WEDNESDAY AT 8 P.M. RIGHT HERE
ON CBS.
HE'LL BE THERE, I WILL BE THERE,
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH MORE OF
THE "LATE, LATE SHOW."
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
I'll take a Coke.
Is Pepsi Ok?
Is Pepsi, OK?
Is Pepsi, OK!?
[laughter]
Are puppies, OK?
Is a shooting star, OK?
Is the laughter of
a small child, OK?
Pepsi's more than, OK!
It's
Okayyyy
Okurrrr
♪ I Like It ♪
Okay, what have
we learned today?
You want a Pepsi?
I want a Pepsi.
There you go.
Okurrr. Aaahh.
I've got to come up with
my own catch phrase.
Okayyy
I'M MISSING OUT ON
OUR FAMILY OUTINGS
BECAUSE I CAN'T FIND A BLADDER
LEAKAGE PRODUCT THAT FITS.
EVERYTHING WAS TOO LOOSE.
BUT DEPEND® FIT-FLEX®
FEELS TAILORED TO ME.
WITH A RANGE OF SIZES
FOR ALL BODY TYPES.
DEPEND® FIT-FLEX® UNDERWEAR
IS GUARANTEED TO
BE YOUR BEST FIT.
DEPEND® FIT-FLEX® UNDERWEAR
♪
Celebrate Valentine's Day!
with hundreds of gifts
under $199!
And, find great deals on other
gifts she'll love!
Now through Valentine's Day.
Only at KAY.
I had this chest cold, but my
medicine kept wearing off.
(coughs)
Ah!
I missed you!
Then I discovered Mucinex.
One pill lasts 12 hours,
and I'm good.
Mucinex releases fast
and lasts 12 hours, not 4.
Let's End This.
Live from the Starlite Lounge.
♪ One plus one equals
too little too late ♪
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]
(announcer)
"Survivor" is about to reinvent
the way the game is played.
♪ Wo"Edge of Extinction"ay? ♪
premieres February 20th.
Dove gives you
fashion ready underarms
so you can wear anything.
From athletic tops
to zebra dresses,
and everything in between.
Enjoy 48 hour protection
and softer, smoother underarms.
With Dove antiperspirants.
♪
>> James: WELCOME BACK.
NOW I'M SURE YOU ALL PROBABLY
KNOW I AM A BIG INSTAGRAM USER,
I CAN'T GET ENOUGH OF IT, I
AM-- MY GRAM GAME IS, I THINK
WHAT THE YOUNG PEOPLE WOULD SAY
IS LIT.
(LAUGHTER)
I THINK THAT'S THE TECHNICAL
TERM.
WHEN IT COMES TO THE GRAM,
HASHTAG CORDEN'S LIT.
OH YEAH, I'M LIT.
I'M LIT.
IT'S ABOUT TO GO OFF, THAT IS
HOW LIT ST.
IT'S REAL TALK, IT'S LIT, RIGHT?
THIS IS HOW-- THIS IS HOW LIT IT
IS.
SO FAR IN THE YEAR OF 2019, I
HAVE POSTED ON INSTAGRAM A TOTAL
OF 0 TIMES.
(LAUGHTER)
YEAH, I APPRECIATE THAT, THANKS.
I MIGHT POST SOMETHING IN APRIL.
DON'T WANT TO GET ANYONE'S HOPES
UP, PROBABLY TIED INTO SOME SORT
OF COMMERCIAL ENDORSEMENT I'M
DOING.
(LAUGHTER)
BUT HERE'S THE THING, I NOTICED
THAT WHEN YOU TAKE A PHOTO ON
INSTAGRAM AND YOU UPLOAD IT,
INSTAGRAM CROPS THE PHOTO AM BUT
INSTA GRAP-- INTRA GRAM IS SO
THANKFUL FOR HOW MUCH I LOVE
USING THEIR PLATFORM AND HOW MI
JUST YOU KNOW SENDING THE SHARE
PRICE THROUGH THE ROOF, THEY
HAVE GIVEN US TONS OF ACCESS TO
USERS' PHOTOS BEFORE THEY GET
CROPPED, OKAY.
SO LIKE THIS PHOTO HERE, THIS IS
ALLISON BRIE, IT'S A CUTE PHOTO,
HER WITH HER CATS AM NOW I KNEW
SHE WAS A CAT PERSON, HI NO IDEA
HOW MUCH OF A CAT PERSON SHE
WAS.
CHECK OUT THE WHOLE THING.
(LAUGHTER)
I MEAN IF SHE'S NOT CAREFUL
THAT'S A REAL CAT-ASTROPHE.
STOP IT, DON'T, DON'T YOU DARE,
DON'T YOU DARE, SIR.
DON'T YOU CLAP THAT.
YOU'RE BETTER THAN THAT, I'M
NOT, YOU ARE.
HERE IS A PHOTO THAT GISELE
POSTED, HER AND HER DAUGHTER
RIDING HORSES, SHE'S ON A BIG
HORSE, HER DAUGHTER IS ON A
LITTLE HORSE.
AND IT IT MADE ME WONDER IF
EVERYONE IN THAT FAMILY HAS A
HORSE SIZED JUST FOR THEM, THEN
I SAW THE WHOLE THING,
(LAUGHTER)
LOOK AT THAT.
TOM BRADY IS HOLDING THE SUPER
BOWL INTEREST OFEE, THAT MUST BE
A VERY RECENT PHOTO.
HE HASN'T EVEN CHANGED OUT OF
HIS JERSEY, THAT IS HOW HE GOT
INTO DISNEYLAND, ERODE ON
HORSEBACK.
(LAUGHTER)
HERE'S A PHOTO THAT HEIDI KLUM
POSTED T IS HER ENGAGEMENT
PHOTO.
I THOUGHT IT WAS SUCH A
BEAUTIFUL-- I KNOW, I KNOW, I
KNOW.
A BEAUTIFUL INTIMATE MOMENT AND
THEN I SAW THE WHOLE THING.
(LAUGHTER)
JEFF GOLDBLUM, DID HE IT TO ME
WHEN I GOTTEN GAGED T IS JUST
WHAT HE DOES.
HERE'S ONE OF SARAH JESSICA
PARKER.
I SAW THAT, I THOUGHT WHAT A
GREAT OUTFIT.
I WAS LIKE WHY, WHY-- I YOU KNOW
WHAT I THOUGHT, REG, I THOUGHT
WHY, WHY WOULD SARAH JESSICA
PARKER CROP HER HEAD OUT OF THIS
PHOTO.
THEN I SAW THE WHOLE THING.
SHE'S MARSHMELLO.
I THINK WE'LL CUT THAT FROM THE
SHOW.
(LAUGHTER)
WHAT IS GOING TO HAPPEN, THAT IS
AN EXCLUSIVE FOR ALL OF YOU.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
THEY SAY THE WORST THING ABOUT
THAT, IT DIED IN REHEARSAL, EVEN
MORE SHOCKING, YES, WE REHEARSED
THIS, BUT IT DIED IN REHEARSAL
AND I SAID NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
I THINK OUR AUDIENCE WILL FIND
THAT HILARIOUS.
(LAUGHTER)
AND YOU COULDN'T HAVE BEEN MORE
NONPLUSSED.
AND NOW I'M WONDERING WILL WE
NOT CUT IT AND JUST KEEP ALL OF
THIS IN.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
IT'S HARD TO KNOW, TUNE IN
TONIGHT TO FIND OUT.
(LAUGHTER)
YOU GET IT, RIGHT, SHE'S
MARSHMELLO.
THIS IS THE THING.
NO ONE KNOWS WHO MARSHMELLO IS,
RIGHT?
AND WE WERE LIKE WOULDN'T IT BE
HILARIOUS IF IT WAS
SARAH-- DOESN'T MATTER.
DOESN'T MATTER.
OKAY.
CUZ SHE IS-- IT IS SO LUDICRIS
THAT CAT-- LIKE SHE'S THE WOMAN
FROM SEX AND THE CITY, RIGHT,
AND THE PROSPECT OF HER
APPROXIMATING MARSHMELLO IS
HILARIOUS.
YOU KNOW, THE SONG WITH BASSILE,
IT UNT DID MATTER, OKAY.
HERE'S ONE, NOW WE HAVE TO DO T
AS IF THAT DID GET CUT, SEE?
REG, GIVE US A NATURAL LAUGH
LEAD-IN AS IF YOU SAW-- WHICH
ONE WAS T JEFF GOLDBLUM.
WAIT, GO.
(LAUGHTER)
WHAT?
IS HERE'S ONE, ZENDAYA POSTED,
HERE IS ZENDAYA IN SUCH A GREAT
DRESS.
I THOUGHT THAT, I THOUGHT WHERE
WOULD YOU EVEN GET A FUR DRESS
LIKE, THAT THEN I SAW THE WHOLE
THING, OH GOD.
(LAUGHTER)
OH GOSH.
I GUY WENT OH, NO.
IT IT ISN'T REAL.
IT IS NOT REAL.
IT IS A JOKE.
SARAH JESSICA PARKER ISN'T
MARSHMELLO.
I DON'T THINK, I DON'T KNOW.
HERE'S ONE, HERE'S ONE THAT
LENNY KRAVITZ POSTED, THIS IS
HIM CASUALLY SITTING AROUND WITH
ONE OVERALL UNDONE, THEN I SAW
THE WHOLE THING BREASTFEED
BREASTFEEDING-- THAT'S AN
AMAZING DEAL, GET IT WHILE YOU
CAN.
THAT WAS CELEBRITY INSTAGRAM,
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH LAURA
DERN AND ALL FONSO KAWRAN.
♪
>> James: WELCOME BACK, LET'S
MEET OUR GUEST TONIGHT SHE IS AN
AWARD-WINNING ACTRESS PLEASE
WELCOME LAURA DERN.
>> James: HE'S THE DIRECTOR OF
THE BRIL YAL OSCAR NOMINATED
FILM ROMA IT'S   IT'S   IT'S
ALFONSO CUARON.
♪
♪ THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
THANK YOU FOR COMING TO SEE USK
I'M SO THRILLED THAT YOU ARE
HERE, YOU JUST WON BEST PICTURE
AT THE DGA AWARDS.
SO RICHLY DESERVED.
NOW BE HONEST, TELL ME HONESTLY,
ARE YOU SICK OF WINNING ALL
THESE AWARDS?
>> NOT REALLY.
>> James: WHEN YOU GET THEM
ARE YOU LIKE OH, I'VE GOT NO
ROOM FOR THIS ANY MORE, WHERE DO
YOU KEEP ALL OF YOUR AWARDS.
>> NOW BECAUSE I'M MOVING, THEY
ARE IN STORAGE.
>> James: RIGHT.
>> SO I NEED TO FIND A PLACE FOR
THEM.
>> YOU NEED BIGGER STORAGE.
>> James: YOU CAN KEEP THEM AT
MY HOUSE.
KEEP THEM AT MY HOUSE SO LONG AS
YOU DON'T MIND THE SLIGHT BIT OF
DAMAGE ON THE ENGRAVING WHERE
YOUR NAME IS.
>> BUT I CAN KEEP THE KEY OF
YOUR HOUSE SO I CAN GO VISIT
THEM.
>> James: GO N TAKE TWO AT A
TIME BUT THE REST JUST STAY
THRMENT YOU TWO, YOU GO WAY
BACK, YOU WORKED TOGETHER IN THE
EARLY 90SST, RIGHT, ON A SHOW
CALLED FALLEN ANGELS, LAURA WA,
DO YOU REMEMBER ABOUT THAT
EXPERIENCE?
>> I REMEMBER ALPHONSO AS WE'VE
ALL GROWN TO LOVE HIM, I
REMEMBER THIS INCREDIBLE GENIUS
WITH THE CLEAREST VISION I HAVE
EVER WITNESSED, AND THE TIME OF
MY LIFE.
>> James: AW, LOOK AT THIS.
BECAUSE ALFONSO, I WAS READING
ABOUT THIS SHOW AND YOU SAID
THAT LAURA SAVED YOUR LIFE WHEN
WERE YOU WORKING ON THATMENT
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT, IN
WHAT WAY, HOW.
>> BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW WHICH
CLEAR VISION SHE'S TALKING
ABOUT.
>> James: RIGHT.
>> IT WAS MY FIRST HOLLYWOOD
PROJECT.
>> James: UH-HUH.
>> AND I WAS WORKING WITH LAURA
DERN, ALAN RICKMAN.
AND I WAS COMPLETELY STAR
STRUCK.
I JUST, I WENT BLANK, I WAS
PETRIFIED, I DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO
TALK TO THEM.
AND THE IT WENT BY AND I DID
ONE-THIRD OF THE DAY AND AT THE
END OF THE DAY THEY PULLED ME
APART AND I SAID THIS IS THE
MOMENT WHERE THEY FIRE YOU.
AND NO, THEY GIVE ME THE MOST A
I MAAING PEP TALK.
>> James: REALLY.
>> YEAH, IT WAS INCREDIBLE.
IT WAS ONE OF THOSE THINGS
REALLY, THAT THE BEAUTIFUL THING
OF THIS IS THAT THERE ARE SOME
PEOPLE IN YOUR LIFE THAT THEY
ARE SO GENEROUS TO YOU IN THOSE
MOMENTS THAT ARE LIKE TURNING
POINTS.
>> James: SURE.
>> AND SO-- .
>> James: WHAT DID YOU SAY, DO
YOU REMEMBER THIS?
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> I HOPE I TOLD HIM THAT HE WAS
THE MOST EXTRAORDINARY DIRECTOR
I COULD DREAM OF.
AND SO CLEAR.
AND TO TRUST HIMSELF BECAUSE WE
TRUSTED HIM.
I ALSO REMEMBER WHAT I DIDN'T
SAY.
>> I'M GLAD YOU DIDN'T SAY.
>> James: WHAT DIDN'T YOU SAY,
THAT WAS WHEN YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO SAY YOU'RE FIRED.
>> NO, NO, I HAVE A HUGE CRUSH
ON YOU AND YOU COULD DO NO
WRONG.
>> James: WELL, COME ON.
GET IN LINE, GET IN LINE.
>> WELL, I'M FIRST, JAMES.
>> James: NOW THE OSCARS ARE
COMING UP.
YOU OF COURSE, LAURA, YOU FIRST
ATTENDED THE OSCARS WITH YOUR
MOTHER DIANNE LADD IN 1975, HERE
YOU ARE HERE.
WHAT WAS, WHAT DO YOU REMEMBER
FROM THIS NIGHT, WHAT WAS IT
LIKE FOR SNU.
>> TERRIFYING.
IT WAS SO TERRIFYING BUT AS YOU
NOTICED, EYEGLASSES ARE REALLY A
GREAT THING TO HAVE.
>> James: FOR SURE.
>> I HAD THEM WITH ME ANSWERED
HAVE NOT SINCE WORN THEM SO THIS
IS PROBABLY THE LAST TIME I HAVE
SEEN THE ACADEMY WARDS
COMFORTABLY, I DON'T KNOW YVMENT
BUT AS I'M WATCHING IT I'M ALSO
REMEMBERING ONE OF MY FAVORITE
MOMENTS.
BECAUSE BEING THERE WITH YOUR
PARENTS IS SUCH A BEAUTIFUL
THING, AS YOU HONOR THEIR WORK,
SHE WAS NOMINATED FOR A HER WORK
ALICE DOESN'T LIVE HERE ANY MORE
SHE WAS SO INCREDIBLE IN.
AND I GOT TO GO WITH MY DAD THAT
HE WAS NOMINATED IN FOR
GRAFERRITY, AND YOU WERE SO
BEAUTIFUL YOU CAME RUNNING TO
HIM ON THE RED CARPET AND I HAD
SUCH A GORGEOUS MOMENT OF
REMEMBERING HIM SORT OF PAY
HOMAGE TO DAD'S WORK IN THIS
FILM HE WAS NOMINATED FOR.
SO IT IS AN AMAZING THING TO
EXPERIENCE.
I ALSO REMEMBER TATUM O'NEILL
STEPPED ON MY DRESS AND I LOVED
HER BECAUSE SHE WAS IN MAIP MOON
AND I WAS HEART BROCKERN AND
SCARED OF HER.
>> James: NOBODY ELSE HAS
STORIES LIKE, THAT HAVE I TWO
STORIES OF GOING TO A GAS
STATION WITH I MOO DAD.
AND THAT WAS LITERALLY AS
GLAMOROUS AS IT GOT.
WELL, I WENT WITH MY DAD AND
THEN I WENT WITH MY MOM T WAS A
I MAGAZINE.
YOU ARE BRINGING YOUR KIDS TO
THE OSCARS.
>> YES.
>> James: ARE THEY EXCITED FOR
THE CEREMONY.
>> MY DAUGHTER IS DRIVING ME
NUTS ABOUT THE DRESS.
>> James: RIGHT, YES, WHAT.
>> YOU KNOW, BECAUSE SHE WANTS
TO ROCK 'N' ROLL AND PEOPLE ARE
TELLING HER SHE HAS TO GO WITH A
GOWN.
>> James: RIGHT.
>> AND I THINK SHE'S GOING TO GO
ROCK 'N' ROLL.
>> James: WELL, THEY'RE PRETTY
FASHIONABLE KIDS.
>> DIDN'T YOUR CHILDREN DESIGN
OR DRAW-- SHOW THE PICTURES.
LOOK AT THIS.
>> LOOK AT, THIS GUYS.
>> James: INCREDIBLE.
>> PAPITO.
>> James: PAPITO.
>> THAT IS AMAZING.
>> James: WITH THAT SORT OF
FLAIR, YOU LET THEM WEAR WHAT
THE HELL THEY WANT TO WEAR.
>> I LET THEM DO WHATEVER THEY
WANT, ALMOST, ALMOST, ALMOST.
>> James: YES.
THIS YEAR RED CARPET LAURA YOU
HAD A MOMENT ON THE RED CARPET,
YOU GOT A PHOTO WITH A BRILLIANT
COMEDIAN AND DIRECTOR BO BURNHAM
AND YOU POSTED THIS PHOTO.
NOW YOU CAN EXPLAIN THIS PHOTO,
WHAT, WHY DO WE HAVE THIS IN
FRONT OF US.
>> BO BURNHAM HAS ESTABLISHED
THAT HE LOOKS JUST LIKE LAURA
DERN, BUT ONLY LAURA DERN IN
JURASSIC PARK.
>> James: RIGHT.
>> AND AS YOU CAN HE SEE HE'S
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
BO BURNHAM WROTE AND DIRECTED
8th GRADE YEAR, AND YOU
POSTED LAURA DERN AND BO BURNHAM
HAVE BEEN SEEN IN THE SAME ROOM
TOGETHER SO IT PUTANCE END TO T
YOU ARE NOT THE SAME PERSON.
>> NO, NO.
>> James: NOW ALFONSO.
WE ARE SO THRILLED ARE YOU HERE,
WE HAVE TO CONGRATULATE YOU ON
ROMA TRK IS THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
FILM, NOMINATED FOR TEN ACADEMY
AWARDS.
IT IS SO SPECIAL T IS SO UNIQUE,
FOR ANYONE WHO HASN'T SEEN IT ET
WHY, JUST EXPLAIN TO THEM WHAT
THE FILM IS ABOUT.
>> IT IS PRETTY MUCH A YEAR IN
THE LIFE OF A FAMILY SEEN FROM
THE POINT OF VIEW OF THE
DOMESTIC WORKER WHO IS AN
INWOMAN, A YEAR IN WHICH IS THE
TURNING POINT FOR THE FAMILY BUT
ALSO TO THE WHAT WERE THEY
LEAVING, THAT IS MEXICO IN 1971.
>> James: IT IS A FANTASTIC
FILM.
I IMPLORE ANYBODY WHO HASN'T
SEEN IT TO SEARCH IT OUT AND
WATCH IT TAKE A LACK AT I A CLIP
OF ROMA WHICH IS CURRENTLY IN
THEATERS AND ON NETFLIX WHRANG
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE).
>> James: AMAZING.
♪
Ok I'll admit. I didn't keep my
place as clean as I would like
'cuz I'm way too busy.
Who's got the time to chase
around down dirt, dust and hair?
So now, I use Heavy Duty Swiffer
Sweeper and Dusters.
For hard-to-reach places, Duster
makes it easy to clean.
It captures dust in one swipe.
Ha! Gotcha!
And Sweeper Heavy
Duty cloths lock away
twice as much dirt and dust.
It gets stuff deep in the
grooves other tools can miss.
Y'know what? My place... is a
lot cleaner now.
Stop cleaning. Start Swiffering.
>> James: WELCOME BACK.
LAURA, YOU HAVE TWO TEENAGERS AT
HOME, THEY ARE OLD ENOUGH TO
WATCH ALL OF YOUR MOVIES.
ARE THERE ANY OF YOUR FILMS THAT
YOU WANT THEM TO AVOID?
ARE THERE ANY FILMS ARE YOU LIKE
OH DON'T WATCH THAT, IGNORE THAT
ONE?
>> WELL, SEVERAL.
>> James: REALLY?
>> MY SON NOT LONG AGO ASKED
DAVID LYNCH WHO I HAD THE HONOR
OF WORKING WITH SINCE I WAS 17.
AND HE SAID HEY, DAVID, THIS
MOVIE YOU DID WITH MY MOM, WILD
AT HEART.
>> James: OH, YES.
>> CAN I SEE THAT NOW, HE SAID
OH NO, YOU SHURNLT SEE THAT
UNTIL YOU ARE 30.
AND HE SAID WELL WHY, IS MY MOM
LIKE SASSY IN THAT MOVIE?
AND HE SAID IT'S NOT YOU SEEING
YOUR MOM IN THAT MOVIE, I'M
WORRIED ABOUT, IT IS YOU SEEING
YOUR GRANDMOTHER THAT I'M
WORRIED ABOUT IT, BECAUSE MY
MOTHER IS EXTRAORDINARY AND AN
AMAZING ACTOR AND INSANE AND
DOES THE SAME THING.
>> James: SHE REALLY COMMITS
TO THE WHOLE PROJECT.
>> RED LIPSTICK AND LOTS OF
OTHER THINGS.
>> James: I AM NOT SURE I
WOULD WANT TO WATCH MY
GRANDMOTHER DOING ANY OF THAT.
SO YOU HAVE MADE SO MANY ICONIC
MOVIES.
>> DO YOU EVER GO BACK AND WATCH
YOUR MOVIES OR IF YOU WATCH ONE
ON TV WILL YOU SIT DOWN AND
WATCH IT?
>> I FIND THAT MY FILMS ARE LIKE
'80S HAIRCUTS.
>> James: RIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW, WHEN I DO THEM T
WAS LIKE A GOOD IDEA.
AROUND THEN AFTER WELL, I BETTER
NOT EVEN SEE THEM AGAIN.
>> James: REALLY?
SO YOU WILL NEVER EVEN LIKE IF
YOU LAP TO SEE THE GRAVITY IS ON
YOU WON'T GO OH, LET'S WATCH
THIS UNWITH.
>> NO, IT'S LIKE SEEING YOUR
PARENTS HAVING SEX OR SOMETHING.
(LAUGHTER).
>> James: THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
IF I MADE THAT BODY OF WORK I
WOULD NEVER BE WATCHING ANYTHING
ELSE AM I WOULD BE LIKE SIT
DOWN, GUYS, YOU'RE GOING TO
ENJOY THIS.
NOW WHEN DID YOU, WHEN DID YOU
KNOW THAT YOU WANTED TO BECOME A
DIRECTOR.
AND WHAT WERE THE FIRST THINGS
THAT YOU EVER DIRECTED?
>> WELL, SINCE I WAS VERY YOUNG,
WHEN I WAS A KID, VERY YOUNG, I
GOT A SUPER8 CAMERA THAT MY
MOTHER WAS VERY GENEROUS TO GIVE
ME A SUPER8 CAMERA AND I WAS
DOING FILMS ALL THE TIME.
I WAS SHOOTING FILMS WITH THE
NEIGHBORS, FAMILY, COUSINS, AND
I DID WHAT I CONSIDERED MY
MASTER PIECES THEN.
>> James: OH REALLY.
>> YEAH, BUT THE PROBLEM WAS
THAT BECAUSE MY MUM COULD AFFORD
THE CAMERA BUT COULD NOT AFFORD
THE FILM.
SO I WAS SHOOTING THOSE FILMS
WITHOUT FILM.
BUT I SWEAR, THEY WERE
BRILLIANT, THEY WERE BRILLIANT.
>> James: WOW.
SOMETIMES I WISH WE WERE
SHOOTING THIS WITHOUT FILM.
SOME OF THE STUFF WE HAVE TO DO
ON THIS SHOW, I'M HALFWAY
THROUGH IT GOING THIS WOULD BE
REALLY GREAT IF NO ONE COULD SEE
IT.
NOW LAURA, SO WE HAVE SOMETHING
THAT THE WHOM WORLD IS GOING TO
SEE, YOU JUST FINISHED THE
SECRETARY SEE ON OF BIG LITTLE
LIES.
WE'RE ALL SO EXCITED TO SEE IT.
HOW WAS IT BEING BACK ON THE SET
WITH EVERYBODY?
>> AMAZING.
IT'S ININCREDIBLE.
WE LOVE DOING THIS SO MUCH.
WE LOVE OUR CHARACTERS AND EACH
OTHER AND WE HAVE A NEW CAST
MEMBER.
>> James: YES.
>> JOINING US THIS YEAR,
WHOSE-- I MEAN-- SHE'S GOOD,
SHE'S VERY GOOD.
>> James: ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT MERYL STREEP.
>> YES, YES, YES.
SHE'S AMAZING.  A DREAM OF MY
LIFE.
>> James: I THINK WILL BE THE
THING THAT COULD REALLY BREAK
HER.
>> I DO, I THINK SO.
>> James: I HAVE BEEN SAYING
IT FOR AWHILE.
NOW LATER IN THE SHOW, THIS IS
HUGELY EXCITING BECK WILL BE
PERFORMING A SONG INSPIRED BY
YOUR FIM, ALFONSO, INSPIRED BY
ROM BLANCA HOW DID THIS
COLLABORATION, AND IN FACT THIS
ENTIRE ALBUM COME ABOUT, THE
SORT OF ALBUM INSPIRED BY PEOPLE
WHO HAVE SEEN THE MOVIE.
HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
>> IT WAS NOTHING BUT AN EXCUSE
TO COLLABORATE WITH PEOPLE I
ADMIRE.
>> James: SURE.
>> IT WAS NOTHING BUT THAT.
AND SO WE STARTED SCREENING THE
FILM.
WE SCREENED THE FILM TO BECK AND
HE LIKED THE FILM.
AND SAID OKAY, I WILL DO A SONG.
AND THE SONG IS ABSOLUTELY
BEAUTIFUL.
WE HAVE GOING FROM VERY YOUNG
FROM BILLY EILISH AND MY
DAUGHTER BOO ALL THE WAY TO, A
WHOLE BE GENERATIONAL,
MULTINATIONAL GROUP OF ARTISTS T
IS REALLY BEAUTIFUL.
>> James: IT WILL BE
BEAUTIFUL, COMING UP LATER IN
THE SHOW, REGGIE, DO YOU HAVE A
QUESTION FOR ANY OF OUR GUEST
THIS EVENING.
>> Reggie: YES, I DO.
TONIGHT'S QUESTION GOES TO
ANYONE WHO HAS DIRECTED OR ACTED
IN ANYTHING WHO ISITYING IS ON
THE COUCH CURRENTLY.
>> OKAY,.
>> Reggie: IF CLOWNS ARE
HADING IN SOME KIND OF ALIEN
VESSEL, WOULD YOU DISCONTINUE
LIKING CLOWNS OR WOULD YOU JUST
SIMPLY LET THEM BE.
>> I MIGHT GROW TO LOVE CLOWNS
WHICH HAVE ALWAYS TERRIFIED ME
SO IT MIGHT BE THE START OF A
BEAUTIFUL FRIENDSHIP THAT NEVER
EXISTED BUT I WOULD LOVE TO
HEAR.
>> I WOULD DEFINITELY LET THEM
BE.
>> Reggie: YES, THAT'S
CORRECT.
>> James: IT'S ABSOLUTELY
PLEASE THANK OUR INCREDIBLE
CORRECT.
GUESTS, LAURA DERN, ALFONSO
PLEASE THANK OUR INCREDIBLE
CUARON, BECK IS BACK WITH A
GUESTS, LAURA DERN, ALFONSO
PERFORMANCE.
CUARON, BECK IS BACK WITH A
COME ON BACK, EVERYBODY.
Dove gives you
fashion ready underarms
so you can wear anything.
From athletic tops
to zebra dresses,
and everything in between.
Enjoy 48 hour protection
and softer, smoother underarms.
With Dove antiperspirants.
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
THE.
>> HERE TO PERFORM TARANTULA,
WITH THE LA PHILHARMONICA AN
CONDUCTED BY GUSTAVO DUDAMEL,
PLEASE WELCOME BECK.
(APPLAUSE)
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ I'M LIVING
BUT I'M FEELING NUMB
♪ CAN SEE IT IN MY STARE
I WEAR A MASK
♪ SO FALSELY NUMB
AND I DON'T KNOW
♪ WHO I AM
DESPITE THE WORLDS
♪ INSIDE OF ME
CRUISING ME AWAY
♪ I'VE NOTICED IN
OTHERS' EYES
♪ THE TIME'S CLOSING IN
AND WHEN THE THUNDER
♪ BREAKS
IT BREAKS FOR YOU
♪ AND ME
TARANTULA
♪ TARANTULA
THE FUTURE'S LOOKING
♪ RATHER GRIM
THE STRANGE BLACK TIDE
♪ DECISIONS LIE WITH
FOOLISH MAN
♪ ALONE WITH MY LIFE
THAT CHOKING AND
♪ HOLDING ME
EXPECTING ME TO FALL
♪ BUT ONLY IF I THREATEN
WILL SEE THE TABLES TURN
♪ AND WHEN THE THUNDER
BREAKS
♪ IT BREAKS FOR YOU
AND ME
♪ TARANTULA
TARANTULA
♪ OUR WORLD IS UNDER
A SENTENCE OF DEATH
♪ I WAS BORN UNDERGROUND
BUT WHEN THE PRESSURE
♪ GETS TOO MUCH FOR
ME
♪ I BITE
TARANTULA
♪ TARANTULA
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
BECK, EVERYONE!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
PICK UP THE ALBUM “MUSIC
INSPIRED BY THE FILM ROMA” THIS
FRIDAY!
AND COME ON BACK!
BEAUTIFUL!
Digestive Advantage Probiotics
have a strong natural
protein shell.
So while other brands
may have billions of probiotics
many can struggle in stomach
acid.
Ours survive 100 times better.
Let our strength
help you stay strong.
I'm Captain Obvious
and Hotels.com
rewards me basically
everywhere.
So why am I sliding into
this ski lodge
with my mini horse?
Because Hotels.com
lets me do me.
Sorry, the cold makes
him a little horse.
Hotels.com.
You do you and get rewarded.
Think only specialty stores have
what's new?
Olay has the hottest debut.
New Olay Clay Stick Masks,
Hydrating Facial Mist,
And Brightening Eye Cream.
Only by Olay.
Cheez-It snacks are
the most satisfying
combination of
crunch with-
Cheese.
With their
delicious perfection-
Cheese.
It's not all about
you Cheese.
You think I have a mouth.
I'm a wheel of cheese.
Got a point.
[yeah]
Cheez-It.
Cheesy,
crunchy satisfaction.
♪
It hasn't always
been easy, has it?
♪
There have been days
when you doubted yourself.
♪
And days when you
were ready to quit.
♪
But you didn't.
Because you had the courage to
venture into something powerful.
Education.
If I leave you with just
three words of advice:
never...stop...growing.
[cheering]
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: THANKS FOR WATCHING.
TOMORROW NIGHT: BILLY CRYSTAL,
SARAH CHALKE, AND MUSIC FROM
BUDDY AND ASAP FERG. WE'LL SEE
YOU THEN.
REGGIE, TAKE US HOME.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Your digestive system has
billions of bacteria,
but life can throw them off
balance.
Re-align yourself,
with Align probiotic.
And try Align Gummies,
with prebiotics and probiotics
to help support digestive health
Do I use a toothpaste that
whitens my teeth,
or one that's good for my teeth?
Now I don't have to choose.
From Crest 3D White, the
Whitening Therapy collection
with new Spearmint and
Peppermint Oil.
It gently whitens,
plus it has a fortifying formula
to protect your enamel.
Crest.
Healthy, beautiful smiles
for life.
So you finally got Fios, huh?
Yep, and wanna know what the
best part about it is?
Nope.
Gaming with less lag?
Watching movies in 4K?