>> GROCERY STORE STEAK.
SO MANY CUTS TO CHOOSE FROM.
WE ARE GOING BEHIND THE
BUTCHER'S COUNTER.
>> YOU COULD SLICE YOUR MEAT IN
HALF IF YOU KNOW WHAT TO LOOK
FOR.
>> ARE YOU GETTING THE BIGGEST
BANG FOR YOUR BUCK?
>> WHAT DO YOU FEEL THAT MOMENT
YOU PRESS CLICK?
>> ARE YOU ADDICTED TO ONLINE
SHOPPING?
>> YOU ARE SPENDING BETWEEN
$3,000 AND $4,000 A MONTH.
>> AFFECTING YOUR BRAIN THE WAY
DRUGS DO.
>> COMING UP NEXT.
DR. OZ: ARE YOU READY FOR
SEASON 10!
AUDIENCE: YEAH!
>> I LOVE YOU, DR. OZ.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: STEAK.
EVERYONE LOVES IT.
IT SHOULDN'T JUST BE FOR THE
WEALTHY.
BUT SOME OF YOU ARE BEING OVER
CHARGED FOR BEEF CUTS AT THE
SUPERMARKET.
IS THIS THERE IS MEAT
CONSPIRACY GOING ON AT YOUR
LOCAL GROCERY STORY.
BRIAN IS TAKING US BEHIND THE
SWINGING DOORS TO REVEAL
SECRETS.
WE WANT OUR BEST BANG FOR THE
BUCK.
MEAT IS SOMETHING THAT IS
DESIRABLE.
WHAT IS THE FIRST TIP TO MAKE
SURE IT GOES AS FAR AS POSSIBLE
>> THE FIRST THING YOU DO IS
GET TO KNOW THE BUTCHER.
ASK THEM WHICH CUTS OF MEAT
THEY LIKE.
I GUARANTEE YOU THEY ARE NOT
THE MOST EXPENSIVE ONES IN THE
CASE.
THEY CAN TELL YOU WHICH TO CUT
AND WHAT IS THE BEST VALUE FOR
THAT DAY.
DR. OZ: WHAT IS A TYPICAL WAY A
BUTCHER CAN SAVE YOU MONEY?
>> WHEN YOU ARE BUYING A ROAST,
TELL THEM TO TRIM OFF THE
EXCESS FAT AND BONE SO YOU ARE
JUST PAYING FOR THE MEAT THAT
YOU EAT.
NOT EVERYBODY WILL DO THIS, BUT
YOU CAN ASK THEM WHAT IT WILL
DELIVER.
DR. OZ: I NEVER THOUGHT OF
ASKING FOR THAT.
WHY PAY FOR BONE UNITED STATES
YOU HAVE A PET.
COUPONS, ANOTHER GREAT MONEY
SAVING TIPS FOR ANYONE BUYING
STEAKS.
WHAT IS THE SECRET?
>> THE SECRET IS MORNING MEAT
MARK-DOWNS.
LET ME TELL WAS THAT IS.
[APPLAUSE]
>> YES.
NOW, YOU GO TO YOUR SUPERMARKET
BETWEEN 8:00 A.M. AND 9:00 A.M.
THEY ARE GOING TO BE MARKING
DOWN MEAT.
IT IS GOING TO BE 50% OFF,
MAYBE 40% OFF.
I CALL THEM MY MORNING MEAT
MARK-DOWNS.
CALL YOUR BUTCHER, CALL YOUR
SUPERMARKET AHEAD OF TIME AND
SAY LISTEN, WHAT TIME ARE YOU
PUTTING THAT MEAT OUT?
IT IS ON SALE.
THAT IS A TIP.
THAT IS AMAZING.
YOU SEE HOW THIS IS $7:30?
IT IS DOWN TO $4.10.
DR. OZ: I HAD NO IDEA THEY HAVE
EVER MARKED IT DOWN.
I DON'T THINK I HAVE EVER GONE
GROCERY SHOPPING AT 8:00 OR
9:00 IN THE MORNING.
>> WHEN YOU ARE A COUPONER LIKE
ME YOU DO.
DR. OZ: AND THAT IS A RIBEYE
STAKE?
>> YES.
NO PROBLEM.
DR. OZ: PUT YOUR BUTCHER HAT ON
AND TEACH US.
THEY HAVE LABELS ON THEM.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> THE FIRST THING YOU WANT TO
CHECK OUT IS THE LABEL.
YOU LOOK FOR THE GRADE.
PRIME, CHOSE AND SELECT.
SELECT IS THE LOWEST GRADE AND
YOU USUALLY DON'T SEE THAT.
PRIME IS THE HIGHEST CHOICE.
IT COMES WITH A HIGH PRICE TAG.
WHAT YOU WANT TO GET IS CHOICE.
IF YOU KNOW WHAT TO LOOK FOR,
IT CAN BE JUST AS GOOD AS A
PRIME STEAK.
DR. OZ: WHAT DO YOU LOOK FOR?
>> THE MARBLING ON THE STEAK,
THE FAT WITHIN THE MEAT.
THESE STRIPS OF FAT IN HERE,
THAT IS WHAT YOU WANT TO GET.
IF YOU HAD THREE STEAKS ALL
SIMILAR CUTS, YOU WANT TO GET
THE ONE WITH MOST MARBLING IN
IT.
AS THAT STEAK COOKS, THAT FAT
MELTS, AND IT IS GOING TO GIVE
YOU A GREATER PERCEPTION OF
JEWELSINESS AND TENDERNESS AND
IT WILL BE MORE FLAVORFUL.
DR. OZ: IF I WANTED A LOW FAT
MEAL, I COULD GET A SLIGHTLY
MARBLED CUT?
OR IT TASTES LIKE RUBBER?
>> NO.
IT DEPENDS ON WHICH CUT YOU
BUY.
DR. OZ: THE NEXT AFFORDABLE
CAN'T THING YOU CAN DO IS FIND
A STEAK THAT YOU CAN DO.
SHE AS HER FAMILY LOVES A GREAT
STEAK DINNER.
WHAT KIND OF STEAK DO YOU GET
TO FEED A FAMILY OF FIVE?
>> I LIKE TO GET RIBEYE STAKE.
IT IS THE BEST TYPE OF STEAK.
I HAVE TRIED OTHER MEATS.
IT COMES OUT TASTING TOUGH AND
CAN GET EXPENSIVE.
DR. OZ: I LOVE RIBEYE, AND IT
IS PRICEY.
BRIAN HAS SOMETHING ELSE, THE
TASTIEST MIKE GOLIC ECONOMICAL
CHOICE.
HE IS BRINGING IT TO YOU.
WHAT IS THIS CALLED?
>> THIS IS A TRI-TIP.
IT IS CUT RIGHT FROM THE
SIRLOIN OF THE SATERI.
IT HAS A NICE INCH OF
INTRAMUSCULAR FAT.
IT COMES IN A CHUNK.
IF YOU SLICE IT THIN, VERY
TENDER.
DR. OZ: YOU BE THE JUDGE.
I TRUST THE BUTCHER, BUT I
TRUST THE MOM MORE.
>> YES.
IT IS VERY TENDER.
DR. OZ: WOULD IT REPLACE YOUR
RIBEYE?
>> I THINK SO.
DR. OZ: IF THE TESTER, WE WILL
SEE IF IT IS ECONOMICAL.
THE RIBEYE THAT SHE USED TO BUY
WOULD COST HER ABOUT $70 TO
FEED A FAMILY OF FIVE.
THE TRI-TIP CAN FEED THE SAME
FAMILY FOR $40.
ENJOY.
DON'T GET CAUGHT UP IN THE
FANCY NAMES.
ASHEVILLE AND JOY ARE HERE WITH
.
THEY ARE TELLING US WHAT THEY
ARE EATING.
WHAT DO YOU ORDER WHEN YOU GO
OUT FOR A MALE?
>> WELL, I LOVE A NILES FILLET
MIGNOT, GRASS FEED.
DR. OZ: THAT WOULD PROBABLY
COST YOU A LITTLE BUILT.
YOU HAVE STEAKS IN FRONT OF YOU
THAT ARE NOT GRASS FED FILLETS.
I HOPE YOU APPRECIATE THEM.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THIS?
>> IT IS JUICY.
IT TASTES LIKE IT HAS BEEN
MARINATED FOR A WHILE TOO.
>> JOEY, YOUR THOUGHT?
>> IT IS NICE.
SUCCULENT, DR. OZ.
DR. OZ: SUCCULENT.
TAKE OFF YOUR BLINDFOLDS.
CONGRATULATIONS.
REVEAL WHAT THEY JUST HAD.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE THINK THAT
BEEF TENDERLOIN AND FIEN A.L.
MIGNOT IS THE BEST COURTS.
IT DOESN'T HAVE AS MUCH FLAVOR
AS OTHER CUTS.
I HAVE REPLACED THAT TENDERLOIN
WITH A HANGER STEAK.
IF YOU SLICE IT AGAINST THE
GREEN, IT HAS A LOT OF BEEFY
FLEAFER AND JUICE TOO.
>> DELICIOUS.
DR. OZ: YOU DON'T HAVE TO BREAK
THE BANK.
I LOVE EATING THIS AT HOME
BALLS IT DOESN'T BREAK THE
BANK.
>> THIS STEAK HERE IS A FLAT
IRON.
DR. OZ: THEY ARE DIFFERENT?
>> YES.
THIS IS THE CUT I LIKE TO THINK
REPLACES THE PORTERHOUSE.
VERY JUICY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
DR. OZ: HOW MUCH DO YOU THINK
WE OVER PAY FOR MEAT?
DO YOU THINK WE COULD
HASSELBECK OUR MEAT BILL?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
YOU COULD SLICE YOUR MEAT BILL
IN HALF IF YOU KNOW WHAT TO
LOOK GO.
DR. OZ: WE ARE CONTINUE AFTER
BREAK.
CHEF BRIAN IS GOING TO REVEAL
THE CHEAPEST TASTIEST STEAK IN
THE SUPERMARKET AND SHOW YOU
HOW TO PREPARE IT LIKE A PRO.
YOU WILL NOT WANT TO MISS THIS.
[APPLAUSE]
>> DID YOU KILL TRAVIS
ALEXANDER?
>> YES, HE DID.
>> CONVICTED OF BRUTALLY
KILLING HER BOYFRIEND.
>> THE BLOODY CRIME SEEN.
IT WAS EVERYWHERE.
>> WHY HER LAWYER SAID TAKING
ON HER CASE RUINED HIS LIFE,
CAREER AND HEALTH.
>> THIS ISN'T THE WAY I WANTED
TO LIVE LIFE.
>> ADDICTED TO LACKS TIFFELS.
>> I COULDN'T GET THROUGH A DAY
BECAUSE I WAS CONSTANTLY GOING
BACK AND FORTH TO A BATHROOM. T.
Is your dry skin cream not doing
enough?
Try Eucerin Advanced Repair
cream.
For 48hour dry skin relief...
Goes beyond ceramides with
moisturizing factors
naturally found in skin...
Eucerin Advanced Repair Cream
For healthier looking skin.
(heavy rain)
♪ ♪
When you eat a bowl
of oatmeal,
you're getting beta-glucan.
That's a soluble fiber
that slows the breakdown
of carbohydrates.
And that provides energy
that lasts.
TOMORROW.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE ARE BACK WITH OUR
INVESTIGATION INTO SUPERMARKET
STEAK.
BRIAN HAS INVESTIGATED, COOKED
AND TESTED ALL THE SUPERMARKET
STEAKS.
HE CAN TELL US WHICH IS THE
TASTIEST AND CHEAPEST STEAK TO
BUY SO YOU DON'T OVERSPEND.
IT IS WHAT?
>> FLANK STEAK.
DR. OZ: MY SON HAS BEEN BUYING
THAT EXCLUSIVELY, AND IT TASTES
SO GOOD.
>> IT IS ONE OF MY FAVORITE
CUTS.
IT IS NICE AND EVEN.
IT GOES WELL IN STIR FRIDAY,
TACOS, IN THE PAN.
IT HAS A NICE AMOUNT OF FAT,
BUT IT IS ALSO LEAN.
YOU CAN SEE THE GRAIN
STRUCTURE.
IT HELPS WITH SLICING.
DR. OZ: WHY DON'T MORE PEOPLE
GET FLANK STEAK?
>> BECAUSE IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
A LOT.
DR. OZ: YES.
THE BIGGEST MISTAKE WE ALL MAKE
IS WHAT WITH MEAT?
>> PEOPLE DON'T GET THE RIGHT
TEMP.
THEY OVER COOK IT AND UNDERCOOK
IT IT IS A PROBLEM BECAUSE
PEOPLE TEND TO FOLLOW RECIPES
AND THEY LOOK AT THE TIMES WHEN
YOU NEED TO BE GOING BY THE
VISUAL CUES OR THE ACTUAL
NUMBERS THE YOU NEED TO INVEST
IN A DIGITAL VERLANDER TER.
YOU CAN GET THEM FOR A FEW DAYS
ONLINE AND THEY MAKE A WORLD OF
DIFFERENCE.
THAT IS WHAT CHEFS USE.
DR. OZ: LOOK AT THIS CHART.
DON'T GO BY THE OUTSIDE.
LOOK AT THE TEMP CHART AND YOU
WILL GET THERE.
DO YOU EVER LOOK AT IT AND SAY
THIS IS RARE?
>> YES.
YOU CAN HOLD YOUR FINGERS
TOGETHER, PINKIE TO THUMB, THAT
IS WELL DONE.
THIS IS RARE, MEDIUM RARE.
DR. OZ: RARE, WELL-DONE.
RARE, WELL-DONE.
THAT WITH YOUR TEMP CHART AND
YOU ARE GOOD.
AND THEN THE MEAT?
>> ONE OF THE MISTAKES PEOPLE
MAKE IS THEY DON'T DRY THE MEAT
BEFORE IT HITS THE SKILLET.
IN ORDER TO GET THE BROWNING
CARMELIZATION IS TO MAKE SURE
THE MOISTURE IS GONE.
YOU WANT TO CUT IT INTO
INDIVIDUAL STEAKS.
SPLIT THIS ONE DOWN THE MIDDLE.
THEN I WILL CUT IT INTO A
LITTLE STEAK LEAK THIS SO YOU
CAN HAVE INDIVIDUAL PORTIONS
FOUR GUESTS.
ALL YOU NEED TO DO IS HEAT UP A
LITTLE OIL IN A CAST-IRON
SKILLET HERE.
SEASON THE STEAK UP NICELY.
A LITTLE KOSHER SALT AND BLACK
PEPPER.
DR. OZ: WHEN IT STARTS TO
BUBBLE A LITTLE BIT, YOU THROW
IT ON.
>> YOU WILL SEE THE OIL START
TO SHIMMER AND BARELY SMOKE.
THEN IT IS HOT, AND YOU DROP
THE STEAK IN THERE.
YOU WANT TO HEAR THAT SIZZLE.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: ALL RIGHT.
ONCE YOU HAVE REGALED YOUR
GUESTS WITH THIS, THERE IS A
BIG MISTAKE WE ALL MAKE.
IT COMES OFF AND LOOKS SO GOOD.
BUT WATCH WHAT HAPPENS IN THIS
VIDEO, AUDIENCE.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT MANY OF
YOU ARE DOING.
YOU ARE NOT LETTING YOUR MEAT
REST.
IT IS STILL HOT, LOOKS GREAT.
BIG MISTAKE.
WHY SHOULD YOU LET YOUR MEAT
REST?
>> WHEN YOU PULL THE MEAT OUT
OF THE SKILLET OR OFF THE
GRILL, IT IS STILL COOKING.
YOU NEED TO GIVE IT TIME TO
COME DOWN TO TEMP WHERE IT IS
EVEN ENJOYABLE TO EAT.
AS THE MEAT COOKS, ALL THE
JUICES IN THE MEAT ARE RUSH TO
THE CENTER.
IF YOU WERE TO IMMEDIATELY
STARS SLICING THAT, THE JUICES
WOULD RUSH OUT ON TO YOUR
BOARD.
DR. OZ: IT STOPS BURNING ME.
KEEP TALKING.
>> YOU WANT TO GIVE IT TIME FOR
THE JUICES TO REDISTRIBUTE.
I USE A WIRE RACK.
THE REASON IS THE AIR
CIRCULATES AROUND THE MEAT AS
IT COOLS.
YOU ARE NOT LETTING IT SIT IN
ITS JUICES.
YOU SEE THE JUICES THAT COME
OFF IN THE BOTTOM OF THE PAN.
IF IT IS SITTING IN ITS JUICES,
WASHES OFF THE CARMELIZED
EXTERIOR.
DR. OZ: MANY OF US DO THIS PART
WRONG.
>> RIGHT.
THIS IS PROBABLY THE BIGGEST
KEY NEXT TO TEMP IT GETTING A
TENDER CUT OF MEAT.
YOU WANT TO SLICE AGAINST THE
GREEN.
THAT IS WHY I LOVE FLANK.
YOU CAN SEE THE GRAIN.
TURN IT 90 DEGREES.
PUT YOUR KNIFE 90 DEGREES TO
THAT AND GIVE IT SOME THIN
SLICES.
DR. OZ: IF YOU DON'T DO THAT,
THE MEAT IS CHEWIER?
>> IF YOU WERE TO CUT IT WITH
THE GRAIN, IT WOULD BE TOO
CHEWY.
DR. OZ: TRY IT AND YOU WILL
SEE.
THANK YOU BRIAN.
CHECK YOU OUT COOKS COUNTRY
MAGEE S.
WHEN WE COME BACK, A LOOK
INSIDE THE CHICKEN NUGGETS
RECALL THAT IS FREAKING
EVERYBODY OUTS.
DR. OZ:
DR. OZ: COMING UP WHAT, IS THE
DEAL WITH ALL THE CHICKEN
NUGGET RECAL
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
Never ending is now even better
at Olive Garden.
All new Never Ending Stuffed
Pastas starting at $12.99.
Pick your favorite stuffed
pasta, sauce and topping.
It's all never ending.
All new
Never Ending Stuffed Pastas.
Only for a limited time,
at Olive Garden.
THAT IS NEXT.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: TODAY WHAT, IS THE DEAL
WITH ALL THE CHICKEN NUGGET
RECALLS LATELY?
THERE IS WOOD CHIPS I HAVE
SEEN, PIECES OF RUBBER
LITERALLY.
THAT IS WHAT THE REPORTS ARE.
120,000 POUNDS OF NUGGETS WERE
RESENTLY RECALLED FROM TWO
MAJOR BRANDS FOR CONTINUED
CONTAMINANTS AND POSSIBLE ALER
GENERALS.
BEHIND THE FOOD HEADLINES, WE
COVER WHAT IS REALLY GOING ON.
OUR CHEF IS HERE TO HELP
INVESTIGATE.
WHAT I HAVE READ ABOUT RUBBER,
I WASN'T QUITE SURE HOW WOULD
IT GET INTO THE CHICKEN NUGGET?
>> WELL, HERE'S THE STORY.
PEOPLE STARRED FINDING LITTLE
BITS OF RUBBER THIS THEIR
CHICKEN NUGGETS, AND THEY
STARTED CALLING IN.
THEY DID A LITTLE
INVESTIGATION, AND WHAT
HAPPENED WAS A PIECE OF A
RUBBER SEAL IN SOME OF THE
MACHINERY THEY USE TO MAKE THE
NUGGETS, FELL IN THERE, GOT
MIXED IN, AND IT WENT OUT.
I HAVE HEARD OF RUB ERI
NUGGETS, BUT NOT RUBBER IN THE
NUGGETS.
>> 70,000 POUNDS OF GLUTEN FREE
NUGGETS WERE RECALLED BECAUSE
THEY HAD WOOD CHIPS.
WHY WOULD THERE BE WOOD CHIPS
IN THERE?
>> THEY LOOKED AT THIS ONE, AND
THEY COULDN'T FIGURE IT OUT.
THEY SAID THERE MAY BE WOOD IN
THERE SO THEY DID THE RECALL.
DR. OZ: NO ONE HAS REPORTED
ADVERSE REACTIONS AFTER EATING
THE NUGGETS.
THE RECALL WAS BEING MADE OUT
OF AN ABUNDANCE OF CAUTION.
YOU SAY IT IS OFTEN A CHALLENGE
TO DETERMINE THINGS?
>> IT IS PARTIALLY BECAUSE OF
THE NATURE OF THE WAY THEY ARE
MADE.
THEY CHOP IT UP INTO BITS AND
PIECES, AND IT IS THIS BIG MIX.
DR. OZ: LET'S GO TO THAT.
YOU ALL THINK CHICKEN NUGGETS
ARE BASICALLY CHICKEN FROM A
CHICKEN WREST, CHOPPED UP INTO
PIECES AND IT LOOKS LIKE THIS.
YOU PASTE THEM TOGETHER, IT
PROBABLY LOOKED LIKE THAT
ORIGINALLY.
IS THAT WHAT WE ALL THINK?
>> THAT IS WHAT YOU WOULD
THINK.
I WOULD HOPE.
DR. OZ: THAT IS NOT QUITE WHAT
HAPPENS.
EXPLAIN WHAT HAPPENS WITH
NUGGETS?
>> YOU HAVE WATER, SOY, WHEAT
PROTEIN, SALT, AND A MYSTERY
INGREDIENT LIKE WHY IS THAT
THERE?
SUGAR.
YOUR ARE PROBABLY GOING TO DUNK
IT INTO BARBECUE SAUCE
ANYWHERE.
WHY DO THAT?
DR. OZ: THERE ARE SOME GUYS
DOING IT THE RIGHT WAY, SOME
ARE NOT.
REWARD THE GUYS DOING THE RIGHT
JOB.
I BET MOST ARE TRYING TO DO THE
RIGHT JOB.
IF WE OPEN OUR EYES, WE CAN
SUPPORT THEM.
IF WE IGNORE THE OTHERS, YOU
WON'T HAVE THAT STUFF.
HELP US FIGURE OUT WHICH
PRODUCTS TO BUY.
WE SHOWED CHICKEN BREASTS, WE
SHOULD LOOK FOR THAT, RIGHT?
>> RIGHT.
THE FIRST INGREDIENT SHOULD BE
CHICKEN.
THE FIRST INGREDIENT SHOULD SAY
CHICKEN BREAST, AND THEN THE
SECOND THING, THE LESS
INGREDIENTS THE BETTER.
THE REST SHOULD BE FLOUR AND
SEASONINGS THAT GO IN THE
COATING.
YOU SHOULD BE ABLE TO PRONOUNCE
ALL
DR. OZ: GOD BLESS YOU.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> YOUR WEAR HELPS YOU STAY
ACTIVE.
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOUR ONLY
ACTIVITY IS PUTTING THOSE
STRETCHY PANTS ON.
DONCIC WE ARE INVESTIGATING THEE
When you're expecting
a little angel, be soft.
When your little angel
expects a lot from you...
You gotta be kidding
me, little dude.
be strong.
Life takes softness
and strength.
That's why we make
Angel Soft Mega with more
of the value you already love.
♪
You're not just mom.
You're her whole world.
Don't just get away, come
together.
Save up to 30%. Hurry.
Offer ends soon.
Z35K8Z Z16FZ
Y35K8Y Y16FY
ESPECIALLY WHEN IT COMES TO
GAINING WEIGHT.
THAT IS WEDNESDAY.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: TODAY WE ARE TALKING
ABOUT A VERY REAL ADDICTION
THAT AFFECTS MILLIONS OF
PEOPLE.
YOU MAY NOT REALIZE THAT YOU
ARE ONE OF THEM.
IF YOU FIND YOURSELF WITH YOUR
INBOX FLOODED WITH PROMOTIONS
FROM STORES.
FILING YOUR CART UP WITH THINGS
YOU DON'T REALLY NEED.
A CLICK, THE SWEATER, SHOES
THAT LOOK TO PRETTY, NEW SKIN
PRODUCT.
YOU FEEL THAT EUPHORIA WITH THE
PURCHASE.
BUT THEN THE DREADED CREDIT
CARD BILLS COME, ALONG WITH
PANIC AND GUILT.
HAVE YOU BEEN THERE?
I AM TALKING ABOUT EXTREME
ONLINE SHOPPING ADDICTION.
DR. OZ: RETAIL THERAPY HAS GONE
HIGH TECH AND VERY INEVASIVE.
FOR MANY, EVERY SALE TEXT OR
E-MAIL MEANS TEMPTATION AND
FUELS ONLINE SHOPPING
ADDICTION.
>> YOU CAN'T AFFORD NOT TO BUY
SOMETHING BECAUSE THE COUPONS
THEY SEND YOU.
THE LINK IS RIGHT THERE.
CONSTANTLY REMINDING YOU THAT
YOU WANT ME, YOU WANT TO BUY
ME.
YOU NEED TO BUY ME.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GET OUT OF
BED.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GET OFF THE
COUCH OR LEAVE YOUR OIFMENT YOU
CLICK AND IT IS THERE.
I AM A REALTOR, I HAVE TO LOOK
GOOD.
IT DOES GET EXPENSIVE TO KEEP
UP TO DATE, TO BE IN FASHION.
>> YOU NEED SLACKS, YOU NEED
SKIRTS, YOU NEED EVERYTHING,
AND YOU NEED BAG TO GO WITH IT.
>> I LOVE SHOES AND
POCKETBOOKS, ALL TYPES.
SHOES AND POCKET BOOKS MAKE ME
HAPPY.
>> CAN YOU GRAB THE MIROTIC LK
PLEASE?
IF I AM NOT ON TOP OF HOUSE
TREMENDOUS AS A REALTOR, HOW AM
I GOING TO EFFECTIVELY SELL
YOUR HOME?
YOU NEED NEW MUGS, AND THEN YOU
NEED NEW SILVERWARE, AND IT
KIND OF SNOWBALLS, AND YOU NEED
NEW THINGS TO GO WITH NEW
THINGS.
>> HER HUSBAND DOESN'T AGREE.
>> I THINK IT IS A PROBLEM
BECAUSE SHE -- SHE THINKS IT
ISN'T, BUT SHE DOESN'T.
SHE WANTS IT.
>> SHE MAY NOT KNOW HOW MUCH.
>> I HANDLE ALL THE BILLS.
I WAS VERY HAPPY WHEN THEY WENT
FROM BEING DELIVERED IN THE
MAIL TO ONLINE BECAUSE THEN MY
HUSBAND CANO SEE THEM.
IF MADE MY LIFE A LOT EASIER.
WE HAVE A SECURITY CAMERA AT
THE FRONT DOOR, AND WE GET
NOTIFICATIONS ON OUR PHONES.
I DISABLED MY HUSBAND'S ON HIS
PHONE WHEN I KNOW I AM GETTING
A DELIVERY, AND I FIX IT AFTER
I GET THE DELIVERY.
>> BUT AS A UPS DELIVERYMAN,
ERIC KNOWS ABOUT THE RISE IN
ONLINE SHOPPING.
>> MOST OF THE TIME I DELIVER
TO THE SAME HOUSES OVER AND
OVER AND THINK THEY ARE ADDICT
THE TO THIS.
NOW I SEE IT AT MY HOUSE, I
KNOW THAT IS A PROBLEM.
DR. OZ: I AM JOINED NOW BY
JOYCE AND HER HONEST
ACKNOWLEDGEMENT OF WHAT IS
HAPPENING.
THANK YOU FOR TELLING THE
TRUTH.
HOW BAD HAS YOUR ONLINE
ADDICTION GOTTEN?
>> IT HAS GOTTEN PRETTY BAD.
I WAKE UP THINKING ABOUT IT.
I THINK ABOUT IT THROUGHOUT THE
DAY.
I AM GETTING THE E-MAILS, THE
TEXT REMINDERS, ON MY SOCIAL
MEDIA.
IT IS PRETTY MUCH CONSUMING MY
DAY.
DR. OZ: SO YOUR HUSBAND ERIC
KINDLY JOINS YOU.
HE IS IN THE AUDIENCE A SAFE
DISTANCE AWAY.
HOW BAD DO YOU THINK YOUR
WIFE'S ADDICTION HAS BECOME AND
HOW IS IT AFFECTING YOU AND THE
FAMILY?
>> WELL, IT IS BAD.
IT IS REALLY BAD.
WE GET TO THE POINT THAT WE ARE
IN AN ARGUMENT.
WE SAY WE HAVE TO STOP.
WHEN WE GET HOME, I START TO
FEEL WHY ARE WE RECYCLING SO
MANY BOXES?
THEN SHE CONTINUES.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO, DR.
OZ.
I NEED HELP.
DR. OZ: YOU REALIZE THIS IS NOT
JUST ABOUT THE SHOPPING.
WE SEE PICTURES OF THE CLOSET
FULL OF SHOES, AND EVERYONE
GASPS.
BUT THE DEEPER PAIN IS WHEN
YOUR RELATIONSHIP IS DESTROYED
OR HURT IN ANY WAY THROUGH THIS
ADDICTION?
>> I FEEL TERRIBLE.
I FEEL SO GUILTY, AND IT
BOTHERS ME.
I FEEL BAD WHEN HE IS UPSET AT
ME, BUT IT REALLY DOESN'T STOP
ME.
I ALMOST NEED TO DO IT.
WHEN I AM BUYING SOMETHING FOR
THE FAMILY, WHEN I AM BUYING
SOMETHING FOR THE KIDS OR FOR
HIM, I AM HAPPY.
GREAT, HE NEEDED GLASSES,
READERS.
I DON'T BUY HIM ONE PAIR, I BY
HIM THREE.
I KNOW HE IS GOING TO BREAK ONE
PAIR.
DR. OZ: THOSE SEEMS LIKE
EXCUSES TO ME.
YOU HAVE WAYS OF JUSTINNING IT,
AND SO THE RELATIONSHIP IS
BEATEN UP.
ALICIA HAS JOINED US.
SHE ADMITS TO SPENDING BETWEEN
$3,000 AND $4,000 A MONTH ON
ONLINE PURCHASE, MOSTLY ON
CLOTHES AND SHOES.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
>> THANK YOU.
DR. OZ: HOW BAD HAS YOUR
ADDICTION TO SHOPPING GOTTEN?
>> IT IS BAD.
IT IS TO THE .WHERE I WAKE UP
IN THE MORNING -- TO THE POINT
WHERE I WAKE UP IN THE MORNING
AND I WANT TO GO ONLINE.
I SLEEP GOING ONLINE.
I DREAM BEING ON LINE.
DR. OZ: HOW IS YOUR
RELATIONSHIP WITH YOUR FAMILY?
>> CURRENTLY RIGHT NOW MY
HUSBAND IS IN KUWAIT.
DR. OZ: HE IS IN THE ARMED
FORCES?
>> HE IS IN THE ARMY.
DR. OZ: THANK YOU FOR THAT.
LET US HELP HIM AND HELP YOU.
>> AND RIGHT NOW I HAVE TONS
AND TONS OF STUFF THAT SINCE HE
HAS BEEN GONE, TO HELP ME COPE
WITH HIM BEING GONE.
WHAT MAKES ME FEEL BETTER IS
SHOPPING.
DR. OZ: WHAT IS YOUR LOWEST
POINT?
HOW BAD HAS IT GOTTEN?
>> MY LOUEST POINT I RECALL IS
WHEN HE WAS HOME ONE DAY AND HE
GAVE ME SOME MONEY TO GO PAY
THE ELECTRIC BILL.
BUT THERE WAS A SALE GOING ON,
SO I WENT AHEAD AND I WENT
SHOPPING, FIGURING LIKE OK, I
WILL TAKE CARE OF IT NEXT WEEK,
NOT KNOWING THAT IT WAS DUE AT
THAT TIME.
SO HE WAS WORKING AT HOME, AND
WE GOT A KNOCK AT THE DOOR, AND
IT WAS THE ELECTRIC PEOPLE
COMING TO TURN OFF THE LIGHTS.
DR. OZ: TURN OFF THE
ELECTRICITY?
>> YES, BECAUSE OF THE FACT
THAT I FORGOT TO PAY IT.
DR. OZ: YOU DIDN'T FORGET NOT
TO PAY IT.
YOU DECIDED NOT TO PAY IT.
HE WAS UPSET ABOUT THAT?
>> YES.
THAT WAS EMBARRASSING.
I FELT LIKE I WANTED TO JUST
DIANE JUST CRY.
HE LOOKED AT ME AND SAID I GAVE
YOU THAT MONEY TO GO PAY THE
ELECTRIC BILL.
I WAS LIKE I KNOW.
I'M SORRY.
DR. OZ: LET'S DIVE INTO WHY
THAT CHOICE IS HAPPENING.
JOYCE, WHAT DO YOU FEEL THAT
MOMENT YOU PRESS CLICK AND BUY
SOMETHING?
>> IT IS ALMOST A HIGH.
IT IS EXHILARATING.
>> YES.
DR. OZ: ALMOST A HIGH.
>> IT IS LIKE A DRUG.
IT FEELS REALLY GOOD.
DR. OZ: WELL, IT TURNS OUT IT
IS EXACTLY LIKE A DRUG.
IT IS LITERALLY AFFECTING YOUR
BRAIN THE WAY DRUGS DO.
WHEN YOU TAKE CRACK COCAINE,
YOU TURN ON THE DOPE MINUTE.
-- DOMPAMINE.
SUGAR DOES TO.
WHEN YOU DO THINGS THAT FEEL
GREAT, IT IS SUPPOSED TO FEEL
GREAT SO YOU DO MORE OF THEM.
THERE IS WAYS OF HACKING THE
SYSTEM.
IT MAKES YOU FEEL GREAT WHEN
YOU DIDN'T DO ANYTHING GREAT
NECESSARILY.
FOR THAT REASON, YOU GET THE
SAME DRUG HIGH, THE SAME
ADDICTIVE REACTIONS.
HE HAS A REAL PROBLEM WITH THE
ENACT THAT YOU ARE NOT HONEST
ABOUT WHAT YOU ARE DOING.
YOUR HUSBAND IS SERVING OUR
NATION BRAVELY, BUT HE FINDS
OUT WHAT IS HAPPENING.
>> WHAT I AM DOING IS TAKING
ALL THE STUFF THAT IVAN I AM
ACTUALLY OPENING UP A LITTLE
BOTIQUE IN MY HOUSE SO I CAN
KIND OF GET RID OF A LOT OF
STUFF.
DR. OZ: THAT HELPS A LITTLE
BUILT.
>> YEAH.
[LAUGHTER]
DR. OZ: ARE YOU OPEN TO GETTING
HOPE TO DEAL WITH THE
UNDERLYING REASON THAT YOU WANT
SOMETHING THAT YOU DON'T NEED,
THAT YOU WANT TO COMPROMISE THE
MOST PRECIOUS COVENANT WE HAVE
WITH THE PEOPLE WE LOVE FOR AN
ADDICTION TO SHOPPING?
>> YES.
DR. OZ: COMING UP, WE ARE GOING
TO OFFER SOME CONCRETE
SOLUTIONS TO HELP EVERYONE AT
HOME WITH THEIR ONLINE SHOPPING
ADDICTION BECAUSE THERE ARE A
LOT OF US.
NEXT.
>> DID YOU KILL TRAVIS
ALEXANDER?
>> YES, I DO.
>> WHYLER LAWYER SAYS TAKING ON
HER CASE RUINSED HIS LIFE,
CAREER AND HEALTH.
PLUS, ADDICTED TO LAXATIVES.
>> I WAS CONSTANTLY GOING BACK
AND FORTH TO A BATHROO
(VO) At Pro Plan,
we believe nutrition is full of
possibilities to improve
your pet's life.
We're redefining
what nutrition can do.
Because the possibility
of a longer life
and a healthy life
is the greatest
possibility of all.
Purina Pro Plan.
Nutrition that Performs.
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
♪
It hasn't always
been easy, has it?
♪
There have been days
when you doubted yourself.
♪
And days when you
were ready to quit.
♪
But you didn't.
Because you had the courage to
venture into something powerful.
Education.
If I leave you with just
three words of advice:
never...stop...growing.
[cheering]
(Sigh)
(Crunch)
Babybel:
That snack just sounded boring.
Coming through.
No photos, please.
Babybel:
Bye bye, bland.
Helloooo, delicious.
VO:
Rich, creamy, 100% real cheese.
VO: With Mini Babybel,
snack time is saved.
Babybel:
Saved it!
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE ARE BACK TALKING
ABOUT ONLINE SHOPPING
ADDICTION.
IT IS A SERIOUS PROBLEM.
IN FACT, THERE IS BETWEEN 5%
AND 8% OF AMERICANS WE THINK
WHO SUFFER FROM SOME SORT OF
SHOPPING ADDICTION.
WE ARE JOINED BY THE AUTHOR OF
A PODCAST.
LET'S GO THROUGH THIS.
KEEP TRACK OF THESE.
THE FIRST IS ANXIETY AND
STRESS, DEALING WITH THE
ISOLATION THAT RESULTS.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WE HAVE A STRING OF BAD DEAS
WHERE WE ARE DOWN ON OURSELVES,
OFTEN WE TURN TO VICES.
SHOPPING ADDICTION IS ONE OF
THOSE VICES THAT MILLIONS TURN
TO.
SOCIAL MEDIA IS FUN AN
ENGAGING, BUT ON THE OTHER END
IT CAN BE A RABBIT HOLE.
IT LOOKS PERFECT AND FILTERED.
THEN YOU START TO FEEL BAD
ABOUT YOURSELF AND YOUR TURN TO
YOUR VICE IN SHOPPING.
>> 24/7 AVAILABILITY, AND IN
YOUR PHONE IN YOUR HAND.
>> YOU LITERALLY SHOP FOR
SOMETHING, IT IS ON YOUR
DOORSTEP THE NEXT DAY.
THEN FINALLY IT IS ALL THE
TARGETED E-MAILS, ALL THE
TARGETED YARDS WE EXPERIENCE
ONLINE.
OUR WEB BROWSERS ARE STALKING
US.
WE KNOW WHAT WE LIKE AND HAVE
SEARCHED FOR, AND WE GET THOSE
ADAMS.
DR. OZ: WHAT DO YOU THINK IS
GOING ON IN YOUR LIVES?
>> THE FEEDS FOR ME.
THEY ARE AUTOMATICALLY THERE.
WHEN I GO ON SOCIAL MEDIA, YOU
CAN CLICK THE LINK, AND IT
TAKES YOU DIRECTLY INTO THE
CART.
AND IF YOU LEAVE IT THERE, IT
REMINDS YOU TO GO BACK AND LOOK
FOR IT.
IF YOU GO TO A STORE'S WEBSITE
AND YOU DROP IT IN THE CART, IT
TELLS YOU AGAIN, AND IT SENDS
YOU A COUPON.
IT ADDS YOU TO A MAILING LIST
AND IT SENDS YOU A COUPON IN
THE MAIL.
DR. OZ: NOT AN ACCIDENT.
YOU THINK IT IS CALLED SERVICE.
IT IS CALLED HUNTING.
THEY SEE YOU OUT THERE, A BIG
BULLSEYE, BALLS YOU ARE YELLING
OUT HERE I AM.
THE PRODUCER IS GOING TO GIVE
US CREET SOLUTIONS FOR
EVERYBODY.
FOR EVERYBODY OUT THERE
WATCHING, WE ARE GOING TO HELP
YOU OUT.
FIRST IS UNSUBSCRIBE.
YOU HAVE TO TAKE IT AWAY.
>> WHEN YOU GET ALL OF THOSE
TARGETED E-MAILS, ALTHOUGH
THOSE SHOP SITES, YOUR FIRST
INSTINCT EXTINCT SHOULD BE TO
UNPRESCRIBE -- JUNE SUBSCRIBE.
>> HOW DO YOU DELAY
GRATIFICATIONS?
>> IT IS LIKE A TWO-STEP
PROCESS.
YOU CAN LEARN BY GOOGLING IT.
YOU CAN BLOCK CERTAIN WEBSITES.
YOU CAN BLOCK THEM ON YOUR
PHONE OR COMPUTER SO YOU DON'T
GET THE TEMPTATION.
IF YOU KNOW YOU ARE ALWAYS ON
ONE PARTICULAR SITE, BLOCK IT
TEMPORARILY.
THEN DELAY GRATIFICATION.
MY TIP IS DISTANCE YOURSELF FOR
24 HOURS, GO TAKE A WALK, A
SHOWER.
COME BACK THE NEXT DAY.
WHY?
WE TALK ABOUT DOPAMINE LEVELS
SURGING WHEN YOU ARE ABOUT TO
BUYING SOMETHING.
THAT IS NOT WHEN YOU WANT TO
MAKE A RATIONAL CHOICE.
THEN YOU REALIZE YOU PROBABLY
DON'T WANT THE SHOES.
>> WHAT IF YOU TRIED THAT
ALREADY?
YOU BLOCKED IT, AND THEN YOU
LEAVE IT AND COME BACK.
DR. OZ: I AM BLOCKING, YOU ARE
BLOCKING HERE.
WHAT I AM HEARING IS THEY ARE
CHUMMING THE WATER FOR YOU.
YOU HAVE TO STOP.
THAT YOU COULD LET THEM PUT
THAT STUFF AROUND YOU BECAUSE
YOU START GOBBLING UP WHATEVER
IS AROUND YOU.
PART OF IT IS AROUND YOU, AND
YOU HAVE TO AVOID THE PRIME
TIME ONLINE SHOPPING.
>> AT THE END OF THE DAY, YOU
HAVE TO CHANGE YOUR HABITS.
PRIME SHOPPING HOURS ONLINE IS
AFTER WORK AND BEFORE WE GO TO
BED.
>> YOU HAVE GIVEN US GREAT
TACTICS.
HOW DO YOU GET THE EMOTIONAL
SUPPORT.
>> THIS IS THE CRUX OF IT.
YOU HAVE TO LOOK WITHIN.
WHAT IS THE EMOTIONAL VOID THAW
OF TRYING TO FILL WITH STUFF?
THIS ISN'T ABOUT EASY ACCESS OR
TECHNOLOGY ALL THE TIME.
REALLY AT THE HEART OF IT IS
THERE IS SOMETHING MISSING.
I THINK TRULY TO ADDRESS THAT
IS OF THE UTMOST.
FOR SOME PEOPLE IT MEANS
THERAPY.
FOR OTHERS IT MAY MEAN REACHING
OUT TO FRIENDS.
I THINK COMING ON THIS SHOW AND
BEING OPEN AND HONEST WITH US
AND YOUR FAMILY AND FRIENDS IS
AN AMAZING FIRST STEP, AND I
WANT TO APPLAUD YOU FOR THAT.
IT IS REALLY THE FIRST STEP TO
RECOVERY.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: LET ME ASK YOU, BECAUSE
WE DO THINK YOU ARE FILLING A
VOID WITH SHOPPING, WHAT IS
THAT STERIOD?
WHERE DO YOU NEED HELP AND
EMOTIONAL SUPPORT?
>> I BELIEVE MINE RIGHT NOW IS
MY HUSBAND NOT BEING HERE AND
ME NOT HAVING ANYONE TO TALK TO
AT NIGHT TIME, AND THE
COMMERCIALS ARE ON.
I ALSO LIKE SHOPPING WHEN I AM
STRESSED, OR MY ANXIETY.
BUT RIGHT NOW I BELIEVE IT IS
BECAUSE OF HIM NOT BEING HERE.
DR. OZ: AT LEAST YOU HAVE A
TARGET NOW.
LET'S FOCUS ON WHAT WE CAN DO.
I WOULD RATHER HE SEND YOU SPAM
E-MAILS RATHER THAN FROM
SHOPPERS.
ERIC IS HERE.
WHAT DOES HE NEED TO DO?
WHAT IS THE VOID YOU ARE
FEELING THAT HE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO HELP YOU?
>> HE COULD BE HERE, BUT HE
WORKS.
HE IS ALWAYS WORKING, AND THERE
IS ALWAYS OVERTIME.
HE IS ALSO A SOCCER COACH.
I WILL NEVER BLAME MY KIDS FOR
ANYTHING, BUT WE HAVE KIDS.
WHOSE KIDS DON'T TAKE UP A
MAJORITY OF THEIR TIME?
THERE IS ALWAYS SOMETHING.
DR. OZ: SO YOU ARE BOTH LONELY,
WHICH IS PROBABLY A BIG REASON
WHY SHOP HAS BECOME AN
ADDICTION.
THE REAL PERSON YOU HAVE TO
KEEP COMPANY WITH IS YOU.
I KNOW WE ARE NOT GOING TO
SOLVE IT JUST LIKE THAT, BUT AT
LEAST WE KNOW WHAT TO AIM AT.
WE ARE NEVER GOING TO GET A
TRUE SENSE OF NULL FILAMENT
DOING THE THINGS YOU ARE DOING.
OBVIOUSLY YOU CHASE AWAY THE
PEOPLE WHO LOVE YOU MOST, WHICH
MAKES YOU LONELIER.
WHAT DO YOU DO WITH AN ONLINE
SHOPPING ADDICTION?
SOME AT HOME HAVE WOKEN UP TO
THAT REALITY?
>> REACH OUT TO SOMEONE YOU
TRUST, A FRIEND.
WE HAVE TALKED ABOUT FEELINGS
OF ISOLATION, FEELING LONELY.
YOU CAN ONLY CONTROL WHAT YOU
CAN CONTROL.
YOU CONTROL YOUR ENVIRONMENT,
CONTROL YOUR COMMUNITY, REACH
OUT TO PEOPLE.
IF YOU HAVE A FRIEND AND YOU
ARE WATCHING, I HAVE A FRIEND
WITH AN ONLINE SHOPPING
ADDICTION, BE THE FRIEND, CALL
YOUR FRIEND.
SHOW UP, INITIATE ACTIVITIES
TOGETHER.
THEN BREAK THE ICE AND TALK
ABOUT HOW YOU ARE REALLY
FEELING.
YOU CANNOT KEEP IT BOTTLED UP.
DR. OZ: GOD BLESS YOU BOTH FOR
BEING HERE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IF YOU THINK YOU HAVE A
SHOPPING ADDICTION,
DR. OZ: GOD BLESS YOU.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> YOUR WEAR HELPS YOU STAY
ACTIVE.
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOUR ONLY
ACTIVITY IS PUTTING THOSE
STRETCHY PANTS ON.
DONCIC WE ARE INVESTIGATING THEE
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
Is your dry skin cream not doing
enough?
Try Eucerin Advanced Repair
cream.
For 48hour dry skin relief...
Goes beyond ceramides with
moisturizing factors
naturally found in skin...
Eucerin Advanced Repair Cream
For healthier looking skin.
Oats and oat bran
have a soluble fiber
called beta-glucan,
which can help
lower cholesterol
as part of
a heart-healthy diet.
Now it's in new
Quaker Oat Beverage,
a super-smooth
dairy alternative.
I knew about the tremors.
But when I started seeing
things,
I didn't know what was
happening...
so I kept it in.
He started believing things
that weren't true.
I knew something was wrong...
but I didn't say a word.
During the course of their
disease
around 50% of people with
Parkinson's
may experience hallucinations
or delusions.
But now, doctors are
prescribing NUPLAZID.
The only FDA approved
medicine...
proven to significantly reduce
hallucinations and delusions
related to Parkinson's.
Don't take NUPLAZID if you are
allergic to its ingredients.
NUPLAZID can increase the risk
of death
in elderly people with
dementia-related psychosis
and is not for
treating symptoms
unrelated to Parkinson's
disease.
NUPLAZID can cause changes in
heart rhythm
and should not be taken if you
have certain
abnormal heart rhythms or take
other drugs
that are known to cause changes
in heart rhythm.
Tell your doctor about any
changes
in medicines you're taking.
The most common
side effects are
swelling of the arms and legs
and confusion.
We spoke up and it made all the
difference.
Ask your Parkinson's specialist
about NUPLAZID.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: ITCH, YOU SCRATCH IT,
AND THEN YOU REPEAT.
RIGHT?
WE ALL DO IT.
WE ITCH, SCRATCH, REPEAT.
ITCH, SCRATCH, REPEAT.
WE ARE HARD WIRED.
CHANCES ARE, IF YOU ARE AN
ECZEMA SUFFERER, THIS AN
EMBARRASSING CYCLE THAT YOU AND
YOUR SKIN ARE ALL TOO FAMILIAR
WITH.
I HAVE BROUGHT IN A BOARD
CERTIFIED DERMATOLOGIST TOE
TALK ABOUT THIS.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
>> THANK YOU.
DR. OZ: ITCHING IS A NATURAL
RESPONSE, BUT SOMETIMES IT GETS
OUT OF HAND.
ECZEMA IS A CLASSIC EXAMPLE.
EXPLAIN WHAT IT IS AND WHAT
CAUSES THIS?
>> THERE ARE SEVERAL DIFFERENT
TYPES OF ECZEMA, BUT ONE OF THE
MOST COMMON IS ATOPIC ECZEMA OR
ATOPIC DERMATITIS.
IT IS A CHRONIC CONDITION.
IT AFFECTS 30% OF CHILDREN AND
15% OF ADULTS.
UNFORTUNATELY, THE PREVALENCE
IS ON THE RISE.
IT RUNS IN FAMILIES AND IT IS
TRIGGERED BY CERTAIN THINGS,
SOME ENVIRONMENTAL FACTORS,
IRRITANTS, ALLERGENS AND
CHANGES IN THE WEATHER.
IT CAN BE REALLY DISRUPTIVE TO
NOT ONLY THE PERSON BUT FAMILY
MEMBERS AS WELL.
IT IS REALLY A QUALITY OF LIFE
ISSUE.
DR. OZ: REMIND EVERYBODY OF THE
CLASSIC SYMPTOMS.
>> THIS TYPE OF ECZEMA IS
CHARACTERIZED BY RED, INFLAMED,
DRY AND ITCHY SKIN.
IT IS INTENSELY ITCHY, SO
PEOPLE START TO SCRATCH IT,
WHICH CAN MAKE IT WORSE.
OVER TIME THE SKIN CAN THICKEN
AS WELL.
ANOTHER KEY FACTOR IS IT IS
CHRONIC AND RELAPSING.
YOU HAVE FLAIR UPS AND
RECURRENCES, AND PERIODS OF
RASH-FREE SKIN.
DR. OZ: THAT IS YOUR
OPPORTUNITY.
LET ME SHOW YOU WHAT EXPERTS
BELIEVE IS HAPPENING IN THE
ECZEMA CYCLE.
WE HAVE BUILT A LITTLE MODEL.
LET'S SAY THIS IS THE IS YOUR
-- IS THE SURFACE OF YOUR SKIN.
HOPEFULLY YOU HAVE SKIN THAT
LOOKS LIKE.
THIS NORMAL, FINE, NO PROBLEMS.
WITH ATOPIC ECZEMA, SOMETHING
IRRITATES YOUR SKIN.
YOU START TO GET A LITTLE
ITCHING.
AS THE IRRITANT BECOMES MORE
PREVALENT, YOU START TO ITCH
HARDER AND HARDER AND YOU
SCRATCH IT.
THEN YOU START TO HAVE THE
BEGINNINGS OF AN ECZEMA
FLAIR-UP.
IT BECOMES PROBLEMATIC BECAUSE
ONCE IT IS THERE IT IS HARDER
TO STOP IT.
YOU GET WRINKLING OF THE SKIN.
IT LOOKS IRRITATED AND WILL DRY
IT OUT.
THE MORE YOU ITCH IT, THE MORE
YOU GET PROBLEMS.
YOU DON'T JUST GET THE SCALING,
BUT MORE SIGNIFICANCE BREAKS IN
THE SKIN, WHICH COULD
COMPLICATE YOUR LIFE THAT MUCH
MORE.
WHAT IS THE GOAL OF TREATING
ECZEMA WHEN YOU DON'T WANT TO
ITCH AWAY EVERYTHING?
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO GET TO THE
POINT WHERE YOU ARE BREAKING
DOWN THE SKIN.
WHEN YOU HAVE A SEVERE FLAIR UP
LIKE THIS, YOU MAY NEED TO GO
TO A DERMATOLOGIST TO GET A
STEROID CREAM TO CALM THIS
DOWN.
SINCE THIS IS A CHRONIC
RELAPSING CONDITION, THE
LONG-TERM GROLE IS TO PROLONG
THE FLAIR-FREE PERIODS AND
REDUCE THE OCCURRENCE.
THE NUMBER ONE THINGS YOU CAN
DO FOR YOUR SKIN IS
MOISTURIZING YOUR SKIN EVERY
DAY.
DR. OZ: WHAT DO YOU RECOMMEND
FOR LONG-TERM MANAGEMENT OF
ECZEMA?
>> I LIKE TO RECOMMENDED USERIN
KAREEM.
IT IS AN OVER THE COUNTER
PRODUCT THAT CAN BE USED EVERY
DAY TO REDUCE THE IRRITATION
AND DRYNESS OF THE SKIN.
IT ALMOST FORMS LIKE A
PROTECTIVE SEAL OVER THE SKIN
TO SOOTHE IRRITATION AND
REDNESS, AND IT IS
STEROID-FREE, WHICH MEANS YOU
CAN USE IT EVERY SINGLE DAY,
WHICH IS KEY.
USERIN CONDUCTED A STUDY IN
WHICH THEY LOOK THE OUT FOUR
OUT OF FIVE CHILDREN USING THE
CREAM EVERY DAY, AND IT SHOWED
THEY WERE FLAIR-FRY FOR SIX
MONTHS WITH EVERY DAY USE.
IF YOU ARE THE PARNTSDE OF A
CHILD WITH THAT TYPE OF ECZEMA,
SIX MONTHS OF NO FLARES IS A
VERY, VERY BIG DEAL.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: THAT IS GOOD.
>> AND FOR THE ADULTS THAT WERE
USING IT, THEY SHOWED
IMPROVEMENT OF THEIR MILD TO
MODERATE SYMPTOMS OF IN TWO
WEEKS OF USING.
DR. OZ: WE GAVE USERIN TO TWO
OF MY VIEWERS.
TERESA HAS BEEN USING IT FOR A
FEW WEEKS, AND PATRICIA FEW
MONTHS.
DESCRIBE WHAT YOUR SKIN WAS
LIKE BEFORE YOU STARTED USING
THIS APPROACH.
>> FIRST OF ALL, ECZEMA CAME
INTO MY LIFE OUT OF NOWHERE
WHEN I WAS PREGNANT WITH MY
SECOND BABY.
HE ACTUALLY HAS A LITTLE BIT OF
ECZEMA TOO, AND I STARTED USING
IT ON HIM.
FIRST I THOUGHT IT WAS FROM MY
DAIRY.
I CUT OUT DAIRY AND A LOT OF
THINGS, DRIVING MYSELF CREZZ.
THEN I STARRED USING ALL THE
NATURAL CREAMS.
IT LITERALLY TOOK OVER MY LIFE,
CHANGING DETERGENT ENTS AND
SHEETS AND EVERYTHING YOU CAN
THINK OF.
SOME OF IT WENT AWAY, BUT THE
KNUCKLES, THE PARTS THAT GET
CONSTANT TOUCH, AS I AM A BUSY
MOM OF TWO.
THEY WILL ACTUALLY KEPT THE
SAME AND GETTING WORSE,
IRRITATED AND CRACKING.
IT WAS JUST UNCOMFORTABLE.
HAVING THAT ON YOUR HANDS, AND
IT NEVER WAS GETTING A CHANCE
TO RECOVER.
ANYTHING I WAS USING WAS GOING
TO TAKE LONGER TO RECOVER.
DR. OZ: OH, MY GOODNESS.
LOOK AT THIS.
>> YES.
A HUGE DIFFERENCE.
DR. OZ: SHE IS JUST TRYING TO
GET US TO PAY ATTENTION TO THE
RING.
IT IS REALLY ABOUT THE RING.
THAT IS REMARKABLE.
>> THIS IS ANOTHER THING.
HOW DO YOU LOOK AT THE RING
WHEN YOU HAVE THE ECZEMA HERE?
I HAVE TO GET RID OF IT.
DR. OZ: ARE YOU SURPRISED AT
WHAT TERESA IS SAYING?
>> NO.
AS A DERMATOLOGIST, WE HEAR A
LOT ABOUT ECZEMA AND ABOUT HOW
IT AFFECTS PEOPLE'S LIVES.
THERE ARE REAL PHYSICAL
PSYCHOLOGICAL AND SOCIAL ISSUES
THAT COME ACROSS, THAT ARE
REALLY IMPORTANT, WITH ATOPIC
DERMATITIS.
PEOPLE FEEL ITCHY IN THEIR
CLOTHING.
THEY ARE SOMETIMES EMBARRASSED
TO SHOW THEIR SKIN, AND IT CAN
REALLY AFFECT YOUR SLEEP
PATTERN.
IF THAT IS HAPPENING IN YOUR
FAMILY, IT IS EXTREMELY
DISRUPTY.
>> SINCE I HAVE BEEN USING IT
ON MY SON, HE HAS BEEN HAVING
BETTER SLEEP.
DR. OZ: PATRICIA, YOU HAVE BEEN
USING IT FOR SEVERAL MONTHS?
>> WE HAVE BEEN USING IT FOR A
VERY LONG TIME.
MY DAUGHTER ACTUALLY STARTED
WITH ECZEMA WHEN SHE WAS ABOUT
1 1/2.
SHE IS 8 NOW.
WE HAVE BEEN USING USERIN FOR A
LONG TIME, BUT MUCH MORE
CONSISTENTLY.
EVERY DAY WE USE IT.
WE HAVE HAD ZERO SFLARE UPS.
I AM VERY EXCITED THAT I DON'T
HAVE ANY SFLARE UPS.
>> DR. OZ, PATRICIA KNOWS, WHEN
YOU HAVE A YOUNG CHILD WITH
ECZEMA, IT IS A VERY BIG DEAL.
TO BE USING IT EVERY DAY TO
PREVENT THE FLAIR UPS.
IF YOU CAN PREVENT THE FLAIR
UPS FOR MONTHS ON END AND THE
KIDS ARE SLEEPING, IT IS A VERY
LEPISTOFUL THING.
DR. OZ: HOW DID YOUR CITIZEN --
HOW DOES YOUR SKIN FILE
DIFFERENTLY?
>> I HAVE NO CRACKS ON MY ENDS,
ON MY LEGS WHERE I USUALLY GET
IT ARE FREE OF IT IT IS
AMAZING.
DR. OZ: THE
[INAUDIBLE QUESTION]
IS ARE YOUR FRIENDS JEALOUS OF
YOU AND YOUR HAPPINESS?
>> TOTALLY.
DR. OZ: DOESN'T IT MAKE YOU
FEEL GOOD?
>> TOTALLY.
DR. OZ: USERIN IS OUR PARTNER.
THE FIRST 5,000 PEOPLE DOING TO
DOCTOROZ.COM WILL RECEIVE A
COUPON FOR A FREE TEA-PARTY OF
THE ECZEMA CREAM.
I AM NOT GOING TO STOP THERE.
MY ENTIRE STUDIO AUDIENCE IS
NOT GOING HOME WITH JUST ONE,
BUT TWO TUBES OF USERIN
Is your dry skin cream not doing
enough?
Try Eucerin Advanced Repair
cream.
For 48hour dry skin relief...
Goes beyond ceramides with
moisturizing factors
naturally found in skin...
Eucerin Advanced Repair Cream
For healthier looking skin.
Alright, I brought in
Ensure Max Protein...
To give you
the Protein you need
with less of
the sugar you don't.
(Straining)
I'll take that.
(Cheers)
30 grams of protein
and 1 gram of sugar.
Ensure Max Protein.
In two great flavors.
I'm not picking it up. You pick
it up!
I'm not picking it up.
I'll pick it up! They're clean!
♪'Cuz my hiney's clean.♪
♪Oh yeah I'm Charmin clean.♪
Charmin Ultra Strong just cleans
better.
Enjoy the Go with Charmin.
Oui is so thick and creamy, it
can stay upside down.
Oui the french style yogurt.
YQ by Yoplait.
40% less sugar than the leading
Greek yogurt
and packed with protein.
Now that's smart.
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: TODAY THE NEW SCIENCE
SAYS THE BRAIN POWER CHANGES
WITH THE SEASONS.
YOUR BRAIN MAY HAVE TO WORK
HARDER DEPENDING ON WHETHER IT
IS HOT OR COLD OUTSIDE.
WHO LOVES THE COLD HERE?
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: AND WHO IS MISSING THE
SUNNY AND HOT DAYS RIGHT ABOUT
NOW?
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE ARE ALL DIFFERENT.
A RECENT STUDY LOOKED AT BRAIN
ACTIVITY AND MEMORY IN THE WARM
AND COLD WEATHER.
FOR SUSTAINED TASKS, PEOPLE'S
BRAIN HAVE TO WORK HARDER IN
THE SUMMER COMPARED TO WINTER.
DON'T FEEL BAD IF YOU HAVE
TROUBLE IN THE SUMMER.
HOWEVER, WORKING MEMORY,
REMEMBERING A PHONE NUMBER OR
THE SHOPPING LIST, PEOPLE'S
BRAINS HAVE TO WORK HARDER
AROUND THAT WHEN AUTUMN CAME
COMPARED TO SPRING.
IT COULD BE BECAUSE OF OUR
RHYTHM.
IN WINTER AND SPRING YOUR
MEMORY HAS A BIT OF A LEG UP.
MAYBE THAT IS WHY THERE IS NO
SCHOOL IN THE SUMMER.
THINK ABOUT THAT.
PROVING THERE IS A BEST TIME
FOR EVERYTHING.
NEXT TIME YOU THINK YOUR MEMORY
OR ATTENTION SPAN IS LACKING, I
GIVE YOU PERMISSION TO BLAME IT
ON THE WEATHER.
CHANGES ARE HAPPENING.
OUR JOURNEY IS JUST BEGINNING.
Oats and oat bran
have a soluble fiber
called beta-glucan,
which can help
lower cholesterol
as part of
a heart-healthy diet.
Now it's in new
Quaker Oat Beverage,
a super-smooth
dairy alternative.
Now it's in new
Quaker Oat Beverage,
Never ending is now even better
at Olive Garden.
All new Never Ending Stuffed
Pastas starting at $12.99.
Pick your favorite stuffed
pasta, sauce and topping.
It's all never ending.
All new
Never Ending Stuffed Pastas.
Only for a limited time,
at Olive Garden.
>>> COMING UP RIGHT NOW ON "PAGE
SIX TV" LIVE -- JEFF BEZOS AND
LAUREN SANCHEZ ARE STILL
TOGETHER AND LAUREN'S BROTHER IS
TELLING US ABOUT THE LEAKED SEX.
WAS HE INVOLVED?
>>> AND KATY PERRY IS ENGAGED.
THAT'S RIGHT, ORLANDO PLOOM
POPPED THE QUESTION AND THE
SUPERSTAR CAN'T STOP GUSHING
OVER THE RING.
>>> AND WE'VE GOT THE LATEST
DEVELOPMENTS IN THE JUSSIE
SMOLLETT ASSAULT CASE.
>>> PLUS, HAILEY BALDWIN/BIEBER
HAVE TWO WORDS TO DESCRIBE HER
MARRIAGE TO JUSTIN.
BRACE YOURSELF, IT'S THE LAST
THING YOU WOULD EXPECT TO HEAR.
IT'S NOW COMING UP RIGHT NOW ON
"PAGE SIX TV."
>> WELCOME TO "PAGE SIX TV."
I'M BEVY SMITH.
WE HAVE CARLOS GREER AND
ELIZABETH WAGMIESTER.
NOW, WE'RE LIVE SO YOU KNOW YOU
NEED TO GET THAT TINSEL BUN
READY