Buy One Take One is back,
starting at just $12.99,
at Olive Garden.
Join us for a NEW
favorite today.
Then bring one home
for tomorrow--on us.
Buy One Take One
For a limited time.
Only at Olive Garden.
ANNOUNCER: MICROWAVE BREAKFASTS.
DR. OZ: BURRITOS AND EGG
MUFFINS.
ANNOUNCER: FAST AND EASY.
>> BREAKFAST FOODS ARE PLAYING.
ANNOUNCER: BUT ARE THEY REALLY
GOOD FOR YOU?
DR. OZ: ARE THEY JUST JUNK FOOD
IN DISGUISE?
ANNOUNCER: PLUS, FAT SEAMERS
CAUGHT ON TAPE.
>> SHE IS EATING TOO MUCH
CHOCOLATE.
>> WHY ARE YOU INSULTING ME
ABOUT MY WEIGHT?
ANNOUNCER: COMING UP NEXT.
♪
DR. OZ: ARE Y'ALL READY FOR
SEASON 10?
>> YEAH!
♪
>> I LOVE YOU, DR. OZ.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: TODAY, AN INVESTIGATION
INTO THE FROZEN FOOD I'LL.
THE FOOD INDUSTRY IS OFFERING AN
UNPRECEDENTED NUMBER OF
MICROWAVEABLE BREAKFAST FOOD
OPTIONS INCLUDING BURRITOS AND
EGG MUFFINS READY IN MINUTES.
MANY CLAIM TO BE HEALTHIER.
BUT ARE THEY?
OR ARE THEY JUST JUNK FOOD IN
DISGUISE?
SHE PUT MANY OPTIONS TO THE TEST
IN THE BEST FOOD LAB THERE IS,
HER OWN BUSY KITCHEN.
>> I AM SHOPPING FOR BREAKFAST
SANDWICHES.
I CANNOT REMEMBER THE LAST TIME
I BOUGHT A BREAKFAST SANDWICH.
THIS SHOULD BE INTERESTING.
DO YOU WANT TO TRY THESE FOR
BREAKFAST?
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> IT IS A BREAKFAST SANDWICH
MADE ON A WAFFLE.
BACON EGG AND CHEESE.
>> I DON'T LIKE EGGS OR CHEESE
BUT I COULD TRY IT WITH
SOMETHING ELSE.
>> THIS IS WHAT I ENDED UP
GETTING.
TWO DIFFERENT ENGLISH MUFFINS.
THEY ARE DIFFERENT.
THIS IS ON A WAFFLE.
AND THIS IS A BREATHLESS E --
BREADLESS EGG CUP I AM EXCITED
ABOUT.
DR. OZ: WAS THAT THE BEST
ASSIGNMENT YOU HAVE EVER BEEN
GIVEN?
>> ANY ASSIGNMENT WITH FOOD,
SIGN ME UP.
BREAKFAST IS NOT A HARD MEAL FOR
ME.
I WAS HAPPY TO GET THIS
ASSIGNMENT BECAUSE IT IS TOUGH
FOR ME.
I AM A LOW-CARB EATER.
FOR MY KIDS, I AM LOOKING FOR
ALTERNATIVES TO THE STAPLES THAT
ARE HIGH SUGAR AND HIGH CARB.
THIS COULD CHANGE THINGS AT MY
HOUSE.
DR. OZ: HOW BIG HAVE THESE
BECOME?
>> WHEN IT COMES TO FROZEN FOOD,
BREAKFAST FOODS ARE DOING SO
WELL.
IT IS FOR TWO REASONS.
ONE IS MILLENNIALS.
82% OF MILLENNIALS SAY THIS IS A
GOOD OPTION FOR THEIR KIDS.
I AGREE WITH THAT COMPLETELY.
THE OTHER ONE IS THE KETO CROWD.
THEY ARE LOOKING FOR LOW-CARB
OPTIONS.
THOSE TWO THINGS ARE DRIVING THE
INDUSTRY.
DR. OZ: THE BUN IS EGG.
WE ASKED FOOD SCIENTIST TAYLOR
WALLACE TO BREAK DOWN HOW
MICROWAVABLE BREAKFASTS ARE
MADE.
IS THERE REAL EGG IN THESE?
>> ACTUALLY, YES.
IN MANY OF THE PRODUCTS, THE
MAIN INGREDIENT IS A WHOLE EGG.
YOU WILL SEE SOME OF YOUR NORMAL
CULPRITS, DIFFERENT FOOD
ADDITIVES.
THEY MIGHT LOOK SCARY, BUT THEY
ARE IN THERE FOR A FUNCTIONAL
PURPOSE.
SAM TIM GUNN  ZANTHAM GUM IS
WHAT WE ADD SO THE EGG DOES NOT
CRUMBLE.
MODIFIED FOOD STARCH PROVIDES
TEXTURE.
YOU MIGHT HAVE DIFFERENT
FLAVORS.
YOU MIGHT ASK, WHY NOT JUST ADD
BUTTER?
IT OXIDIZES AND MAKES THE
PRODUCT GO STALE.
INSTEAD, THESE PRODUCE THE
TASTE.
DR. OZ: I LOVE THAT IT IS REAL
EGG.
YOU HAVE A WAY OF MAKING THE
FROZEN MICROWAVABLE BREAKFASTS
WITH FLAVOR.
IT HAS TO DO WITH THIS.
YOU ARE A FLAVOR SCIENTIST.
WHAT DOES THIS HAVE TO DO WITH
FLAVOR?
>> THERE ARE TWO THINGS YOU HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT IN PRODUCTS LIKE
EGG SANDWICHES.
ONE IS WATER BECAUSE WE KNOW
THAT WATER MAKES THINGS GO BAD.
NUMBER TWO IS OXYGEN BECAUSE
OXYGEN OXIDIZES THINGS.
FROZEN WATER CANNOT DO MUCH.
THEN WE ADD NITROGEN TO THE
PACKAGE, SIMILAR TO WHAT YOU SEE
IN POTATO CHIPS WITH THE AIR
INSIDE.
THAT IS NITROGEN.
WHEN YOU OPEN THE BAG, THE
OXYGEN COMES IN.
YOU LEAVE IT OUT FOR A DAY AND
IT GOES STALE.
THE SAME THING HAPPENS WITH EGG
SANDWICHES.
DR. OZ: I TOOK THE LIST YOU HAVE
AN SPLIT IT UP.
EXPLAIN HOW PEOPLE HAVE HACKED
THE SYSTEM.
>> AS A REMINDER, IT IS VERY
HIGH-FAT, LOW-CARB.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT TRADITIONAL
BREAKFAST SANDWICHES, THESE ARE
NOT ANAN OPTION FOR KETO FOLLOWS
BECAUSE OF THE BREAD.
THIS IS A GAME CHANGER IF YOU
ARE A KETO DEVOTEE.
THEY HAVE MADE THE BREAD OUT OF
EGGS.
THIS IS BREADLESS.
DR. OZ: I WAS NOT SURE IT WAS
REAL.
>> IT IS REAL.
IT IS EGGS.
IT IS HIGH-PROTEIN.
EXTREMELY LOW CAR.
THIS IS THE INDUSTRY RESPONDING
TO THE DEMAND.
DR. OZ: SEVEN GRAMS OF CARBS.
HOW DOES THE REST OF IT COMPARE?
>> ENGLISH MUFFIN OPTION, 28
GRAMS OF CARBS.
HERE WE HAVE THE CROISSANT, 27
GRAMS.
THE BISCUIT LOOKS THE MOST
DELICIOUS.
I'M WORKING HARD NOT TO TAKE A
BITE.
DR. OZ: FLATBREAD IS A GOOD
IDEA.
>> IT IS A GREAT IDEA.
IT IS STILL HIGHER.
DR. OZ: HOW DID THE BREAD LESS
VERSION DO?
>> IT WAS DELICIOUS.
I DID NOT MISS THE BREAD BUT I
HAD TO WONDER IF IT WAS TOO MUCH
PROTEIN.
DR. OZ: I THINK PROTEIN IS OK.
THE BIGGER ISSUE FOR ME IS SALT.
RE-FREEZE THINGS, -- WHEN YOU
FREEZE THINGS, HE CAN HAVE MORE
SALT THAN YOU WANT.
I WAS IMPRESSED WITH THE
OPTIONS.
THE NEXT INVESTIGATION HAS TO DO
WITH THE CRUSTLESS QUICHES.
THERE ARE NO CARBS?
DO I HAVE THAT RIGHT?
COMPARE THESE AND SEE IF YOU
TASTE A DIFFERENCE.
>> I THOUGHT YOU WOULD NEVER
ASK.
DR. OZ: I'M GOING TO REVEAL
SOMETHING TO YOU IN A SECOND.
THESE ARE NOT MADE THE SAME WAY.
WHICH DO YOU LIKE MORE?
MUCH BETTER?
ONE OF THESE IS HOMEMADE BY
YOURS TRULY.
THE OTHER WAS MADE IN A STORE.
THIS WAS MADE BY US.
>> NICE JOB, DR. OZ.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: THIS IS THE STORE-BOUGHT
ONE.
I POINTED OUT BECAUSE IT TAKES A
TON OF TIME.
I THINK MOST PEOPLE PREFER IT
BUT I GET WHAT YOU DON'T DO IT
BECAUSE OF LACK OF TIME.
DOES THIS TASTE GOOD ENOUGH THAT
YOU WOULD BE OK WITH IT?
IT WORKS?
>> GREAT OPTION.
DR. OZ: I DON'T THINK IT IS
QUITE THE SAME AS MAKING IT
YOURSELF BUT GOOD ENOUGH FOR
MOST BUSY MOMS.
HOW DO THEY COMPARE
NUTRITIONALLY?
>> THERE IS A LOT OF GOOD NEWS.
THE STORE-BOUGHT ONES ARE REAL
EGG OR EGG-BASED.
THEY DO HAVE OTHER THINGS ADDED
BECAUSE THEY HAVE TO LIVE ON A
SHELF AND BE FROZEN.
FOR THE MOST PART, IT IS CLOSE
TO THE REAL THING.
YOU CAN FEEL GOOD ABOUT EATING
THEM AND GIVING THEM TO YOUR
KIDS.
DR. OZ: WE INVESTIGATED FROZEN
MICROWAVE BREAKFAST BURRITOS.
THEY SEEM TO BE MAKING A
COMEBACK.
>> WHEN I WAS A KID, IT WAS LIKE
THESE THINGS ARE TERRIBLE.
THEY ARE MUSHY AND GOOEY.
FOOD SCIENTISTS HAVE IT DOWN TO
AN ART.
NOW THEY TASTE FANTASTIC.
THERE ARE VEGETARIAN OPTIONS.
THERE ARE FARM TO TABLE OPTIONS.
THEY HAVE SOMETHING FOR
EVERYBODY.
DR. OZ: WE SAY MAKE BACON A
SPECIAL FOOD.
WHEN WE COME BACK, WE SHOW YOU A
NEW MICROWAVABLE BREAKFAST THAT
ALLOWS YOU TO USE YOUR OWN FRESH
EGG.
IS IT THE BEST OF BOTH WORLDS?
You're going to do your thing.
And no period is gonna slow you
down!
With Tampax, you get protection
that moves with you
for total comfort.
Choose Pearl for your chill,
pocket for your moves,
and Active for your hustle.
Do your thing with Tampax.
BABYBEL: I used be a one-cheese
operation,
but me and Crunchy here make a
great team.
We even finish each other's...
BABYBEL: (To Crunchy)You're
supposed to say sentences...
CRUNCHY: ---sentences.
BABYBEL: Well not now.
Delicious new Babybel Cheese
and Crackers.
BABYBEL: Saved it!
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: IF YOU HAVE EVER TRIED
TO MAKE AN OMELETTE AND THIS
HAPPENED, YOU ARE NOT ALONE.
RESTAURANTS USE MAKING AN
OMELETTE IS THE ULTIMATE TEST OF
A CHEF'S TRUE SKILLS.
TODAY, WE ARE INVESTIGATING A
NEW SHORTCUT TURNING ON LET'S --
OMELETS INTO A WEEKDAY MEAL.
OMELETS IN A CUP.
THERE ARE TWO MAIN KINDS.
MAKE THEM UP FOR US.
>> GO AHEAD AND OPEN THE
PACKAGE.
IT HAS EVERYTHING INSIDE.
YOU HAVE VEGETABLES AND MEAT.
THEN YOU HAVE LIQUID EGG.
IT IS BASICALLY THE SAME THING
YOU BUY IN THE GROCERY STORE IN
THE DRUGS.
IT IS A LITTLE BIT MORE THAN
REAL EGG TO PREVENT BACTERIA
FROM GROWING.
YOU CAN POP IT IN THE MICROWAVE
AND YOU ARE GOOD TO GO.
DR. OZ: SO SIMPLE.
HOW IS THIS DIFFERENT?
>> THIS IS FOR CONSUMERS WHO
PREFER THEIR PRODUCTS LESS
PROCESSED.
WE CHARGE THE SAME PRICE BUT DO
NOT ADD THE EGG.
YOU HAVE TO ADD YOUR OWN.
DR. OZ: YOU'RE KIDDING.
IT IS THE SAME PRICE?
>> YOU HAVE TO ADD YOUR OWN
EGG.
YOU HAVE THE CHEESE, VEGETABLES,
MEAT, SAME AS THE OTHER PRODUCT.
DR. OZ: BREAK THE EGG.
MY GOODNESS.
BREAK IT OVER HERE AND PUT IT IN
THE PAN.
THAT IS IT.
YOU ADD THE GOODIES.
>> MIX IT UP AND THERE YOU GO.
DR. OZ: I AM IMPRESSED.
THIS IS SO CLOSE TO WHAT I
NORMALLY DO BUT I WOULD THINK
ABOUT THIS.
>> THEY ARE VERY CLOSE TO THE
NORMAL FOOD PRODUCTS YOU WOULD
COOK IN YOUR KITCHEN.
I HAVE A LITTLE BIT OF ADDITIVES
TO PREVENT MOLD OR BACTERIAL
GROWTH.
BUT OVERALL, IT IS THE SAME
THING.
DR. OZ: THE FOOD SCIENTIST IS
HAPPY, I'M HAPPY.
THE PRICE IS THE SAME.
>> ABOUT $3 A PACKAGE.
GREAT FOR A COLLEGE STUDENT OR
SOMEONE ON THE GO.
CAN YOU GET ADDICTED TO
MICROWAVE MEALS?
♪ ♪ ♪
So Kim, you going for our big
Drive Safe & Save discount?
Yup, using the app. I've been
quite vigilant.
Sharon says step on it. The
meeting's started.
OK, write her back 'Dear Sharon,
don't mess with my discount!'
Faster Mommy, I gotta go to the
bathroom.
I do too honey, but we're gonna
hold it for Mommy's discount.
Easy, easy!
But you're in labor?
Don't mess with my discount!
Uh hem.
Get a discount up to 30%
with Drive Safe & Save
from State Farm.
MICROWAVE FOODS COULD BE DOING
TO YOUR BRAIN.
♪
[BEEPING]
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: I KNOW.
DID YOU START TO SALIVATE AT THE
SOUND OF THE MICROWAVE?
MILLIONS RELY ON QUICK MICROWAVE
MEALS FOR A QUICK LUNCH OR HOT
DINNER.
THE CAN YOU GET ADDICTED TO
THESE -- BUT CAN YOU GET
ADDICTED TO THESE FAST FOOD
FROZEN FOODS?
DOES YOUR FREEZER LOOK LIKE
THIS?
SOMEONE IN OUR AUDIENCE IS THE
OWNER OF THIS STOCK FREEZER FULL
OF MICROWAVE MEALS AND IT HAS
TURNED INTO AN OBSESSION WITH
MICROWAVE MEALS.
PLEASE WELCOME ANGELA WHO WAS
TURNED IN BY HER BEST FRIEND
BELLA.
>> I THINK I AM FINE.
DR. OZ: WHAT IS THE ISSUE?
>> SHE HAS A VERY BIG PROBLEM.
DR. OZ: THAT IS A REAL PHOTO OF
HER FREEZER?
>> YES.
DR. OZ: HOW OFTEN DOES SHE
MICROWAVE FROZEN FOOD?
>> ALL THE TIME.
BREAKFAST, LUNCH, SNACKS.
>> I LOVE IT.
DR. OZ: WHAT DO YOU LOVE ABOUT
IT?
>> THEY HAVE HEALTHY ONES.
LEAN CUISINE, HOT POCKETS IN A
RUSH.
EASY AS CAN BE.
DR. OZ: WHAT YOU THINK ABOUT
YOUR FRIEND'S CONCERN OVER YOUR
PERCEIVED ADDICTION FOR
MICROWAVE FAST FOOD?
>> I DON'T KNOW HER CONCERN.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW MY CONCERN?
YOU SEND ME COUPONS.
YOU WANT TO BUY THINGS OFF EBAY.
YOU GO TO THE DOLLAR STORE.
NO.
IT IS TOO MUCH.
DR. OZ: COME UP HERE.
I UNDERSTAND THE ALLURE OF
FROZEN MEALS.
BUT IN REALITY, THERE IS
SOMETHING REALLY ADDICTIVE IN
THESE FOODS THAT MAKES THEM SO
DESIROUS FOR US.
MARK HAS MADE A TASTE TEST YOU
AND I WILL BE PARTICIPANTS IN.
TELL US WHAT WE WILL TASTE.
>> WE HAVE THREE LASAGNAS.
THE FIRST IS FRESH LIKE YOU MAKE
AT HOME.
THIS IS ALSO LASAGNA WE MADE BUT
NOT FRESH.
WE FROZE IT AND REHEATED IT.
DR. OZ: FRESH IS GOOD.
KEEP GOING.
I AM MOVING ALONG.
>> THEN WE HAVE THE
MICROWAVEABLE LASAGNA LIKE YOU
BUY AT THE SUPERMARKET.
SOMETHING INTERESTING HERE.
DR. OZ: LET ME TRY IT.
THAT IS GOOD.
THAT IS REALLY GOOD.
>> TELL ME WHAT YOU LIKE ABOUT
IT.
DR. OZ: SEE IF YOU LIKE IT.
>> TASTES GOOD.
DR. OZ: THIS IS ACTUALLY BETTER
THAN THE FRESH.
>> SOMETHING REALLY INTERESTING
HAPPENING HERE.
THIS IS ANOTHER TALE OF TASTE
BUDS TRICKERY.
IT IS IN THE FLAVOR.
IT IS AND HOW THEY CREATED THE
EXPERIENCE OF LASAGNA IN A
FROZEN FOOD WHERE WE WILL FIND
SOMETHING INTERESTING.
DR. OZ: AND COVER THE ANATOMY OF
A MICROWAVE -- UNCOVERED THE
ANATOMY OF THE MICROWAVE MEAL.
WHAT DO THEY DO DIFFERENTLY?
THE FIRST ISSUE IS
PRESERVATIVES.
WHAT KIND ARE WE TALKING ABOUT?
>> TO GET THE FLAVOR, THEY USE
SYNTHETIC FLAVORINGS.
THAT IS HOW THEY JACK UP THE
FLAVOR.
WE SEE A LOT OF THE SAME GUILTY
SUSPECTS WE SEE IN OTHER
PROCESSED FOODS.
POLYSORBATE 80 IS A BOOKING
AGENT.
IT MAKES THE SAUCE TASTE NICE
AND SMOOTH.
POTASSIUM BROMINE IS ILLEGAL IN
SOME COUNTRIES.
DR. OZ: IT IS ILLEGAL IN SOME
COUNTRIES?
>> ILLEGAL AND IT IS IN OUR
FROZEN FOODS.
DR. OZ: THESE ARE THEORETICAL
CONCERNS.
THE NEXT IS A REAL CONCERN,
SUGAR.
WHY WOULD YOU ADD SUGAR TO
LASAGNA?
>> AS WE SAW, THE FLAVOR TAKES A
BEATING.
WHAT IS AN EASY WAY TO JACK UP
THE FLAVOR?
JUST DUMP IN SOME SUGAR.
YOU WILL BE SHOCKED HOW MUCH.
WE FOUND ONE FROZEN ENTRÉE THAT
HAD 29 GRAMS OF SUGAR IN A
SERVING.
IT GETS WORSE.
GUESS HOW BIG THE SERVING IS?
THIS BIG.
IT IS ONLY HALF.
MOST PEOPLE THINK I GET TO EAT
THE WHOLE THING.
THEN YOU ARE GETTING 58 GRAMS OF
SUGAR.
THAT IS THE SUGAR IN TWO CANDY
BARS.
WHO WOULD EVER THINK THERE IS
TWO CANDY BARS WORTH OF SUGAR?
IT IS CRAZY.
DR. OZ: A LOT OF SUGAR.
A HIDDEN SOURCE OF CARBS,
MODIFIED STARCH.
>> IT IS THERE TO GET RID OF
SOME OF THE PROBLEMS YOU GET
WHEN YOU REHEAT FROZEN FOODS.
YOU DO NOT GET THE PUDDLES OF
WATER.
IT HOLDS ITS SHAPE.
IT IS CARBOHYDRATES THAT HAVE NO
FLAVOR.
YOU'RE GETTING CARBS IN YOUR
TUMMY DO NOT TASTE.
THAT IS THE WORRY.
DR. OZ: EXPLAIN WHAT HAPPENS TO
YOUR BRAIN WHEN YOU ARE HAVING
THESE EMPTY CARBS HIDDEN.
TAKE A BITE OUT OF ONE OF THESE
MEALS.
YOU BEGIN TO FALL IN LOVE WITH
THIS.
YOU BEGIN TO CRAVE IT.
YOUR BLOOD SUGAR STARTS TO
SPIKE.
WHEN THE BLOOD SUGAR GOES UP,
DOPAMINE IS RELEASED THAT MAKES
YOU REALLY HAPPY AND SMILING.
WE KNOW THAT FROM COMFORT FOOD.
THEN YOUR BLOOD SUGAR FALLS
AGAIN AND YOU CRAVE THAT HIGH
YOU JUST HAVE.
YOUR BLOOD SUGAR LEVELS CAUSE
INCREASED APPETITE.
YOU EAT MORE FOOD.
THE NEXT THING YOU KNOW, YOU'RE
EATING MORE OF THE FROZEN FOODS
YOUR CRAVING AND FEELING GOOD
ABOUT DOING IT --OK ABOUT DOING
IT.
LIKE CHEMICAL ADDICTION, THERE
IS A PSYCHOLOGICAL ADDICTION
THESE MICROWAVE MEALS CAN CAUSE.
>> WE HAVE SEEN THIS INTERACTION
BEFORE WITH FOODS WITH A LOT OF
SUGAR AND FLAVOR.
HARD TO STOP EATING.
THERE ARE A LOT OF WAYS THESE
GET US EATING TOO MUCH.
DR. OZ: DON'T BE A KILLJOY.
SHE IS NERVOUSLY LAUGHING.
SHE WILL PROBABLY STILL EAT SOME
OF THE MEALS IN HER FREEZER.
GIVE US SOME TACTICS AND HACKS.
>> LOOK AT THE INGREDIENT LIST
BECAUSE THEY ARE NOT ALL THE
SAME.
INGREDIENTS AT THE BEGINNING OF
THE LIST, THERE ARE MORE OF
THEM.
LOOK AT THE GOOD THINGS AT THE
BEGINNING.
IF THERE IS SOME AT THE END,
THERE IS NOT MUCH.
DR. OZ: THEY SEEM TO THINK YOU
ARE BETTER SERVED TO EAT
MICROWAVE MEALS DIFFERENTLY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I THINK I WON'T DO IT EVERY
DAY.
MAYBE TWO OR THREE TIMES A WEEK.
THANK YOU.
DR. OZ: ACTUALLY HAVING AN
IMPACT.
NICELY DONE.
THANK YOU FOR SAYING THAT.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.[APPLAUSE]
When I showed my mom
the DNA results,
it made her
feel proud.
Ancestry specifically
showed the regions
that my family was from.
New features.
Greater details.
Richer stories.
Get your DNA kit today
at Ancestry.com.
♪♪
From new love.
♪
To life long friends.
Moments together call for
America's family favorite.
♪
Lipton®.
Live Alive.
Get in for lunch now,
at Olive Garden
With Lunch Duos
starting at $6.99
Lipton®.
Choose a favorite, like Lasagna
Or all new pasta bowls,
like Shrimp Scampi
Paired with unlimited soup
or salad and breadsticks
Get never ending value
for lunch, at Olive Garden.
DR. OZ: WE ARE BACK WITH OUR
INVESTIGATION INTO PUBLIC FAT
SHAMING.
WOULD YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO IF IT
HAPPENED TO YOU?
WHAT IF IT CAME FROM THE ONE
PERSON YOU TRUST THE MOST, YOUR
DOCTOR.
ACCORDING TO ONE STUDY, ABOUT
HALF OF WOMEN SAID TO HAVE BEEN
SHAMED BY A PHYSICIAN.
SHE SAYS SHE WAS FAT SHAMED BY
HER DOCTOR WHO IGNORED HER PAIN
SYMPTOMS.
AFTER FEELING ILL, REBECCA SAYS
HER DOCTOR TOLD HER TO LOSE
WEIGHT.
IT TURNS OUT HER HEALTH ISSUES
WERE NOT A RESULT OF HER SIZE.
EXACTLY CANCER.
--IT WAS ACTUALLY CANCER.
YOUR CASE IS SERIOUS.
YOU GO TO THE DOCTOR.
YOU ARE NOT FEELING WELL.
HOW DID THEY RESPOND TO THE
OBSERVATIONS YOU WERE MAKING
ABOUT YOUR OWN BODY?
>> VERY MUCH A DISMISSAL.
IT WAS A DISMISSAL OF SYMPTOMS
OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
IF YOU JUST LOST A LITTLE
WEIGHT, YOU WOULD BE FINE.
IF YOU LOST A LITTLE WEIGHT, YOU
COULD BRIEF BETTER.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT IS GOING ON,
BUT IF YOU LOST WEIGHT,
EVERYTHING WOULD BE OK.
DR. OZ: AFTER THREE YEARS OF
LOOKING AROUND, YOU FINALLY GOT
A DIAGNOSIS.
WHAT WAS HAPPENING INSIDE YOUR
BODY?
>> I HAD A TUMOR IN MY LUNG.
AND IT HAD KIND OF KILLED THE
BOTTOM HALF OF MY LUNG AND THEY
HAD TO TAKE THE WHOLE LEFT LUNG
OUT.
DR. OZ: IT TOOK THREE YEARS TO
FIGURE OUT WHAT WAS GOING ON.
WHAT WAS IT LIKE WHEN YOU
FINALLY REALIZED YOU HAD A
LIFE-THREATENING PROBLEM CAUSING
THIS AND IT WAS NOT AN ISSUE
WITH YOUR WEIGHT WHICH YOU NEVER
THOUGHT WAS A PROBLEM TO BEGIN
WITH?
>> IT WAS THE FIRST TIME I
FINALLY GOT A DIAGNOSIS.
I SPENT SO MUCH TIME TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT WHAT WAS WRONG WITH
ME.
SOMEONE FINALLY TOLD ME
SOMETHING WAS WRONG.
IT WAS FREEING TO REALIZE THERE
WAS SOMETHING THERE AND NOT JUST
SOMETHING WRONG IN THIS BODY.
DR. OZ: I WISH YOU WERE THE ONLY
PERSON WHO FELT THE WAY YOU
FELT.
IT TURNS OUT OBESE PATIENTS ARE
65% MORE LIKELY THAN OTHERS TO
HAVE UNDIAGNOSED MEDICAL
CONDITIONS.
WE WRITE IT OFF, SAY SOMETHING
ELSE.
SOMETIMES IT IS THE WEIGHT THAT
IS A PROBLEM.
OTHER TIMES, IT IS NOT.
ARE YOU FEELING OK NOW?
>> I HAVE BEEN CANCER FREE SINCE
2012.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: GOOD FOR YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
DR. OZ: LET'S TALK ABOUT YOUR
STORY.
ALSO AN EXAMPLE OF DOCTORS
OVERLOOKING A REAL DIAGNOSIS.
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I HAD BEEN IN PAIN FOR THE
PAST TWO DECADES SINCE I STARTED
ADMINISTRATION -- MENSTRUATION
SINCE I WAS 10 OR 11.
I WOULD FEEL THIS PARALYZING
PAIN EVERY TIME MY MENSES
WOULD COME ABOUT.
THEY SAID HOW ABOUT WE GIVE YOU
BIRTH CONTROL.
I STARTED GAINING WEIGHT AFTER I
HAD MY SON.
IT WAS AUTOMATICALLY SHIFTED TO
IT HAS TO BE AWAKE.
-- YOUR WEIGHT.
DR. OZ: YOUR DOCTORS FOUND THE
REAL DIAGNOSIS.
WHAT WAS GOING ON?
>> I WOULD DIAGNOSES WITH
ENDOMETRIOSIS.
IT WAS NOT FOUND UNTIL I MISSED
MY PERIOD FOUR TIMES.
IT IS SOMETHING PEOPLE BRUSH OFF
AS NOTHING.
I FIND THAT IS AN ISSUE WITH A
LOT OF THINGS IN REPRODUCTIVE
HEALTH.
DR. OZ: THE REASON I AM
PASSIONATE ABOUT THE TOPIC OF
FAT SHAMING IS IT CAN EMBARRASS
PEOPLE.
WE ALSO MISS THE REAL DIAGNOSIS
WHICH IS THE MORE OBVIOUS WAY WE
HURT PEOPLE.
SHE IS ABOUT TO RUN HER 17TH
MARATHON.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: NEITHER OF YOU GOT HELD
BACK.
WHAT IS YOUR MESSAGE TO DOCTORS
WHO ARE TOO EASILY WRITING OFF
SYMPTOMS FOR THE PATIENTS BEING
OVERWEIGHT?
>> LISTEN TO YOUR PATIENTS.
BE PATIENT WITH YOUR PATIENTS.
DON'T JUST BRUSH IT OFF.
TRY TO GIVE THEM A DIAGNOSIS.
DO THE WORK.
LOOK INTO IT.
DO BLOOD TESTS.
THEY PROVED I DID NOT HAVE
THINGS THEY THOUGHT I HAD.
LISTENED TO US.
WHEN YOU DON'T LISTEN TO US, WE
HAVE MISTRUST AND WORRY AND REAL
FEAR THAT NOBODY IS GOING TO
TAKE US SERIOUS.
IT MAKES PEOPLE NOT WANT TO COME
TO YOU.
WE GO TO YOU TO TRUST YOU, SO
JUST LISTEN TO US AND KNOW THAT
THIS IS NOT ALL IN OUR HEADS.
WE KNOW OUR BODIES MORE THAN
ANYBODY ELSE.
DR. OZ: THANK YOU FOR SHARING
YOUR STORIES WITH US.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: NEXT, FAT SHAMING CAUGHT
ON TAPE.
THE VIDEO YOU HAVE TO SEE TO
BELIEVE.
(VO) At Pro Plan,
we believe nutrition is full of
possibilities to improve
your pet's life.
We're redefining
what nutrition can do.
Because the possibility
of a longer life
and a healthy life
is the greatest
possibility of all.
Purina Pro Plan.
Nutrition that Performs.
Buy One Take One is back,
starting at just $12.99,
at Olive Garden.
Join us for a NEW
favorite today.
Then bring one home
for tomorrow--on us.
Buy One Take One
For a limited time.
Only at Olive Garden.
♪
>> MY GOODNESS.
I DON'T KNOW HOW I WILL DO THIS
FOR THE NEXT FOUR HOURS.
[INDISCERNIBLE]
UNBELIEVABLE.
GET ME OUT OF HERE.
[INDISCERNIBLE]
>> I EAT SALAD, OK?
I CANNOT SIT HERE.
DR. OZ: PRETTY AWKWARD.
THAT IS A SMALL TASTE OF WHAT
GOT THE PASSENGER KICKED OFF A
RECENT FLIGHT.
SHE CALLED HER SEATMATE BIG PIG
AMONG OTHER THINGS.
TODAY, WE ARE EXPOSING FAT
SHAMING CAUGHT ON TAPE.
STRANGERS BULLYING AND VERBALLY
ABUSING OTHERS BECAUSE OF THEIR
WEIGHT.
IT IS A MILITIAS -- MALICIOUS
AND DISTURBING ONLINE TREND.
FAT SHAMING VIDEOS.
>> A CAR FULL OF MEN STOPPED IN
THE MIDDLE OF A BUSY ROAD JUST
SO THEY COULD ROLL DOWN THE
WINDOW AND SAY IT THE ICE CREAM
YOU FAT [BLEEP]
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW I WILL DO
THIS FOR THE NEXT FOUR HOURS.
DR. OZ: UNRESTRAINED AND HURTFUL
COMMENTS SHARED IMPOSTS -- IN
POSTS ARE LEAVING PEOPLE
OUTRAGED AND SHOCKED.
>> I WILL NOT BE VERBALLY
ABUSED.
>> YOU SAYING THAT TO ME COULD
HAVE MADE ME GO KILL MYSELF.
DR. OZ: SOME SHOW NO MERCY.
>> WHEN YOU WANT TO DANCE AROUND
WITH YOUR FAT ROLLS HANGING OUT
AND SAYING YOU SHOULD LET ME FOR
MY PERSONALITY AND NOT MY BODY,
AND YOUR EATING UNHEALTHY, ALL
OF A SUDDEN, EVERYONE IN THIS
WORLD HAS SOME EXCUSE WHY THEY
CANNOT BE HEALTHY.
DR. OZ: HEAR FROM -- THE PLAYBOY
PLAYMATE SEEMS TO HAVE TAKEN FAT
SHAMING TO THE EXTREME POSTING
THIS PICTURE OF A NAKED WOMAN
WITH THE COMMENT, "IF I CAN'T
AND SEE THIS -- UNSEE THIS, YOU
CAN'T EITHER."
>> I CAN'T SIT HERE.
>> WHY DON'T YOU [INDISCERNIBLE]
>> KISS MY FAT [INDISCERNIBLE]
DR. OZ: LOOKING AT THESE VIDEOS,
YOU HAVE TO ASK WHAT DRIVES
PEOPLE TO SUCH HATRED.
THE WOMAN WHO RECORDED THE VIRAL
VIDEO OF HER SEATMATE PUBLICLY
FAT SHAMING HER JOINS ME NOW.
THANK YOU FOR COMING TO THE
SHOW.
>> THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME, DR.
OZ.
DR. OZ: GO BACK TO WHAT HAPPENED
WHEN YOU FIRST GOT TO YOUR SEAT.
>> REALIZING THIS WOMAN COMING
INTO THE MIDDLE SEAT WAS HAVING
A BAD DAY.
SHE WAS NOT A HAPPY PERSON.
VERBALLY SAYING NEGATIVE THINGS
AND MAKING IT A LITTLE
UNCOMFORTABLE.
DR. OZ: HOW DID IT MAKE YOU FEEL
WHEN YOU APPRECIATED WHAT SHE
WAS REALLY GETTING AT?
>> UNCOMFORTABLE, ANGRY.
ANGRIER.
AND MADDER.
THAT IS WHY I STARTED DOING THE
OUTBURST AND DECIDED TO DO A
VIDEO.
DR. OZ: SHE KEPT GOING EVEN WITH
YOU RECORDING?
>> YES.
SHE KNEW THAT I WAS RECORDING.
DR. OZ: WHAT PROMPTED YOU TO
WANT TO POST IT?
DOES PUT YOU AT RISK.
THE WHOLE THING IS SO
EMBARRASSING.
OF COURSE, FOR HER, BECAUSE SHE
IS DOING ALL OF THIS.
>> I GUESS BECAUSE I AM A NURSE
AND HAVE A PLATFORM, I THOUGHT
BULLYING AND FAT SHAMING IS
UNACCEPTABLE BEHAVIOR FOR
CHILDREN AND EVEN MORE THAN
ADULTS.
SO I FELT THE NEED TO SHOW IT
HAPPENING.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: GOOD FOR YOU.
A LOT OF PEOPLE WOULD HAVE
PRETENDED IT NEVER HAPPENED.
YOU TRAVEL A LOT.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN PUBLICLY
SHAMED LIKE THIS?
>> 15 YEARS ON THE ROAD AND THIS
WAS TRULY A FIRST.
I AM ON THE ROAD ALMOST EVERY
WEEK AND THIS WAS A FIRST.
DR. OZ: YOU MUST HAVE AT SOME
POINT BEEN DISBELIEVING THIS WAS
HAPPENING.
>> I DID.
THERE WAS A DELAY.
BUT SOMEBODY -- BUT WHEN
SOMEBODY ATTACKS IN PUBLIC, YOU
CAN WALK AWAY.
ON A PLANE, THERE IS NOWHERE TO
WALK TO.
DR. OZ: THE AIRLINE ULTIMATELY
KICKED HER OFF.
WHAT WAS THE REASON THEY GAVE
FOR DOING THAT?
>> THEY WERE SAYING THERE WERE
SO MANY PEOPLE COMPLAINING
BESIDES MYSELF.
WHEN I GOT OFF THE PLANE, THERE
WERE PEOPLE BEHIND ME THAT TOLD
ME HER BEHAVIOR AFTER I STOPPED
VIDEOTAPING WAS SHE WAS STILL
RANTING SO THE AIRLINE HAD TO
TAKE HER OFF THE PLANE FOR THE
SAFETY OF ALL PASSENGERS.
DR. OZ: IT WAS UNITED AIRLINES.
HERE IS WHAT THEY HAD TO SAY
ABOUT THE INCIDENT.
DR. OZ: SHE SPENT THE NIGHT
WHERE EVER YOU WERE COMING FROM.
WIDE DO YOU THINK THAT WOMAN WAS
SO ANGRY?
>> I DON'T THINK I'LL EVER KNOW
WHY SHE BEHAVED THAT WAY AND WHY
SHE THOUGHT THAT WAS ACCEPTABLE
BEHAVIOR.
DR. OZ: YOU ARE BRAVE.
YOUR BRAVE DESIRE TO SHARE THAT
EXPENSE RESULTED IN A VIDEO THAT
ATTRACTED 600,000 VIEWS IN A FEW
WEEKS.
IF YOU COULD TALK TO THAT WOMAN,
AND THERE IS A GOOD CHANCE SHE
MIGHT BE WATCHING THIS
BROADCAST, WHAT WOULD YOU TELL
HER?
>> SHE NEEDS TO BE HEALED.
SHE NEEDS TO LOOK INSIDE AND
DETERMINE WHY SHE BEHAVED THAT
WAY.
WHAT IS HURTING INSIDE HERSELF
THAT MAKES HER THINK IT IS OK TO
HURT OTHER PEOPLE BECAUSE HURT
PEOPLE HURT PEOPLE.
SHE NEEDS TO UNDERSTAND WHY SHE
DID WHAT SHE DID.
I AM ON THE PATH OF FORGIVING
HER BECAUSE AS A WOMAN OF GOD,
THAT IS MY JOB, TO FORGIVE AND
MOVE FORWARD.
[APPLAUSE]
>> THIS IS A TEACHABLE MOMENT
WHICH IS WHY I AGREED TO COME
ON.
I WOULD LIKE TO TAKE A QUICK
MOMENT TO APOLOGIZE TO THE
UNITED FLIGHT ATTENDANTS BECAUSE
THEY DID AN AMAZING JOB, BUT FOR
MY LANGUAGE I USED IN THE VIDEO,
TO TELL THEM I'M SORRY FOR USING
THAT LANGUAGE TOWARD THEM WHEN I
WAS REFERRING TO THE OTHER
WOMAN.
DR. OZ: I DON'T THINK YOU HAVE
TO APOLOGIZE.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: COMING UP, WHERE IS THE
LINE BETWEEN FAT SHAMING AND
CONCERN?
WHAT YOU SHOULD DO IF YOU FEEL
LIKE A DOCTOR IS FAT SHAMING[AP]
Wow!
That's Ensure Max Protein,
with high protein and
1 gram sugar.
It's a sit-up, Banana!
Bend at the waist!
I'm tryin'!
Keep it up.
You'll get there.
Whoa-hoa-hoa!
30 grams of protein,
and one gram of sugar.
ENSURE Max Protein.
If you have postmenopausal
osteoporosis
and a high risk for fracture now
might not be the best time
to ask yourself are my bones
strong?
Life is full of make or break
moments.
That's why it's so important to
help reduce your risk of
fracture with Prolia®.
Only Prolia® is proven to help
strengthen and protect bones
from fracture with 1 shot every
6 months.
Do not take Prolia® if you have
low blood calcium,
are pregnant, are allergic to it
or take XGEVA®
Serious allergic reactions,
like low blood pressure trouble
breathing;
throat tightness; face, lip, or
tongue swelling rash;
itching; or hives have happened.
Tell your doctor about dental
problems
as severe jaw bone problems may
happen
or new or unusual pain in your
hip groin, or thigh,
as unusual thigh bone
fractures have occurred.
Speak to your doctor before
stopping Prolia®
as spine and other bone
fractures have occurred.
Prolia® can cause serious side
effects, like low blood calcium;
serious infections which could
need hospitalization;
skin problems; and severe bone
joint, or muscle pain.
Are you ready?
Ask your doctor how Prolia® can
help strengthen your bones.
With so many nourishing shades,
A color change is easy.
Nutrisse has 77.
From our darkest blacks,
to our lightest blondes.
It nourishes while
it colors.
Plus avocado, olive and shea.
Change a little, or a lot.
Nutrisse.
Nourished Hair. Better Color.
By Garnier,
Naturally!
>> UNFORTUNATELY, I WAS THAT
SHAMED A FEW YEARS AGO.
I WENT TO THE DOCTOR AFTER A CAR
ACCIDENT AND HE WAS SUPPOSED TO
DO SOME WORK ON MY BACK.
WHILE I WAS THERE, HE TOLD ME AT
THE TIME, I WAS ALMOST 100
POUNDS HEAVIER THAN NOW, HE TOLD
ME I SHOULD HAVE BARIATRIC
SURGERY BECAUSE I COULD NOT LOSE
THE WEIGHT NATURALLY.
>> I WAS GAINING WEIGHT LIKE
CRAZY>>.
I WOULD GO TO MY DOCTORS FOR
HELP.
ALL THEY WOULD SAY WAS TO
WORKOUT HARDER AND EAT BETTER.
THEY SAID I WOULD ALWAYS HAVE A
WEIGHT PROBLEM.
THEY DISMISSED ALL OF MY OTHER
SYMPTOMS AND SAID I WAS CRAZY.
THIS WENT ON FOR ABOUT EIGHT
YEARS.
I FINALLY DID MY OWN RESEARCH
AND DISCOVERED I HAD A BRAIN
TUMOR CAUSING ALL OF MY WEIGHT
GAIN.
A YEAR AGO, I HAD BRAIN SURGERY.
I HAD A TUMOR REMOVED.
SINCE THEN, I HAVE LOST 40
POUNDS.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE ARE BACK WITH OUR
INVESTIGATION INTO FAT SHAMING.
COULD YOU BE FAT SHAMING BY YOUR
OWN DOCTOR?
WHERE IS THE LINE BETWEEN
CONCERN AND FAT SHAMING?
WHY IS THERE AN INCREASE?
>> IT BREAKS MY HEART.
THIS ABSOLUTELY BREAKS MY HEART
AS A FAMILY DOCTOR.
WE ARE DOCTORS.
I AM NOT ENTIRELY SURPRISED.
I DO NOT THINK THIS IS NEW.
I THINK WE ARE HEARING ABOUT IT
MORE BECAUSE PEOPLE ARE WILLING
TO TALK ABOUT IT AND RECORDED
AND HAVE CONVERSATIONS.
SOCIAL MEDIA HAS OPENED UP A
PLATFORM TO SHARE OUR STORIES
AND COMPARE EXPERIENCES.
DR. OZ: GIVE THE AVERAGE PERSON
WATCHING ADVICE AS A PHYSICIAN.
HOW DO YOU KNOW IF YOUR DOCTOR
IS DOING HIS BEST BORDER
CROSSING THE LINE INTO SHAMING
-- OR CROSSING THE LINE INTO
SHAMING?
>> TRUST YOUR GUT.
IF IT DOES NOT FEEL RIGHT.
IF YOU FEEL SHAMED OR
EMBARRASSED, YOU KNOW WHAT?
BELIEVE YOURSELF.
BELIEVE HOW YOU FEEL.
A DOCTOR WANTING TO DO THE RIGHT
THING DOES NOT EXCUSE MAKING A
PATIENT FEEL THAT WAY.
THAT IS NEVER OK.
IF YOU HAVE A DOCTOR THAT MAKES
YOU FEEL THAT WAY OR YOU ARE NOT
COMFORTABLE, I'M GIVING YOU
PERMISSION TO FIND A NEW ONE.
DR. OZ: STUDIES HAVE FOUND
OVERWEIGHT WOMEN ARE LESS LIKELY
THAN AVERAGE TO GET PREVENTATIVE
CARE LIKE MAMMOGRAMS.
THERE IS NO EXCUSE FOR THIS.
BUT PEOPLE TREAT OVERWEIGHT
PEOPLE DIFFERENTLY.
WHAT IS THE RIGHT WAY FOR A
PHYSICIAN TO ADDRESS A PATIENT'S
WEIGHT?
>> AS PHYSICIANS, WE HAVE TO
TALK ABOUT THIS.
THESE ARE DISCRIMINATORY
PRPRACTICES.
IT IS WRONG.
AS PHYSICIANS, WE NEED TO TALK
WITH OUR PATIENTS.
LET'S NOT TALK AT THEM, TALK TO
THEM.
ASK THEM QUESTIONS.
TELL ME WHAT YOU HAVE BEEN DOING
AND WHAT YOU HAVE TRIED, WHAT
YOUR STORY IS.
ASKING QUESTIONS IS KEY.
THE IDEA OF NEVER DISMISSING
SYMPTOMS BECAUSE OF WEIGHT.
WE SHOULD NOT DISMISS PATIENT
SYSTEMS --SYMPTOMS BECAUSE OF
ANYTHING.
WE SHOULD ALWAYS BE DOING DUE
DILIGENCE.
TO SAY IT IS YOUR WEIGHT OFF AND
IS NEVER OK -- OFFHAND IS NEVER
OK IN MY OPINION.
I AM A FAMILY DOCTOR.
DO I TAKE SOMEONE'S BLOOD
PRESSURE IN A PUBLIC SPACE WITH
AIR TEMPERATURE?
--FOR THEIR TEMPERATURE?
NEVER.
BUT SOMETIMES IN DOCTOR'S
OFFICES, PEOPLE ARE WEIGHED IN
PUBLIC PLACES LIKE THE WAITING
ROOM.
THIS SHOULD BE PRIVATE.
THIS IS PERSONAL, PROTECTED
INFORMATION.
IT IS NO ONE ELSE'S BUSINESS.
THERE ARE THINGS WE CAN DO TO
MAKE THIS A MORE COMFORTABLE AND
APPROPRIATE SITUATION.
DR. OZ: I DON'T WANT YOU NOT
GOING TO THE DOCTOR BECAUSE YOU
ARE WORRIED ABOUT IT.
IT IS A NECESSARY TOPIC.
MAKE SURE YOU TALK WITH THE
DOCTOR.
I WANT TO BRING IN THE NURSE WE
MET EARLIER WHO WAS ON THE
PLANE.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WHAT IS THE BEST WAY YOU
THINK A PATIENT SHOULD BE ABLE
TO ADDRESS THEIR DOCTOR IF THEY
ARE WORRIED ABOUT WEIGHT ISSUES?
>> LETTING THE DOCTOR KNOW THAT
THIS IS NEW TO ME, THIS IS AN
UNUSUAL FEELING.
I HAVE BEEN FEELING LIKE THIS
FOR TWO WEEKS OR TWO MONTHS,
PUTTING A TIMEFRAME TO IT.
IF THEY DOCTOR IS STILL NOT
LISTENING TO YOU, CHANGE
DOCTORS.
ALWAYS GET A SECOND OPINION.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APP A
SEXUAL RELATIONSHIP WITH AN
UNDERAGED GIRL WHO IS NOW A
PASTOR.
STICK WITH US.
>> I LOVE GETTING TO TALK WITH
YOU ON MY SHOW EVERY SINGLE DAY.
WHEN THE CAMERAS STOP ROLLING,
THE CONVERSATION IS NOT OVER.
I STILL HAVE A LOT THAT I WANT
TO TALK ABOUT.
DOWNLOADABOUT.
DOWNLOAD
Starting a business means
I have to be well rested, every
night of the month.
Always Overnight Pads have up to
a 2x larger back
for up to 10 hours of
protection.
It catches leaks, so you can
catch zzzzs.
Because my morning starts,
before morning starts.
Always.
L'Oréal Paris introduces
Rouge Signature Sunset
Matte Lip
Stain
Eight new, warm shades.
Less texture,
more colors.
More Paris.
All-day matte.
Bare-lip
sensation.
Rouge Signature Sunset.
By L'Oréal Paris.
We're worth it.
What might seem
like a small cough
can be a big bad problem
for your grandchildren.
Babies too young
to be vaccinated
against whooping cough
are the most at risk
for severe illness.
Help prevent this!
Talk to your doctor
or pharmacist today
about getting vaccinated
against whooping cough.
Talk to your doctor
or pharmacist today
PODCASTS.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: IT IS A BIG DAY.
I'M EXCITED TO ANNOUNCE THE
LAUNCH OF MY ALL-NEW OZ GUIDE,
LITTLE MAGAZINES THAT TACKLE
SOME OF YOUR BIGGEST HEALTH
PROBLEMS.
OUR FIRST ISSUE WILL BE ON
NEWSSTANDS AND CHECKOUT COUNTERS
LATER THIS MONTH.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: MONOUNSATURATED FATTY
ACID OUR PLANT-BASED FATS.
THE EASIEST WAY TO REMEMBER THEM
ARE TO LOOK FOR HEALTHY FATS
THAT ARE NOT FROM ANIMAL SOURCES
SUCH AS AVOCADOS WERE NUTS AND
SEEDS.
THEY CAN REALLY FILL YOU UP.
ONE OF MY FAVORITES.
OLIVES.
THERE WAS A STUDY DONE THROUGH
THE AMERICAN DIABETIC
ASSOCIATION THAT FOUND A DIET
RICH IN THESE WORKS TO REDUCE
BELLY FAT.
IT IS A BIG DEAL.
YOU DON'T WANT THESE FOODS
GETTING BORING.
THAT IS THE PROBLEM.
I KNOW YOU ARE THINKING THAT.
I HAVE BEEN HEARING REPORTS OF
NUTS AND SEEDS FATIGUE.
SHY AWAY FROM THIS PROBLEM.
AND THEN THERE IS AVOCADO APATHY
MAKING HEADLINES.
AND THERE IS OLIVE MONOTONY.
I HAVE CHALLENGED THREE BITE
CLUB MEMBERS TO COME UP WITH NEW
DELICIOUS RECIPES IN MY FIRST A
WARDS.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE'VE SPARED NO EXPENSE
AS YOU CAN TELL.
I HOPE YOU ARE IMPRESSED BY
THAT.
THEY WERE JUDGED BY TASTERS WHO
WERE HARSH IN NATURE.
PRIOR TO THE SHOW, THEY TASTED
ALL OF THE FOODS.
THE WINNER WILL TAKE HOME A
COVETED FROZEN AVOCADO.
>> ♪
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: I AM EXCITED TO HEAR
WHAT THEY MADE.
WHAT DID YOU MAKE?
>> I MADE A BURGER.
I COMBINED MACADAMIA NUTS, ALMO
NDS, CACHES, AND PECANS WITH A
LOT OF SEEDS.
PUMPKIN SEEDS, HELD SEATS,
SESAME SEEDS, QUINOA, MUSHROOMS,
AND OLIVES.
DR. OZ: IT TASTES MEETING
WITHOUT THE MEAT -- MEATY
WITHOUT THE MEAT.
NICELY DONE.
ROBERTA CAME UP WITH THE NEXT
LEVEL WAY TO USE AVOCADOS.
>> SECRET AGENT CHOCOLATE
PUDDING.
DR. OZ: VERY CLEVER.
DIABOLICAL.
>> AVOCADO IS A SECRET AGENT.
IT IS GREAT WITH WINE.
DR. OZ: IF YOU BROUGHT WINE, IT
COULD INFLUENCE THE JUDGES.
>> SO DECADENT AND  YOU WOULD
NOT KNOW THERE IS AVOCADO IN IT.
DR. OZ: THIS IS A STRONG
COMPETITOR.
BEFORE WE JUDGE, WE HAVE POWER
-- PAULA.
>> WE HAVE TAHINI-FILLED HUMMUS.
THESE ARE GLUTEN-FREE CRACKERS
MADE FROM SEEDS.
EVERYONE EATS HUMMUS.
I LIGHTENED IT UP BY ADDING
CAULIFLOWER.
DR. OZ: YOU DID?
>> THAT LOWERS THE POWER CAP.
YOU CANNOT TELL THE DIFFERENCE.
-- IT LOWERS THE CALORIE COUNT.
AND DAIKON RADISH.
TRY IT.
DR. OZ: I LIKE THIS IDEA.
YOU PUT A LOT OF GARLIC IN THIS.
I'M VERY PROUD OF YOU.
>> I DID.
DR. OZ: ALL OF THESE YOU WILL
LOSE WEIGHT WITH IF YOU EAT THEM
THE RIGHT WAY.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: I HAVE THE UNFORTUNATE
AND DIFFICULT TASK OF REVEALING
THE WINNER.
ARE WE READY FOR THIS?
NO HARD FEELINGS?
I HAVE DELIBERATED WITH THE
JUDGES AND THE PERSON TAKING
HOME THE GOLDEN AVOCADO TODAY IS
PAULA!
MY GOODNESS.
PAULA WINS!
[APPLAUSE]
>> YOU LIKE ME, YOU REALLY LIKE
ME.
DR. OZ: I LIKE ALL THREE OF YOU.
WE WILL BE PUBLISHING BOTH OF
YOUR RECIPES IN THE MINIBOOK
ZINE.
IT IS AVAILABLE LATER THIS
MONTH.
CHECK IT OUT AND SHARE IT WITH
YOUR FRIENDS.
TOGETHER, CHANGE IS HAPPENING.
OUR JOURNEY IS JUST BEGINNING.
I WILL SEE YOU NEXT TIME.
[APPLAUSE]
[HEART BEAT]
-Keep it down there.
I have a system.
-Keith used to be great
to road-trip with.
But since he bought his house...
Are you going 45?
-Uh, yes.
55 is a suggestion.
-...it's kind of like driving
with his dad.
-What a sign, huh?
Terry, can you take
a selfie of me?
-Take a selfie of you?
-Yeah.
Can you make it look
like I'm holding it?
-He did show us how to bundle
home and auto at progressive.com
and save a bunch of money.
-Oh, a plaque.
"He later navigated northward,
leaving...
Progressive can't protect you
from becoming your parents.
But we can protect
your home and auto
when you bundle with us.
(VO) At Pro Plan,
But we can protect
your home and auto
we believe nutrition is full of
possibilities to improve
your pet's life.
We're redefining
what nutrition can do.
Because the possibility
of a longer life
and a healthy life
is the greatest
possibility of all.
Purina Pro Plan.
Nutrition that Performs.