>> FINAL PHASE BEFORE KRISTOFF
ST. JOHN'S DEATH.
WHAT REALLY HAPPENED?
HIS EX-WIFE OPENS UP ABOUT HIS
PERSONAL DEMONS, THEIR LAST
CONVERSATION.
AND WHAT HE SAID HE SAW RIGHT
BEFORE HE DIED.
PLUS --
>> BASICALLY A TATTOO ON YOUR
FACE.
>> ADDICTED.
PERMANENT MAKEUP REGRETS.
COMING UP NEXT.
♪
DR. OZ: SEASON 10 STARTS NOW.
HE WAS A SOAP OPERA SUPERSTAR.
KRISTOFF ST. JOHN WAS BEST KNOWN
FOR HIS ROLE IN THE YOUNG AND
THE RESTLESS.
THE TAKE CHARGE, CHARISMATIC
BUSINESSMAN WAS A ROLE HE PLAYED
FOR NEARLY 30 YEARS.
HIS SUDDEN DEATH STUNNED
MILLIONS OF FANS AROUND THE
WORLD AND THE HEARTBREAKING NEWS
COMES JUST FOUR YEARS AFTER HIS
SON COMMITTED SUICIDE.
TODAY, KRISTOFF'S EX-WIFE MIA IS
HERE, OPENING UP ABOUT THE
TRAGIC LOSS AND WHAT REALLY
HAPPENED TO KRISTOFF IN THOSE
FINAL DAYS.
HERE'S A LOOK AT THE ROLE THAT
MADE HIM FAMOUS.
>> HOW IS EVERYTHING ELSE IN
YOUR LIFE?
>> REALLY GOOD, ACTUALLY.
THANKS TO THIS ONE HERE.
>> I KNEW I COULD COUNT ON YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I FIGURED YOU COULD USE SOME
FAMILY AROUND.
>> SHE'S BEEN HELPING ME GET MY
HEAD ON STRAIGHT.
I'M SEEING A THERAPIST NOW,
SLEEPING REGULARLY.
>> GLAD TO HEAR IT.
>> WORK LIFE IS GOOD.
PERSONAL LIFE IS GOOD.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT ME
ANYMORE.
>> DON'T GO GETTING CRAZY ON ME.
IT IS A FATHER'S JOB TO WORRY
ABOUT HIS KIDS.
DR. OZ: KRISTOFF'S EX-WIFE MIA
JOINS ME NOW.
I KNOW IT IS HARD.
MIA: I DIDN'T EXPECT IT TO BE SO
-- SORRY.
DR. OZ: DON'T BE SORRY.
IT HAS ONLY BEEN THREE WEEKS.
I PICKED SOMETHING THAT I
THOUGHT IT WOULD REMIND
EVERYBODY WHAT A GREAT ACTOR HE
WAS.
MIA: HE WAS SO AMAZING.
A TWO-TIME EMMY AWARD-WINNING
ACTOR AND HE HAD BEEN ACTING
SINCE HE WAS A KID.
HE LOVED IT.
IT WAS HIS LIFE.
DR. OZ: HOW ARE YOU DOING?
MIA: STRUGGLING.
I NEVER RECOVERED, REALLY, FROM
THE DEATH OF OUR SON.
AND NOW WITH THE DEATH OF
KRISTOFF, IT IS A LOT.
BUT I KNOW THAT THERE'S SO MANY
PEOPLE COUNTING ON ME AND MY
DAUGHTER, AND JUST FOR KRISTOFF
AND JULIAN TO KNOW THAT I'M
STILL HERE FIGHTING AND I'M
GOING TO CONTINUE TO FIGHT.
DR. OZ: LET'S TALK A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT KRISTOFF.
HE WAS CHARISMATIC, STRONG,
CONFIDENT, SO MANY ADJECTIVES,
MASCULINE ADJECTIVES, AND THAT
CONFIDENCE WASN'T THERE
OFF-CAMERA AS MUCH.
MIA: NO, HE ALWAYS APPEARED TO
ME AND A LOT OF PEOPLE TO BE
LIKE THE MOST CONFIDENT PERSON
I'VE EVER MET.
BUT AT HOME, PERSONALLY, WITH
HIS FAMILY, HE WAWAS ACTUALLY VY
INSECURE ABOUT HIMSELF.
I JUST COULDN'T UNDERSTAND IT.
HE WAS SO GOOD-LOOKING, SO
CHARMING, AND MY GOODNESS, WITH
THE LADIES, HE WAS SO POPULAR.
INSIDE, THERE WAS JUST A VERY
INSECURE, LONELY PERSON.
DR. OZ: LONELY?
MIA: LONELY.
HE WOULD OFTEN JUST HIDE IN HIS
HOUSE AND NOT GO OUT, BA
RECLUSE.
DR. OZ: YOU WERE MARRIED TO
KRISTOFF FOR FIVE YEARS.
TWO WONDERFUL CHILDREN.
WHAT KIND OF A FATHER WAS HE?
MIA: HE WAS THE DISCIPLINARIAN.
OUT OF THE TWO OF US, HE WAS --
HE COULDN'T DO IT FOR VERY LONG.
HE WOULD ALWAYS BE A JOKESTER,
VERY LOVING WITH THE KIDS, VERY
FUNNY, ALWAYS HAD SUCH A GREAT
TIME WITH THEM.
AND ESPECIALLY DURING MY CAREER,
HE REALLY STEPPED UP AND PLAYED
THE ROLE OF MOM AND DAD.
HE WAS A GREAT FATHER.
OBVIOUSLY THE RELATIONSHIP
BETWEEN HIM AND HIS SON BECAME
VERY TURBULENT AS MY SON GOT
OLDER.
DR. OZ: A WORLD CHAMPION BOXER,
ACCOMPLISHED IN YOUR OWN RIGHT,
YOU ARE MARRIED TO A MAN WHO IS
POWERFUL ONSTAGE, BUT LONELY AND
INSECURE AT HOME.
JULIAN, YOUR SON, HAS MENTAL
HEALTH ISSUES.
MIA: HE HAS CRIST --
SCHIZOPHRENIA AND KRISTOFF HAD
BIPOLAR.
DR. OZ: YOUR SON TOOK HIS LIFE
FOR YEARS AGO.
MIA: YES, IN A MENTAL HEALTH
FACILITY.
DR. OZ: HOW DID KRISTOFF DEAL
WITH THAT?
MIA: IT WAS OUR BIGGEST
NIGHTMARE.
HE NEVER COULD RECOVER FROM THE
GUILT.
HE FELT GUILTY, RESPONSIBLE.
EVEN THOUGH THE FACILITY WAS
FOUND GUILTY OF NEGLECT AND
FALSIFYING RECORDS.
I KEPT TRYING TO TELL HIM OVER
AND OVER AGAIN THAT IT WAS NOT
HIS FAULT, BUT THERE WAS NOTHING
I COULD SAY OR DO TO MAKE HIM
BELIEVE THAT.
HE FELT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE
DEATH OF OUR SON.
DR. OZ: YOU RETREATED THIS POST
FROM JANUARY, GRIEVING A LOSS OF
A CHILD IS A PROCESS.
IT BEGINS THE DAY YOUR CHILD
PASSES AND ENDS THE DATA PARENT
JOINS THEM.
KRISTOFF RETWEETED, NEVER A
TRUER WORD WAS SPOKEN.
HE TWEETED THIS LESS THAN A
MONTH BEFORE HE DIED.
WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF THAT TWEET?
MIA: NOTHING, BECAUSE THIS WAS
OUR DAILY CONVERSATION.
WHEN PEOPLE TELL ME ABOUT THIS,
I SAY, I DON'T REMEMBER A DAY
THAT HE DIDN'T CRY ABOUT HIS
SON.
THIS IS REALLY ALL WE TALKED
ABOUT.
DR. OZ: HE CARRIED THAT BURDEN,
YOU ARE FEELING THE PAIN TOO,
BUT WITH YOUR HUSBAND'S BIPOLAR
DIAGNOSIS, WAS HE ABLE TO GET
HIMSELF BACK TOGETHER AGAIN?
DID HE TAKE HIS MEDICATION?
WAS HE DOING HIS BEST, DO YOU
FEEL?
MIA: HE WAS SELF-MEDICATING.
WE WERE BOTH IN RECOVERY.
I HAD 30 YEARS OF SOBRIETY.
HE HAD MANY YEARS, AND AFTER OUR
SON PASSED, HE WENT OFF THE
WAGON.
BUT HE WAS TAKING HIS MEDS.
I THINK THAT, YOU KNOW AS A
DOCTOR, THESE MEDS, THEY ARE
NEVER GOING TO CURE THE ILLNESS.
THEY MIGHT HELP THE SYMPTOMS.
SO HE ALSO SELF MEDICATED FOR
WHAT THE PILLS DID NOT DO, WHICH
WAS OUR GRIEF.
DR. OZ: WHEN HE HAD SACRIFICED
HIS SOBRIETY AND WAS
SELF-MEDICATING, DO YOU FEEL HE
WAS IN A DANGEROUS SITUATION?
WAS THERE A TIME HE MIGHT HAVE
THREATENED TO TAKE HIS LIFE, OR
DID HE TRY TO TAKE ACTION ON
THAT?
MIA: HE WAS ALWAYS THREATENING.
DR. OZ: HE WAS?
MIA: ALWAYS.
THE LAST TIME I TALKED TO HIM,
EVEN -- OUR ATTORNEY HAD HIM
5150'ED RECENTLY, RIGHT BEFORE
HE PASSED.
DR. OZ: 5150 MEANS PUTTING HIM
IN A PSYCHIATRIC INSTITUTION.
MIA: YES.
OUR ATTORNEY INTENDED HIM TO BE
THERE FOR A 50 TO 50, WHICH WAS
A TWO-WEEK-OLD.
THEY LET HIM OUT ON THE FOURTH
DAY.
DR. OZ: IF I UNDERSTAND
CORRECTLY, WHAT PROMPTED THAT
ACTION WAS THAT YOUR HUSBAND HAD
TAKEN A GUN AND PUT IT TO HIS
HEAD.
IS THAT CORRECT?
MIA: IN THE PREVIOUS MONTH, YES.
DR. OZ: THAT IS PRETTY SCARY.
MIA: SO WE KNEW THAT THAT WAS
GOING THROUGH HIS MIND.
DR. OZ: WHAT WOULD YOU SAY TO
HIM?
MIA: OF COURSE I TOLD HIM THIS
IS NOT WHAT JULIAN WANTS FROM
YOU.
HE WANTS YOU TO GO ON AND BE
HAPPY AND LEAD A PRODUCTIVE
LIFE.
DR. OZ: NEXT, MIA'S FINAL
CONVERSATION WITH KRISTOFF.
FIND OUT WHAT HE SAYS HE SAW
RIGHT BEFORE HIS SUDDEN DEATH.
♪
Is your dry skin cream not doing
enough?
Try Eucerin Advanced Repair
cream.
For 48hour dry skin relief...
Goes beyond ceramides with
moisturizing factors
naturally found in skin...
Eucerin Advanced Repair Cream
For healthier looking skin.
♪ We buy any car dot com ♪
♪ we buy any car dot com ♪
♪ ANY ANY ANY ANY ♪
Did you know trading in your car
at a dealer could cost
you money?
A recent study found consumers
who trade in their car
pay an average of $990
dollars more.
So don't trade in...
sell it....
to We Buy Any Car.
Learn more and get your free
online valuation
now at we buy any car dot com
♪ Find out how much your car is
worth at WeBuyAnyCar.com ♪
Sensitive skin?
Cetaphil Moisturizing Cream
with 24- hour
moisture lock formula...
gives continuous
soothing relief
for dry sensitive skin.
Cetaphil skin
is healthy skin.
♪♪
When cravings hit, hit back.
Choose Glucerna, with
slow release carbs
to help manage blood sugar, and
start making everyday progress.
Glucerna.
♪
DR. OZ: IT IS HARD TO LOOK AT.
MIA: IT IS HARD.
HIS PICTURES -- I'VE JUST TRIED
NOT TO BECAUSE IT IS TOO MUCH
RIGHT NOW.
TO SEE HIM.
BECAUSE HE IS STILL HERE.
DR. OZ: HE IS STILL HERE.
AND I LOVE SEEING ALL THESE
SUPERSTARS.
THESE ARE TWEETS FROM KRISTOFF
ST. JOHN'S COSTARS.
MILLIONS OF FANS AROUND THE
WORLD STILL SEARCHING FOR
ANSWERS AFTER KRISTOFF
TRAGICALLY DIED.
YOU WERE RIGHT THERE, TALKING TO
HIM, AS THOSE FINAL DECISIONS
WERE BEING MADE.
WHEN YOU CALLED HIM, WHAT DID HE
SAY?
MIA: HE CALLED ME AT 11:00 THAT
MORNING.
IT WAS SUPER BOWL SUNDAY.
THE FIRST THING OUT OF HIS MOUTH
WAS, THANK GOD YOU ANSWERED.
I SAID, WHAT IS GOING ON.
HE WAS JUST REALLY DEPRESSED AND
DRINKING, JUST SOBBING ABOUT
OUR SON, SAYING -- AT ONE POINT,
HE JUST SAID, I WANT TO DIE.
AND I JUST -- I HAD A FEAR OF
DEATH, SO I WOULD REMEMBER, AND
HE WOULD SAY, YOU ARE RIGHT.
THEN I GOT REALLY PANICKED WHEN
HE SAID, HANG ON A SECOND.
JULIAN IS HERE.
DR. OZ: YOUR SON?
MIA: RIGHT.
AND I SAID NO.
NO HE IS NOT.
HE WANTS TO SEE HIM, BUT NOT
TODAY.
NOT TODAY, KRISTOFF.
HE SAID, IT'S OK.
HE'S COME TO TAKE ME FOR A WALK.
DR. OZ: YOUR SON COMMITTED
SUICIDE.
HE BELIEVED HE HAD COME TO GET
HIM.
MIA: TO TAKE HIM FOR A WALK.
SO I PANICKED.
I WAS LIKE TWO HOURS AWAY.
I DIDN'T KNOW IF I COULD GET TO
HIM IN TIME.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT HE WAS GOING
TO DO.
I STARTED CALLING HIS FAMILY.
HE WENT OVER THERE AND CALLED ME
AND SAID, NO ONE IS ANSWERING
THE DOOR.
I SAID, BREAK OPEN THE DAMN
DOOR.
GETTING THAT HOUSE NOW.
SO HE CALLED KRISTOFF'S SECOND
EX-WIFE, BECAUSE SHE LIVED
CLOSE, AND SHE GOT A KEY AND
CAME AND OPENED THE DOOR, AND
THEY FOUND HIM FACEDOWN.
THEY TRIED TO REVIVE HIM.
THEY CALLED 911.
WHEN SHE CALLED TO TELL ME, IT
WAS LIKE -- I JUST COULDN'T.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT.
IT WAS LIKE MY SON ALL OVER
AGAIN.
DR. OZ: ACCORDING TO THE LOS
ANGELES POLICE DEPARTMENT, A
DEATH INVESTIGATION TOOK PLACE
FOR A POSSIBLE ALCOHOL OVERDOSE.
THE CAUSE OF DEATH HAS BEEN
DEFERRED PENDING ADDITIONAL
RESULTS.
ALCOHOL CAN KILL YOU, BUT OTHER
MEANS CAN AS WELL.
WHAT DO YOU THINK REALLY
HAPPENED TO KRISTOFF?
MIA: I WANT TO BELIEVE THAT IT
WAS AN ALCOHOL ACCIDENTAL
OVERDOSE.
DR. OZ: HAVE YOU BEEN ABLE TO
STAY SOBER?
MIA: YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY NO.
I LOST MY 30 YEARS.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT, I JUST, I'M
NOT GIVING UP.
SO I START OVER AGAIN.
I PICKED MYSELF BACK UP, AND I'M
GOING TO CONTINUE MY PATH FOR
BETTER MENTAL HEALTH IN THIS
COUNTRY.
I'M GOING TO CONTINUE TO FIGHT
FOR IT.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: LET'S TALK ABOUT THAT.
BOTH OF YOUR BOYS, YOU COULD
ARGUE, WHERE FAILED BY THE
HEALTH CARE SYSTEM.
MIA: DEFINITELY.
DEFINITELY.
ULTIMATE FAILURE.
AND IF I JUST SIT AND DO
NOTHING, TO ME, THAT WOULD BE A
CRIME.
DR. OZ: YOU CAN CHANGE THE WORLD
.
WHAT IS HIS LEGACY?
MIA: I JUST WANT PEOPLE TO
REMEMBER HIM FOR HOW FUNNY AND
SWEET HE WAS.
PEOPLE DON'T KNOW THIS, BUT
BEFORE HE PASSED -- I WORKED
WITH HOMELESS YOUNG ADULTS AND
HE CAME TO THE SHELTER AND GAVE
FREE ACTING CLASSES TO
EVERYBODY.
THAT IS JUST HOW HE WAS.
I SAID, YOU ONLY HAVE TO SPEND
AN HOUR HERE.
HE SPENT THE WHOLE DAY.
HE WAS A GOOD PERSON.
DR. OZ: THE ULTIMATE LEGACY, TO
LEAVE BEHIND PEOPLE WHO LOVE YOU
BECAUSE YOU WERE KIND.
THANK YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪
DR. OZ: NEXT, THE CRAZY TEXT
MESSAGES YOU HAVE TO READ.
ARE YOU OVERSHARING?
(Sigh)
(Crunch)
Babybel:
That snack just sounded boring.
Coming through.
No photos, please.
Babybel:
Bye bye, bland.
Helloooo, delicious.
VO:
Rich, creamy, 100% real cheese.
VO: With Mini Babybel,
snack time is saved.
Babybel:
Saved it!
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
My name is
Elaine Barber,
and I'm a
five-year cancer survivor.
Surviving for five years
is a big deal.
I had so many people at CTCA
helping me find a way to go
through the treatments.
The reality of cancer is
not everybody survives.
At CTCA,
they have a huge
celebrate life event.
That was amazing
because the whole day
was about all of the survivors.
I'm excited about my future.
Learn more at
cancercenter.com/Philadelphia.
I'm excited about my future.
I'm not picking it up. You pick
it up!
I'm not picking it up.
I'll pick it up! They're clean!
♪'Cuz my hiney's clean.♪
♪Oh yeah I'm Charmin clean.♪
Charmin Ultra Strong just cleans
better.
It's time for the Ultimate
Sleep Number Event
on the Sleep Number
360 smart bed.
It senses your movement
and automatically adjusts
to keep you both comfortable.
Save 50% on the
Sleep Number 360
Limited Edition smart bed.
Plus, 24-month financing
on all smart beds.
Ends Sunday.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: THEY ARE ALL ABOUT
TEXTING THESE DAYS, WHETHER IT
IS A QUICK HELLO OR QUESTION,
SOMETIMES A RANDOM EMOJI, OR
SOME HEALTH ADVICE.
TODAY WE ARE EXPOSING THE
CRAZIEST TEXT MESSAGE
CONVERSATIONS THAT YOU HAVE TO
SEE TO BELIEVE.
LIKE THIS ONE.
>> I CUT MY FINGER ON THE
BLENDER.
CAN I STILL DRINK THE SMOOTHIE?
DR. OZ: THAT IS A HARD ONE.
SOMEONE IN THE AUDIENCE IS
NOTORIOUS FOR SENDING THESE
TYPES OF TEXT.
WHO BRAVELY VOLUNTEERED THIS
TEXT?
WOULD YOU STILL LOVE ME IF MY
BACK FUNGUS ATTACKED YOU IN YOUR
SLEEP?
THERE HE IS.
ROSS, HOW ARE YOU?
WELCOME TO THE SHOW.
A VERY BRAVE MAN.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: I'VE SEEN TEXTS LIKE
THAT ALL THE TIME IN MY FAMILY,
BUT YOU WENT ONE STEP FURTHER.
>> WE BOTH TRAVEL FOR WORK A LOT
THROUGHOUT THE COUNTRY.
WE ARE APART DURING THE WEEKS.
I GET TEXT MESSAGES FROM SARAH.
SOMETIMES I WORRY, BUT SHE'S A
LITTLE OVERDRAMATIC ABOUT MINOR
THINGS LIKE COCKROACHES OR
APPARENTLY THIS.
SHE'S A GOOD SPORT, SO I WANTED
TO BRING HER OUT HERE.
DR. OZ: SO I THOUGHT WE WOULD DO
TWO THINGS.
I'M GOING TO HELP YOU WITH THAT
PROBLEM YOU WERE COMPLAINING
ABOUT, BUT THIS IS ANOTHER TEXT.
I READ THIS TO MY WIFE LAST
NIGHT.
SHE GOT A KICK OUT OF IT.
I THOUGHT YOU COULD RECONNECT IT
FOR US.
>> SOS, WE ARE NEVER HAVING
KIDS.
DID YOU KNOW YOU POO WHILE YOU
ARE GIVING BIRTH?
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> APPARENTLY IT IS SOMETHING
EVERYONE BUT ME SEEMS TO KNOW.
MAYBE IT IS SOME SECRET THAT
PARENTS KEEP THE TRIP THERE KIDS
INTO HAVING KIDS.
>> THAT IS HILARIOUS, BUT SOUNDS
LIKE A SMALL PRICE TO PAY FOR
HAVING A KID.
>> EASY FOR HIM TO SAY.
DR. OZ: SO GIVE ME THE BACK
STORY ON THIS MESSAGE THAT YOU
TEXTED HIM THAT GOT YOU ON THIS
SHOW.
WOULD YOU STILL LOVE ME IF MY
BACK FUNGUS ATTACKED YOU IN YOUR
SLEEP?
SOMETHING WAS GOING ON HERE.
>> IT REALLY IS NOT SOME SEXY
FUNGUS YOU MIGHT IMAGINE.
IT WAS JUST THESE SPOTS ON MY
BACK.
DR. OZ: HERE IS WHAT THE RASH
LOOK LIKE.
>> THIS IS WHEN MY FRIEND
NOTICED IT.
I THOUGHT NOTHING OF IT AFTER
THE DRAMATIC TEXT.
MY FRIEND SAID SHE KNEW WHAT IT
WAS BECAUSE ONE OF HER FRIENDS
EXPERIENCED IT.
SO I GOT IT CHECKED OUT.
IT WAS OK.
DR. OZ: DID THEY TELL YOU IT WAS
--
>> THAT IS WHAT THEY SAID.
DR. OZ: THAT IS FROM A FUNGUS
THAT IS VERY BENIGN.
IT GROWS MORE IN SOME PEOPLE
THAN OTHERS.
YOU ARE JUST KEEPING IT DRY,
MAYBE ANTIFUNGAL CREAM.
>> THEY GAVE ME A SHAMPOO TO PUT
ON.
DR. OZ: DID IT EVER ATTACK ROSS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
DID IT?
>> IT DID NOT.
DR. OZ: NOT YET.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN MARRIED?
>> A YEAR AND A HALF.
DR. OZ: KEEP SENDING THE TEXT.
GOOD LUCK WITH BABIES.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: NEXT, OUR ADDICTED
SERIES CONTINUES.
WE ARE TAKING ON SCARY CELL
PHONE ADDICTION.
THERE'S A QUIZ YOU CA'S A QUIZ N
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
[ remote bloop ]
Show me The Crown.
Show me Homecoming.
[ remote bloop ]
Baby sloth videos on YouTube.
Amy, do you uh, mind
giving someone else a turn?
Oh, oh yeah I made myself
a little comfortable here.
I got a pizza for Amy.
Yes! That's me.
Xfinity lets you search Netflix,
Prime Video and YouTube
with the sound of your voice.
And I don't have
my wallet, so...
That's simple, easy, awesome.
Switch to Xfinity and get
started with this great offer.
Plus, ask about 4K Ultra HD and
packages that include Netflix.
Click, call, or visit
a store today.
When you're expecting
a little angel, be soft.
When your little angel
expects a lot from you...
You gotta be kidding
me, little dude.
be strong.
Life takes softness
and strength.
That's why we make
Angel Soft Mega with more
of the value you already love.
PHONE?
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT
ADDICTION WITH TEXTING.
EVERY MINUTE AND ESTIMATED 15
MILLION TEXT MESSAGES ARE SENT
AROUND THE WORLD.
PART OF A BIGGER HEALTH PROBLEM
I THINK EVERY ONE OF US MAY BE
DEALING WITH TO SOME DEGREE.
CELL PHONE ADDICTION.
HERE'S MY AUDIENCE, COOKED TO
THEIR PHONES BEFORE THE SHOW.
WE ARE ALL GUILTY OF IT.
WE GET THAT URGE TO LOOK AT
FACEBOOK, INSTAGRAM, 10 TIMES AN
HOUR.
IN THE MIDDLE OF A CONVERSATION,
WE CHECK OUR EMAIL OR SEND A
TEXT, WATCH VIDEO, TAKE SELFIES.
WE GET LOST FOR HOURS, HOPED
LIKE ZOMBIES.
IT IS TIME WE ALL TAKE A LOOK TO
SEE IF WE ARE ADDICTED.
THINK OF IT AS A WAKE-UP CALL.
AN ESTIMATED 270 MILLION
AMERICANS OWN SMARTPHONES.
STATISTICS SHOW WE ARE SPENDING
MORE TIME ON THEM THAN EVER.
CHECKING THEM AN AVERAGE 52
TIMES A DAY AND OVER ONE THIRD
OF US LABEL OUR SMARTPHONE USE
AS EXCESSIVE.
BUT COULD THIS HIGH TECH TREND
COME AT A COST TO OUR MENTAL AND
PHYSICAL HEALTH, AND OUR IN
PERSON RELATIONSHIPS?
IT IS A REAL WORRY FOR BELINDA,
WHO HAS BEEN MARRIED TO ERIC FOR
15 YEARS.
>> MAYBE AROUND THE 11TH YEAR OF
OUR MARRIAGE, DURING OUR DATE
NIGHT, HE STARTED SPENDING A LOT
OF TIME ON HIS PHONE, NOT BEING
ENGAGED AND GIVING ME HIS FULL
ATTENTION.
HE WAS STILL WORKING.
EMAILS, PHONE CALLS, VIDEOS,
DOING HIS PERSONAL DEVELOPMENT
DURING OUR TIME.
I DON'T LIKE TO REPEAT MY
CONVERSATION OVER AND OVER.
>> HERE'S WHAT I DO KNOW.
I AM NOT ADDICTED TO MY PHONE.
I AM A COACH.
I AM A SINGER.
NO ADDICTION.
DR. OZ: BELINDA DISAGREES.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER IF WE ARE
AT DINNER, AT THE GYM, GOING
SHOPPING, BEFORE A PLAY,
WHEREVER WE ARE, HE HAS THAT
PHONE IN HIS HAND AND HE'S
ENGAGED IN IT.
DR. OZ: BELINDA AND HER HUSBAND
ARE JOINING US NOW.
HOW MANY HOURS A DAY DO YOU
THINK THIS WONDERFUL MAN USES
HIS CELL PHONE?
>> AT LEAST 14.
DR. OZ: WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
THAT?
YOU USE YOUR PHONE 14 HOURS A
DAY?
>> NO.
NOT AT ALL.
WHO COULD BE ON THE PHONE 14
HOURS A DAY?
I'M A STYLIST AND A SINGER.
NO.
>> 14 HOURS A DAY.
DR. OZ: I CAN ATTEST TO WOMEN.
THEY TELL ME THE TRUTH.
WE GOT 14 HOURS, WE DON'T THINK
IT IS 14, BUT HOW MANY HOURS?
>> MAYBE SIX.
DR. OZ: DO YOU THINK -- >> NO, I
DON'T.
DR. OZ: THERE HAVE BEEN FISSURES
IN YOUR RELATIONSHIP.
FOR EXAMPLE?
>> WHEN EVER WE ARE DOING
SOMETHING THAT WE SET OUT FOR
OUR TIME, HE'S ENGAGED IN THE
PHONE.
DR. OZ: DO YOU THINK SHE'S RIGHT
TO BE A LITTLE ANGRY?
>> I THINK SHE HAS A RIGHT TO BE
ANGRY OR DISAPPOINTED.
IF THAT WERE THE TRUTH.
DR. OZ: BUT YOU DON'T THINK IT
IS AN ISSUE.
OK, JUST FOR NOW, I THINK A LOT
OF US ARE RIGHT WHERE YOU ARE.
I'M NOT QUITE SURE.
I KNOW I'M USING IT A LOT.
I DON'T KNOW IF I'M INTERFERING
WITH PEOPLE AROUND ME.
WHAT YOU JUST SAID, THAT HAPPENS
ALL THE TIME.
I HAVE DEVON AND MACKENZIE IN
THE AUDIENCE.
THEY ARE BEST FRIENDS.
THEY ARE CONSTANTLY ARGUING OVER
CELL PHONE USE.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: MACKENZIE, WHAT IS SAM
DOING THAT IS BOTHERING YOU?
>> SAM IS ALWAYS ON HER PHONE.
DOESN'T MATTER IF WE ARE AT
LUNCH, DINNER, GETTING DRINKS.
SHE'S ALWAYS ON HER PHONE.
IT IS NOT JUST ME THAT SEES THIS
AS A PROBLEM.
IT IS ALSO HER KIDS, HER FAMILY.
IT GOT SO BAD, I HAD TO TAKE THE
PHONE AWAY.
DR. OZ: YOU IMPOUNDED THE PHONE.
SAM, DO YOU THINK YOU HAVE A
PROBLEM?
>> I DON'T THINK I HAVE AN
ADDICTION.
I USE MY CELL PHONE A LOT FOR
WORK.
IT IS IMPERATIVE AS AN EVENT
PLANNER.
I RUN SEVERAL FACEBOOK AND
INSTAGRAM PAGES AND I HAVE TO
CONNECT WITH MY EMPLOYEES.
I DON'T REALLY THINK IT IS A
PROBLEM.
DR. OZ: IF IT IS A PROBLEM, AND
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU A QUIZ TO
FIND OUT IF WE GOT AN ISSUE, ARE
YOU WILLING TO GET HELP?
>> DEFINITELY.
DR. OZ: YOU CARE ABOUT THE
PEOPLE IN YOUR LIVES.
>> LIGHT.
DR. OZ: WE HAVE TWO OF THE
WORLD'S LEADING EXPERTS ON CELL
PHONE ADDICTION.
DR. DAVID GREENFIELD IS A
MEDICAL PSYCHOLOGIST.
CATHERINE PRICE IS A SCIENCE
JOURNALIST AND THE AUTHOR OF HOW
TO BREAK UP WITH YOUR PHONE.
DR. GREENFIELD BELIEVES WE ARE
SPENDING TIME ON OUR CELL PHONE
AND THAT IS HAVING A BAD EFFECT
ON OUR BODIES.
DR. GREENFIELD: THE IDEA IS THAT
WHEN YOU USE YOUR SMART PHONE,
YOU ARE ELEVATING DOPAMINE,
WHICH IS A PLEASURE CHEMICAL.
AT THE SAME TIME, YOU ARE
ELEVATING CORTISOL, WHICH IS A
STRESS HORMONE.
IT LEAVES YOU FEELING DEPLETED
AND DISCONNECTED AND UNHAPPY.
DR. OZ: WHAT IS HAPPENING TO OUR
ATTENTION SPAN?
WHAT IS HAPPENING TO OUR FOCUS?
CATHERINE: THE PHONES ARE HAVING
A HUGE EFFECT ON OUR ABILITY TO
STAY FOCUSED.
WE ARE NOT DOING ONE THING ON
THE PHONE.
WE ARE DOING APPS, SOCIAL MEDIA,
ALL THESE THINGS.
EVERY TIME YOU DO THAT, YOU ARE
CHANGING YOUR BRAIN.
THAT HAS IMPACTS ON
PRODUCTIVITY.
STUDIES SHOW THAT HAVING THE
PHONE NEARBY CAN MAKE IT MORE
DIFFICULT TO COMPLETE A TASK.
THEY ARE ALSO DISTRACTING US
FROM OUR EXTERNAL ENVIRONMENT,
WHICH NOT ONLY TAKES AWAY FROM
OUR EXPERIENCE OF OUR LIVES, BUT
CAN HAVE HARM TO US.
I WAS ONCE WALKING DOWN THE
STREET LOST IN MY PHONE I DID
NOT SEE A MAN COMING TOWARD ME
WITH A GUN.
I WAS MUGGED FOR MY PHONE.
THERE'S MANY WAYS IN WHICH THEY
ARE AFFECTING OUR LIVES.
DR. OZ: ARE YOU OK, ERIC?
>> THAT SWITCHED IT.
DR. OZ: SO YOU'VE GOT A CELL
PHONE COMPULSION QUIZ.
ARE YOU COMPULSIVELY USING IT?
YOU CAN ALL TAKE IT.
PLUS, A SIMPLE TRICK THAT WILL
HELP YOU BREAK THIS ADDICTION,
NEXT.
Oats and oat bran
have a soluble fiber
called beta-glucan,
which can help
lower cholesterol
as part of
a heart-healthy diet.
Now it's in new
Quaker Oat Beverage,
a super-smooth
dairy alternative.
DR. OZ: WE ARE BACK, TALKING
ABOUT A PROBLEM WE JOKE ABOUT,
BUT IT IS QUITE SERIOUS.
CELL PHONE ADDICTION.
BELINDA AND ERIC ARE CONSTANTLY
FIGHTING OVER HIS CELL PHONE
USE.
MACKENZIE AND SAM ARE DEALING
WITH THE SAME ISSUE.
ARE YOU READY FOR SOME HELP?
THE FIRST PART IS TO FIGURE OUT
IF YOU NEED IT.
WHICH WE HAVE A DEBATE OVER NOW.
ERIC SAYS HE IS BUSY WORKING ALL
DAY LONG.
SAM, YOU ARE SAYING YOU HAVE TO
DO YOUR WORK.
WE HAVE TWO OF THE WORLD'S
LEADING EXPERTS HERE.
CATHERINE PRICE IS BACK AND DR.
DAVID GREENFIELD, WHO HAS
CREATED A CELL PHONE COMPULSION
TEST.
DURING THE BREAK, OUR GUESTS AND
THE ENTIRE STUDIO AUDIENCE TOOK
THIS TEST.
YOU CAN FIND IT ON DOCTOROZ.COM.
I URGE YOU TO GIVE IT TO PEOPLE
IN YOU LIFE WHO YOU THINK ARE
ADDICTED TO THEIR CELL PHONES.
FIVE QUESTIONS RIGHT NOW.
FIRST QUESTION, DO YOU SLEEP
WITH YOUR PHONE TURNED ON UNDER
YOUR PILLOW OR NEXT TO YOUR BED?
ONLY YOU KNOW THE TRUTH.
WHAT IS THE IMPORTANCE OF THAT
QUESTION?
DR. GREENFIELD: WHEN YOU HAVE
THE PHONE NEXT TO YOU, IF IT IS
IN YOUR SITE, YOUR CORTISOL
LEVELS ARE GOING TO BE RAISED.
THAT IS GOING TO WORK
ANTITHETICAL HE TO YOUR DESIRE
TO FEEL SLEEPY.
IT IS GOING TO SCREW UP YOUR
CIRCADIAN RHYTHM.
DR. OZ: DO YOU TEXT OR EMAIL
WHILE DRIVING OR DOING OTHER
ACTIVITIES THAT REQUIRE
CONCENTRATION?
WHEN YOU EAT, IS YOUR CELL PHONE
ALWAYS PARKED ON THE TABLE PLACE
SETTING?
IN THE RESTAURANTS WE SEE IT A
LOT.
DO YOU FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE WHEN
YOU ACCIDENTALLY LEAVE YOUR
PHONE IN THE CAR OR AT HOME AND
HAVE NO SERVICE?
AND FINALLY, DO YOU MINDLESSLY
CHECK YOUR CELL PHONE MANY TIMES
A DAY, EVEN WHEN THERE IS
NOTHING NEW TO SEE?
I WANT TO KNOW, HOW MANY OF YOU
ANSWERED YES TO MOST OF THESE
QUESTIONS?
OH MY GOODNESS.
LIKE 90% OF THE AUDIENCE.
THAT IS UNBELIEVABLE.
WHAT DOES IT MEAN THAT YOU ARE
ANSWERING THREE OR MORE OF THOSE
FIVE QUESTIONS?
DR. GREENFIELD: AS YOU SAW, I
RAISED MY OWN HAND.
MOST OF US CAN PROBABLY ANSWER
THESE QUESTIONS POSITIVELY.
IT PROBABLY JUST MEANS YOU NEED
TO LOOK AT YOUR USE AND EXAMINE
IT.
WE ARE USING OUR PHONES
MINDLESSLY AND WITHOUT
AWARENESS.
THE IDEA IS TO BECOME AWARE OF
OUR USED PATTERNS.
DR. OZ: ERIC, DID YOUR HAND GO
OF?
>> YES.
DR. OZ: I THOUGHT SO.
IT WAS UP AFTER THE FIRST PAGE.
>> I WASN'T GOING TO SAY
ANYTHING.
DR. OZ: ON NATIONAL TELEVISION.
AND SAM, DID YOUR HAND GO UP?
>> IT DID.
DR. OZ: I THOUGHT SO.
LET'S GO THROUGH SOME SIMPLE
STEPS WE CAN DO RIGHT NOW TO CUT
DOWN ON OUR CELL PHONE USE.
THE FIRST THING WE ARE GOING TO
DO IS, YOU KNOW IT IS SO
BEAUTIFUL AND COLORFUL.
TURN IT TO BLACK AND WHITE.
WHY DOES THAT WORK?
CATHERINE: THE OVERALL POINT IS
TO MAKE YOUR PHONE A TOOL, NOT A
TEMPTATION.
IT IS HELPFUL BECAUSE WE ARE
ATTRACTED TO BRIGHT COLORS.
YOU CAN LOOK IN THE PHONE
SETTINGS OR DO AN INTERNET
SEARCH FOR YOUR MODEL TO FIGURE
OUT HOW TO DO IT.
ANOTHER THING I RECOMMEND IS,
TAKE YOUR TEMPTING APPS, SOCIAL
MEDIA, NEWS, PUT THEM IN A
FOLDER.
MAKE YOUR PHONE AS BORING AS
POSSIBLE.
DR. OZ: FANTASTIC.
THE FINAL TIP IS TO TURN OFF AS
MANY NOTIFICATIONS AS POSSIBLE.
I THINK THIS IS THE MOST
IMPORTANT.
IN MY OWN PERSONAL LIFE, IT HAS
BEEN IMPACTFUL.
DR. GREENFIELD: NOTIFICATIONS
ARE THE KEY.
THE SMARTPHONE IS THE WORLD'S
SMALLEST SLOT MACHINE.
EVERY TIME YOU CHECK YOUR PHONE,
YOU GET A HINT OF DOPAMINE.
NOTIFICATIONS LET YOU KNOW THAT
THE DRUG IS THERE.
THIS IS SUCH A BIG ISSUE.
WE ARE ABOUT TO OPEN A PROGRAM
FOR PEOPLE ADDICTED TO THIS
SCREEN.
DR. OZ: AN INPATIENT ADDICTION
CENTER FOR ADDICTS?
DR. GREENFIELD: YES.
DR. OZ: DO YOU FEEL ANY OF THESE
TOOLS MIGHT COME IN HANDY FOR
YOU?
>> YES.
[LAUGHTER]
DR. OZ: WELL, BELINDA --
>> WHERE IS THE PLACE?
IS IT GOING TO BE REALLY NICE?
AND WHERE IS THE LADY THAT TOOK
MY CELL PHONE?
[LAUGHTER]
DR. GREENFIELD: YOU ARE WATCHING
THAT, WAITING FOR THAT.
DR. OZ: I DIDN'T GET ANYTHING
FROM YOU.
WHAT IS GOING DOWN, ERIC?
>> IN MY DEFENSE, MY WIFE HAS
CELL PHONE, LAPTOP, TABLET, AND
DESKTOP.
I ONLY HAVE MY PHONE, WHICH IS
USED FOR ALL OF THAT.
BUT OF COURSE I'M A MAN AND SHE
IS RIGHT.
[LAUGHTER]
DR. OZ: THANK YOU.
I LOVE IT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
DR. OZ: WHEN I FIRST GOT
MARRIED, MY FATHER-IN-LAW TOLD
ME TO GET INTO MY WIFE ON THE
SMALL THINGS, BECAUSE WHEN THE
BIG DECISIONS CAME UP, I NEEDED
TO KNOW WHAT IT FELT LIKE.
I WASN'T GETTING THOSE EITHER.
WHAT ABOUT YOU GUYS?
>> THE THOUGHT OF ACTUALLY GOING
TO A REHAB FREAKS ME OUT.
BUT I WANT TO GIVE MORE TIME TO
MY FAMILY AND MY KIDS SO I'M
DEFINITELY GOING TO USE THOSE
TIPS.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: GOOD FOR YOU.
NICE JOB, MACKENZIE.
THANKS TO ALL OF YOU.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: STAY TUNED FOR ANOTHER
INSTALLMENT OF OUR ADDICTED
SERIES.
THIS TIME, PERMANENT MAKEUP.
WOMEN ACROSS THE COUNTRY ARE
GETTING PROCEDURES WEAR MAKEUP
IS PERMANENTLY PUT ON THEIR
FACE.
PERMANENTLY PUT ON THEIR
♪Inside out
got it figured out♪
FACE.
♪I'm feeling good♪
♪And it feels good♪
♪to feel good♪
Sunsweet Amazin! Prunes.
The Feel Good Fruit.
Oats and oat bran
have a soluble fiber
called beta-glucan,
which can help
lower cholesterol
as part of
a heart-healthy diet.
Now it's in new
Quaker Oat Beverage,
a super-smooth
dairy alternative.
Now it's in new
Quaker Oat Beverage,
Woman:
I've been saying, "I'm fine."
But, really
I'm struggling to keep
up this brave face
to hide my symptoms
of depression.
I'm taking my antidepressant,
like we discussed.
But, I'm still
feeling depressed.
Is it just me?
Doctor: It's not just you.
Two out of three people
on antidepressants
may still
experience symptoms.
When added to an
antidepressant,
REXULTI has been proven
to help reduce
symptoms of depression.
Woman:
So I can stay on my
current antidepressant
and help build on
the progress I've made.
Hey, guys.
(Mixed greetings)
REXULTI is not for everyone.
Call your doctor about
unusual changes in behavior,
worsening depression,
or thoughts of suicide.
Antidepressants
can increase these
in those 24 and younger.
Elderly dementia
patients taking REXULTI
have an increased risk
of death or stroke.
Call your doctor if
you have high fever,
stiff muscles, and confusion
to address a possible
life-threatening condition
or if you have uncontrollable
muscle movements,
as these may be permanent.
REXULTI has been shown
to increase blood sugar
in some people.
Other risks are increased
cholesterol; weight gain;
unusual urges
or compulsive behaviors;
decreased white blood cells,
which can be serious;
dizziness on standing;
seizures; trouble swallowing;
and impaired judgment
or motor skills.
Now, I'm glad I talked
with my doctor
about adding REXULTI.
Feel better about
facing the world.
Pay $0 for your first
REXULTI prescription.
Details at REXULTI.com.
RESULTS AND REGRETS.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: ALL WEEK LONG, WE'VE
BEEN BRINGING YOU STORIES ABOUT
ADDICTION.
TODAY, A TREND THAT HAS GROWN IN
POPULARITY, PERMANENT MAKEUP.
MY TEAM RESEARCH ON INSTAGRAM
AND FOUND OVER 3 MILLION POSTS
ABOUT PERMANENT MAKEUP TATTOOED
ON EYEBROWS OR EYELIDS.
THIS IS INK EMBEDDED INTO THE
FACE.
IT CAN LOOK NATURAL AS IF YOU'VE
JUST APPLY MAKEUP IF IT IS DONE
RIGHT.
BUT NOT EVERYONE HAS BEEN SO
LUCKY.
SOME WOMEN HAVE BEEN BOTCHED.
LOOK AT THIS ONE.
THE ARTIST DREW THE EYEBROWS
BADLY.
YOU DON'T NORMALLY HAVE TWO
PAIRS OF DUPLICATE EYEBROWS.
THIS ONE, THE PERMANENT EYELINER
IS DISCOLORED.
YOU ARE BETTER OFF DOING IT
YOURSELF.
AND THESE LIPS LOOK TO BE
INFECTED TO ME.
DEFINITELY NOT FILLED IN
PROPERLY.
INVESTIGATIVE REPORTER TIA BROWN
IS HERE WITH MORE.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: I LOOK AT THESE PICTURES
AND I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW THESE
PEOPLE GOT HURT.
WHAT IS PERMANENT MAKEUP?
TIA: IT IS BASICALLY A TATTOO ON
YOUR FACE.
WE ARE SEEING PEOPLE GETTING IT
ON THEIR EYE LINE, THEIR
EYEBROWS.
THEY WANT TO HAVE THAT FRESH
MADE UP LOOK ALL THE TIME.
PEOPLE ARE GETTING IT ON THEIR
EYEBROWS.
THEY EVEN GET IT ON THEIR LIPS.
THAT IS THE EYELINER RIGHT
THERE.
BEAUTICIANS DO IT.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS IT IS
SOMETHING THAT PEOPLE ARE DOING
FOR VANITY.
DR. OZ: ARE THERE DANGERS?
I JUST SAW SOME OF THE COSMETIC
COMPLICATIONS.
TIA: THERE'S A BIG COMPLICATION,
INFECTION.
YOU CAN GET INFECTIONS.
YOU CAN GET SCARRING.
THAT IS A BIG DEAL.
PEOPLE ARE USING DIRTY NEEDLES.
THEY ARE NOT DEALING WITH
LICENSED PROFESSIONALS.
IT IS NOT SOMETHING TO PLAY
WITH.
DR. OZ: THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
GETTING MAKEUP THAT IS PERMANENT
AND GETTING A TATTOO.
I'VE BEEN CURIOUS FOR A WHILE.
WHEN YOU GET PERMANENT MAKEUP,
THERE'S A ROTARY MACHINE.
A NEEDLE GOES BENEATH THE
EPIDERMIS, ONE LAYER BELOW TO
THE DERMIS.
SEE THAT?
WHEN YOU GO THERE, YOU CAN LEAVE
PIGMENT THAT CAN LAST UP TO FIVE
YEARS.
WHEN YOU GET A TATTOO, A LITTLE
DIFFERENT.
A TATTOO NEEDLE, TECHNICIANS USE
A COILED MACHINE WITH A BIGGER
NEEDLE, AND THAT NEEDLE GOES
DEEPLY INTO THE HYPO DERMIS.
BENEATH THE SUPERFICIAL LAYER.
IT GOES LOWER INTO THE SKIN.
FOR THAT REASON, IT SHOULD LAST
A LIFETIME.
BOTH TECHNIQUES ARE SORT OF
PERMANENT, IDEALLY.
ON THE MAKEUP SIDE, FIVE YEARS
TO ME IS PERMANENT.
THE QUESTION IS, ARE YOU GETTING
THESE PROCEDURES DONE BY THE
RIGHT PEOPLE AT THE RIGHT PLACE?
LET ME SHOW YOU A PICTURE OF
SOMEONE WHO HAS A REGRET.
THIS IS VICTORIA.
SHE DECIDED TO GET A PERMANENT
EYEBROW DONE.
IT ENDED UP LOOKING LIKE THIS.
HER BROWS LOOK SOMEWHAT MAGENTA
COLORED WHICH IS NOT WHAT SHE
DESIRED.
LUCKILY SHE WAS ABLE TO GET THEM
CORRECTED AND SHE IS JOINING US
TO TELL HER STORY.
HOW ARE YOU?
THANKS FOR THE SUNGLASSES TO
CAMOUFLAGE YOU.
I WOULD LOVE TO SEE WHAT YOUR
BROWS LOOK LIKE NOW.
>> YOU BET.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: OH.
WELL CONGRATULATIONS.
BEFORE I GET TO HAVE YOU FIXED
THEM, WHY DID YOU CHOOSE TO GET
PERMANENT MAKEUP IN THE FIRST
PLACE?
>> UNFORTUNATELY I WAS NOT
BLESSED WITH BEAUTIFUL BUSHY
BROWS.
MY EYEBROWS ARE COMPLETELY
BLONDE SINCE THE DAY I WAS BORN.
AND SO EVERY DAY I WOULD HAVE TO
PUT ON MAKEUP TO EVEN GIVE
MYSELF THE EFFECT OF HAVING A
BROW.
DR. OZ: WHAT HAPPENED WHEN YOU
WENT TO GET THE PERMANENT
EYEBROWS DONE?
>> I HAVE RESEARCHED THIS
PERMANENT MAKEUP ARTIST.
I HAD LOOKED AT HER REVIEWS
ONLINE.
I HAD LOOKED AT THE BEFORE AND
AFTER.
SHE WAS A SEEMINGLY REPUTABLE
ARTIST.
DR. OZ: WHEN DO YOU REALIZE
SOMETHING WAS WRONG ESTON MARK
-- WRONG?
>> I REALIZED THE INK COLOR SHE
HAD CHOSEN WAS OBVIOUSLY WRONG
FOR MY FACE.
I WAS MORTIFIED.
DR. OZ: ANY BOTCHED PROCEDURE IS
A NIGHTMARE, ESPECIALLY WHEN THE
EVIDENCE IS ON YOUR FACE.
WERE YOU ABLE TO FIND SOMEONE TO
FIX THE PROBLEM?
YOU LOOK SO MUCH BETTER.
YOU STREAMED THE PROCEDURE LIVE
ON FACEBOOK.
HOW DOES IT FEEL TO HAVE YOUR
EYEBROWS LOOK THE WAY YOU WANT
THEM TO?
>> I WAS GRATEFUL THAT ANYBODY
WOULD TOUCH THEM.
I CONTACTED PROFESSIONALS IN NEW
YORK AND CALIFORNIA AND ASKED
AND THEY SAID THEY WOULDN'T
TOUCH THEM FOR UP TO A YEAR
BECAUSE OF THE INK THAT WAS IN
MY SKIN.
THEY WERE WORRIED IT WOULD HAVE
AN ADVERSE REACTION.
I DID FIND A MAKEUP ARTIST OR A
PERMANENT ARTIST HERE, BUT I
TOLD HER I WOULD SIGN AWAY ANY
DISCLAIMERS, BUT I WOULD BE OK
WITH GRAY EYEBROWS OVER RED.
I WAS SEEING UNICORN EYEBROWS.
I EVEN HAD PEOPLE ASK IF I HAD
CANCER BECAUSE THEY LOOKED SO
INAPPROPRIATE ON MY FACE.
DR. OZ: WHAT ADVICE WOULD YOU
GIVE TO SOMEONE THINKING ABOUT
PERMANENT MAKEUP?
>> ONE OF THE BIGGEST THINGS
I'VE LEARNED IS TO NOT JUST LOOK
FOR BEFORE AND AFTER.
GO BACK FOR A ONE-MONTH TOUCHUP
ALWAYS.
LOOK FOR THAT FOLLOW-UP AFTER
THE ONE-MONTH TOUCHUP.
LOOK FOR SOMEONE THAT HAS THREE
PICTURES.
BEFORE, AFTER, AND THE
FOLLOW-UP.
DR. OZ: THANK YOU FOR SHARING
YOUR STORY.
I'M GLAD IT FINALLY WORKED OUT.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: TINA WANTED TO
INVESTIGATE FURTHER.
SHE MADE AN APPOINTMENT AT ONE
OF THESE CLINICS FOR A
CONSULTATION.
Our grandparents checked
their smartphones
zero times a day.
Times change.
Eyes haven't.
That's why there's Ocuvite.
Screen light...
Sunlight...
Longer hours...
Eyes today are stressed.
But Ocuvite has vital
nutrients...
...to help protect them.
Ocuvite.
Eye nutrition for today.
The in-laws have moved in
with us.
And our adult children are here.
So we save by using Tide.
Which means we use less.
Three generations of clothes
cleaned in one wash.
Anybody seen my pants?
#1 stain and odor fighter, #1
trusted.
It's got to be Tide.
Is your dry skin cream not doing
enough?
Try Eucerin Advanced Repair
cream.
For 48hour dry skin relief...
Goes beyond ceramides with
moisturizing factors
naturally found in skin...
Eucerin Advanced Repair Cream
For healthier looking skin.
(Cat 1) Friskies World...
(Cat 2) Smell that?
(Cat 1) Gravy!
(Cat 2) That's not gravy, that's
extra gravy.
(Cat 1) Whoa!
(Cat 2) That's Friskies
Extra Gravy! Paté and Chunky!
(Cat 1) Gravy purr-adise.
(Cat 2) Purr-adise? Really?
(VO) Feed Their Fantasy.
Friskies.
You're not just Mom
you're her whole world.
Don't just get away, come
together.
(Sigh)
(Crunch)
Babybel:
That snack just sounded boring.
Coming through.
No photos, please.
Babybel:
Bye bye, bland.
Helloooo, delicious.
VO:
Rich, creamy, 100% real cheese.
VO: With Mini Babybel,
snack time is saved.
Babybel:
Saved it!
TIA: I'VE BEEN DOING RESEARCH ON
PERMANENT MAKEUP.
YOU CAN GET YOUR LIPS, YOUR EYE
LINE, EVEN YOUR EYEBROWS.
BUT YOU CAN ALSO GET SCARRED FOR
LIFE.
I DECIDED TO CHECK OUT A FEW
PLACES.
I'M ABOUT TO GO IN.
I'M BACK.
EVERYTHING I ASKED, SHE HAD AN
ANSWER FOR.
SHE HAD CERTIFICATION.
SHE TOLD ME THE PRICE WAS $500
FOR THE FIRST VISIT.
$120 FOR EVERY FOLLOW-UP.
SHE EVEN SAID AFTERCARE AND MY
HEALTH WAS ON ME.
THE BIGGEST THING, SHE SAID I
COULD COME BACK TOMORROW AND GET
MY LIPS, BROWSE, OR EYE LINE
DONE.
I'M NOT SURE I'M READY FOR THAT
COMMITMENT.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: THAT WAS TIA GOING FOR A
CONSULTATION TO GET PERMANENT
MAKEUP.
WERE THERE ANY RED FLAGS?
TIA: I THINK THE BIGGEST THING
IS THAT THERE'S THIS RUSH TO
COMMIT.
YOU SHOP AROUND FOR A CAR OR
SHOES.
PERMANENT MAKEUP HAS A LONG
EFFECT ON YOUR LIFE.
DON'T RUSH.
DR. OZ: SO WE FOUND A CERTIFIED
SPECIALIST IN THE CITY, ROCHELLE
, WHO IS WORKING ON A CLIENT.
WHAT SHOULD FOLKS BE LOOKING FOR
WHEN THEY MEET SOMEONE LIKE YOU?
ROCHELLE: FIRST THING YOU SHOULD
DO IS DO YOUR RESEARCH.
FIND SOMEONE THAT IS LICENSED,
CERTIFIED.
ASK FOR PHOTOS, BEFORE AND AFTER
AS WELL.
AND DON'T BE AFRAID TO ASK FOR A
REFERRAL.
DR. OZ: I SEE A FAIR AMOUNT OF
EFFORT JUST PLANNING OUT WHAT
YOU'RE GOING TO DO, LIKE A
SURGEON.
ROCHELLE: THIS IS WHAT WE DO.
DR. OZ: YOU MUST SEE SOME
COMPLICATIONS, BOTCHED JOBS.
ROCHELLE: YES.
WE HAVE QUITE A FEW THAT COME.
PEOPLE ARE COMING IN FROM LAS
VEGAS.
THEY ASK US, AND YOU DO A
CONSULTATION FOR CORRECTION?
DR. OZ: I'LL LET YOU GET
STARTED.
IN THE MEANTIME, DO YOUR
HOMEWORK.
THIS IS FIVE YEARS OF LOOKING
DIFFERENT.
TOGETHER, CHANGE IS HAPPENING.
OUR JOURNEY IS JUST BEGINNING.
GOOD LUCK.
[CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY THE
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE,
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTION CONTENT AND ACCURACY.
VI
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com