>> Announcer: LIVE FROM
NEW YORK CITY, IT'S
"THE WENDY WILLIAMS SHOW."
♪ ♪
>> NOW, HERE ARE TODAY'S HOT
TALKERS!
B1 HELLO!
I FEEL LIKE WE SHOULD DO A CONGA
LINE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
OH, HELLO!
WELCOME TO "THE WENDY WILLIAMS
SHOW."
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
I'M CARSON KRESSLEY, HOST OF
BRAVO'S "GET A ROOM."
SAILOR TO ACTRESS AND TV
PERSONALITY, TAMMY ROMAN!
HQ TO BE HOST, SHARON CARPENTER!
AND POP EXPERT INTO PERSONALITY,
BRIAN BALTHAZAR!
ALL RIGHT!
SHOW WE DIVE INTO HOT TOPICS
DUES YOU ARE?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THE SUPER BOWL IS THIS SUNDAY.
I HAD NO IDEA.
IT'S THE NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS
VERSUS THE L.A. RAMS.
I THINK I LIKE THE RAMS!
MAROON 5 IS DOING THE HALFTIME
SHOW.
THAT'S WHERE MY INTEREST PEAKS.
HALFTIME SHOW, I WATCH.
THE NFL ANNOUNCED THAT THE GROUP
WILL NOT PARTICIPATE IN THE
TRADITIONAL PREGAME PRESS
CONFERENCE, SAYING THE ARTISTS
WILL LET THEIR SHOW DO THE
TALKING.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
WHAT GIVES?
DO THINK IT'S WEIRD?
SHOULD THEY HAVE CANCELED THAT?
>> Tami: EDIFICATION TO
CANCELED IT.
>> Sharon: I DON'T THINK THEY
SHOULD'VE CANCELED IT.
I THINK IT WAS THEIR OPPORTUNITY
COME AFTER ALL THE BACKLASH, TO
GET OUT IN FRONT OF THE
CONTROVERSY BEFORE THE HALFTIME
SHOW.
IF THEY REALLY FEEL THEY MADE
THE RIGHT DECISION BY AGREEING
TO DO IT, THEY SHOULD BE AFRAID
TO SPEAK ON IT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Carson: I AGREE.
>> Brian: THIS IS THE FIRST
THROUGH THAT PRESS CONFERENCE
WOULD HAVE BEEN INTERESTING AT
ALL.
EVERY YEAR, "WE HAVE A GREAT
SHOW, IT WILL BE AMAZING."
THIS IS THE RE-WANT TO HEAR WHAT
THEY HAVE TO SAY.
>> Carson: THAT, AND THE YEAR
THAT CHER DID IT.
[LAUGHTER]
A >> Sharon: THEY SAID THEY
WANT TO REACH THE FANS DIRECTLY.
ARE THEY GOING TO DO SOME SORT
OF A LIFE Q ON SOCIAL MEDIA?
I DOUBT IT!
AND THE FANS ARE GOING TO HAVE
EVEN MORE PROBING QUESTIONS THAN
THE PRESS, AT THE END OF THE
DAY.
THE PRESS IS THERE TO ANSWER
THOSE QUESTIONS.
>> Tami: THIS IS WHY IT'S
UNFORTUNATE.
THEY COULD HAVE TAKEN THIS
OPPORTUNITY TO SAY SOMETHING OF
VALUE.
RUNNING AWAY, NOT BEING
INVOLVED, WHEN IN ACTUALITY THEY
ARE REALLY NOT COMMITTING A
CRIME.
THEY ARE NOT DOING ANYTHING
THAT'S WRONG.
THEY ARE PERFORMERS.
THAT IS THEIR JOB.
IT IS THE SUPER BOWL, IT'S AN
AMAZING PLATFORM.
HALFTIME SHOW.
WHY NOT BE PROUD TO PARTICIPATE
IN THAT?
[APPLAUSE]
AND, YOU ARE TAKING THE MONEY
AND DONATING IT TO A CAUSE THAT
CAN HELP SO MANY OTHERS' LIVES.
I FEEL LIKE THEY SHOULD BE PROUD
OF THAT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Sharon: THE ONLY THING
ABOUT THAT DONATION -- $500,000
WITH INTERSCOPE RECORDS AND THE
NFL, TO A CHARITABLE
ORGANIZATION.
IS IT TOO LITTLE TOO LATE?
BECAUSE TRAVIS SCOTT DID THIS A
COUPLE OF WEEKS BACK.
AND MAROON 5 -- EXACTLY, THEY
WERE THE FIRST ONES.
TRAVIS SCOTT CAME AFTERWARDS.
WHY ARE THEY JUST DOING THIS NO
NOW?
I LOVE MAROON 5, BUT IT'S A
LITTLE SUSPICIOUS.
>> Brian: I WILL SAY, IF THE
MONEY'S GOING TO A GOOD PLACE,
BRING IT ON.
THEY NOW HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY.
WHEN THEY TAKE THAT STAGE, ARE
THEY GOING TO SAY SOMETHING?
ARE THEY GOING TO DO SOMETHING?
ARE THEY GOING TO TAKE A KNEE?
IT'S UP TO THEM NOW.
WE ARE LISTENING.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Sharon: THEY'VE GOT TO MAKE
A STATEMENT.
THEY'RE GOING TO COME OUT THERE
STRONG, TRAVIS SCOTT, BIG BOI AS
WELL.
AS CONTROVERSY
YOU AS THIS HAS BEEN, THERE'S A
PETITION OF PEOPLE ASKING THEM
TO PULL OUT.
PULL OUT OF THE SHOW LAST
MINUTE.
SO THEY NEED TO REALLY COME OUT
STRONG IN THE WORLD IS GOOD TO
BE WATCHING.
IT'S GOING TO BE THE HIGHEST
RATED HALFTIME PERFORMANCE.
>> Carson: WE WILL SEE.
THE SUPER BOWL AIRS THIS SUNDAY
ON CBS.
KICK OFF TIME IS AT 6:30 P.M.
I'M SO GLAD I FOUND OUT ABOUT
THIS SUPER BOWL THING!
[LAUGHS]
TAMAR BRAXTON MADE A SHOCKING
REVELATION DURING A CONVERSATION
WITH KANDI BURRUSS IN THE BIG
BROTHER HOUSE.
SHE ADMITS THAT HER 5-YEAR-OLD
SON, LOGAN, SLEEPS WITH HER AND
HER NEW BOYFRIEND.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
TAKE A LOOK.
>> SLIPPING OF THE BED WITH
ANOTHER MAN?
>> THAT'S NOT REALLY HIS
BUSINESS.
SOMEBODY THAT LOOKS LIKE HE WAS
GETTING READY TO MARRY --
>> HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN
ALLOWING YOUR SON TO SIT IN THE
BED WITH Y'ALL?
>> RECENT.
BUT HE DON'T SLEEP ME AND HIM,
HE WILL COME IN AND SCOOP ME
OVER.
>> Carson: OKAY, I DON'T HAVE
KIDS.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT PARENTING
FREE BUT THIS DOESN'T SEEM RIGHT
TO ME.
IT SEEMS A LITTLE INAPPROPRIATE.
[APPLAUSE]
ALSO, WHY DOES SHE LOOK LIKE THE
UNABOMBER?
[LAUGHTER]
>> Sharon: IT LOOKS LIKE SHE'S
HAD NO SLEEP.
PROBABLY BECAUSE THERE'S THREE
PEOPLE IN THE BED.
>> Carson: I WANT TO ASK TAMI.
YOU COPARENT.
>> Tami: I HAVE TWO DAUGHTERS.
IF IT GETS INAPPROPRIATE.
SHE HAS A YOUNG SON.
[APPLAUSE]
LET ME JUST SAY THIS.
I LOVE TEMA, SHE KNOWS THAT SHE
IS MY SIS, BUT SIX MONTHS INTO A
RELATIONSHIP YOU WOULDN'T HAVE
EVEN MET MY SON.
[APPLAUSE]
I NEED TO MAKE SURE THAT WE ARE
GOOD-GOOD.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
LET GO OF YOUR SEPARATION
ANXIETY.
WHEN A CHILD COMES IN TO CLIMB
INTO BED WITH YOU AND YOUR MAN,
KEEP THAT SEPARATE.
TAKE YOUR CHILD BACK TO THEIR
BED, PUT THEM BACK TO SLEEP,
MAKE THEM BE A MAN.
YOU ARE RAISING A MAN, TAE MAR.
YOU ARE RAISING A MAN.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Sharon: YOU DON'T WANT TO
BE 20 YEARS OLD, COASTING A
BETWEEN THE TWO.
>> Brian: IT'S EARLY IN THE
RELATIONSHIP.
ISN'T THAT WHEN YOU ARE HAVING
THE MOST SEX?
THREE YEARS LATER, THREE OR FOUR
YEARS LATER, HE DON'T WANT TO BE
NEXT TO EACH OTHER.
GET IN THE MIDDLE, KID.
I DON'T WANT TO BE SEEING YOU.
>> Sharon: I'M SURE THE
BOYFRIEND ISN'T TOO HAPPY ABOUT
IT, EITHER.
>> Tami: WE HOPE COME A
BECAUSE IF HE'S OKAY WITH IT...
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
>> Carson: IT'S KIND OF WEIRD
ANYWAY SLICES.
>> Brian: ALSO, BE CAREFUL
WHAT YOU SAY ON "CELEBRITY BIG
BROTHER."
THAT'S WHAT THE CAMERAS OF A4.
>> Carson: MOVING ON,
DIXIE CHICKS SINGER NATALIE
MANES IS GOING THROUGH A NASTY
DIVORCE.
AND HER EX WANTS HER TO PAY OFF.
SHE AND HER HUSBAND SIGNED A
PRENUP BEFORE THEY GOT MARRIED
17 YEARS AGO, BUT NOW HE WANTS
IT THROWN OUT.
HE'S CLAIMING THAT NATALIE IS
WORTH $50 MILLION.
HE ALSO CLAIMS THAT HE IS
STRUGGLING NOW BECAUSE HE PUT
HIS CAREER ON HOLD TO TAKE CARE
OF THEIR TWO KIDS.
WHO ARE NOW 14 AND 17.
ADRIENNE WANTS $60,000
A MONTH IN CHILD AND SPOUSAL
SUPPORT, PLUS 350 GRAND FOR HIS
ATTORNEY FEE.
THAT SEEMS A LITTLE BIT MUCH TO
ME.
I'M SORRY.
$350,000 A MONTH?
[APPLAUSE]
>> Sharon: THIS IS GOING TO
SOUND A LITTLE SEXIST, BUT THIS
MAN SOUNDS LIKE A COMPLETE
LEECH.
IF IT WAS THE OTHER WAY AROUND,
IT WOULD SEEM SO BAD.
IT IS EXCESSIVE.
WHAT HE'S ASKING FOR IS $16,000
IN CHILD SUPPORT, $44,000 AND
SPOUSAL SUPPORT.
THREE TIMES AS MUCH!
THERE IS NO EXCUSE FOR THAT.
>> Carson: RIGHT.
I DON'T HAVE A PROBLEM WITH --
IF YOU'RE PUTTING YOUR CAREER ON
HOLD, HELPING RAISE THE KIDS,
YOU ARE INVESTING IN THAT
MARRIAGE.
YOU ARE HELPING GROW THAT
NETWORK.
I DO THINK THAT THE AMOUNT
DOESN'T SEEM REASONABLE.
I FEEL LIKE YOU DISAGREE.
>> Tami: AS A PERSON WHO HAS
GONE THROUGH THIS MYSELF, I AM
ACTUALLY ALL FOR HIM GETTING
CHILD SUPPORT.
IF IT HAD BEEN A FEMALE, WE
WOULD HAVE MORE EMPATHY, SAYING,
"GIVE HER EVERY TIME SHE'S
ASKING FOR."
[APPLAUSE]
I THINK 17 YEARS OF BEING
MARRIED, I WAS MARRIED FOR SEVEN
YEARS AND I WANTED ALL MY COINS.
[LAUGHTER]
I THINK YOU SHOULD BE ENTITLED
TO THE SAME.
HE PUT HIS CAREER ON HOLD, HE
HAS RAISED THE CHILDREN.
HOMEMAKER IS A JOB EVEN THOUGH
PEOPLE LIKE TO MINIMIZE IT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Carson: ABSOLUTELY.
>> Tami: IS AN ACTUAL
POSITION.
HE SHOULD BE PAID FOR THAT.
SPEAKING TO THE PRENUP,
EVERYTHING IS UP FOR NEGOTIATIO
NEGOTIATION.
>> Brian: BUT ARE THE KIDS
ALWAYS GOING TO WANT TO STAY AT
MOM'S HOUSE?
BECAUSE SHE'S GOT THE
$10 MILLION PLACE IN THE
IN-GROUND POOL.
AND HE'S AT THE APARTMENT
COMPLEX WITH THE TUB.
KIDS WON'T BE WANTING TO BE AT
DADS HOUSE OF MONSTER OF THE
PALACE.
>> Tami: THAT'S WHY I THINK
YOU SHOULD GET THAT.
SO THE QUALITY OF LIFE FOR THE
CHILDREN REMAINS THE SAME.
>> Sharon: I FIND IT VERY
INTERESTING, THOUGH, THAT HE
SAYS HE BACKED UP $200,000 IN
DEBT TRY TO SUPPORT HIMSELF.
DOING WHAT?
>> Brian: HE'S A WORKING
ACTOR, HE DOES WORK.
>> Carson: HE'S BEEN ON BIG TV
SHOWS.
"HEROES."
>> Brian: SUPERGIRL.
>> Carson: THANK YOU!
[LAUGHTER]
>> Sharon: HE DOES HAVE HIS
EYE ON THE MONEY SHE'S MAKING
RIGHT NOW.
SHE'S ABOUT TO GO ON TOUR THIS
YEAR, THERE WILL BE EXTRA DOUGH.
>> Tami: THAT THE ISSUE, THE
FUTURE MONEY IS AN ISSUE.
BUT YOU SPOKE TO SPOUSAL SUPPORT
EARLIER AND THAT'S WHAT HE WANTS
A MAJORITY OF HIS MONEY IN.
HERE'S ONE THING THAT HE'S
PROBABLY DOING.
THE CHILDREN, I UNDERSTAND, ARE
OLDER IN AGE PAID 17 AND 14.
THAT'S A GOOD FIVE YEARS OF
CHILD SUPPORT STILL ABLE TO BE
HAD.
SOMEONE THAT RUNS OUT, HE'S
LOOKING FOR THE SPOUSAL SUPPORT.
THAT IS THE PART THAT I DO NOT
AGREE WITH.
I COME FROM THE OLD SCHOOL, THAT
MEN SHOULD BE ABLE TO TAKE CARE
OF THEMSELVES.
BUT AS IT PERTAINS TO THE
CHILDREN, HE SHOULD BE ALLOWED
TO GET THAT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Brian: I DO THINK THIS
SPEAKS TO THE FACT THAT YOU
DON'T REALLY KNOW A PERSON UNTIL
YOU'VE BROKEN UP.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY ARE
CAPABLE OF, AND WHAT YOU ARE
CAPABLE OF.
BECAUSE THAT'S WHEN THE CLAWS
COME OUT.
THIS WILL GET UGLY FOR THEM.
>> Sharon: AND HE MAKES
$150,000 A YEAR.
THAT'S MORE THAN MOST PEOPLE IN
AMERICA.
THAT'S NOTHING TO SNIFF AT.
>> Carson: OF COURSE.
WE WILL SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
[APPLAUSE]
MORE DRAMA FOR TYRESE AND HAS
ASKED.
TYRESE IS CLAIMING HIS EX,
NORMA, JETTED OFF TO TRINIDAD
WHILE THEIR DAUGHTER WAS
SUPPOSED TO BE IN HER CUSTODY.
INSTEAD SHE LEFT HER DAUGHTER TO
SPEND THE NIGHT AT A CLASSMATE'S
HOUSE.
TYRESE IS FUMING BECAUSE NORMA
IS SUPPOSED TO GIVE HIM THE
FIRST RIGHT OF REFUSAL IF SHE
CAN'T BE WITH THEIR DAUGHTER.
IS HE BEING PETTY, IS THIS A
LEGITIMATE CONCERN?
>> Tami: PETTY BOOTS.
LET ME TELL YOU WHY.
THE MOTHER WAS CAUGHT BETWEEN A
ROCK AND A HARD PLACE.
SHE WAS GOING ON VACATION, THE
DAUGHTER WANTED TO SPEND THE
NIGHT WITH HER FRIEND.
SHE SAID, "OKAY, I WILL LET YOU
HAVE ONE NIGHT WITH YOUR FRIEND,
YOU COULD SPEND THE REST OF YOUR
TIME WITH YOUR FATHER."
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH THAT,
BECAUSE GUARANTEE THAT DAUGHTER
WANTED TO SPEND THE NIGHT WITH
HER FRIEND INSTEAD OF SPENDING
THE WHOLE WEEKEND WITH HER DAD.
[APPLAUSE]
HE NEEDS TO JUST UNDERSTAND, LET
YOUR CHILD BE A CHILD.
I WILL ACKNOWLEDGE, THERE WAS A
COURT ORDER AND HE WANTS HER TO
FOLLOW IT.
BUT HE IS DIGGING.
GRASPING AT STRAWS.
>> Brian: HE'S LOOKING FOR IT,
YEAH.
KEEPING SCORE AT THAT POINT.
>> Sharon: I DO AGREE WITH HIM
FOR THE FIRST TIME ON THIS ONE.
ONLY BECAUSE I THINK THERE IS A
SAFETY ISSUE HERE, AND I CAN'T
HELP BUT -- SORRY GUYS, I THINK
OF THE MICHAEL JACKSON
DOCUMENTARY.
YOU NEED TO KNOW WHERE YOUR
CHILD IS AT ALL TIMES.
>> Carson: SURE.
>> Sharon: AS THE FATHER,
AGAIN, THERE WAS A COURT ORDER
IN PLACE.
HE SHOULD HAVE BEEN INFORMED.
HE SHOULD KNOW WHERE HIS
DAUGHTER IS SLEEPING AT ANY
GIVEN TIME.
>> Carson: IT'S PROBABLY A
CASE WHERE THE X SHOULD HAVE
JUST CALLED AND SAID, "HEY, THIS
IS WHAT'S HAPPENING."
>> Brian: YOU DON'T WANT TO
FIND OUT ON INSTAGRAM.
"OH, SHE'S IN TRINIDAD?"
[LAUGHTER]
>> Sharon: HE PICKED HER UP
THE VERY NEXT DAY.
BUT HERE'S WHERE IT GETS REALLY
PETTY.
APPARENTLY HE'S UPSET ABOUT A
COUPLE OF SOCIAL MEDIA POSTS.
FROM 2017.
HE'S BEEN SCROLLING THROUGH ALL
THE YEARS THAT FEATURE SHAYLA IN
THOSE POSTS.
THERE'S ANOTHER COURT ORDER THAT
SAYS NEITHER OF THEM CAN POST
PICTURES OF SHAYLA ON SOCIAL
MEDIA.
THAT, HE NEEDS TO LET GO OF.
>> Carson: THAT'S CALLED
TROLLING THE INTERNET.
HE'S LOOKING FOR STUFF.
>> Sharon: EXACTLY.
HE ACCIDENTALLY LIKES THE
PICTURE, UNLIKE, UNLIKE.
>> Carson: I WORRY ABOUT THAT
ALL THE TIME!
WHEN YOU ARE SCROLLING.
"WHO IS THAT FACE NEXT TO THEM?"
"DID I JUST LIKE THAT?"
AND THEN YOU LIKE IT LIKE 15
TIMES.
"I DON'T EVEN WANT TO SEE HER
FACE!"
>> Brian: HE HAS A NEW KID AND
A NEW WIFE.
SO HE IS ALL ABOUT AIRING HIS
GRIPES ON INSTA AND SOCIAL
MEDIA.
HE'S NOT SHY.
IS THAT A GOOD IDEA?
NO, I DON'T THINK IT'S A GOOD
IDEA.
THAT'S NOT YOUR DIRTY LAUNDRY
PLACE.
>> Sharon: SHAYLA IS THE ONE
SUFFERING AT THE END OF THE DAY.
HER PARENTS ARE GOING AT IT, SHE
SAYS IT FIRST HAND AND ALSO ALL
OVER THE INTERNET.
SHE'S ONLINE, I'M SURE HER
CLASSMATES ARE, IT'S
EMBARRASSING.
HUMILIATING, AND PAINFUL.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Carson: ONE OF THOSE
SITUATIONS WHERE IF THE PARENTS
ARE GETTING TOGETHER, THEY WOULD
BE MUCH BETTER FOR THE CHILD.
>> Sharon: THEY SHOULD BE THE
MODEL SPARE THE COMPANY
COPARENTING.
MOVING ON, SORRY TO CUT YOU OFF.
LORENA BOBBITT IS BACK IN THE
SPOTLIGHT.
[APPLAUSE]
REMEMBER BACK IN 1993?
I DON'T EVEN LIKE SAYING THIS.
LORENA CAUGHT OFF HER HUSBAND'S
PENIS AND THREW IT INTO A FIELD.
RIGHT OUT OF THE CAR.
HOW CAN THEY COULD FIND THAT
QUESTION BACK THEY CAN'T FIND
MISSION DOGMAS AND PEOPLE THAT
THEY CAN FIND THAT
ANYWAY, THIS IS SERIOUS.
OFFICIALS LATER FOUND THE
SEVERED -- AND DOCTORS ARE ABLE
TO REATTACH IT.
SHE CLAIMED SHE DID THIS WAS
SERIOUS BECAUSE HER HUSBAND HAD
RAPED HER, SOMETHING SHE HAS
DENIED.
IT'S NOW THE FOCUS OF A
FOUR-PART DOCUMENTARY CALLED
"LORENA" AND WE HAVE A SNIPPET.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> THIS WAS A MODERN LOVE STORY.
BOY MEETS GIRL, BOY FALLS IN
LOVE WITH GIRL, BOY MARY'S GIRL,
GIRL CUTS OFF BOY'S PENIS.
>> IT'LL COME DOWN TO WHO THE
JURORS BELIEF.
>> WHEN HE DO TO MAKE HER DO
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
>> SHE WANTED ME TO HURT.
THAT'S WHY SHE DID IT.
>> HAS BEEN SAYS IF I LEAVE AND
HE WILL KILL ME.
♪ ♪
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
>> Carson: SHE'S NOW GETTING
THE STAR TREATMENT AT THE
SUNDANCE FILM FESTIVAL WHERE SHE
HAS BEEN PROMOTING THE SERIES
WITH PRODUCER JORDAN PEELE.
SO, ONE OF THOSE CASES, SHOULD
SHE BE CELEBRATED FOR WHAT SHE
DID?
>> Sharon: I THINK NOT
NECESSARILY FOR WHAT SHE DID.
SHE HAS BEEN TREATED AS A
CELEBRITY.
TO USE A CELEBRITY, WHO DOESN'T
KNOW THE NAME?
WHAT I'M HAPPY ABOUT US FINALLY
SHE'S GETTING TO TELL HER SIDE
OF THE STORY.
BECAUSE WE'VE ALL BEEN LAUGHING,
LEADING UP TO THE DISCUSSION.
SHE'S BEEN THE BUTT OF SO MANY
JOKES OVER THE PAST 26 YEARS.
FINALLY WE ARE HEARING THE
REALNESS OF A LOT OF PAIN AND
STRUGGLE BEHIND THAT STORY.
IT'S NOT ALL JOKES THERE.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Carson: I AGREE.
>> Tami: OKAY, WELL, I DON'T
WANT TO SEE IT.
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT.
I FEEL LIKE SHE TOLD US THE
STORY ALL THAT MANY YEARS AGO
WHEN THE INCIDENT FIRST
HAPPENED.
I FEEL LIKE SHE IS TRYING TO
POSITION IT IN A WAY THAT WE ARE
NOW BEING COGNIZANT OF HER
EXPERIENCING DOMESTIC VIOLENCE
AND GOING THROUGH THAT.
I FEEL LIKE, "OKAY, THEN YOU
COULD PROBABLY TALK TO SHAMIKA.
YOU COULD TALK TO TONY.
YOU COULD TALK TO MISS JOHNSON.
THEY ARE SO MANY WOMEN GOING
THROUGH THIS IN REAL LIFE, WHY
DO WE NEED TO GLORIFY HER?
TREAT HER LIKE A CELEBRITY?
JUST YOUR STORY, WHEN THERE ARE
SO MANY REAL PEOPLE?
YOU WANT TO DO A DOCUMENTARY,
REACH BACK TO THE REAL PEOPLE.
HERE REAL WOMEN WHO ARE GOING
THROUGH THE STRUGGLE.
I GUARANTEE YOU, WE WILL WATCH
IT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Brian: I THINK YOU ARE
RIGHT.
BUT I DO THINK IT'S INTERESTING
TO SEE HOW THE WORLD REACTS TO
IT NOW VERSUS THEN.
THERE'S THIS OBVIOUS AWKWARDNESS
AND TALKING ABOUT WHAT HAPPEN,
BECAUSE IT WASN'T -- IT BECAME A
JOKE.
THE TWO OF THEM COULDN'T EAT A
HOT DOG IN PUBLIC BECAUSE IT
WOULD'VE BEEN ON
"THE TONIGHT SHOW."
THAT'S WHAT WOULD HAVE HAPPENED.
NO SAUSAGE LINKS.
[LAUGHTER]
LORENA WAS OFFERED A MILLION
DOLLARS TO BE ON THE COVER OF
LABELING MAGAZINE.
SHE SAID NO.
BUT HE WAS OFFERED TO BE IN PORN
MOVIES.
HE SAID YET!
HE WAS CELEBRATED.
BUT THE BOTTOM LINE IS WHAT
ISRAELIS
BELIEVE TO BE A PROBLEMATIC
WIDGET.
NOW I THINK YOU WOULD HAVE
REACTED MUCH OF ITALY THEN WE
DID THEN.
>> Sharon: I'M GLAD THESE TWO
MEN ABIDED AS WELL.
JORDAN PEELE IS ONE OF THE
PRODUCERS.
AND THE DIRECTOR'S MAIL.
BECAUSE THIS IS WHAT WE NEED, WE
NEED MILLER MEN FULLY ON BOARD.
THEY SAY THEY ARE BORED WITH
THIS MOVEMENT, THE #MeToo
MOVEMENT, AND THIS BIGGER
MOVEMENT SO THE WORLD TO BE A
SAFER PLACE FOR MEN IN GENERAL.
>> Tami: THEY WENT AND GOT A
NAME THAT IS SENSATIONALIZED.
I LOVE JORDAN PEELE, BUT I WOULD
HAVE PREFERRED YOU FIND SOME
REAL WOMEN UNTIL THEIR STORY AND
REALLY DIG INTO THE ISSUE SO
THAT WE DON'T LOSE SIGHT OF WHAT
YOU ARE TRYING TO GET US TO
UNDERSTAND THE FIRST PLACE.
THEY ARE STILL LAUGHING.
WE WERE LAUGHING AT THE CLICK.
IT'S LIKE WHEN A CHANGE.
>> Brian: SHE WAS FOUND NOT
GUILTY BY REASON OF INSANITY.
BUT WE WANT TO GET OUT OF THIS
PROBLEM BEFORE IT GETS TO THE
POINT WHERE YOU'RE SO DESPERATE
THAT IT BECOMES AN OPTION.
I CAN'T IMAGINE THE HORROR OF
WHAT HAPPENED BEFORE THAT GOT TO
THAT POINT.
>> Sharon: THIS HASN'T REALLY
BEEN TOLD IN A WAY WHERE HE PAID
ATTENTION.
SHE HAS TRIED TO TELL HER STORY,
BUT WE HAVEN'T LISTENED.
I THINK THAT'S WHAT THE ISSUE
IS.
>> Carson: WELL, "LORENA"
PREMIERES FEBRUARY 15TH ON
AMAZON.
[APPLAUSE]
ALL RIGHT, SO THE FUTURE -- THE
FUTURE OF THE SINGER, NOT JUST
THE CONCEPT OF THE FUTURE.
THAT ALWAYS CONFUSES ME.
I'M LIKE "THE FUTURE QUESTION"
BUT HE DOES NOT HOLD BACK WHEN
IT COMES TO SHOPPING, YELL.
HE JUST REVEALED HOW MUCH HE
SPENDS ON HIS CLOTHES.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> I'M EMBARRASSED TO SHOP,
BECAUSE THEY THINK I'M TROLLING.
I DO THIS [BLEEP] FOR REAL.
I SHOP EVERY DAY.
I PROBABLY SPEND $200,000 OR
$32,000" A MONTH.
IT'S CRAZY, I NEED TO STOP.
>> Carson: THAT'S BASICALLY
MADE, BUT AT T.J.MAXX.
[LAUGHTER]
"I'VE GOT THE CREDIT CARD!
I'M GOING TO TAKE THESE 19
DOUBLE ISSUES!"
I GET IT.
BUT I'M NOT AT THAT LEVEL.
I'M ALSO NOT A CPA.
I DON'T EVEN REALLY DO MATH.
BUT HAVE A CALCULATOR.
HE'S ARE POORLY WORTH
$30 MILLION.
IF YOU SPEND $300,000 A MONTH,"
HE WOULD BE OUT OF MONEY IN TEN
YEARS.
WHAT ABOUT HIS HOUSE AND HIS
FOOD IN HIS SHELTER?
>> Tami: I DON'T BELIEVE HIM.
>> Brian: I DON'T BELIEVE HIM.
IF HE'S BRAGGING.
CLUB IF YOU BELIEVE HIM.
[NO APPLAUSE]
NOBODY BELIEVES HIM!
>> Sharon: THAT'S MORE THAN
10% OF HIS INCOME.
HE IS WORTH $30 MILLION, AS YOU
SAID.
$300,000 A MONTH IS RIDICULOUS.
HE HAS AN ISSUE, AND ADDICTION.
HE NEEDS TO REEL IT IN.
HE WAS NUMBER NINE ON FORBES'
LIST OF RICHEST RAPPERS LAST
YEAR.
HE NEEDS TO TAKE A LEASE OUT.
NAS, JAY Z, P DIDDY, THEY WERE
REAL BUSINESSMEN.
THEY ARE INVESTED AND BUSINESSES
AND TECH BUSINESSES.
HE'S JUST MAKING HIS MONEY FROM
BEING A HOT WRAPPER RIGHT NOW.
YOU ARE NOT GOING TO BE HOT
RATHER FOREVER.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Tami: YOU KNOW WHAT'S
FUNNY?
NONE OF YOU CLAPPED TO SAY THAT
YOU BELIEVE TO BE IN.
BUT YOU KNOW WHO DOES BELIEVE IN
CUSTOMER FEELING KIDS FOLLOWING
HIM ON SOCIAL MEDIA.
SO WOULD FORCE A LICK OF IMAGERY
HE'S PUTTING OUT IS THAT THIS IS
WHAT SHOULD BE SPENDING OUR
MONEY ON INSTEAD OF TEACHING
PEOPLE AND EDUCATING THEM ON HOW
TO INVEST, HOW TO SAVE.
WHAT'S AN IRA COME ALL THESE
OTHER THINGS.
THEY ARE NOT GETTING THE BENEFIT
OF THAT WISDOM.
IT SAID.
>> Sharon: HE SAID IN THE SAME
INTERVIEW THAT HE BITES HIS
9-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER TEN OR 20
PAIRS OF CHANEL EVERY TIME YOU
GO SHOPPING.
AND HE'S GOT FIVE KIDS.
SO THAT'S JUST ONE OF THE KIDS
RIGHT THERE.
>> Tami: IS NOT GOING TO FIT
THEM IN THREE MONTHS.
>> Carson: I WONDER IF YOU'D
LIKE TO ADOPT ANOTHER CHILD!
[LAUGHTER]
CALL ME!
UP NEXT, THE ONE AND ONLY
VICTORIA GOD HE IS HERE.
HAVE A SNACK AND COME ON BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
Live from the Starlite Lounge.
♪ One plus one equals
too little too late ♪
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]
Stouffer's Lasagna With Meat &
Sauce
has two times the beef of the
leading meat sauce lasagna.
That's double the tender ground
beef
baked into every cheesy,
mouthwatering bite.
When it comes to irresistible
taste,
more is always more.
Stouffer's.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Carson: OUR FIRST GUEST IS
A REALITY START IN THE
BEST-SELLING AUTHOR.
SHE HAS A NEW MONEY CALLED
"VICTORIA GODEY:MY FATHER'S
DAUGHTER."
TAKE A LOOK
>> I WAS BORN WITH A CONGENITAL
HEART DEFECT.
ACCORDING TO THE DOCTORS COME I
SHOULD HAVE BEEN DEAD A YEAR
EARLIER.
THAT MORNING, I WISHED I WAS.
I'M VICTORIA GOTTI, AND THIS IS
THE STORY OF MY FATHER AND ME.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
>> Carson: PLEASE WELCOME,
VICTORIA GOTTI!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
PUT YOUR FEET ON THAT SHOE CAM!
WE NEED TO GET A SHOE SHOT!
THERE WE GO.
THERE IS MAGICAL SHOE CAM.
>> Victoria: ALWAYS THE BEST
AUDIENCE.
>> Carson: AREN'T THEY THE
GREATEST CUSTOMER GIVE IT UP FOR
OUR AUDIENCE!
OKAY.
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU IN 100 YEARS.
SINCE LIKE 2003, BECAUSE I WAS
DOING "EYE" AND YOU WERE DOING
"GROWING UP GOTTI."
IT WAS THE BRITNEY GASTINEAU
AREA.
THERE IS A PARTY, YOU WERE THERE
WITH THE BOYS.
>> Victoria: WE WERE RUNNING
INTO EACH OF EVERY WHICH WAY.
>> Carson: PEOPLE THOUGHT WE
WERE DATING.
IT'S NOT TRUE.
[LAUGHTER]
DO YOU MISS REALITY TV?
>> Victoria: I DON'T MISS
ANYTHING IN MY LIFE THAT I'VE
DONE.
I LOVE EVERYTHING -- PEOPLE SAY,
"YOU HAVE ANY REGRETS?"
NO.
I LOOK AT THE BEST PART OF IT.
>> Carson: KEEP MOVING, YES.
WE'VE GOT YOU.
BUT I THINK WE ALL LOVE THE
REALITY SHOW WITH YOUR SON.
RIGHT?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THERE THEY ARE.
THIS IS LIKE PREJERSEY SHORE
SPIKY HAIR.
>> Victoria: THEY WERE OFFERED
THE JERSEY SHORE, THEY SAID NO.
>> Carson: ANY CHANCE HE WOULD
DO IT A SHOW WITH THEM AGAIN?
>> Victoria: WE ARE WORKING ON
SOMETHING RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE THE FIRST TO KNOW.
NOBODY KNOWS THAT.
>> Carson: WHAT'S THE SCOOP,
WHAT CAN YOU TELL US?
>> Victoria: REALLY NOTHING,
THEY HAVEN'T ALLOWED ME TO SAY
ANYTHING.
JUST THAT WE ARE WORKING ON
SOMETHING.
I THINK YOU WILL ALL BE REALLY
HAPPY.
[APPLAUSE]
THOSE WHO HAVE ENJOYED IT, WILL
BE HAPPY.
>> Carson: WITH YOU AT THE
HOTTIE GOTTIS.
>> Victoria: GOD BLESS THE
GIRLS AND THE HOTTIE GOTTIS.
>> Carson: DO ANY OF THEM
STILL LIVE AT HOME?
>> Victoria: THAT'S CHRISTMAS
MINE.
ONLY ONE.
I THINK HE ONLY STAYS THERE
BECAUSE HE THINKS, "I DON'T WANT
TO LEAVE MOM ALONE," THAT KIND
OF THING.
>> Carson: THEY LIVE AT HOME
UNTIL THEY ARE LIKE 38.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Victoria: RIGHT.
I FEEL SO BAD, BECAUSE THE OTHER
TWO BOLTED AS QUICKLY AS THEY
COULD KNOWING HE'D BE THE LAST
ONE LEFT.
SO I THINK HE FEELS LIKE IT'S ON
HIM.
>> Wendy: I FIGURE LIKES
LIVING WITH YOU.
>> Victoria: WOULD GET ALONG
GREAT, WE DO.
THE LITTLE CUTIE IS THE LOVE OF
MY LIFE.
THE NEW LOVE OF MY LIFE.
>> Carson: OH, MY GOSH, IT WAS
THAT?
>> Victoria: HE IS MY
GRANDSON.
I'M A GRANDMA.
I TELL YOU, I THINK OF WAYS
EVERY NIGHT TO KIDNAP HIM AND
GET HIM AWAY WHERE NO ONE COULD
CATCH US.
AND WHERE WERE THEY NOT LOOK?
BECAUSE I WANT THAT BABY.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Carson: I'M HAVING THE SAME
THOUGHTS ABOUT THE DADDY.
I WAS LIKE, "MOVE THAT BABY!
I WANT TO SEE THE SUN!"
[LAUGHTER]
NO, I'M TALKING ABOUT THE ONE ON
THE RIGHT!
>> Victoria: YOU TAKE THE BIG
ONE, I WILL TAKE THE LITTLE ONE.
>> Wendy: I NOTICED EVERYONE
HOW THEY MENTION IT.
YOUR KIDS ARE SO ATTRACTIVE.
YOU TURNED OUT SOME GOOD-LOOKING
PEOPLE.
RIGHT?
[APPLAUSE]
B6 THEY ARE GOOD TO ME.
THEY ARE SO GOOD TO ME.
THAT'S IMPORTANT.
>> Carson: I THINK IT PROBABLY
GOES BOTH WAYS.
YOU ARE A GOOD MOM.
THEY ARE PAYING IT BACK.
YOU WERE MARRIED, DIVORCED.
ARE YOU DATING?
ANYBODY ON THE ROMANCE HORIZON?
>> Victoria: AND DATED, BUT
NOT ANYBODY SPECIAL RIGHT NOW.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
>> Carson: IF YOU ARE
WATCHING, SHE'S NOT TALKING
ABOUT YOU!
OKAY?
[LAUGHTER]
HOW DO YOU DATE?
ARE YOU ONLINE?
>> Victoria: NO, MY GOODNESS,
NO PET I WOULD BE SO AFRAID.
I DON'T TRUST ANYBODY ANYWAY.
I FEEL LIKE EVERYBODY YOU
MEET -- I ALWAYS LOOK THROUGH
THEM ANYWAY, AND I FEEL LIKE
THEY WANT SOMETHING OR THEY NEED
SOMETHING.
I CAN'T RAISE ANOTHER SON.
I CAN'T.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Carson: YOU WILL MEET
SOMEBODY, DIFFERENCE THAT YOU
HAVE?
>> Victoria: FRIENDS.
OR, BELIEVE IT OR NOT, WORK.
THE STRANGEST LITTLE -- AS I
SAID, YEARS AGO, THE EASIEST
PLACE TO MEET SOMEBODY.
I LIKE TO GENERALLY KNOW A
LITTLE BIT ABOUT THEM BEFORE.
IT'S EASIER THAT WAY.
BECAUSE IT'S A LITTLE BIT
MORE -- I JUST MISS TRUST A LOT
OF PEOPLE.
>> Carson: I LIKE TO MEET MY
GUYS AT CHURCH.
[LAUGHTER]
GOOD PLACE!
OR BLOOMINGDALE'S, AS I CALL IT.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Victoria: THAT'S RIGHT.
IF YOU MET THEM IN CHURCH, YOU
KNOW IT'S A GOOD GUY.
>> Carson: I KNOW!
YOU'VE GOT TO DO A LITTLE
PRESCREENING OR SOMETHING.
I KNOW YOU ARE FRIENDS WITH
TERESA FROM "RHONJ" ."
HOW DID YOU GUYS MEET?
>> Victoria: IT WAS SO -- WE
REALLY MEANT DOING
"CELEBRITY APPRENTICE."
BE WHEN I FEEL YOUR PAIN, I DID
THAT SHOW, TOO.
SO HARD.
>> Victoria: WHEN THEY'VE GOT
IT IN FOR YOU, THEY'RE ALL GOING
TO -- YOU HAVE THE BIG --
>> Carson: I'VE NEVER DONE A
SHOW WHERE THEY ACTUALLY WANT
YOU TO MESS UP.
I WAS LIKE, "WAIT A MINUTE, YOU
DIDN'T ORDER MY FURNITURE?
I'M GAY.
I'VE GOT A BACKUP.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Victoria: THEY PLAN IT,
THEY LAY AWAKE AT NIGHT THINKING
HOW TO GET THAT ONE PERSON WITH
A BULL'S-EYE.
>> Carson: AND HE DID THE SHOW
TOGETHER SO YOU COULD HAVE BEEN
ENEMIES BUT THEY BECAME FRIENDS.
>> Victoria: THEY WANTED US TO
BE ENEMIES.
ONE DAY, HER AND HER HUSBAND
KNOCKED ON MY DOOR AND WE HIT IT
OFF.
WE ACTUALLY ARGUED FIRST.
AND THEN WE MADE UP.
>> Carson: THOSE OF THE BEST
FRIEND, I THINK.
WHEN YOU CAN HAVE A LITTLE BIT
OF A PUSH BACK.
"I RESPECT YOU, YOU RESPECT ME."
WHAT DO YOU THINK WILL HAPPEN
WITH JOE AND THAT WHOLE SCENARI
SCENARIO?
>> Victoria: THEM      I'M HEARE
AGE OF THINGS LOOK AT VIDEOS.
I WOULD PERSONALLY BE VERY
SURPRISED TO SEE IF JOE IS SENT
TO ITALY AND DEPORTED, AND SHE
WAS TO STAY HERE.
I WOULD BE VERY SURPRISED.
I DON'T THINK THAT THERESA AND
JOE ARE FINISHED, BY ANY MEANS,
YET.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Carson: GOTCHA.
IT'S KIND OF FUN WHEN YOU ARE
DOING TV PROJECTS, PEOPLE WANT
TO REACH OUT TO YOU.
SO YOU BECOME FRIENDS WITH OTHER
CELEBRITIES.
I GUESS THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED
WITH YOU AND LIL KIM.
>> Victoria: YES.
>> Carson: THERE YOU ARE!
>> Victoria: SHE IS SO COOL.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Carson: SHE HAS!
HOW DID YOU MEET CUSTOMER AND
SHE DOES REACH OUT TO BE IN A
VIDEO?
>> Victoria: YEAH, SHE PUT MY
NAME IN A FEW OF HER SONGS AND
CALLED ONE DAY.
GOT ON THE PHONE, SAID, "I WANT
YOU IN MY NEXT VIDEO."
AND I SAID "I DON'T DO THAT, I
COULD NEVER!"
>> Carson: HOW DID SHE FIND
YOU?
>> Victoria: THROUGH A PRESS
REP OR SOMEONE.
SHE REALLY WANTED ME, SHE WAS
EMPHATICALLY ASKING.
I SAID, "ALL RIGHT."
I ADMIRED HER WORK.
SHE SAID, "MEET US AT THE
BROOKLYN BRIDGE AT 1:AT
45:00 A.M. ON TUESDAY NIGHT."
>> Carson: IF I HAD A
NICKEL...
>>  >> Victoria: I'M LIKE HALF
ASLEEP ALREADY, WE WERE DOING
THE SHOW, WE HAD EARLY CALL.
I GET OUT, SHE HAS THIS WHOLE
RUNWAY SET UP.
THERE'S A FEW GIRLS WITH FOR
PLAYER LIST.
IT VERY COLD.
ONE OF THOSE 6-DEGREE NIGHTS.
LIKE TODAY.
I'M FREEZING, AS YOU CAN SEE IN
THAT PICTURE.
ALL OF THE SUDDEN SHE DOES THIS
BIG REVEAL IN THE END, WHIPS UP
IN HER COAT FOR THIS PRESS
PHOTO.
YOU DON'T SEE IT IN ERROR, YOU
DON'T REALIZE IT, BUT EVERYBODY
IS LIKE, "BE NOT!"
AND I'M WONDERING WHAT HAPPENED,
AND I LOOK AT HER, AND I WENT,
"OH, MY GOD!
SHE'S GOT A MAKE BIKINI ON!"
AND I HAD THE NERVE TO COMPLAIN
THAT I'M COLD!
[APPLAUSE]
AND SHE'S JUST GIVING IT.
YOU GO GOOD,.
[LAUGHTER]
I'M JUST FOLLOWING YOU.
SEE WHEN YOU HAVE A NEW MOVIE
OUT FOR A LIFETIME.
TELL US ABOUT IT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Victoria: IS A MOVIE ABOUT
MY LIFE.
PEOPLE SAY, "YOU AND YOUR DAD,
YOU'RE DEAD."
IT'S REALLY MY LIFE.
I WOULD BE REMISS IF I EXCLUDED
HIM AND JUST CALLED HIM
"MR. SMITH."
SO IT'S INTERESTING, THE
WRITER -- THINGS DIDN'T WORK OUT
WITH THE WRITER INITIALLY, AND
THIS IS A PROJECT THAT WE'VE
BEEN WORKING ON FOR LIKE SEVEN
YEARS.
IN THE END, IN 14 DAYS, I WROTE
IT.
EXECUTIVE PRODUCER, AND THEY
RATED IT.
THEN THEY WANT TO BE IN IT.
I WENT TO THE SHOOTS.
IT WAS A PROJECT I THOUGHT I
WOULDN'T HAVE AS MUCH INPUT OR
CONTROL OVER.
I HAVE TO TELL YOU, I REALLY
FELT SO GRATIFIED ABOUT IT.
>> Carson: YOU DID THE WHOLE
THING.
GOOD FOR YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING
HERE.
I HOPE THE MOVIE IS A BIG HIT.
VICTORIA'S NEW MOVIE, "VICTORIA
GOTTI: MY FATHER'S DAUGHTER,"
PREMIERES ON LIFETIME.
CAP NEXT WE ARE COOKING IN THE
"WENDY" KITCHEN.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
When I received the diagnosis,
I knew at that exact moment,
whatever it takes,
wherever I have to go...I'm
beating this.
My main focus
was to find a team of doctors
that work together.
When a patient comes to CTCA,
they're meeting a team of
physicians that specialize
in the management of cancer.
Breast cancer treatment is
continuing to evolve.
And I would say that CTCA
is definitely on the cusp of
those changes.
Patients can be overwhelmed
...
We really focus on taking the
time
with each individual patient
so they can choose
the treatment appropriate for
them.
The care that CTCA brings is
the kind of care
I've wanted for my patients.
Being able to spend time with
them,
have a whole team to look
after them is fantastic.
I empower women with choices.
It's not just picking a
surgeon.
It's picking the care team, and
feeling secure where you are.
Surround yourself with the
team of breast cancer experts
at Cancer Treatment Centers of
America
Comprehensive Cancer
Care Network.
Visit cancercenter.com.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Sharon: SUPER BOWL PARTIES
AREN'T ANYTHING WITHOUT GOOD
FOOD!
HERE WITH SOME IDEAS FOR YOUR
PARTY IS CHEF GEORGE DURAND!
>> George: HELLO, HELLO!
WHO'S GOT TO EAT DURING THE
SUPER BOWL.
IT'S ALL ABOUT THE SNACKS.
WE WILL MAKE TWO OF THEM FOR THE
RAMS AND TWO FOR THE PATRIOTS.
MAYBE A COCKTAIL FOR THE BOTH OF
US TO CELEBRATE WITH.
SOMETHING HEALTHIER WITH THE
GUACAMOLE, AND WE WILL TAKE A
COOKED SWEET POTATO AND STUFF IT
WITH SOME WALK IN THERE.
WE WANT TO MAKE IT LOOK LIKE A
FOOTBALL.
HE PUT THE ONE OF THESE
RESEALABLE BAGS, YOU PUT IT IN
THE SOUR CREAM.
PUT THE STITCHES OF THE BALL
COME RIGHT OVER THERE.
NOTHING FANCY.
>> Sharon: RICO!
WHAT IS THAT OVER THERE?
>> Carson:          >> Sharon: Y
SATISFYING!
>> George: THIS IS BETTER.
OKAY, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL BE FINE.
THEN YOU GET YOUR CHIPS, YOU
KIND OF DIP IT IN THERE.
IT'S VERY CALIFORNIAN.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
YOU CAN ALSO TAKE THE WHOLE
SWEET POTATO.
VERY NICE.
ALL RIGHT.
THEN WE'RE GOING TO KEEP MOVING.
THIS IS CALLED THE FRENCH DIP
SANDWICH.
THE FRENCH DIP WAS INVENTED IN
CALIFORNIA, AND L.A., BUT A
FRENCH GUY.
THAT'S WHY IT'S CALLED THE
FRENCH DIP.
WE WILL TAKE ONE OF THESE
HAWAIIAN SWEET ROLLS AND CUT
THEM IN HALF.
TAKE SOME OF THIS -- WHAT IS
THIS CALLED EXACTLY?
>> Sharon: I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THAT IS.
BEEF?
ROAST BEEF.
>> George: LAID A LACROSSE.
ADD SOME OF THE SLICED EURO
SPRING.
THE BEAUTY
OF THE AHLERS BERG IS
ITS REALLY NUTTY.
YOU PUT IT BACK IN THE PAN
COMING MELTED.
I'M GOING TO FAST FORWARD OVER
HERE.
USE OF IT WITH AU JUS.
WHAT COMES OUT IS THIS.
IT'S APOLLO PART.
YOU PULL IT APART A LITTLE BIT,
YOU JUST KIND OF -- OH, MY
GOODNESS PAY LOOK AT THAT.
IT'S ALL ABOUT THAT WILL BE
DOING THIS.
AT NUTTY FLAVOR.
AND YOU DIP IT IN THE AU JUS,
IT'S LIKE THE CALIFORNIA VERSION
OF SLIDERS.
WE ARE GOING TO MAKE A REALLY
NICE LOBSTER TO.
IT'S LOBSTER MEAT, CREAM AND
CHEESE.
>> Brian: IS THAT SOUR CREAM?
>> George: BELL PEPPERS,
ONIONS.
AGAIN, WE WILL ADD SOME OF THE
JARLSBERG.
MELTED.
AT THE VERY LAST SECOND, PUT
INTO THE OVEN, SHOW IT TO THE
GAS, AND DIG IN DEEP.
LOBSTER.
THE GOOD STUFF.
ARE YOU A BIG NEW ENGLAND
PATRIOTS FAN?
>> Brian: I WANT TO CHECK THE
FOOTBALL.
IT'S A LITTLE BIT DEFLATED.
[LAUGHTER]
THIS IS PERFECT.
WHAT'S THIS CUSTOMER GOOD LOOKS
AMAZING.
>> George: FISH AND CHIPS IS
QUINTESSENTIALLY NEW ENGLAND.
YOU TAKE THE FROZEN PREFRIED COD
THAT YOU HAVE, HE PUT INTO THE
OVEN, AND ONCE IT MEANT CRISPS
UP YOU MAKE YOUR OWN SLIDER.
GRABS THAT.
>> Brian: WHAT AM I DOING?
>> George: PUT THE SAUCE ON
TOP LIKE THAT.
SQUEEZE IT UP.
>> Brian: I LOVE THE SLIDER
BECAUSE YOU CAN EAT TWO OR
THREE.
IT'S NOT AS BAD AS OLD ONE.
>> George: YOU CAN CURSE THESE
OR PUT THEM ON TOP.
YOU CAN PUT SOME LETTUCE IN
THERE TOO.
GO IN THERE, SAY CHEERS, AND YOU
GOT A FISH AND CHIPS LIGHTER.
SUPER EASY TO MAKE!
VERY EASY TO MAKE.
>> Brian: I SEE BROWN.
WENT TO GET STARTED ON THIS
COCKTAIL WHILE I ENJOY THIS.
>> George: IT'S A MISHMASH OF
BOTH WEST COAST AND EAST COAST.
YOU GOT A BOSTON GREEN TEA PARTY
PUNCH.
GREEN TEA, BROWN SUGAR.
TO ADD A LITTLE BIT OF RUM.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Sharon: THE GOOD STUFF.
>> Brian: A LITTLE BIT MORE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Sharon: IT'LL BE A FUN
PARTY TONIGHT!
>> George: HE RICO!
WE HAD A LITTLE OF THOUGHT!
>> Brian: WE ARE ALL WALKING
HOME FROM THE SUPER BOWL.
THE >> George: THIS IS VERY
HEALTHY FOR THE WEST COAST
PEOPLE.
WHAT IS THE BOSS IN PART ABOUT
THIS?
THE RUM, OF COURSE.
>> Brian: SURE.
>> George: SERVE IT FOR YOUR
FRIENDS.
ADD A LOT OF ICE, LITTLE BROWN
SUGAR, BALANCE IT TO YOUR
LIKING.
ARE YOU READY?
>> Brian: HOW COULD YOU NOT
LOVE THIS?
GEORGE, THANK YOU FOR BEING
HERE.
FOR MORE INFORMATION ON THESE
RECIPES, GO TO WendyShow.com.
UP NEXT, AUDIENCE MEMBERS
COMPETE IN WENDY'S ANNUAL
END ZONE DANCE CONTEST.
WE WILL BRING IT RIGHT BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Excuse me.
Mister, Mister Batman.
Is there like a truck?
♪ ♪
>> Carson: IT'S TIME FOR
WENDY'S ANNUAL END ZONE DANCE
OFF.
THREE MEMBERS OF OUR STUDIO
AUDIENCE WILL COMPETE TO FIND
OUT WHO HAS THE BEST TOUCHDOWN
DANCE.
MR. ANNOUNCER, TELL THEM WHAT
THEY'RE PLAYING FOR!
♪ ♪
>> Announcer: IT'S A BIG
SCREEN TV WITH A SOUND BAR FROM
OUR FRIENDS AT SHOP YOUR WAY
PERSONAL SHOPPER!
TAKE THE HASSLE OUT OF SHOPPING
WITH A FREE PERSONAL SHOPPER
FROM SHOP YOUR WAY.
YOUR DEDICATED PERSONAL SHOPPER
CAN HELP YOU FIND AND BUY
ANYTHING, LIKE THIS BRAND-NEW
KENMORE FOR COBURNER GAS GRILL.
CONNECTING WITH YOUR PERSONAL
SHOPPER IS EASY.
OPEN THE IN THERE AT.
BUT WAIT, THERE'S MORE.
OUR FRIENDS AT A
HotelPlanner.com ARE SENDING
YOU TO THE SUPER BOWL!
YOU AND I GUESS WE'LL GET FREE
HOTEL AND ROUND-TRIP AIRFARE TO
ATLANTA.
PLUS, FREE TICKETS TO WATCH THE
RAMS AND PATRIOTS SQUARE OFF IN
THE BIG GAME, WITH OVER
1 MILLION GROUP BOOKINGS.
HotelPlanner.com IS NUMBER ONE
IN GROUP TRAVEL.
THIS PRIZE PACKAGES WORTH OVER
$13,000.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Tami: LET'S GET STARTED.
OUR FIRST CONTESTANT IS ALINA!
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
WHEN I SAY "TOUCHDOWN," THAT'S
WHEN YOU DO THE BEST DANCING YOU
COULD DO FOR YOUR LIFE.
[MUMBLES]
ARE YOU READY?
>> OH, I'M READY.
>> Tami: TOUCHDOWN!
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Carson: OKAY!
I DON'T KNOW BUT I THINK DELANO
REALLY WANTS TO GO TO THE
SUPER BOWL
>> Tami: I KNOW LONGER HAVE A
BLACK CARD.
I DON'T HAVE THAT MUCH RHYTHM.
THE ONE SHE THREW THIS THING AT
ME!
[LAUGHTER]
ANYWAY, UP NEXT IS JAMIL.
TAKE YOUR POSITION.
THAT WAS AWKWARD.
READY?
TOUCHDOWN!
♪ ♪
["LOW" BY T-PAIN."
>> Carson: WOW!
IT WENT INTO THE END ZONE!
THAT WAS REALLY GOOD, JAMIL.
>> Tami: I FEEL THIS IN MY
SPIRIT.
I FEEL LIKE SHE IS GOING TO KILL
IT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
CHANTEL!
ARE YOU READY?
>> I'M SO READY.
>> Tami: LET'S DO IT.
TOUCHDOWN.
♪ ♪
["LOW" BY T-PAIN]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Tami: I TOLD YOU!
>> Carson: THESE PEOPLE ARE
NOT PLAYING!
WHEN THEY COME BACK, PEOPLE
CROWN A WINNER.
DON'T MISS IT!
[CHE
>> Carson: WELCOME BACK.
IT'S TIME TO VOTE FOR OUR
WINTER.
IS IT ELANA?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
IS IT JAMIL?
OR IS THAT CHANTEL?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
OUR WINTER IS
ALINA THE ENTIRE STUDIO AUDIENCE
IS GOING HOME WITH GIFT CARDS
FOR $300 OF FREE CASH-IN POINTSM
SHOP YOUR WAY PERSONAL SHOPPER!
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪ ♪
At Outback,
your Steak & Lobster wish
is our command.
Steak & Lobster is back
by popular demand,
starting at only $15.99.
Hurry in to Outback!
Steak & Lobster is only here
for a limited time.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Sharon: THERE IS SOMEONE
SPECIAL THE AUDIENCE!
IT'S THE COO, BRUCE ROSENSTEIN!
FROM HotelPlanner.com!
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE AND FOR
SENDING ELAINE OUT TO THE
SUPER BOWL.
IT'S BECAUSE SHE'S GOING TO HAVE
A BLAST, WE ARE EXCITED FOR HER!
>> Sharon: TELL ME WHAT YOUR
COMPANY.
>> HotelPlanner.com HAS
500,000 HOTELS YOU COULD BOOK
WORLDWIDE.
IF YOU'RE TRAVELING AS A GROUP,
TO NEW YORK CITY WITH A GROUP OF
FRIENDS, WE HAVE EXCELLENT RATES
FOR YOU.
THEY WILL BE THE LOWEST RATES
GUARANTEED.
IF YOU'RE TRAVELING FOR VACATION
TRAVEL OR BUSINESS TRAVEL, GREAT
RATES AND OPTIONS.
YOU HAVE A WONDERFUL TIME ON THE
SITE.
>> Sharon: YOU HAVE A SPECIAL
SURPRISE FOR HER COHOSTS, FOR
THE AUDIENCE?
>> YES.
WE WANTED TO SEE EVERYBODY
DANCE, BUT EVERYBODY ELSE IN THE
STUDIO AUDIENCE, FROM
HotelPlanner.com, IS GOING TO
GET A $100 GIFT CARD.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Sharon: SAINT DOMINIC
THANK YOU SO MUCH, BRUCE!
WE WILL BE RIGHT
(James)
I can't believe it could take
weeks to get our tax refund.
(Lisa)
At H&R Block, you could get an
Advance Refund up to
$3,000 the day you file.
(James)
We can get a pool table.
(Cori)
Or we can get the car fixed.
(Lisa VO) ♪
Up to $3,000 the day
you file at H&R Block.
I'M ALEX TREBEK
HERE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50-85
AND LOOKING
TO BUY LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET,
REMEMBER THE THREE P'S.
THE THREE WHAT?
THE THREE P'S?
WHAT ARE THE THREE P'S?
THE THREE P'S OF LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET
ARE PRICE, PRICE, AND PRICE.
A PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD,
A PRICE THAT CAN'T INCREASE,
AND A PRICE
THAT FITS YOUR BUDGET.
I'M 54 AND I WAS
A SMOKER BUT QUIT.
ALEX, WHAT'S MY PRICE?
YOU CAN GET COVERAGE
FOR $9.95 A MONTH.
I'M 65, RETIRED,
AND TAKE MEDICATIONS.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
ALSO $9.95 A MONTH.
I JUST TURNED 80
AND I'M ON A FIXED INCOME.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
$9.95 A MONTH FOR YOU, TOO.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85,
CALL NOW ABOUT
THE NUMBER ONE MOST POPULAR
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE PLAN
AVAILABLE THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IT HAS AN AFFORDABLE RATE
STARTING AT $9.95 A MONTH.
THAT'S LESS THAN 35 CENTS A DAY.
YOU CANNOT BE TURNED DOWN
BECAUSE OF YOUR HEALTH.
NO MEDICAL EXAM,
NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE IS GUARANTEED,
AND THIS PLAN HAS A GUARANTEED
LIFETIME RATE LOCK,
SO YOUR RATE CAN NEVER GO UP
FOR ANY REASON.
AND WITH THIS PLAN,
YOU CAN PICK YOUR PAYMENT DATE,
SO YOU CAN TIME
YOUR PREMIUM DUE DATE
TO WORK WITH YOUR BUDGET.
OPTIONS START AT $9.95 A MONTH,
PLUS, YOU GET A 30-DAY
MONEY BACK GUARANTEE.
SO CALL NOW
FOR FREE INFORMATION.
AND YOU'LL ALSO GET
THIS FREE BENEFICIARY PLANNER,
AND IT'S YOURS JUST FOR CALLING.
SO CALL NOW.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Carson: I WANT TO THANK
TODAY'S GUESTS COME OUT MY
STUDIO AUDIENCE AND COHOSTS.
CHECK ME OUT ON "RUPAUL'S DRAG
RACE ALL-STARS" TONIGHT AT 8:00
ON VH1.
WATCH TAMI ROMAN ON "THE FAMILY
BUSINESS" ON BET, AND
SHARON CARPENTER ON THE BBC'S HQ
TRIVIA.
AND BRIANNA, ON HIS WEBSITE,
PopGoesTheWeek.com.
WE WILL BE BACK NEXT WEEK FOR A
FULL HOUR OF HOT TOPICS.
WE LOVE YOU FOR WATCHING TODAY
AND WE WILL SEE YOU NEXT TIME ON
"WENDY."
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
When I received the diagnosis,
I knew, whatever it takes,
wherever I have to go... I'm
beating this.
Breast cancer treatment is
continuing to evolve.
CTCA is definitely on the cusp
of those changes.
We really focus on taking the
time
with each individual patient
so they can choose the treatment
appropriate for them.
I empower women with choices.
It's not just picking a
surgeon.
It's picking the care team, and
feeling secure where you are.
Visit cancercenter.com.
Appointments available now.
AMY:
So, Sheldon, there's something
I've been wanting to talk about.
But I know it's
kind of a touchy subject.
Way to narrow it down
to everything.