Captioning sponsored by CBS
♪ ♪ ♪
>> Stephen: LET'S SEE, I'VE GOT
ALL MY SUPER BOWL SNACKS.
I'VE GOT PIGS IN A BLANKET.
PIGS OUT OF BLANKETS.
AND JUST BLANKETS.
( DOORBELL RINGS )
HEY!
IT'S MY MUTUAL INSTAGRAM FRIEND,
SIR PATRICK STEWART!
HEY, THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
I HAD NO WHY YOU WERE SUCH A
SUPER BOWL FAN.
>> OH, OF COURSE!
I LOVE AMERICAN FOOTBALL!
THEY GET TO USE THEIR HANDS.
NOW, LET'S GET THIS MOTHER
STARTED!
YEE-HAW!
YEAH, BUDDY!
GIVE ME A BEER!
( DOORBELL RINGS )
( LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE )
( ♪ CREEPY MUSIC ♪ )
>> Stephen: GAH!
>> GRITTWOLD G. GRITTINGTON.
I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND, BUT I
BROUGHT A FRIEND.
HE WAS JUST OUT PARKING THE VAN.
>> Stephen: OH, SORRY, SORRY FOR
THE CONFUSION EARLIER.
SHAKE?
>> GRITTY AND I GO WAY BACK.
WE USED TO BE IN THE ROYAL
SHAKESPEARE COMPANY TOGETHER.
>> Stephen: OH, SURE, "HAMLET."
>> NO!
GRITTY PLAYED JULIET.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHERE THE SKULL
CAME FROM.
>> Stephen: OKIE-DOKE.
>> ♪ WE'D BETTER GET A BUZZ
GOING! ♪
WHO WOULD LIKE TO SHOTGUN A
BREWSKI?
>> AND IT'S INTERCEPTED.
>> Stephen: ONE, TWO, THREE--
( DOORBELL RINGS )
OH, DOORBELL.
>> Stephen: SPEAKER OF THE HOUSE
NANCY PELOSI AND SENATE
DEMOCRATIC LEADER CHUCK SCHUMER!
>> PLEASE, STEPHEN, WE'RE
FRIENDS.
>> JUST CALL US "CHUCK" AND
"SPEAKER OF THE HOUSE NANCY."
>> Stephen: OKAY.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING HERE?
>> WE FIGURED YOUR LITTLE GET-
TOGETHER NEEDED US.
>> Stephen: OH, WHY'S THAT?
>> 'CUZ WE'RE THE PARTY LEADERS!
( ♪ ELECTRIC GUITAR ♪ )
>> Stephen: GRITTY!
( LAUGHTER )
WELL, I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
WHY DON'T YOU COME ON IN?
>> OH, NO.
THERE'S MORE TROUBLE IN
WASHINGTON.
>> WE'VE GOT TO GO.
>> Stephen: OH, OKAY...
>> JUICE IT, NANCY!
>> Stephen: THANKS...
THANKS FOR STOPPING BY.
( APPLAUSE )
GRITTY, THAT'S OUT OF TUNE.
>> COME ON!
GET IN THERE!
KNOCK HIS HEAD OFF!
>> Stephen: PATRICK, THIS IS THE
HALFTIME SHOW.
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ I'VE GOT THE MOOOVES ♪
>> I'M AWARE OF THAT.
SNAP HIS FEMUR!
>> Stephen: WHAT DO YOU WANT TO
DO NOW?
>> WELL, I HEAR THERE'S AN ALL-
NEW "LATE SHOW."
>> Stephen: ON SUNDAY?
>> MM-HMM.
>> Stephen: I'LL HAVE TO CHECK
THAT OUT.
HUH.
THAT'S WEIRD.
WHERE'S THE HOST?
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
OH, GOD!
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE THERE!
CAPTAIN, BEAM ME UP!
>> STEPHEN, THAT'S NOT A REAL
THING.
>> Stephen: IT IS TO ME.
GRITTWOLD!
( BEEPING )
>> GRITTWOLD!
YOU HAVE VIOLATED THE PRIME
DIRECTIVE.
GIVE THAT BACK TO ME!
>> Announcer: IT'S "THE LATE
SHOW WITH STEPHEN COLBERT."
SUPER BOWL EDITION.
TONIGHT, ARE YOU READY FOR SOME
"LATE SHOW?"
PLUS, STEPHEN WELCOMES:
CONAN O'BRIEN.
MUSICAL GUEST JAMES TAYLOR.
AND, A SPECIAL APPEARANCE BY
STEVE CARELL.
FEATURING JON BATISTE AND
STAY HUMAN.
AND NOW, LIVE ON TAPE FROM THE
ED SULLIVAN THEATER IN NEW YORK
CITY, IT'S STEPHEN COLBERT!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: COME ON!
WOOO!
HELLO.
BEAUTIFUL.
PLEASE, HAVE A SEAT, EVERYBODY.
THANKS SO MUCH.
WELCOME, ONE AND ALL, LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN, TO "THE LATE SHOW."
I'M YOUR HOST, STEPHEN COLBERT.
HAPPY, HAPPY SUPER BOWL SUNDAY.
IT'S ALWAYS AN EXCITING NIGHT.
IT'S A GREAT DAY.
IT'S OUR ONE TRUE NATIONAL
HOLIDAY.
THIS IS THE ONE DAY WHEN,
DESPITE OUR DIVISIONS, AMERICANS
COME TOGETHER, AROUND THEIR TVs
AND, FOR JUST ONE BEAUTIFUL
MOMENT, DON'T FAST FORWARD
THROUGH THE COMMERCIALS.
( LAUGHTER )
WE ALL WANT TO SEE WHICH TALKING
ANIMAL WANTS TO SELL US BEER,
AND WHICH CELEBRITY REALLY
WANTED THE MONEY.
( LAUGHTER )
I'VE BEEN THERE, MY BROTHERS AND
SISTERS.
YOU ENJOY THAT.
ANOTHER ANNUAL TRADITION IS THE
PRE-GAME PRESIDENTIAL INTERVIEW.
IT GOES BACK TO THE VERY FIRST
SUPER BOWL, WHEN LYNDON JOHNSON
MADE THE SURPRISE ANNOUNCEMENT
THAT HE WAS SENDING BOTH TEAMS
TO VIETNAM.
( LAUGHTER )
YEAH.
>> Jon: OH, WOW.
>> Stephen: FUN FACT: THAT'S HOW
THE N.F.L. DRAFT STARTED.
( LAUGHTER )
>> Jon: OH, MY!
>> Stephen: LAST YEAR-- LAST
YEAR-- IS THIS LAST YEAR?
LAST YEAR, TRUMP SKIPPED THE
INTERVIEW.
BUT FRIDAY, HE SAT DOWN WITH
MARGARET BRENNAN OF CBS' "FACE
THE NATION," AND HE BROUGHT THE
NATION A WHOLE LOT OF FACE.
HE STARTED BY DESCRIBING HOW HE
BELIEVES HE'S IN A GOOD POSITION
TO DECLARE A NATIONAL EMERGENCY
TO GET HIS BORDER WALL, WHEN
NEGOTIATIONS WITH CONGRESS END
ON FEBRUARY 15.
>> WHEN YOU HAVE PEOPLE DYING
ALL OVER THE COUNTRY BECAUSE OF
PEOPLE LIKE NANCY PELOSI, WHO
DON'T WANT TO GIVE PROPER BORDER
SECURITY FOR POLITICAL REASONS,
SHE'S DOING A TERRIBLE
DISSERVICE TO OUR COUNTRY.
AND ON THE 15th, WE HAVE NOW SET
THE TABLE BEAUTIFULLY.
>> Stephen: NOT A HOPEFUL SIGN.
BECAUSE WE ALL KNOW WHAT IT
LOOKS LIKE WHEN TRUMP SETS THE
TABLE BEAUTIFULLY.
( LAUGHTER )
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
"LOOK HOW BEAUTIFUL--
LOOK HOW--"
THE SUBJECT TURNED TO SPORTS,
WHEN BRENNAN ASKED IF TRUMP
WOULD LET A CHILD OF HIS PLAY
FOOTBALL.
>> IT'S VERY... IT'S VERY TOUGH
QUESTION, IT'S A VERY GOOD
QUESTION.
IF HE WANTED TO, YES.
WOULD I STEER HIM THAT WAY?
NO, I WOULDN'T.
>> WHY?
>> I WOULDN'T.
AND HE ACTUALLY PLAYS A LOT OF
SOCCER.
HE'S LIKING SOCCER.
AND A LOT OF PEOPLE, INCLUDING
ME, THOUGHT SOCCER WOULD
PROBABLY NEVER MAKE IT IN THIS
COUNTRY, BUT IT REALLY IS MOVING
FORWARD RAPIDLY.
>> Stephen: ( AS TRUMP )
"YES, WE TRIED TO KEEP SOCCER
OUT FOR A LONG TIME, BUT IT'S
HARD.
IT'S MOVING SO RAPIDLY.
THAT'S HOW THE CARAVAN DOES IT.
THEY JUST-- THEY JUST DRIBBLE
THEIR KIDS UP TO THE BORDER, AND
THEN, JUST A LITTLE BIT OF THAT,
A LITTLE BIT OF THIS, A LITTLE
BIT OF THAT.
DOT, DOT.
DOT.
A LITTLE DOT.
AND THEN-- AND THEN-- AND THEN
THEY BICYCLE-KICK THEM INTO
EL PASO, YELLING, 'GOOOOAL'!
THAT'S REALLY WHY WE NEED THE
WALL.
BUT IT'S HARD TO BUILD WHEN YOU
CAN'T USE YOUR HANDS.
SOCCER, SOCCER."
SOCCER, JON.
>> Jon: SOCCER?
IS THAT SOCCER?
IS IT?
>> Stephen: AND HE EXPLAINED HIS
CONCERNS ABOUT FOOTBALL.
>> I JUST DON'T LIKE THE REPORTS
THAT I SEE COMING OUT HAVING TO
DO WITH FOOTBALL.
>> CONCUSSIONS?
>> YEAH, CONCUSSIONS AND OTHER
THINGS-- KNEES AND HIPS AND
SHOULDERS AND ELBOWS, AND
EVERYTHING ELSE.
>> Stephen: ( AS TRUMP )
♪ "HEADS, SHOULDERS, KNEES AND
TOES, KNEES AND TOES
♪ EYES AND EARS AND MOUTH AND,
MANY PEOPLE SAY-- AND I'M
HEARING THIS A LOT-- AND NOSE."
BUT, HERE'S THE DEAL.
TRUMP'S NOT GOING TO BE
PRESIDENT FOREVER.
WE BARELY--
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jon: WOOOO!
>> Stephen: WHO KNOWS?
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
WE'RE BARELY A MONTH INTO 2019,
>> Stephen: WHO KNOWS?
AND WE'VE ALREADY GOT AT LEAST
WE'RE BARELY A MONTH INTO 2019,
TEN DIFFERENT CANDIDATES HOPING
AND WE'VE ALREADY GOT AT LEAST
TO SECURE THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY'S
TEN DIFFERENT CANDIDATES HOPING
NOMINATION, BECAUSE ON FRIDAY
TO SECURE THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY'S
ANOTHER DEMOCRAT ENTERED THE
NOMINATION, BECAUSE ON FRIDAY
RACE: NEW JERSEY SENATOR AND MAN
ANOTHER DEMOCRAT ENTERED THE
TRYING TO PASS UNIVERSAL HEALTH
RACE: NEW JERSEY SENATOR AND MAN
CARE WITH HIS MIND, COREY
TRYING TO PASS UNIVERSAL HEALTH
BOOKER.
CARE WITH HIS MIND, COREY
HERE'S A LITTLE TASTE OF COREY
BOOKER.
BOOKER'S VIDEO ANNOUNCEMENT:
HERE'S A LITTLE TASTE OF COREY
>> WHEN I WAS A BABY, MY PARENTS
BOOKER'S VIDEO ANNOUNCEMENT:
TRIED TO MOVE US INTO A
>> WHEN I WAS A BABY, MY PARENTS
NEIGHBORHOOD WITH GREAT PUBLIC
TRIED TO MOVE US INTO A
SCHOOLS.
NEIGHBORHOOD WITH GREAT PUBLIC
BUT REALTORS WOULDN'T SELL US A
SCHOOLS.
HOME BECAUSE OF THE COLOR OF OUR
BUT REALTORS WOULDN'T SELL US A
SKIN.
HOME BECAUSE OF THE COLOR OF OUR
SO, OVER 20 YEARS AGO, I MOVED
SKIN.
INTO THE CENTRAL WARD OF NEWARK
SO, OVER 20 YEARS AGO, I MOVED
TO FIGHT SLUMLORDS AND HELP
INTO THE CENTRAL WARD OF NEWARK
FAMILIES STAY IN THEIR HOMES.
TO FIGHT SLUMLORDS AND HELP
I STILL LIVE THERE TODAY.
FAMILIES STAY IN THEIR HOMES.
>> Stephen: THAT IS INSPIRING.
I STILL LIVE THERE TODAY.
AND, I'VE GOT TO SAY, DARING.
>> Stephen: THAT IS INSPIRING.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYONE SO PROUD
AND, I'VE GOT TO SAY, DARING.
TO BE FROM NEWARK.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYONE SO PROUD
NEWARK: HOME OF THE AIRPORT YOU
TO BE FROM NEWARK.
DIDN'T REALIZE YOU WERE LANDING
NEWARK: HOME OF THE AIRPORT YOU
AT.
DIDN'T REALIZE YOU WERE LANDING
( LAUGHTER )
AT.
COME BECAUSE YOU'RE LOST.
( LAUGHTER )
STAY BECAUSE YOU'RE LOST!
COME BECAUSE YOU'RE LOST.
( LAUGHTER )
STAY BECAUSE YOU'RE LOST!
REMEMBER WHEN ALL THOSE PARKED
( LAUGHTER )
CARS CAUGHT ON FIRE?
REMEMBER WHEN ALL THOSE PARKED
THAT WAS THIS WEEK!
CARS CAUGHT ON FIRE?
THIS WEEK, IN NEWARK.
THAT WAS THIS WEEK!
( LAUGHTER )
THIS WEEK, IN NEWARK.
AND, THERE WAS A LOT OF NOT-SO-
( LAUGHTER )
SUBTLE ANTI-TRUMP MESSAGING IN
AND, THERE WAS A LOT OF NOT-SO-
THIS AD.
SUBTLE ANTI-TRUMP MESSAGING IN
BOOKER TELLS A STORY OF A RACIST
THIS AD.
LANDLORD TURNING AWAY HIS
BOOKER TELLS A STORY OF A RACIST
PARENTS, IMAGERY OF KIDS IN
LANDLORD TURNING AWAY HIS
CAGES.
PARENTS, IMAGERY OF KIDS IN
AND, OF COURSE, A SCENE OF HIM
CAGES.
IN A BARBER SHOP.
AND, OF COURSE, A SCENE OF HIM
WHICH IS AN OBVIOUS DIG AT
IN A BARBER SHOP.
TRUMP, SINCE IT IMPLIES BOOKER
WHICH IS AN OBVIOUS DIG AT
COULD GROW HAIR BUT CHOOSES NOT
TRUMP, SINCE IT IMPLIES BOOKER
TO.
COULD GROW HAIR BUT CHOOSES NOT
( LAUGHTER )
TO.
BUT, BUT--
( LAUGHTER )
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
BUT, BUT--
BUT BOOKER'S TAKING A REAL RISK
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
WITH THE NAME OF HIS CAMPAIGN:
BUT BOOKER'S TAKING A REAL RISK
CORY 2020.
WITH THE NAME OF HIS CAMPAIGN:
BOLD MOVE, GOING WITH A FIRST
CORY 2020.
NAME.
BOLD MOVE, GOING WITH A FIRST
IF YOU'LL RECALL, THAT DID NOT
NAME.
WORK OUT TOO WELL FOR "JEB!
IF YOU'LL RECALL, THAT DID NOT
2016."
WORK OUT TOO WELL FOR "JEB!
ALSO, I DON'T KNOW HOW I FEEL
2016."
ABOUT HAVING A "PRESIDENT CORY."
ALSO, I DON'T KNOW HOW I FEEL
IT SOUNDS LIKE A DISNEY SHOW.
ABOUT HAVING A "PRESIDENT CORY."
( LAUGHTER )
IT SOUNDS LIKE A DISNEY SHOW.
PROBABLY BECAUSE IT WAS A DISNEY
( LAUGHTER )
SHOW.
PROBABLY BECAUSE IT WAS A DISNEY
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
SHOW.
WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
TONIGHT!
WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
CONAN O'BRIEN IS HERE.
TONIGHT!
BUT WHEN I RETURN, I BECOME A
CONAN O'BRIEN IS HERE.
PLAYER IN "MADDEN NFL 19".
BUT WHEN I RETURN, I BECOME A
STICK AROUND.
PLAYER IN "MADDEN NFL 19".
I'M A MONSTER OF THE MIDWAY!
STICK AROUND.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
I'M A MONSTER OF THE MIDWAY!
( BAND PLAYING )
Nosy neighbor...
with a keen sense of smell.
Glad bag full of trash
What happens next?
Nothing.
Only Glad has Febreze
to neutralize odors for 5 days.
Guaranteed.
Even the most perceptive noses
won't notice the trash.
Be Happy, It's Glad™.
With Advil Liqui-Gels,
you'll ask...
What stiff joints?
What bad back?
Advil is... Relief that's
fast. Strength that lasts.
You'll ask...
What pain?
With Advil Liqui-Gels.
I'll take a Coke.
Is Pepsi Ok?
Is Pepsi, OK?
Is Pepsi, OK!?
[laughter]
Are puppies, OK?
Is a shooting star, OK?
Is the laughter of
a small child, OK?
Pepsi's more than, OK!
It's
Okayyyy
Okurrrr
♪ I Like It ♪
Okay, what have
we learned today?
You want a Pepsi?
I want a Pepsi.
There you go.
Okurrr. Aaahh.
I've got to come up with
my own catch phrase.
Okayyy
♪ When you have nausea, ♪
♪ heartburn, ♪
♪ indigestion, ♪
♪ upset stomach, ♪
♪ diarrhea... ♪
Girl, Pepto ultra coating will
treat your stomach right.
♪Nausea, heartburn, ♪
♪ indigestion, upset stomach,♪
♪ diarrhea... ♪
Try Pepto with Ultra coating.
Introducing high-rise
Rockstar 24/7 denim
now with sculpt.
Hurry in to Old Navy for
all jeans on sale
up to fifty percent off.
With kids from eight dollars,
adults from fifteen dollars,
only at Old Navy.
With Expedia,
I saved when I added
a hotel to our flight.
So even when
she grows up,
she'll never outgrow the
memory of our adventure.
Unlock savings
when you add
select hotels to your
existing trip.
Only with Expedia.
NEW Theraflu PowerPods.
The cold and flu fighting
exi machine.p.
You put in your machine.
Press the button to brew up
powerful relief.
To defeat your toughest
cold and flu symptoms fast.
NEW Theraflu PowerPods.
Press. Sip. Relief.
( BAND PLAYING )
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: JON BATISTE AND STAY
HUMAN, EVERYBODY, RIGHT OVER
THERE.
GIVE IT UP FOR THE BAND.
THERE YOU GO.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
JON, BOOM.
>> Jon: YEAH.
>> Stephen: JON, I'M PRETTY
EXCITED.
WE HAVE OUR OLD FRIEND CONAN
O'BRIEN COMING OUT HERE IN JUST
A MINUTE.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jon: GREAT GUY.
I LOVE CONAN.
>> Stephen: JAMES TAYLOR.
JAMES TAYLOR WILL PERFORM HERE
TONIGHT IN THE ED SULLIVAN
THEATRE.
AND WE HAVE A SPECIAL LITTLE
GAME WE WILL BE PLAYING WITH OUR
FRIEND STEVE CARELL.
HE'S GOING TO BE HERE TONIGHT,
TOO.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jon: OH, YEAH, YOU ALL GO WAY
BACK.
>> Stephen: THIS IS THE SUPER
BOWL.
>> Jon: YEAH, YOU GOTTA DO IT.
>> Stephen: TONIGHT IS THE SUPER
BOWL OF LATE-NIGHT SHOWS, I'VE
GOT TO SAY.
RIGHT NOW.
ALSO, TOMORROW, TARAJI P.
HENSON IS GOING TO BE HERE.
THAT'S GOING TO BE FANTASTIC.
NEVER INTERVIEWED THEM BEFORE.
RIGHT, FIRST TIME?
OF COURSE, AS I SAID, THIS IS
OUR SUPER BOWL SPECIAL, AND I
LOVE FOOTBALL.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO PLAY THE
GAME PROFESSIONALLY, BUT MY
DOCTOR SAYS I CAN'T BECAUSE I
HAVE A MEDICAL CONDITION KNOWN
AS "MORTALITY."
( LAUGHTER )
BUT THERE IS SOME FOOTBALL I AM
HEALTHY ENOUGH TO PARTICIPATE
IN: THE VIDEO GAME KIND.
AND, LUCKILY, THE GOOD FOLKS
OVER AT E.A. SPORTS AGREED TO
MAKE ME A PLAYER IN THE NEW
"MADDEN NFL 19."
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jon: YEAH!
>> Stephen: HERE'S THE DEAL: I
WAS EXCITED, OBVIOUSLY.
BUT IN ORDER TO MAKE THE MOST
LIFELIKE AND ACCURATE DIGITAL
VERSION OF ME, THEY FIRST NEEDED
HARD DATA ON MY ATHLETIC
ABILITIES.
( LAUGHTER )
SO, I HEADED DOWN TO THE
ATLANTIC HEALTH NEW YORK JETS
TRAINING CENTER AND PUT MY
SKILLS TO THE TEST.
STEPHEN COLBERT, NORTHWESTERN
UNIVERSITY, THEATER MAJOR.
( N.F.L. MUSIC )
>> Stephen (narrating): I'VE
ALWAYS BEEN TOLD I DON'T HAVE
WHAT IT TAKES TO PLAY
PROFESSIONAL FOOTBALL, AND THAT
IS TRUE.
LUCKILY, THE FINE PEOPLE AT
"MADDEN NFL 19" AGREED TO PUT ME
IN THEIR GAME.
SO, I MET WITH LEAD PLAYER-
RATINGS ADJUSTER, DUSTIN SMITH,
SO HE COULD RANK MY
FOOTBALLYNESS.
>> Stephen: DUSTIN, CAN I CALL
YOU DUSTY?
>> UH...
>> Stephen: DUSTY, WHAT'S
CONSIDERED A GOOD SCORE?
WHAT'S THE SCALE HERE?
>> 99'S THE BEST.
>> Stephen: OKAY.
WHAT TYPE OF THINGS ARE YOU
GOING TO BE JUDGING ME IN TODAY,
DUSTY?
>> STRENGTH, SPEED, THROW POWER,
KICK POWER, KICK ACCURACY,
CATCHING, JUMPING.
>> Stephen: THERE'S NO BLOOD
TEST TODAY IS THERE?
BECAUSE I'M HIGH AS A KITE RIGHT
NOW.
( LAUGHTER )
ANY TIME I KNOW I NEED TO USE MY
KNEES, I GET AN EPIDURAL.
WHAT DO YOU THINK MY RATING'S
GOING TO BE?
>> CONSERVATIVE 20.
>> Stephen (narrating): TO HELP
ME FIGURE OUT JUST WHERE I
STAND, WE BROUGHT IN 6'4" NEW
YORK JETS QUARTERBACK, SAM
DARNOLD.
SAM.
>> SIR.
>> Stephen: THANKS SO MUCH FOR
TALKING TO ME TODAY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Stephen: HOW OLD ARE YOU?
>> I'M 21-YEARS-OLD.
YEAH.
( LAUGHTER )
>> Stephen: AND THE FACT THAT
YOU ARE YOUNGER THAN MY OLDEST
CHILD IS IN NO WAY DEPRESSING TO
ME.
>> NO.
IT'S NOT A CONCERN, IS IT?
>> Stephen: NOPE.
NO, IT'S NOT.
SINCE YOU'RE ON THE JETS, DO YOU
EVER, LIKE, FEEL LIKE BREAKING
OUT INTO SINGING SONGS FROM
"WEST SIDE STORY"?
>> UMM.
♪ WHEN YOU'RE A JET, YOU'RE A
JET ALL THE WAY
♪ FROM YOUR FIRST CIGARETTE TO
YOUR? ♪
>> OH, GOSH.
♪ I LIKE TO LIVE IN AMERICA ♪
COME ON.
WE GOT IT.
>> WHERE IS DUSTY?
BRING IN DUSTY.
>> Stephen: LET'S DO THIS.
>> I CAN'T DANCE.
>> Stephen: IT WAS TIME FOR MY
FIRST OFFICIAL TEST, CATCHING.
>> READY, SET, HUT.
YOU HAVE TO JUMP UP AND GRAB IT.
>> Stephen: WHAT THE HELL WAS
THAT?
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
>> YOU'VE GOT TO JUMP UP AND GET
THAT BALL.
>> Stephen: HOW TALL DO YOU
THINK I AM?
>> HUT.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> Stephen: YOU THROW THAT
REALLY HARD.
>> HUT.
OH, THAT WAS SWEET!
( APPLAUSE )
>> THAT WAS REALLY COOL.
>> NOT BAD.
>> AND THE SPIN.
>> Stephen (narrating): NEXT UP:
THROW UNDER PRESSURE.
>> THROW UNDER PRESSURE.
>> Stephen: THROW UNDER
PRESSURE.
YOU SEE THAT?
YOU COULD CUT A DIAMOND.
ALL RIGHT, BRING IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
GUYS?
♪ ♪ ♪
>> Stephen: HI, STEPHEN.
HI, STEPHEN.
HI, NICE TO MEET YOU.
THIS IS A COMEDY SHOW.
OBVIOUSLY, YOU GUYS WERE TOLD
THAT THIS IS A COMEDY SHOW?
GOOD.
SET, HUT!
>> THAT'S GOT TO BE, LIKE, THE
WORST.
>> OKAY.
>> 18.
>> Stephen: WHAT THE ( BLEEP ).
I DON'T THINK DUSTIN'S GIVEN ME
A FAIR SHAKE.
I MEAN... I'M A 54-YEAR-OLD MAN.
I MEAN, THE DOCTOR SAID I'D
NEVER BE ABLE TO COMB MY HAIR
AGAIN.
( LAUGHTER )
IT'S LIKE HE DOESN'T EVEN SEE
HOW I'M TRYING.
PLEASE DON'T USE THIS.
PROMISE ME.
>> Stephen (narrating): BACK ON
THE FIELD, BECAUSE IT'S TIME FOR
SPEED.
>> Stephen: OKAY, WHEN YOU'RE
READY TO GO, JUST SAY, JUST YELL
"JUICE IT."
>> "JUICE IT."
YOU GOT IT.
>> Stephen: I'M JUST TRYING TO
DETERMINE WHICH KNEE I WANT TO
POP FIRST.
( LAUGHTER )
>> JUICE IT!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> LOOK AT THAT.
>> Stephen: WOOOOO!
>> Stephen (narrating): THEN MY
JUKE MOVE.
>> Stephen: I'LL JUKE YOU!
WATCH OUT!
WOO!
HERE WE GO!
>> Stephen (narrating): AND,
WOO!
FINALLY, TRUCKING.
>> Stephen (narrating): AND,
>> I'M GOING TO NEED YOU TO
FINALLY, TRUCKING.
KNOCK OVER ONE OF THESE BIG
>> I'M GOING TO NEED YOU TO
FELLOWS, AND YOU STAY ON YOUR
KNOCK OVER ONE OF THESE BIG
FEET AND KEEP GOING.
FELLOWS, AND YOU STAY ON YOUR
( LAUGHTER )
FEET AND KEEP GOING.
>> Stephen: HUT!
( LAUGHTER )
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
AND TIME FOR MY FINAL RATING.
WHAT IS MY PLAYER RATING?
AND THE IMPORTANT THING IS THAT
I NEED TO REALLY KNOW.
AND THIS IS IMPORTANT.
THIS IS ON TELEVISION.
YOU HAVE TO TELL ME THE TRUTH.
AND DON'T WORRY ABOUT MY
FEELINGS.
I HAVE A SUCCESSFUL CAREER.
I HAVE A BEAUTIFUL WIFE.
I HAVE WONDERFUL CHILDREN.
UM, JUST BE HONEST.
IT'S IMPORTANT THAT I-- I-- I
KNOW WHAT THE TRUTH IS, AND
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO HURT MY
FEELINGS.
>> OKAY.
SO, UH, OFFICIALLY, 19 OVERALL.
>> Stephen: STINGING FROM MY
UNFAIR RATING, I SWITCHED TO AN
ACTIVITY I EXCEL AT-- SITTING IN
A CHAIR.
TO CREATE MY DIGITAL PLAYER,
CERTIFIED E.A. NERD BEN
HAUMILLER ENTERED MY TEST
RESULTS.
SPEED, STRENGTH, AGILITY-- WHAT
HAS HE GOT ME FOR ELUSIVENESS?
>> 47.
>> Stephen: I CAN BE WAY MORE
ELUSIVE THAN THAT.
YOU WANT TO... I'LL SHOW YOU HOW
ELUSIVE I CAN BE.
>> OKAY.
>> Stephen: TELL ME YOU LOVE ME.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> Stephen: I DON'T DESERVE YOU.
( LAUGHTER )
SEE, YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHETHER I
LOVE YOU OR NOT.
>> I DON'T.
>> Stephen: AND, YET, I HAVEN'T
SAID ANYTHING BAD.
OKAY.
THAT'S ELUSIVE.
( LAUGHTER )
OKAY.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT ME.
HERE WE GO.
OKAY, THAT LOOKS LIKE ME.
LET'S DO-EY.
AND-- OH, GOOD, I'M WEARING
GLASSES.
SO FEW FOOTBALL PLAYERS DO.
IS THERE ANY WAY TO TAKE THIS
UNIFORM OFF?
BECAUSE I'VE NEVER SEEN ME WITH
ANYTHING APPROACHING A MALE
PHYSIQUE.
>> SO, WE ARE AN E-FOR-EVERYONE
GAME.
>> Stephen: OH, OKAY.
>> ACTUALLY, WOULD YOU LIKE TO
RUN A PLAY?
>> Stephen: SURE.
THERE I AM AS A QUARTERBACK, AND
I ALREADY HAVE A PENALTY.
WHAT THE HELL JUST HAPPENED?
WHAT DID I DO?
THERE I AM...
>> YOU'RE NOT... YOU'RE NOT
HAPPY AS A COACH, EITHER.
>> Stephen: WAIT A SECOND.
HOW OLD DID YOU MAKE ME AS THE
COACH?
>> OH, COME ON.
YOU'RE SMOOTHED OUT RIGHT THERE.
YOU'RE LOOKING ALL RIGHT.
>> Stephen: YOU LOOK LIKE YOU
CARVED MY HEAD OUT OF AN APPLE
CORE AND LET IT DRY IN THE SUN.
GOOD GOD, MAN.
ALL RIGHT.
IN THE POCKET.
BULLET.
AND... I SUCK.
I SUCK IN REAL LIFE.
WHY WOULD I WANT TO SUCK IN A
GAME?
LOOK, EVEN I'M MAD AT ME.
I AGREE WITH THAT GUY.
NOW, BEN.
>> YES?
>> Stephen: THIS IS ALL JUST
ZEROS AND ONES, RIGHT?
>> UH-HUH.
>> Stephen: WELL, WHAT IF I GAVE
YOU A ONE WITH TWO ZEROS BEHIND
IT?
WOULD THAT HELP CHANGE MY
PROFILE?
>> I LIKE THIS.
>> Stephen: THANK YOU.
>> Stephen (narrating): WITH
THAT AND JUST A FEW CLICKS, BEN
PUMPED UP ALL OF MY STATS AND
GAVE ME A TIGHT END.
OH, YEAH.
BO-BRO-DONK-A-DONK.
BACK IT UP LIKE A TONKA TRUCK
GOD, I'M MAGNIFICENT.
AND GO.
HERE WE GO.
DRILLS IT!
HERE COMES THE PAIN TRAIN!
ALL ABOARD!
>> TOUCHDOWN!
>> Stephen: WOOO!
HOW DO YOU LIKE ME NOW?
BOOM.
>> RIGHT THERE.
>> Stephen: WOOO!
WOOO!
OH, COME ON!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
WOOO!
>> Stephen: THANK YOU E.A.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
SPORTS.
>> Stephen: THANK YOU E.A.
THANK YOU, NEW YORK JETS.
SPORTS.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK WITH CONAN
THANK YOU, NEW YORK JETS.
O'BRIEN.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK WITH CONAN
♪ ♪ ♪
O'BRIEN.
( APPLAUSE )
When you find yourself
in a strange land...
discover your inner hero.
And unlock the power...
to speed through everything...
in the blink of an eye.
Hertz Fast Lane
powered by CLEAR...
in select airports 2019.
Hertz.
We're here to get you there.
Marvel Studios' Captain Marvel.
In theaters March 8th.
♪
Charmin Ultra Soft!
It's softer than ever.
Charmin Ultra Soft is
softer than ever...
so it's harder to resist.
Okay, this is getting a little
weird.
Enjoy the go!
With Charmin!
For mild-to-moderate eczema,
there's EUCRISA.
It's steroid-free.
Do not use if you are allergic
to EUCRISA or its ingredients.
Allergic reactions may occur
at or near the application site.
The most common side effect
is application site pain.
Ask your doctor about EUCRISA.
-Their Béarnaise sauce here
is the best in town.
[ Soft piano music playing ]
Mm, uh, what do you do for fun?
-Not this.
♪
-Oh, what am I into?
Mostly Progressive's
Name Your Price Tool.
Helps people find coverage
options based on their budget.
Flo has it, I want it,
it's a whole thing,
and she's right there.
-Yeah, she's my ride.
This date's lame.
He has pics of you on his phone.
-They're very tasteful.
Julie means more to me
than anything.
And I wanted to ask you
Before I ask her
May I have your permission
to marry her?
You're marrying her and
her whole world
Shop Neil Lane diamond
engagement rings...
...at KAY.
( BAND PLAYING )
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: WELCOME BACK,
EVERYBODY.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, MY FIRST
GUEST TONIGHT HAS WRITTEN FOR
"THE SIMPSONS" AND "S.N.L.," AND
AFTER 25 YEARS, HE'S THE ELDER
STATESMAN OF LATE-NIGHT HOSTS.
PLEASE WELCOME BACK TO SHOW, MY
FRIEND AND YOURS, CONAN O'BRIEN!
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
>> Stephen: CONAN O'BRIEN.
NICE TO SEE YOU.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> Stephen: THANK YOU FOR BEING
HERE.
>> A LOVELY CROWD.
THANK YOU.
>> Stephen: VERY DELIGHTED TO
SEE CONAN O'BRIEN.
>> WHAT A DAY.
WHAT A DAY.
>> Stephen: BACK ON THE EAST
COAST.
SO A TREAT FOR US.
>> BACK IN TOWN.
>> Stephen: FOR THE SUPER BOWL.
>> BIG DAY.
SUPER BOWL.
THAT WAS A CRAZY GAME.
>> Stephen: IT WAS.
( LAUGHTER )
YOU HAVE EXCITING NEWS, THE NEW
CONAN.
>> IT'S REALLY NOT.
IT'S THE SAME CONAN.
>> Stephen: YOU'RE THE SAME
CONAN BUT IT'S A NEW FORMAT.
>> IT'S A NEW FORMAT.
>> Stephen: NEW SET!
>> I'VE BEEN DOING IT FOR SO
LONG, LET'S DO HALF AN HOUR.
BECAUSE WE NOTICED THAT OUR
CROWD AFTER A HALF HOUR THEY'RE
LIKE, "WE'RE GOOD."
( LAUGHTER )
>> Stephen: REALLY?
( PIANO RIFF )
>> ANYWAY...
>> Stephen: I THINK-- I THINK IN
SHOW BUSINESS WE CALL THAT,
"LEAVE THEM WANTING SOME."
>> YEAH.
NO, EVEN AT HALF AN HOUR THEY'RE
LIKE, "YOU KNOW, YOU CAN GO TO
15."
SO--
( LAUGHTER )
>> Stephen: NOW, THERE'S--
TONIGHT, OBVIOUSLY, YOU'RE
DRESSED BEAUTIFULLY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Stephen: BUT SUEDE-- A SUEDE
JACKET.
>> YEAH.
>> Stephen: I'M SEEING-- I'M
SEEING A LOT MORE LEATHER
JACKETS.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> Stephen: DENIM, A LOT MORE
DENIM.
NO MORE SUITS--
>> YES, YES.
I LIKE TO LOOK LIKE A PROSPEROUS
FARMER, YOU KNOW?
( LAUGHTER )
A FARMER WHO HAS INVESTED WELL
IN HIGH-TECH.
THAT'S THE LOOK I'M GOING FOR.
>> Stephen: OKAY, UH-HUH...
>> NO, IT'S IMPORTANT TO ME.
I GOT TIRED OF WEARING A SUIT,
AND I THINK THE SUIT IS GREAT.
BUT I'VE DONE IT FOR SO MANY
YEARS --
>> Stephen: YOU SAID THAT LIKE
YOU'RE AFRAID TO HURT THE SUIT'S
FEELINGS.
( LAUGHTER )
"SUIT'S GREAT."
>> I'M SORRY, THERE'S A SUIT
HERE GOING, "COME ON, GIVE ME A
CHANCE."
( LAUGHTER )
NO, IT LOOKS GREAT.
IT LOOKS TERRIFIC.
>> Stephen: SURE.
>> BUT I FEEL LIKE YOU'RE
INTERVIEWING ME FOR A BANK LOAN.
( LAUGHTER )
AND I WANTED TO JUST SORT OF--
I'M A REAL HARD WORKER.
( LAUGHTER )
I WANTED TO KIND OF JUST WEAR
THE KIND OF CLOTHES THAT I DO IN
REAL LIFE.
THE ONLY THING THAT'S IMPORTANT
TO ME IS THAT I WEAR A JACKET.
I HAVE TO WEAR A JACKET.
>> Stephen: WHY IS THIS?
>> THANK YOU FOR ASKING.
( LAUGHTER )
>> Stephen: IT'S MY JOB.
IT'S MY JOB.
( LAUGHTER )
>> IT'S GOING JUST AS WE
REHEARSED.
I WEAR-- I HAVE TO WEAR A JACKET
BECAUSE I HAVE TO BREAK UP WHERE
MY-- THE MIDDLE OF MY BODY IS
BECAUSE I HAVE A-- AND THIS IS A
CONFESSION-- I HAVE A VERY
DISPROPORTIONATE BODY.
>> Stephen: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> WHEN I WAS 14 YEARS OLD, I
HAD A MASSIVE GROWTH SPURT,
MASSIVE.
I AM 6'4".
I BECAME-- I WENT FROM BEING A
KID TO 6'4" OVERNIGHT, LITERALLY
OVERNIGHT.
WHAT HAPPENED IS MY LEGS GREW
AND GREW AND GREW, AND MY TORSO
NEVER DID.
( LAUGHTER )
I HAVE THE LEGS-- THE LEGS OF AN
N.B.A. CENTER, AND I HAVE THE
TORSO OF A LITTLE GIRL.
( LAUGHTER )
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
SHE'S NOT EVEN A HEALTHY LITTLE
GIRL.
SHE WAS BORN IN THE 1840s, HER
NAME IS MOLLY AND SHE HAS
RICKETS.
( LAUGHTER )
>> Stephen: WE ACTUALLY HAVE AN
IMAGE OF YOUR TORSO.
>> OH, THAT'S GREAT.
THAT'S MY TORSO RIGHT THERE.
THAT WAS FROM A LONG TIME.
>> Stephen: THAT'S CONAN RIGHT
THERE.
>> OKAY.
THANKS.
THANKS FOR SHOWING THAT.
>> Stephen: YOU LOOK FINE.
>> THANK YOU.
THAT'S FUNNY.
NO ONE MENTIONED YOU WOULD BE
SHOWING THAT PHOTO.
>> Stephen: KEEP UP THE B-12.
>> YEAH.
BUT IT IS, I HAVE-- AND SO I
HAVE VERY, VERY LONG LEGS, AND
THEN THIS TINY LITTLE TORSO THAT
SITS ATOP.
AND PEOPLE THINK I AM
EXAGGERATING, BUT I CAN PROVE TO
YOU THAT I AM NOT--
( CHEERS )
NO.
LOOK AT THIS-- THIS...
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
THIS IS MY NATURAL...
AND, LOOK, STEPHEN.
>> Stephen: YES?
>> I LOOK LIKE A SHORE BIRD
AVOIDING AN OIL SPILL, DON'T I?
( LAUGHTER )
IT'S JUST A FREAK SHOW.
AND THEN I HAVE THIS LITTLE R2-
D2 BODY ON TOP.
( MAKES R2-D2 NOISES )
IT'S A FREAK SHOW.
>> Stephen: IT IS.
>> IT'S A FREAK SHOW AND IT'S
CAUSED ME--
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: IT IS.
>> AND I HAVE--
>> Stephen: NO-- NO PHOTOGRAPHS.
NO PAPIER-MÂCHÉ.
HE IS ALIVE.
>> HE IS ALIVE.
HE'S ALIVE!
AND MY PANTS, I'M ALWAYS PUSHING
THEM DOWN.
THEY'RE PUSHED DOWN NOW.
THEY ARE ARTIFICIALLY PUSHED
DOWN.
MY PENIS IS HERE.
( LAUGHTER )
WHEN I USE A URINAL, I HAVE TO
FLIP THE TIE BACK!
( LAUGHTER )
UNBUTTON TWO BUTTONS, LADIES,
NOT ONE.
LEAN DOWN, TAKE CARE OF
BUSINESS.
>> Stephen: SURE.
SURE.
>> IT'S A BAD SCENE, MAN.
>> Stephen: SURE.
>> A REAL BAD SCENE.
>> Stephen: SO, NO MORE SUITS.
NO MORE SUITS.
>> YOU BREAK IT UP A LITTLE BIT.
I REALIZE I JUST UNDID ALL THE
GOOD I'M TRYING TO DO BY
DISPLAYING MY BODY.
BUT, YEAH, IT'S BEEN A SOURCE OF
GREAT SHAME FOR ME AND I WANT
OTHER KIDS OUT THERE--
>> Stephen: I'M GLAD, I'M GLAD.
>> YOU'RE GLAD THAT I FEEL
SHAME?
>> Stephen: YES, A LITTLE SHAME
IS A GOOD THING.
>> IT'S A VERY GOOD THING.
>> Stephen: AFTER 25 YEARS ON
THE AIR, THE SHOW HAS CHANGED.
WHAT ELSE-- WHAT ELSE HAVE YOU
LEARNED ABOUT YOURSELF OVER THE
YEARS?
BECAUSE, CERTAINLY, YOU-- WHEN
YOU DO ONE OF THESE SHOWS, YOU
LEARN WHAT YOU'RE CAPABLE OF.
>> RIGHT.
>> Stephen: BUT THEN YOU'LL FIND
OUT THINGS ABOUT YOURSELF THAT
YOU NEVER KNEW.
>> YES.
I FOUND OUT-- AND THIS ISN'T
EVEN THROUGH THE SHOW, THIS IS
JUST LIFE, AS YOU GO ON IN LIFE.
WHEN I STARTED MY SHOW, I HAD
JUST TURNED 30, I DIDN'T KNOW
WHO I WAS YET.
I'VE GROWN UP AND BECOME SORT OF
A MAN.
( LAUGHTER )
ON TELEVISION, OVER THESE LAST
25 YEARS.
BUT I'M FINDING OUT NEW THINGS
ALL THE TIME.
I FOUND OUT-- I WENT TO SEE MY
DOCTOR A COUPLE OF MONTHS AGO.
AND-- JUST FOR A PHYSICAL.
HE WAS DOING THE PHYSICAL.
AND HE SAID, "BY THE WAY, CONAN,
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'RE INTO
THIS, BUT I DO D.N.A. TESTING.
I'M VERY GOOD AT IT.
WE COULD FIND OUT ABOUT YOUR
HERITAGE."
I THINK SOME PEOPLE HAVE DONE
THAT-- 23ANDME.
I SAID "SURE, LET'S DO IT."
SO, HE TOOK A D.N.A. SAMPLE, AND
I LEFT.
TWO WEEKS LATER HE CALLED ME UP.
AND HE SAID, "I HAVE NEVER,
EVER, EVER HAD A D.N.A. RESULT
LIKE THIS BEFORE, AND I'VE BEEN
DOING THIS FOR 10 YEARS."
AND I SAID, "WHAT IS IT?"
AND HE SAID "YOU ARE"-- AND THIS
IS TRUE-- "YOU ARE 100% IRISH."
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
NOW, LISTEN, THERE'S MORE.
HOLD IT.
HE SAID, "YOU ARE 100%."
HE SAID, "I'VE NEVER SEEN A 100%
ANYTHING."
HE SAID "I'VE BEEN DOING THIS A
LOT.
I'VE DONE THIS WITH LOTS OF
PEOPLE.
I'VE SEEN 93.5.
I'VE SEEN 96.1.
THERE'S NO SUCH-- NO ONE IS 100%
IRISH."
HE SAID, "IF YOU GO TO
IRELAND"... AND I LOOKED IT UP
AND IT'S TRUE, AND YOU GET THEIR
D.N.A. SAMPLES AND YOU WILL FIND
OUT THE MOST IRISH-LOOKING
PEOPLE ARE LIKE 86% IRISH, 94%
IRISH.
THE LUCKY CHARMS LEPRECHAUN--
TRUE FACT-- 11% SPANISH.
AND--
( LAUGHTER )
I-- HE SAID, "YOU'RE 100%."
AND I SAID-- I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT
TO MAKE OF THIS.
I SAID, "WHAT DOES IT MEAN?"
HE SAID, "WHAT DOES IT MEAN?"
HE SAD "IT MEANS YOU'RE INBRED."
( LAUGHTER )
AND HE SAID IT-- HE SAID IT JUST
LIKE THAT!
HE SAID IT LIKE THAT, "YOU'RE
INBRED."
AND I WAS LIKE, "WHAT!"
FIRST OF ALL, THAT'S VERY RUDE.
( LAUGHTER )
BUT THEN ALL THIS STUFF STARTED
TO MAKE SENSE TO ME, YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN?
SUDDENLY, EVERYTHING CAME
TOGETHER.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: WELL, CAN I ASK-- IF
YOU DON'T MIND ME ASKING, IN
YOUR GENERATION, IS YOUR WIFE
IRISH?
DID YOU MARRY--
>> HERE'S WHAT WHERE IT GETS
CRAZY, OKAY.
BECAUSE I-- YOU KNOW, I LOOKED
INTO IT, AND I FOUND OUT THE
REASON I'M 100% IRISH IS THAT MY
PEOPLE-- WE CAME TO BOSTON
AROUND THE TIME OF THE CIVIL
WAR.
WE JUST ALL MOVED INTO A VERY
SMALL AREA, A CORNER OF
WORCESTER, MASSACHUSETTS--
>> WOO!
>> DON'T WOOO WORCESTER.
NOBODY WOOOS WORCESTER.
( LAUGHTER )
IT'S UN-WOOABLE.
ANYWAY, THEY MOVED INTO A SMALL
CORNER OF WORCESTER,
MASSACHUSETTS, ALL LIVED IN ONE
HOUSE AND MARRIED EACH OTHER FOR
180 YEARS.
THAT'S WHAT THEY DID.
AND I REALIZED-- AND THEN I SAW
THAT MY BROTHERS WERE MARRYING
100% IRISH WOMEN.
AND HAVING KIDS THAT LOOKED LIKE
THOSE KIDS THAT WOULD BE LIKE,
"WE'RE OFF TO GET ON THE
'TITANIC.'
IT WILL ALL GO WELL."
( LAUGHTER )
SO IRISH LOOKING.
AND SO I-- I-- I STOPPED THE
MADNESS.
I STOPPED THE MADNESS.
LET ME TELL YOU ABOUT MY WIFE--
I'VE BEEN MARRIED FOR 17 YEARS.
I LOVE HER TO DEATH.
MY WIFE IS 50% IRISH.
( LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE )
25% SCOTTISH.
( LAUGHTER )
25% WELSH.
AND I SWEAR TO GOD, IN MY
FAMILY, THEY ACT LIKE, "CONAN
GOT JUNGLE FEVER."
( LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE )
MY BROTHERS ARE LIKE, "WHAT'S IT
LIKE, MAN?
YOU WENT CRAZY!"
>> Stephen: "CONAN" AIRS
WEEKNIGHTS ON TBS, AND NEW
EPISODES OF THE PODCAST "CONAN
O'BRIEN NEEDS A FRIEND" ARE
AVAILABLE EVERY MONDAY.
CONAN O'BRIEN, EVERYBODY!
WHEN WE COME, BACK I SHARE SOME
PERSONAL SPACE WITH STEVE
CARELL.
THANK YOU, CONAN!
skin wants to drink!ater'sr
With hard water skin can dry
out more.
Culligan Water's what your
skin's crying out for!
Cos skin is important whether
you're a baby or bald,
That's why we say get a Culligan
water softener installed!
(Thunderclap)
If your day doesn't
unfold as predicted.
Unfold this.
New Neutrogena®
Makeup Remover single.
And remove 99% of makeup.
100% rain or shine.
Neutrogena®.
I'M MISSING OUT ON
OUR FAMILY OUTINGS
BECAUSE I CAN'T FIND A BLADDER
LEAKAGE PRODUCT THAT FITS.
EVERYTHING WAS TOO LOOSE.
BUT DEPEND® FIT-FLEX®
FEELS TAILORED TO ME.
WITH A RANGE OF SIZES
FOR ALL BODY TYPES.
DEPEND® FIT-FLEX® UNDERWEAR
IS GUARANTEED TO
BE YOUR BEST FIT.
Why shop Marshalls?
Because...
Their prices will thrill you.
Whoo-hoo!
The brands will surprise you.
Mwah!
And every trip feels
like an instant victory.
Woman:
Marshalls.
Never boring.
Always surprising.
Woman:
Marshalls.
I can't believe it.
That there's a lobster
in our hot tub?
Lobster: Oh, you guys.
There's a jet!
Oh...I needed this.
No, I can't believe how
easy it was
to save hundreds of dollars on
our car insurance with GEICO.
We could have been doing
this a long time ago.
So, you guys staying
at the hotel?
Yeah, we just got married.
Oh ho-ho! Congratulations!
Thank you.
Yeah, I'm afraid of
commitment...
and being boiled alive.
Oh, shoot.
Believe it.
GEICO could save you 15% or more
on car insurance.
That guy's the worst.
You.
All of you.
How you live,
what you love.
That's what inspired
us to create
America's most
advanced internet.
Internet that puts
you in charge.
That protects
what's important.
It handles everything,
and reaches everywhere.
This is beyond WiFi,
this is xFi.
Simple. Easy. Awesome.
Xfinity, the
future of awesome.
( BAND PLAYING )
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: HEY, EVERYBODY,
WELCOME BACK.
NOW STEVE, OBVIOUSLY WE'VE KNOWN
EACH OTHER A LONG, LONG TIME.
>> YEAH.
>> Stephen: BUT YOU'RE A VERY
PRIVATE PERSON.
YOU KNOW?
>> SO ARE YOU.
>> Stephen: YEAH.
AND, BUT, YOU KNOW, DOING THESE
INTERVIEWS SOMETIMES CAN FEEL
FALSE, OR KIND OF FORCED, IN
FRONT OF AN AUDIENCE.
BECAUSE I KNOW YOU'RE BEING
HONEST AND YOU'RE TELLING ME HOW
YOU REALLY FEEL, BUT THERE'S AN
AUDIENCE HERE WATCHING US.
>> RIGHT.
YOU HAVE TO MONITOR YOURSELF, I
THINK.
>> Stephen: AND ALSO THERE'S A
LITTLE BIT OF A PERFORMANCE
ENERGY.
>> SURE.
>> Stephen: PUTTING ON A FACE
FOR THE FACES THAT YOU MEET.
I'D LOVE TO TAKE A MOMENT JUST
TO TALK TO YOU IN A MORE
PERSONAL, LIKE, UP-CLOSE WAY.
LIKE, IN A PRIVATE SPACE.
>> I WOULD REALLY LOVE THAT.
( LAUGHTER )
>> Stephen: WELL, I'M SO GLAD TO
HEAR THAT.
JOIN US NOW IN THE "LATE SHOW'S"
PERSONAL SPACE.
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: STEVE...
( APPLAUSE )
LONGTIME VIEWERS WILL KNOW THIS
IS THE "LATE SHOW'S" PERSONAL
SPACE.
STEVE CARELL, I'LL SEE YOU IN
THE BOX.
( LAUGHTER )
WE'VE KNOWN EACH OTHER FOR 30
YEARS.
RIGHT?
1988.
>> IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME.
>> Stephen: YEAH.
HONESTLY, STEVE, WHAT WAS YOUR
FIRST IMPRESSION OF ME?
>> WELL, IF I'M COMPLETELY
HONEST, YOU WERE VERY HANDSOME.
YOU WERE TALENTED, INTELLIGENT,
AND THERE WAS A CERTAIN JOIRE DE
VIVE YOU HAD, THAT FELT LIKE IT,
IT WAS JUST DIFFERENT THAN THE
OTHER GUYS AT SECOND CITY.
>> Stephen: OH, THANKS SO MUCH,
MAN.
>> WHAT WAS YOUR FIRST
IMPRESSION OF ME?
>> Stephen: HE IS GOING TO BE SO
HANDSOME IN HIS LATE 50s.
( LAUGHTER )
I MEAN, REALLY, THAT GUY IS
GOING TO BLOSSOM.
>> THAT'S SO NICE.
>> Stephen: WHY DID YOU WAIT SO
LONG TO GET SEXY?
( LAUGHTER )
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
I JUST-- I JUST FIGURED IT WAS--
IT WAS ABOUT TIME.
( LAUGHTER )
>> Stephen: UH-HUH.
YOU ARE AWARE THAT, NOW, YOU ARE
A HOT, SALT-AND-PEPPER ZATTY,
RIGHT?
( LAUGHTER )
YOU HAVE TO HAVE HEARD THIS,
RIGHT?
>> NO.
( LAUGHTER )
>> Stephen: CAN'T GET OUT OF THE
BOX!
CAN'T-- YOU'RE STUCK IN THE BOX.
>> YOU'RE EMBARRASSING ME!
( LAUGHTER )
>> Stephen: ARE YOU EVER SICK OF
PEOPLE QUOTING "THE OFFICE" TO
YOU?
>> NO, I LOVE IT.
>> Stephen: THAT'S WHAT SHE
SAID.
( LAUGHTER )
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> CAN I ADMIT SOMETHING TO YOU?
>> Stephen: YOU CAN, IT'S
PERSONAL SPACE, STEVE.
>> THE COMPONENTS OF BOTH OF OUR
BREATH...
( LAUGHTER )
... IS REALLY WARM.
>> Stephen: IT IS-- IT IS
( LAUGHTER )
GETTING A LITTLE STEAMY IN HERE.
>> Stephen: IT IS-- IT IS
WOULD YOU, WOULD YOU-- WOULD YOU
GETTING A LITTLE STEAMY IN HERE.
LIKE-- YOU USED TO BE-- YOU'RE
WOULD YOU, WOULD YOU-- WOULD YOU
FAMOUSLY A BIT OF A SWEATER?
LIKE-- YOU USED TO BE-- YOU'RE
>> YEAH.
FAMOUSLY A BIT OF A SWEATER?
>> Stephen: YEAH, WOULD YOU--
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S HAPPENING.
>> Stephen: YEAH, WOULD YOU--
( LAUGHTER )
>> IT'S HAPPENING.
>> Stephen: IT IS.
( LAUGHTER )
IT IS.
>> Stephen: IT IS.
WOULD YOU-- WOULD YOU LIKE A
IT IS.
FAN?
WOULD YOU-- WOULD YOU LIKE A
>> SURE.
FAN?
DO YOU HAVE A FAN?
>> SURE.
( LAUGHTER )
DO YOU HAVE A FAN?
>> Stephen: HOW'S THAT FEEL?
( LAUGHTER )
IS THAT GOOD?
>> Stephen: HOW'S THAT FEEL?
>> THAT'S ACTUALLY A LOT BETTER.
IS THAT GOOD?
>> Stephen: THAT IS REALLY
>> THAT'S ACTUALLY A LOT BETTER.
DANGEROUSLY CLOSE TO MY RIGHT
>> Stephen: THAT IS REALLY
EYEBALL.
DANGEROUSLY CLOSE TO MY RIGHT
( LAUGHTER )
EYEBALL.
>> IS THAT A RUBBER-TIPPED FAN?
( LAUGHTER )
>> Stephen: LET'S FIND OUT.
>> IS THAT A RUBBER-TIPPED FAN?
>> LET ME CHECK.
>> Stephen: LET'S FIND OUT.
( LAUGHTER )
>> LET ME CHECK.
>> Stephen: ACK!
( LAUGHTER )
YES, YES!
>> Stephen: ACK!
( LAUGHTER )
YES, YES!
WOULD YOU-- WOULD YOU LIKE A
( LAUGHTER )
MINT?
WOULD YOU-- WOULD YOU LIKE A
>> YES, I WOULD LIKE A MINT.
MINT?
OH!
>> YES, I WOULD LIKE A MINT.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
OH!
>> I HAVE A FEELING-- I HAVE A
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
FEELING THAT THIS IS GOING TO BE
>> I HAVE A FEELING-- I HAVE A
A MEME.
FEELING THAT THIS IS GOING TO BE
MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T DO THAT
A MEME.
ANYMORE.
MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T DO THAT
>> Stephen: OKAY.
ANYMORE.
( SIGHS )
>> Stephen: OKAY.
>> IT REALLY IS-- IT'S REALLY
( SIGHS )
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> IT REALLY IS-- IT'S REALLY
>> Stephen: IT REALLY IS GOOD TO
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
SEE YOU, TOO.
>> Stephen: IT REALLY IS GOOD TO
CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
SEE YOU, TOO.
I WANT YOU TO BE HONEST.
CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
>> SURE.
I WANT YOU TO BE HONEST.
>> Stephen: I MEAN IT-- I WAS
>> SURE.
JOKING BEFORE, BUT YOU LOOK
>> Stephen: I MEAN IT-- I WAS
FANTASTIC.
JOKING BEFORE, BUT YOU LOOK
YOU HAVE JUST AGED, WHAT, LIKE
FANTASTIC.
A, JUST A... FRAGRANT CHEESE.
YOU HAVE JUST AGED, WHAT, LIKE
>> THANK YOU.
A, JUST A... FRAGRANT CHEESE.
>> Stephen: REALLY, YOU LOOK
>> THANK YOU.
FANTASTIC.
>> Stephen: REALLY, YOU LOOK
DO I... DO I LOOK OLD TO YOU?
FANTASTIC.
>> DO YOU LOOK OLD?
DO I... DO I LOOK OLD TO YOU?
NO, YOU LOOK FANTASTIC, TOO.
>> DO YOU LOOK OLD?
>> Stephen: STEVE--
NO, YOU LOOK FANTASTIC, TOO.
>> YOU LOOK EXACTLY...
>> Stephen: STEVE--
>> Stephen: STEVE!
>> YOU LOOK EXACTLY...
STEVE, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO HURT
>> Stephen: STEVE!
MY FEELINGS.
STEVE, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO HURT
JUST BE HONEST.
MY FEELINGS.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO ME.
JUST BE HONEST.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO HURT MY
IT'S IMPORTANT TO ME.
FEELINGS.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO HURT MY
>> OKAY, I'LL BE HONEST.
FEELINGS.
YOU DO LOOK GREAT.
>> OKAY, I'LL BE HONEST.
( LAUGHTER )
YOU DO LOOK GREAT.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
( LAUGHTER )
>> Stephen: WHY DID YOU SWITCH
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
TO DRAMA?
>> Stephen: WHY DID YOU SWITCH
YOU'RE THE-- YOU ARE ONE OF THE
TO DRAMA?
FUNNIEST PEOPLE I KNOW.
YOU'RE THE-- YOU ARE ONE OF THE
YOU CAN MAKE ANYTHING FUNNY.
FUNNIEST PEOPLE I KNOW.
WHY DID YOU-- IS IT-- WHY DID
YOU CAN MAKE ANYTHING FUNNY.
YOU BECOME A DRAMATIC ACTOR?
WHY DID YOU-- IS IT-- WHY DID
>> ALL I WANT IS TO BE RESPECTED
YOU BECOME A DRAMATIC ACTOR?
AND TO BE PRETENTIOUS.
>> ALL I WANT IS TO BE RESPECTED
( LAUGHTER )
AND TO BE PRETENTIOUS.
>> Stephen: YOU'RE HALFWAY
( LAUGHTER )
THERE.
>> Stephen: YOU'RE HALFWAY
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
THERE.
>> Stephen: STEVE CARELL,
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
EVERYBODY.
>> Stephen: STEVE CARELL,
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK!
EVERYBODY.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
I wanted more from
my COPD medicine...
...that's why I've got the Power
of 1-2-3 medicines with TRELEGY.
The only FDA-approved
3-in-1 COPD treatment.
♪ TRELEGY. The Power of 1-2-3 ♪
♪ TRELEGY 1-2-3 TRELEGY ♪
With TRELEGY and the Power of
1-2-3, I'm breathing better.
TRELEGY works 3 ways to...
...open airways,...
...keep them open...
...and reduce inflammation...
...for 24 hours
of better breathing.
TRELEGY won't replace
a rescue inhaler
for sudden breathing problems.
TRELEGY is NOT for asthma.
Tell your doctor if you
have a heart condition
or high blood pressure
before taking it.
Do not take TRELEGY
more than prescribed.
TRELEGY may increase your
risk of thrush, pneumonia,
and osteoporosis.
Call your doctor if worsened
breathing, chest pain,
mouth or tongue swelling,..
...problems urinating, vision
changes, or eye pain occur.
Think your COPD
medicine is doing enough?
Maybe you should think again.
Ask your doctor about once-daily
TRELEGY and the
Power of 1-2-3.
♪ TRELEGY 1-2-3 ♪
Save at TRELEGY.com.
My digestive system used
to make me feel sluggish
But now, I take
Metamucil every day.
It traps and removes the
waste that weighs me down,
So I feel lighter.
Try Metamucil, and begin to
feel what lighter feels like.
I work hard to protect
this Tookus.
To take care of any
messy situations.
And put irritation in its place.
And if I can get comfortable
keeping this Tookus
safe and protected...
you can get comfortable doing
the same with yours.
PREPARATION H.
Get comfortable with it.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
( BAND PLAYING )
Colon cancer screening
for people
50 and older at average risk.
I think it's time
for a new screen.
For a different
kind of screen...
for colon cancer.
Thought about it?
His wife asked
about screening options
and her doctor
ordered me.
I'm Cologuard,
the noninvasive
test you use at home.
No special drink.
Just a trip
to the bathroom!
Cologuard.
Colon cancer screening
that's as easy as get,
go, gone.
Cologuard is not
right for everyone,
so ask your doctor if
it's right for you.
♪(oh oh oh oh)
It's taking over.♪
♪There's no escape...♪
right for everyone,
♪...You better get moving. Ready
or not♪
♪...It's about to go down here
it comes now♪
♪...Get ready (oh oh oh oh), Get
ready♪
♪...Moving. Ready or not♪
♪...Get ready (oh oh oh oh)♪
New Galaxy. Free Buds.
Music to your ears.
Get free Galaxy Buds when you
pre-order Galaxy S10 or S10+.
Great news, Liberty
Mutual customizes-
Uh uh - I deliver
the news around here.
♪  ♪
Sources say Liberty
Mutual customizes
your car insurance,
so you only pay
for what you need.
Over to you, logo.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
You'd rather
dog-sit Cupcake
than clean
the toilet?
(Clap of thunder)
Oh come on!
With Scrubbing Bubbles
cleaning doesn't have to stink.
The foaming bubbles
make your toilet super fresh.
It's cleaning reinvented.
Introducing high-rise
Rockstar 24/7 denim
now with sculpt.
Hurry in to Old Navy for
all jeans on sale
up to fifty percent off.
With kids from eight dollars,
adults from fifteen dollars,
only at Old Navy.
>> Stephen: MY NEXT GUEST HAS A
12-SHOW LAS VEGAS RESIDENCY THIS
SPRING AT THE COLISEUM AT
CAESAR'S PALACE.
HERE PERFORMING HIS CLASSIC
SONG, "YOUR SMILING FACE,"
PLEASE WELCOME LEGENDARY SINGER-
SONGWRITER, JAMES TAYLOR.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ WHENEVER I SEE YOUR
SMILING FACE
♪ I HAVE TO SMILE MYSELF
BECAUSE I LOVE YOU
♪ AND WHEN YOU GIVE ME
THAT PRETTY LITTLE POUT
♪ IT TURNS ME INSIDE OUT
THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT YOU BABY
♪ I DON'T KNOW
ISN'T IT AMAZING
♪ A MAN LIKE ME
CAN FEEL THIS WAY
♪ TELL ME HOW MUCH LONGER
IF IT GROWS STRONGER EVERY DAY
♪ OH
I THOUGHT I WAS IN LOVE
♪ A COUPLE OF TIMES BEFORE
WITH THE GIRL NEXT DOOR
♪ BUT THAT WAS
LONG BEFORE I MET YOU
♪ NOW I'M SURE THAT
I WON'T FORGET YOU
♪ AND I THANK MY LUCKY STARS
THAT YOU ARE WHO YOU ARE
♪ AND NOT JUST
ANOTHER LOVELY LADY
♪ SENT DOWN TO BREAK MY HEART
ISN'T IT AMAZING
A MAN LIKE ME
♪ CAN FEEL THIS WAY
TELL ME HOW MUCH LONGER
♪ IF IT GROWS STRONGER
EVERY DAY
♪ OH
HOW MUCH LONGER?
♪ NO ONE CAN TELL ME THAT I'M
DOING WRONG TODAY
♪ WHENEVER I SEE YOU SMILE AT ME
NOBODY CAN TELL ME THAT I'M
♪ DOING WRONG TODAY, NO
WHENEVER YOU SHINE THAT THING
♪ MY WAY, OH HONEY
OH, NO, NO, NO
♪ NO, NO, NO, NO
LA-LA-LA
♪ COME ON, COME ON
OH
♪ OH, NO, NO, NO
NO, NO, NO, NO
LA-LA-LA
♪ NOBODY GONNA TURN ME ROUND
NOBODY GONNA PUT ME DOWN
♪ NOBODY GONNA PUSH ME AROUND
WHENEVER I SEE YOUR SMILING
♪ NO ONE CAN TELL ME THAT
OOH
♪ I'M DOING WRONG TODAY ♪
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: THANK YOU, JAMES.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Stephen: JAMES TAYLOR,
EVERYBODY!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: GOOD NIGHT!
Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org