Captioning sponsored by CBS
>> AND NOW THE RUSSIAN RESPONSE
TO THE STATE OF THE UNION.
>> IT'S "THE LATE SHOW WITH
STEPHEN COLBERT."
TONIGHT, LATEST UNION!
PLUS, STEPHEN WELCOMES
THE HOSTS OF "CBS THIS MORNING."
AND SPIKE LEE.
FEATURING JON BATISTE AND STAY
HUMAN.
AND NOW, LIVE FROM THE ED
SULLIVAN THEATER IN NEW YORK
CITY, IT'S STEPHEN COLBERT!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: I LOVE IT!
I LOVE IT!
YOU GOTTA LOVE IT LIVE!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
LIVE!
>> Dickerson: STEPHEN!
STEVE STEPHEN!
STEPHEN!
>> Stephen: HI, CHRIS.
HOW ARE YOU?
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
HEY, PAUL!
WHAT'S UP?
HEY EVERYBODY, UP THERE, DOWN
HERE, PLEASE, SIT DOWN!
SIT DOWN!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
WELCOME, WELCOME ONE AND ALL TO
"THE LATE SHOW."
I'M YOUR HOST, STEPHEN COLBERT.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
EVERYBODY'S EXCITED BECAUSE
TONIGHT, TRUMP GAVE HIS STATE OF
THE UNION, AND WE ARE LIVE, IF
WHAT YOU CALL WHAT WE JUST
WATCHED "LIVE."
IT WAS PRETTY RAUCOUS ON THE
REPUBLICAN SIDE, I'LL TELL YOU
THAT MUCH.
PRETTY QUIET ON THE DEMOCRACY
SIDE BECAUSE IT WASINANCY'S
HOUSE.
SHE SHOWED GREAT RESTRAINT.
SHE DID NOT STICK ON OUT HER
TONGUE ONCE.
THIS WASN'T A PARTICULARLY GOOD
SPEECH, BUT WHAT IT LACKED IN
QUALITY, IT MADE UP IN LENGTH.
(  LAUGHTER  )
IT WAS-- IT WAS LIKE--
( APPLAUSE )
THIS SPEECH WAS LIKE WATCHING
PAINT LIE.
(  LAUGHTER  )
NOW, LEADING UP TO THE BIG
SPEECH THE PRESIDENT REFUSED TO
GIVE ANY SPOILERS.
>> YOU'LL HEAR THE STATE OF THE
UNION AND THEN YOU'LL SEE WHAT
HAPPENS RIGHT AFTER THE STATE OF
THE UNION.
>> Stephen: OKAY, YES.
THAT IS HOW TIME WORKS.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THROUGHOUT THE SPEECH, TRUMP
STUCK TO HIS TELEPROMPTER MOST
OF THE NIGHT.
HIS STAFF TRIED TO KEEP HIM
FOCUSED ON THE PROMPTER BY
ADDING A BOUNCY CHEESEBURGER.
(  LAUGHTER  )
SNAP IN!
WHAT, WHAT, WHAT, WHAT!
NO SURPRISE, THE DEMOCRATS WHO
HAVE ANNOUNCED THEIR 2020
CAMPAIGNS,  ALREADY REALLY TRIED
TO MAKE A SPLASH WITH THEIR
GUESTS.
ELIZABETH WARREN BROUGHT AN
EMPLOYEE OF THE U.S. DEPARTMENT
OF HOUSING AND URBAN DEVELOPMENT
FURLOUGHED DURING THE GOVERNMENT
SHUTDOWN.
KAMALA HARRIS BROUGHT AN AIR
TRAFFIC CONTROLLER WHO WENT
WITHOUT A PAYCHECK DURING THE
SHUTDOWN AND LOST HER HOME IN A
WILDFIRE.
NOT TO BE OUTDONE, SENATOR CORY
BOOKER BROUGHT A HERO FROM HIS
HOMETOWN OF NEWARK: A FLAMING
PARKED CAR.
(  LAUGHTER  )
STAY STROK, FLAMING PARKED CAR!
EARLY-- EARLY IN THE EVENING, I
HAD HIGH HOPES.
I HAD HIGH HOPES.
ESPECIALLY WHEN CNN TEASED US
WITH THIS GRAPHIC:
"TRUMP LEAVES WHITE HOUSE SOON."
COME ON!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
YOU CAN'T-- YOU CAN'T TEASE US.
THAT'S NOT COOL!
CNN, UNCOOL, CNN.
"THIS JUST IN: PRESIDENT TRUMP
HAS OFFICIALLY STEPPED DOWN...
THE FRONT STAIRS TO GET IN HIS
CAR."
(  LAUGHTER  )
EVERYBODY WAS THERE, INCLUDING
DON JR., WHO APPARENTLY ARRIVED
WITH POLICE.
KIND OF HOW IT IS FOR HIM NOW.
COPS HANG OUT NEAR HIM WITH
CUFFS OPEN AND READY.
(  LAUGHTER  )
TRUMP STARTED THE NIGHT BY
CHOOSING ENERGY SECRETARY RICK
PERRY AS THE DESIGNATED
SURVIVOR.
SO THAT'S IN CASE, IF
SOMETHING-- GOD FORBID--
HAPPENED AT THE CAPITOL
TONIGHT-- A METEOR TOOK OUT ALL
OUR LEADERSHIP, RICK PERRY WOULD
BE OUR OWN HOPE.
AND AN EXPERT ON RICK PERRY HAS
THIS REACTION TO THAT CHOICE:
>> OOPS.
>> Stephen: OOPS, INDEED.
OOPS, INDEED.
STATE OF THE UNION, ALWAYS A BIG
NIGHT.
ALWAYS A BIG NIGHT.
EVERYBODY WHO WAS ANYBODY WHO
WAS NOT INDICTED WAS THERE.
LET'S SEE, DEMOCRATIC WOMEN WORE
WHITE TO COMMEMORATE THE
SUFFRAGETTES.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
BEAUTIFUL.
>> Stephen:
>> Jon: YEAH, THAT'S AMAZING.
I LOVE THAT.
>> Stephen: BEAUTIFUL.
( APPLAUSE )
SO, SO THE DEMOCRATIC SIDE WAS A
SEA OF WHITE, AND THE REPUBLICAN
SIDE ALSO A SEA OF WHITE.
( APPLAUSE )
NOW, AS HE ENTERED, HE DID THE
NORMAL HANDSHAKING, SHAKING THE
HAND OF THE PEOPLE WHO WILL
EVENTUALLY DECIDE IF HE CAN BE
INDICTED.
IT WAS A WIDE-RANGING SPEECH.
TRUMP HONORED SOME WONDERFUL
CHILDREN, SOME WORLD WAR II
VETERANS, SOME FORMER PRISONERS
WHO WERE FREED BY CLEMENCY OR
THE NEW PRISON REFORM.
I THINK HE DECLARED HIMSELF
PRESIDENT OF VENEZUELA AT ONE
POINT.
WHEN THE SPEECH BEGAN, ONE OF
THE FIRST THINGS TRUMP DID WAS
INTRODUCE HIS WIFE.
>> MADAM SPEAKER, MR. VICE
PRESIDENT, MEMBERS OF CONGRESS,
THE FIRST LADY OF THE UNITED
STATES.
( APPLAUSE )
( CHEERS )
>> Stephen: THAT'S A REALLY
SMART MOVE:  SAY WHO SHE IS,
THEN WAIT FOR HER TO STAWND
BEFORE ACKNOWLEDGING HER.
(  LAUGHTER  )
THAT IS THE "HEY, CHAMP" OF
FORGETTING WHO YOU ARE CURRENTLY
MARRIED TO.
HE STARTED-- HE STARTED THE
EVENING-- "WHAT'S UP, BIG GUY?"
HE STARTED WITH A CALL FOR
BIPARTISANSHIP:
>> THE AGENDA I WILL LAY OUT
THIS EVENING IS NOT A REPUBLICAN
AGENDA OR A DEMOCRAT AGENDA.
IT'S THE AGENDA OF THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE.
>> Stephen: "CAN SOMEBODY PLEASE
TELL THEM THESE WERE THEIR
IDEAS?
BECAUSE I'M GETTING KILLED IN
THE POLLS RIGHT NOW."
AND HE TOOK A MOMENT TO TOUT
AMERICAN GREATNESS.
>> AMERICA SAVED FREEDOM,
TRANSFORMED SCIENCE, REDEFINED
THE MIDDLE CLASS, AND WHEN YOU
GET DOWN TO IT, THERE'S NOTHING
ANYWHERE IN THE WORLD THAT CAN
COMPETE WITH AMERICA.
>> Stephen: (AS TRUMP):
"HOME OF THE WHOPPER, UNDEFEATED
HEAVYWEIGHT CHAMPION OF THE
WORLD.
AMERICA: IT'S EVERYWHERE YOU
WANNA BE.
BA-DA-BA-BA-BA, I'M LOVING IT."
I COULD GO FOR ONE.
I'M LOVING IT, JON.
>> Jon: IT'S A LITTLE LATE FOR
THAT.
I AM NOT MESSING WITH THAT.
>> Stephen: AND HE PRESENTED A
STARK CHOICE:
>> WE MUST CHOOSE BETWEEN
GREATNESS OR GRIDLOCK, RESULTS
OR RESISTANCE, VISION OR
VENGEANCE, INCREDIBLE PROGRESS
OR POINTLESS DESTRUCTION.
>> Stephen: (AS TRUMP):
"SOUP OR SALAD, PAPER OR
PLASTIC, ROSS AND RACHEL,
ALIEN V. PREDATOR...
WHOEVER WINS, WE LOSE."
(  LAUGHTER  )
AND, OF COURSE--
( APPLAUSE )
PREDATOR FANS.
ALIEN VERSUS PREDATOR.
OF COURSE, HE BRAGGED MORE ABOUT
THE ECONOMY:
>> AND WE ARE CONSIDERED, FAR
AND AWAY, THE HOTTEST ECONOMY
ANYWHERE IN THE WORLD.
>> Stephen: (AS TRUMP):
"IT IS SO HOT, IF IT WASN'T MY
ECONOMY, PERHAPS I'D BE DATING
IT."
>> Jon: OH, NO!
OH, NO!
>> Stephen: "JON, I'M TELLING
YOU, JON, YOU KNOW, I LOVE A HOT
ECONOMY."
THE EVENING WENT ON...
AND ON.
(  LAUGHTER  )
G.O.P. LAWMAKERS STOOD UP AND
SAT DOWN SO MANY TIMES, IT
SOUNDED LIKE THEY WERE MAKING
POPCORN WITH THEIR KNEECAPS.
(  LAUGHTER  )
HE MADE A NOT-SO-SUBTLE THREAT
TO HOUSE DEMOCRATS.
>> AN ECONOMIC MIRACLE IS TAKING
PLACE IN THE UNITED STATES, AND
THE ONLY THING THAT CAN STOP IT
ARE FOOLISH WARS, POLITICS, OR
RIDICULOUS PARTISAN
INVESTIGATIONS.
>> Stephen: "YOU HEARD ME, YOU
GET THE TRUTH OR A FUNCTIONING
ECONOMY, OKAY.
KEEP IN MIND, I TURNED THIS
SUCKER OFF FOR A MONTH OVER A
WALL.
YOU THINK I WON'T BURN THIS
PLACE TO THE GROUND TO STAY OUT
OF JAIL?
OKAY.
I'M JUST SAYING NICE COUNTRY YOU
GOT HERE, SHAME-- SHAME IF
SOMETHING HAPPENED TO IT."
( APPLAUSE )
IN THAT SAME VAIN, HE KEPT GOING
IN WHAT HE CLEARLY THOUGHT WAS A
LINE THAT WOULD GET A STANDING
OVATION.
>> IF THERE IS GOING TO BE PEACE
AND LEGISLATION, THERE CANNOT BE
WAR AND INVESTIGATION.
IT JUST DOESN'T WORK THAT WAY!
( SINGLE CLAP )
(  LAUGHTER  )
>> Stephen: EVEN-- EVEN THE
REPUBLICANS WERE LIKE-- HEY!
DID HE... WHAT?
WHAT-- NICE TRY ON THAT
ARGUMENT."
"YOU CAN'T HAVE LEGISLATION AND
INVESTIGATION.
WHOEVER HEARD OF LAW AND ORDER?
COME ON.
( APPLAUSE )
YOU CAN'T HAVE BOTH.
YOU HAVE TO CHOOSE.
JON, YOU HAVE TO CHOOSE.
YOU HAVE TO GIVE ME THAT ONE.
YOU HAVE TO GIVE ME THAT ONE."
( APPLAUSE )
AND TRUMP TALKED THE TALK ON
IMMIGRATION.
>> NOW IS THE TIME FOR CONGRESS
TO SHOW THE WORLD THAT AMERICA
IS COMMITTED TO ENDING ILLEGAL
IMMIGRATION AND PUTTING THE
RUTHLESS COYOTES, CARTELS, DRUG
DEALERS, AND HUMAN TRAFFICKERS
OUT OF BUSINESS.
>> Stephen: AND NO ONE KNOWS
HOW TO PUT SOMETHING OUT OF
BUSINESS LIKE DONALD TRUMP.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
YOU CAN TAKE THAT TO THE BANK!
BECAUSE THEY ARE REPOSSESSING IT
IN THE CHAPTER 11!
NOW, TRUMP KNOWS-- TRUMP KNOWS
IMMIGRANTS ARE TAKING AMERICAN
JOBS.
>> WORKING CLASS AMERICANS ARE
LEFT TO PAY THE PRICE FOR MASS
ILLEGAL IMMIGRATION:  REDUCED
JOBS.
>> Stephen: BUT HE ALSO KNOWS
THIS:
>> MORE PEOPLE ARE WORKING NOW
THAN AT ANY TIME IN THE HISTORY
OF OUR COUNTRY.
>> Stephen:  THE BOTH OF THOSE
THINGS ARE TRUE, IF YOU DON'T
THINK ABOUT IT TOO HARD.
I DON'T.
I DON'T THINK ABOUT IT AT ALL.
OKAY.
YES AND NO."
AND HE LAID OUT A STRONG
ARGUMENT AGAINST ILLEGAL
IMMIGRATION.
>> TOLERANCE FOR ILLEGAL
IMMIGRATION IS NOT COMPASSIO
COMPASSIONATE.
IT IS ACTUALLY VERY CRUEL.
>> Stephen: "I MEAN, NOT KIDS
IN CAGES CRUEL, BUT, STILL,
PRETTY BAD."
THE POINT IS-- AND THIS IS MY
POINT ULTIMATELY-- TOLERANCE IS
CRUELTY.
WAR IS PEACE.
FREEDOM OF SLAVERY, AND I WEIGH
239 POUNDS.
( LAUGHTER )
( APPLAUSE )
TRUMP-- TRUMP--
TRUMP WAS BRAVELY WILLING TO
TAKE CREDIT FOR ANY GOOD THING
THAT HAPPENED IN THE COUNTRY.
>> NO ONE HAS BENEFITED MORE
FROM A THRIVING ECONOMY THAN
WOMEN WHO HAVE FILLED 58% OF THE
NEWLY CREATED JOBS LAST YEAR.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: THEY'RE WAY AHEAD
OF YOU, DON.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Jon: WOOOOO!
WOOOO!
>> Stephen: MOST OF THOSE JOBS
WERE NEW DEMOCRATIC WOMEN IN
CONGRESS.
AND TRUMP SUPPORTED THEIR
CELEBRATION WITH THIS:
>> YOU WEREN'T SUPPOSED TO DO
THAT.
>> Stephen: DONALD TRUMP
TRYING TO TELL WOMEN WHAT TO DO
IS WHY THEY WON.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
BUT-- BUT-- BUT--
BUT COME ON, TRUMP ROLLED WITH
IT.
>> DON'T SIT YET.
YOU'RE GOING TO LIKE THIS.
>> Stephen: "I RESIGN."
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
IS THAT NOT WHAT HE SAID?
>> Jon: THAT'S NOT WHAT HE
SAID.
>> Stephen: AND HE ROLLED OUT
SOME POLICY PROPOSALS TO APPEAL
TO WORKING PARENTS.
>> I AM ALSO PROUD TO BE THE
FIRST PRESIDENT TO INCLUDE IN MY
BUDGET A PLAN FOR NATIONWIDE
PAID FAMILY LEAVE SO THAT EVERY
NEW PARENT HAS THE CHANCE TO
BOND WITH THEIR NEWBORN CHILD.
>> Stephen: "BECAUSE, YOU
KNOW, SOME PEOPLE ARE TOO BUSY
TO BOND WITH THEIR WIFE AND
NEWBORN CHILD.
UNSTEAD, THEY'RE FORCED TO GO TO
A VODKA LAUNCH PARTY AND TAG A
PORN STAR.
I'M SORRY.
NOT ON MY WATCH!
NO, NO, I'M SORRY.
I MEANT TO SAY NOT WHILE ANYONE
IS WATCHING ME."
TRUMP ALSO MADE-- GETS YOU.
IT GETS YOU-- GETS YOU RIGHT
THERE, CHRIS.
TRUCH ALSO MADE A BIG
ANNOUNCEMENT ABOUT HIS BUDDY,
KIM JONG-UN.
>> CHAIRMAN KIM AND I WILL MEET
AGAIN ON FEBRUARY 27 AND 28 IN
VIETNAM.
>> Stephen: "UNLESS MY BONE
SPURS ACT UP.
IN WHICH CASE, I'M SENDING ERIC,
OKAY?
STRAP ON.
STRAP ON, ERIC."
( APPLAUSE )
TRUMP MADE SURE TO INSIST THAT
THIS GOVERNMENT WILL STRICTLY
ENFORCE ITS SMALL-GOVERNMENT
STANCE.
>> WE ARE ALARMED BY THE NEW
CALLS TO ADOPT SOCIALISM IN OUR
COUNTRY.
( BOOING )
AMERICA WAS FOUNDED ON LIBERTY
AND INDEPENDENCE AND NOT
GOVERNMENT COERCION, DOMINATION,
AND CONTROL.
WE ARE BORN FREE AND WE WILL
STAY FREE.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: JIMMY, HOLD ON.
I BELIEVE WE HAD A MIC ON BERNIE
SANDERSINAR.
CAN WE-- CAN WE GO BACK AND TURN
THAT UP?
>> WE ARE BORN FREE AND WE WILL
STAY FREE.
( APPLAUSE )
( "CURB YOUR ENTHUSIASM THEME."
>> THEN HE RAMPED UP FOR HIS BIG
FINISH.
>> TOGETHER WE REPRESENT THE
MOST EXTRAORDINARY NATION IN ALL
OF HISTORY.
WHAT WILL WE DO WITH THIS
MOMENT?
HOW WILL WE BE REMEMBERED?
>> Stephen: "HOW MANY YEARS
WILL WE SERVE, AND WILL WE GET
TIME OFF FOR GOOD BEHAVIOR?"
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
AND-- AND--
AND HE ENDED HIS SPEECH WITH
SOME LOFTY WORDS.
>> THIS IS THE TIME TO SEARCH
FOR THE TALLEST SUMMIT AND SET
OUR SIGHTS ON THE BRIGHTEST
STAR.
>> Stephen: THAT I BELIEVE,
BECAUSE I ACTUALLY REMEMBER
SEEING TRUMP SET HIS SIGHTS ON
THE BRIGHTEST STAR.
( APPLAUSE )
AND THAT-- THAT HE BROUGHT IT
ALL HOME, HE BROUGHT IT ALL HOME
WITH A SIMPLE PLEA.
>> I ASKING YOU TO CHOOSE
GREATNESS.
NO MATTER THE TRIALS WE FACE.
>> Stephen: WELL, IN THAT
CASE, SIR, I CHOOSE YOU FACE A
TRIAL BECAUSE THAT WILL BE
GREAT.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
WE'VE GOT A FANTASTIC SHOW FUR
TONIGHT.
THE TEAM FROM "CBS THIS MORNING"
IS HERE.
SPIKE LEE IS HERE.
STICK AROUND.
WE'VE JUST BEGUN.
AND IT'S LIVE!
♪ ♪ ♪
( APPLAUSE )
Stop fearing your alarm clock...
With ZzzQuil PURE Zzzs.
A drug-free blend of botanicals
with melatonin
that supports your natural sleep
cycle
so you can seize the morning.
ZzzQuil PURE Zzzs.
HVR.
You either love it
or you really love it.
I'm Captain Obvious
and Hotels.com
rewards me basically
everywhere.
So why am I sliding into
this ski lodge
with my mini horse?
Because Hotels.com
lets me do me.
Sorry, the cold makes
him a little horse.
Hotels.com.
You do you and get rewarded.
It's just a cough.
Yeah right.
And the earth is flat.
Ahhh!!
Treat your cough seriously
with Robitussin CF Max.
Nothing lasts longer
and treats more symptoms for
your cough, cold and flu.
Robitussin. Because
it's never just a cough.
-We're doing karaoke later,
and you're gonna sing.
-Jamie, this is your house?
-I know, it's not much,
but it's home.
Right, kids?
-Kids?
-Papa, Papa!
-[ Laughs ]
-You didn't tell me
your friends were coming.
-Oh, yeah.
-This one is tiny like a child.
-Yeah, she is.
Oh, but seriously,
it's good to be surrounded
by what matters most --
a home and auto bundle
from Progressive.
-Oh, sweetie,
please, play for us.
-Oh, no, I couldn't.
-Please.
-Okay.
[ Singing in Spanish ]
What's better than having fast,
-Please.
-Okay.
reliable WiFi with
coverage throughout your home?
How about having Internet
that can help you save
on wireless phone service?
Xfinity gives you
the fastest speeds
from America's best
Internet provider
to stream on
all your devices.
Plus, with Xfinity
Mobile included,
you can switch
your wireless carrier
and save hundreds
of dollars a year.
Now that's
simple, easy, awesome.
Get started for $39.99
a month for 12 months.
Plus, ask how you can
get Xfinity Mobile included
so all you pay for
is data. Switch today.
( APPLAUSE )
♪ NOT GONNA LET THEM CATCH ME NO
>> Stephen: "MIDNIGHT RIDER"
JON BATTISTE AND STAY HUMAN.
"MIDNIGHT RIDER."
I LOVE IT.
FANTASTIC!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
>> Stephen: WELL, FOLKS,
WELCOME BACK TO OUR LIVE SHOW
FOLLOWING THE STATE OF THE UNION
BY DONALD TRUMP.
PLEASE HAVE A SEAT, EVERYBODY.
I'M SO GLAD THEY'RE HERE.
MY FIRST GUESTS TONIGHT HOST THE
BEST MORNING SHOW ON TV.
FROM "CBS THIS MORNING," PLEASE
JOHN DICKERSON NORAH O'DONNELL,
AND BIANNA GOLODRYGA AND GAYLE
KING.
♪ ♪ ♪
( APPLAUSE ).
>> Stephen: PLEASE, HAVE A
SEAT.
THERE YOU GO.
COME ON DOWN.
FIRST OF ALL,--
>> THIS FEELS LIKE A BIG COUCH,
STEPHEN.
>> Stephen: WE CUT OUT THE BIG
COUCH FOR YOU GUYS.
I DON'T THINK WE'VE EVER HAD
THIS MANY PEOPLE AT ONCE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING
HERE.
I KNOW THAT YOU GUYS WORK REAL
JOBS AND HAVE TO GET UP IN THE
MORNING.
THANKS FOR COMING TO OUR LITTLE
REINDEER GAMES TONIGHT.
>> WE'RE JUST THINKING SLEEP IS
OVERRATED.
AND IF YOU'RE GOING TO STAY UP
LATE ON A SCHOOL NIGHT,
SHOULDN'T YOU BE WITH STEPHEN
COLBERT?
( APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: OKAY, LET'S GET
RIGHT TO IT.
WE'VE GOT A LOT TO COVER AND
VERY LITTLE TIME, AND WE'RE
LIVE!
OKAY, SO, HOW DID HE DO?
HOW-- GAYLE, HOW DO YOU THINK HE
DID?
>> WELL, WE KEPT HEARING-- ALL
AFTER WE KEPT HEARING IT'S GOING
TO BE UNITY, UNITY, UNITY.
THEN AN HOUR BEFORE I HEARD IT'S
GOING TO BE VERY AGGRESSIVE,
VERY CAUSTIC, AND VERY
ACRIMONIOUS.
I ACTUALLY THOUGHT IT WAS VERY--
I THOUGHT IT WAS PRETTY TAME.
THERE WERE A COUPLE OF MOMENTS
WHERE YOU WENT "HUH," YOU COCKED
YOUR HEAD.
I THOUGHT HE TRIED TO EXTEND THE
OLIVE BRANCH.
>> Stephen: WHEN WAS THAT--
>> WHEN HE GAVE THE SHOUTOUT TO
THE WOMEN.
WHEN HE GAVE THE SHOUTOUT TO THE
WOMEN ALL WEARING WHITE.
>> Stephen: THAT'S TRUE,
THAT'S TRUE.
>> THAT'S WHAT I WAS SAYING.
>> Stephen: THAT WAS REALLY A
LOVELY MOMENT THAT THEY HAD
BEFORE HE COULD NAME IT.
YOU KNOW?
I THINK THEY KNEW IT WAS COMING,
AND THEY SAID, "WE'RE NOT GOING
TO LET YOU CONGRATULATE US."
>> THEY ALL ROSE--
>> HE WAS TRYING TO TAKE CREDIT
FOR THE FACT SO MANY WOMEN-- WE
HAVE A RECORD NUMBER OF WOMEN IN
THE WORKFORCE NOW.
74 MILLION WOMEN.
BUT SOME OF THE WOMEN IN
CONGRESS TOOK MEN'S JOBS.
>> AND HE HAS EVERY RIGHT TO
TAKE CREDIT FOR THAT BECAUSE
THEY WON IN LARGE PART BECAUSE
THEY RAN AGAINST HIM.
>> Stephen: WHERE'S THE THANK
YOU?
AT LONG LAST, WHERE IS THE THANK
YOU 124.
>> BUT IT GOT THE BIGGEST
APPLAUSE LINE.
>> HE WAS ALSO HAPPY THEY WERE
STANDING UP.
YOU HAD DEMOCRATS STANDING UP
AND APPLAUDING THE PRESIDENT.
HOW OFTEN DOES THAT HAPPEN?
>> Stephen: HE CAN THINK THEY
WERE APPLAUDING HIM.
THAT'S VERY SWEET.
IT WAS VERY BEAUTIFUL, THOUGH,
TO SEE ALL OF THAT WHITE PUP GOT
AN IMMEDIATE-- IT WAS A GREAT
EFFECT.
I THINK ALL THE WOMEN ON THE
DEMOCRATIC SIDE WORE WHITE.
YOU SAW THE IMPACT OF THE
CHECKIN THE CONGRESS
IMMEDIATELY.
THAT IN SOME WAYS WAS-- WE'LL
GET TO THE DEMOCRATIC RESPONSE
IN A MOMENT-- BUT IN WAYS, THAT
WAS SORT OF A PRERESPONSE TO
ANYTHING THE PRESIDENT WAS GOING
TO SAY WAS THE DIVERSITY OF THE
DEMOCRATIC SIDE.
>> YOU COULDN'T HELP BUT NOTICE
IT WITH NANCY PELOSI STANDING
RIGHT BEHIND HIM.
>> AND WEARING WHITE IN HONOR OF
THE SUFFRAGETTES, IN HONOR OF
WOMEN GETTING TO VOTE.
>> I NOTICE ALL THE GUYS GOT
TOGETHER, TOO, AND WORE NAVY
SUITS.
>> Stephen: JON, THANK YOU FOR
THE SOLIDARITY.
>> IT TURNS OUT-- WE SLEEP IN
THESE.
THIS IS ACTUALLY WHAT I WEAR TO
BED NORMALLY.
>> Stephen: SO WHAT DO YOU
THINK-- TOMORROW MORNING, YOU
KNOW, WHEN-- WHEN WE GET UP,
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS GOING TO BE
TALKING ABOUT?
WHAT DO YOU THINK THE TAKEAWAY
FROM THE SPEECH IS GOING TO BE?
>> WELL, I DID LEARN, IF IT
WASN'T FOR HIM, WE WOULD BE AT
WAR WITH NORTH KOREA.
THAT WAS A MOMENT WHERE I GO --
>> Stephen: THAT'S A VEILED
THREAT.
THAT'S A VEILED THREAT.
THAT'S LIKE, "IF YOU DON'T
RE-ELECT ME, I'LL START A WAR
FIVE MINUTES BEFORE I LEAVE, "BY
THE WAY, WHEN YOU SAY, "WHEN WE
GET UP," THAT CUTS A LITTLE
CLOSE FOR US BECAUSE IT'S IN
ABOUT TWO HOURS.
>> Stephen: WHEN YOU ALL GET
UP.
I'M SLEEPING IN TOMORROW.
>> WE'LL CALL YOU.
>> IN THE MORNING, FING YOU'RE A
TRUMP SUPPORTER OR YOU'RE A
REPUBLICAN THERE WAS A LOT IN
THAT SPEECH TO LIKE.
HE TALKED ABOUT THE ECONOMY AT
LENGTH.
I BET THERE WERE A LOT OF
REPUBLICANS WHO THOUGHT WHY
DIDN'T HE DO THIS ALL THE TIME
DURING THE 2018 ELECTION, TALK
ABOUT THE ECONOMY AND CRIMINAL
JUSTICE REFORM, WHICH WAS A
BIPARTISAN EFFORT.
BUT I THINK STATE OF THE UNIONS
EVAPORATE PRETTY QUICKLY AFTER
THEY'VE BEEN GIVEN BASED ON THE
CONTEXT OF WHAT'S HAPPENING
OUTSIDE.
AND WHAT'S HAPPENING OUTSIDE
THAT BUILDING NOW, THERE ARE
MUELLER INVESTIGATIONS, THERE
ARE OTHER FEDERAL
INVESTIGATIONS.
WE ARE IN THE SNOOZE BAR PERIOD
BETWEEN ONE GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN
AND A POTENTIAL OTHER GOVERNMENT
SHUTDOWN.
YOU HAVE DEMOCRATS HAVING WON
THE HOUSE FEELING ENERGIZED
BECAUSE THEY FOUGHT HIM.
THAT'S THE CONTEXT AND
EVERYTHING HE SAYS WILL PROBABLY
EVAPORATE.
AND WE HAVE DONALD TRUMP THE
TWEETER DIFFERENT FROM DONALD
TRUMP THE TELEPROMPTER WHO
WILL-- WHO WILL--
( APPLAUSE ).
>> Stephen: RIGHT.
NORAH?
>> WELL, I THINK THERE'S A KEY
LINE.
HE THREATENED CONGRESS AS WELL.
HE SAID IF THERE IS GOING TO BE
PEACE AND LEGISLATION, THERE
CANNOT BE WAR AND INVESTIGATION.
THAT WAS A THREAT.
HE CALLED THEM THESE RIDICULOUS
INVESTIGATIONS.
>> AND HOW MANY INVESTIGATIONS
ARE THERE?
>> THERE ARE 17 CURRENT KNOWN
INVESTIGATIONS AGAINST TRUMP
BY-- INCLUDING MUELLER, BY THE
SOUTHERN DISTRICT OF NEW YORK,
IN THE DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA, BY
THE EASTERN DISTRICT OF NEW
YORK.
SO THOSE ARE OUTSIDE OF
CONGRESS, THOSE INVESTIGATIONS
THAT ARE--
>> SMOKY THE BEAR.
>> INSPECTOR CLU SO.
>> THERE'S ALSO A DIFFERENCE
TALKING ABOUT A HEALTHY ECONOMY
AND THE HOTTEST ECONOMY IN
HISTORY.
IT IS JUST NOT THE CASE.
GHANA'S ECONOMY IS GROWING
FASTER THAN THE UNITED STATES.
>> Stephen: MAKE AMERICA GHANA
AGAIN.
>> EVEN CHINA.
IT'S SLOWING BUT GROWING AT A
FASTER RATE THAN THE U.S.
ECONOMY.
A LOT TO BE EXCITED ABOUT.
100 STRAIGHT MONTHS OF JOB
GROWTH.
BUT WE HAVE SEEN STRONGER
ECONOMIC GROWTH IN YEARS PAST.
>> HE DOES DESERVE SOME CREDIT
FOR THE ECONOMY, HIM AND THE
PREVIOUS ADMINISTRATION
( APPLAUSE )
( CHEERS )
>> AND I THINK REPUBLICANS WISH
HE WOULD FOCUS ON THAT.
I ALWAYS FIND IT DISTURBING,
THOUGH, STEVE WHEN HE TALKS
ABOUT THE WALL, AND YOU WOULD
THINK THERE ARE MARAUDING
IMMIGRANTS AND MIGRANT WORKERS
WHO ARE COMING INTO THIS COUNTRY
WHO ARE GOING TO MURDER US WHILE
WE'RE SLEEPING IN OUR BEDS.
I WAS AT TEXAS AT THE BORDER,
AND WHEN YOU SEE THESE PEOPLE
AND YOU TALK TO THESE PEOPLE,
JUST THINK WHAT IT'S LIKE, YOU
HAVE TO LEAVE YOUR OWN COUNTRY
TO COME TO A COUNTRY WHERE
YOU'RE NOT WELCOMED BUT YOU
STILL THINK IT'S BETTER TO BE
HERE THAN THERE.
THEY'RE FLEEING FOR THEIR LIVES.
THEY'RE TRYING TO SUPPORT THEIR
FAMILIES.
THEY'RE TRYING TO REALLY SAVE
THEIR LIVES.
I MET A WOMAN WHOSE DAUGHTER HAD
BEEN RAPED SEVERAL TIMES.
AND SHE SAID, "I'VE GOT TO GO.
THE ANOTHER GUY WHO WAS A MEMBER
OF A GANG HE DIDN'T WANT TO BE
AND HIS FATHER BROUGHT HIM.
YOU'RE SEPARATING THESE CHILDREN
FROM THEIR PARENTS.
THEY ARE COMING BECAUSE THEY
WANT A BETTER LIFE.
THEY ARE TRYING TO LIVE.
SURE, THERE ARE SOME OUTLIARS
BUT THAT IS NOT THE MAJORITY OF
THE PEOPLE AND THAT BOTHERS ME.
>> Stephen: THAT LEADS TO MY
NEXT QUESTION, JOHN, YOU WERE
SAYING THE STATE OF THE UNION
SPEECHES ARE KIND OF LIKE
EMOTIONAL COTTON CANDY.
AS SOON AS THEY HIT WATER, THEY
EVAPORATE.
WHAT DOES HE GET OUT OF THIS FOR
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING RIGHT
NOW, WHICH IS TO FULFILL THE
CAMPAIGN PERHAPS TO BUILD THAT
WALL.
HE'S UP AGAINST-- ARE WE 10 DAYS
AWAY, FIVE DAYS-- I FORGOT-- 30
SECONDS?
>> 10.
>> Stephen: FROM THE 15th.
WILL THIS MOVE THE NOODLE.
>> NO, IT WON'T MOVE THE NEEDLE,
BUT IT SLIDDIFIES HIS SUPPORT.
AND WHERE WAS THAT WEAKENING?
WE SAW FROM THE POLLS HE WAS
LOSING SUPPORT DURING THE
SHUTDOWN.
WHEN HE TALKS ABOUT DECLARING AN
EMERGENCY FOR, THIS A LOT OF
REPUBLICANS STOOD UP WHEN MIKE
PENCE WENT TO MEET WITH HIM TWO
WEEKS AGO AND SAID, "DON'T DO
THAT.
WE YLTD YLD AND SCREAMED WHEN
BARACK OBAMA DID SIMILAR THINGS,
THIS IS UNCONSTITUTIONAL."
IF HE'S MAKING THE CASE LOOKING
LIKE HE WAS EXTENDING AN OLIVE
BRANCH-- ALTHOUGH, I'M WITH YOU,
I DIDN'T SEE ANY PARTICULAR
OLIVE BRANCHES-- IT SHORES UP
HIS TROOPS AND THAT'S GOOD FOR
ONE SPEECH FOR ONE NIGHT.
>> Stephen: WE HAVE TO TAKE A
QUICK BREAK AND--
>> DO YOU WANT US TO STAY?
>> Stephen: YES, PLEASE STAY.
I'LL BE BACK WITH THE HOSTS OF
"CBS THIS MORNING."
PLEASE DO.
SO NICE.
I'M MISSING OUT ON
OUR FAMILY OUTINGS
BECAUSE I CAN'T FIND A BLADDER
LEAKAGE PRODUCT THAT FITS.
EVERYTHING WAS TOO LOOSE.
BUT DEPEND® FIT-FLEX®
FEELS TAILORED TO ME.
WITH A RANGE OF SIZES
FOR ALL BODY TYPES.
DEPEND® FIT-FLEX® UNDERWEAR
IS GUARANTEED TO
BE YOUR BEST FIT.
DEPEND® FIT-FLEX® UNDERWEAR
It's back!
Lobsterfest is on
at Red Lobster.
With the most lobster dishes
of the year,
what'll you choose?
How 'bout Lobster Lover's Dream?
More like a lobster dream
come true.
A butter-poached Maine tail,
roasted rock tail
and creamy lobster linguine.
Or try NEW Lobster in Paradise.
It's a crispy coconutty,
vacation on a plate.
New Ultimate Lobsterfest
Surf & Turf is here, too.
'Cause what's better than
steak and lobster?
Steak and LOTS of lobster.
So hurry in and see how
you're going to Lobsterfest.
NEW Theraflu PowerPods.
The cold and flu fighting
machine.
You put in your machine.
Press the button to brew up
powerful relief.
To defeat your toughest
cold and flu symptoms fast.
NEW Theraflu PowerPods.
Press. Sip. Relief.
Moderator:
This is the Chevy Equinox.
Various:
Beautiful. Wow.
Ooh, this is fancy.
Moderator:
That's the available
HD surround vision camera.
The top of your car?
Moderator:
Mm-hmm. It helps you see
dangers around the vehicle.
What is that?
Various:
Wait, wait, wait,
what is that? Oh, my...
(Mixed shouting)
Man:
These are big alligators.
Moderator:
So who's getting out first?
(Laughter)
Get 0% financing for 60 months
on most Equinox models.
Or, current GM owners
can get $3,500
total cash allowance
when financing
with GM Financial.
Find New Roads at your
local Chevy dealer.
Live from the Starlite Lounge.
♪ One plus one equals
too little too late ♪
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]
( APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: HEY, EVERYTHING,
WELCOME BACK!
WE'RE HERE WITH OUR--
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
OUR KIND AND GENEROUS FRIENDS
FROM "CBS THIS MORNING."
NOW, BEFORE WE GO ON, A COUPLE
OF THINGS I WANT TO TALK ABOUT,
THE OTHER PEOPLE IN THE ROOM.
LET'S TALK ABOUT WHAT THE
PRESIDENT DID NOT SAY IN THIS
SPEECH.
WERE THERE THINGS THAT YOU
EXPECTED HIM TO TOUCH ON,
POLICIES OR SUBJECTS--
>> THE FURLOUGHED WORKERS.
>> Stephen: TO SAY SOMETHING
ABOUT THE POSSIBLE WHO LOST--
>> STACEY ABRAMS TOUCHED ON IT.
>> Stephen: IN THE DEMOCRATIC
RESPONSE.
>> YES.
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT THE PEOPLE
WHO HAVE BEEN LIVING PAYCHECK TO
PAYCHECK, WHO HAD MISSED ONE
PAYCHECK, AND MANY MISSED A
SECOND PAYCHECK, HOW THAT
TOTALLY UPENDS YOUR LIVES, I
THOUGHT HE WAS GOING TO SAY
SOMETHING ABOUT THAT, NOTHING.
>> Stephen: HE MADE A BIG SHOW
DURING THE SHUTDOWN OF SAYING,
"THEY AGREE WITH ME.
THEY WANT THIS."
>> AND THERE WERE NO INROADS
MADE WITH THE CHINA
NEGOTIATIONS.
MARCH 1 ARE THE TARIFF
DEADLINES.
HE SAID WE'RE MAKING PROGRESS.
AND THERE ARE NO SPECIFICS AND
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT COULD
REALLY DESTABILIZE THE ECONOMY
IF WE DON'T SEE PROGRESS BEFORE
THE DEADLINE.
>> ONE THING I THOUGHT HE COULD
HAVE DONE THAT WAS SYMBOLIC,
GEORGE BUSH, IN HIS STATE OF THE
UNION, STARTED THE SPEECH BY
SAYING, "IT IS MY GREAT HONOR
TO... AND TURNED TO MADAM
SPEAKER, TURNED TO NANCY PELOSI,
AND TOOK THAT MOMENT TO
ACKNOWLEDGE THAT SHE WAS THERE
AND THAT THE ELECTION HAD
HAPPENED.
IT WAS A GIMME.
WHICH IS TO SAY, TALK ABOUT AN
OLIVE BRANCH, IT'S A GIMME TO
SAY, "I ACKNOWLEDGE YOU, YOUR
POWER."
AND EVERYBODY WOULD HAVE LOVED
IT, AND EVERYBODY WOULD HAVE
SAID, "HE REALLY SHOWED HE IS
PUTTING SOMETHING BEHIND THE
CLAIMS OF UNITY AND
BIPARTISANSHIP."
HE JUST WENT INTO IT.
>> DO YOU THINK HE FORGOT OR DO
YOU THINK IT WAS A BIT OF A--
(  LAUGHTER  ).
>> SERIOUSLY, SERIOUSLY.
DO YOU THINK HE FORGOT TO DO
THAT OR DIDN'T KNOW TO DO THAT
OR IT WAS A BIT OF A DIG?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THEY CHOSE NOT TO DO-- NOT TO
ACKNOWLEDGE THAT --
>> Stephen: I THINK HE
REMEMBERED TO BE RUDE.
( LAUGHTER )
( APPLAUSE )
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> Stephen: OKAY, WE'VE GOT IT
KEEP MOVING HERE.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> Stephen: THE POWER HAS
SHIFTED, OKAY.
SO THAT'S ONE EXAMPLE.
DO YOU THINK THAT HE FEELS IT?
IS THIS IN ANY WAY DIFFERENT?
IS THIS A DIFFERENT TRUMP THAN A
YEAR AGO WHEN HE ADDRESSED THAT
CHAMBER?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
IT WAS CLEAR HE KNEW HE WAS
GOING INTO A DIVIDED GOVERNMENT.
THERE IS THOSE ROUTINE CALLS FOR
UNITY, BUT THERE SEEMED TO BE AN
ABUNDANCE OF IT TONIGHT IN THAT
SPEECH.
HE DID SEEM TO BE TRYING TO
REACH ACROSS THE AISLE, AT THE
SAME TIME, THREATENING THEM TO
END THE INVESTIGATIONS.
( LAUGHTER )
BUT MAKE NO MISTAKE, JUST LIKE
WE SAW IT ON TV, HE SAW THE SEA
OF WHITE OUT THERE.
HE SAW A DIFFERENT CONGRESS
LOOKING BACK AT HIM, AND HE
THOUGHT TO HIMSELF, PROBABLY,
"DANG, I HAD A WHOLE REPUBLICAN
CONGRESS FOR TWO YEARS.
I SHOULD HAVE DONE MORE THAT
FIRST TWO YEARS."
>> YOU THINK HE SAID "DANG?"
THINK ABOUT THIS.
HIS NICKNAME FOR NANCY PELOSI IS
NANCY.
SO HE KNOWS --
>> Stephen: IT'S A REAL
ZINGER.
>> AND YOU COULD SEE THE POWER
THAT SHE HELD IN THAT ROOM.
THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF CONCERN
ABOUT DISCONTENT WENT DEMOCRATIC
PARTY AS WELL, AND YOU WOULD SEE
MOMENT WHERE'S IT LOOKED LIKE
MAYBE SOME OF THE NEWLY ELECTED
DEMOCRATS WOULD SPEAK OUT OR BOO
AND YOU SAW NANCY JUST SAY
THIS...
>> Stephen: SHE WAS GIVING
THE--
>> THERE WILL BE DECORUM IN THE
HOUSE.
AND SHE SORT OF SET THAT TONE
FROM THE VERY BEGINNING.
>> HER FACE DID NOT LOOK LIKE HE
WAS SPARKING JOY WITH HER.
>> NO, SHE'S LOOKING AT THE
SPEECH.
>> Stephen: I THINK SHE'D LIKE
TO MARIE CONDO HIM OUT OF HER
HOUSE.
>> SHE'S LOOKING AT THE SPEECH,
"HOW MANY MORE PAGES ARE THERE."
>> Stephen: SHE'S SITTING
THERE NEXT TO PENCE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK THAT'S LIKE TO
BE SITTING NEXT TO MIKE PENCE
FOR THAT ENTIRE THING?
>> WELL, HE'S GOING TO BE ON
TOMORROW.
WE CAN ASK HIM.
>> THOORS ON "CBS THIS MORNING."
>> I'M GOING TO SAY STEPHEN
COLBERT WANTS TO KNOW.
>> Stephen: SAY I DIDN'T THINK
YOU WERE ALLOWED TO SPEND THAT
MUCH TIME WITH A WOMAN WHO IS
NOT HIS WIFE.
>> HIS WIFEs OF THERE, THOUGH.
SHE WAS KEEPING AN EYE ON HIM.
>> Stephen: SO ALL IS FINE.
HOW ABOUT, HOW ABOUT-- HOW ABOUT
NORMS?
THE STATE OF THE UNION IS ONE OF
THE GREAT REPEATED CEREMONIES OF
THE PRESIDENCY.
IT'S FULL OF NORMS AND CEREMONY.
I-- I.
>> -- I'VE ONLY WATCHED IT ON
TV.
YOU HAVE ALL BEEN DOWN IN
WASHINGTON, D.C.
HAS HE KEPT UP THE NORMS OF THE
STATE OF THE UNION?
>> LARGELY.
>> LARGELY, YEAH.
I MEAN, I THINK SINCE WOODROW
WILSON HE STARTED DELIVERING
THEM IN PERSON TO THE WHOLE
JOINT CONGRESS.
IT'S BECOME MUCH MORE OF A
POLITICAL SPEECH.
HE SEEMS TO BE GOING A LOT
LONGER, THOUGH, THAN SOME OF OUR
PREVIOUS PRESIDENT S.
>> Stephen:  IT WAS
CLINTONNESQUE.
>> HE WAS REALLY KIND OF
STRETCHING IT OUT.
>> Stephen: KIND OF THE
REPUBLICANS' FAULT, BECAUSE THEY
WERE APPLAUDING-- THEY WERE
GIVING STANDING OVATION BETWEEN
SYLLABLES OF WORD.
>> THE BAR IS LOW.
>> IT WAS AN ODDIBLE REMINDER OF
JUST HOW LOCKED IN THE PARTY IS
TO THAT PRESIDENT AND THAT'S NOT
AN INSIGNIFICANT THING AS HE
FACES INVESTIGATIONS AND FACES
ALL OF THESE ROILING TROUBLE S.
>> Stephen:  IF HE GOES DOWN,
IT'S GOING TO BE VERY HARD FOR
THEM TO ABANDON SHIP.
>> IT WOULD BE IMPOSSIBLE.
THEY HAVE STOOD BY HIM --
>> Stephen: IT WILL BE HARD.
>> I PREDICT MUCH OF WHAT WE
HEARD TONIGHT WILL BE FORGOTTEN
BY THE END OF THE WEEK OR NEXT
WEEK.
>> Stephen: I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
"CBS THIS MORNING" AIRS WEEKDAYS
AT 7:00 A.M.
THE "CBS THIS MORNING" TEAM,
EVERYBODY!
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH SPIKE
LEE SNP.
COME ON!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
♪ ♪ ♪
Oh!
♪ Ozempic®! ♪
(announcer)
People with type 2 diabetes
are excited about
the potential
of once-weekly Ozempic®.
In a study with Ozempic®,
a majority of adults
lowered their blood sugar
and reached an A1C
of less than seven
and maintained it.
Oh!
Under seven?
And you may lose weight.
In the same
one-year study,
adults lost on average
up to 12 pounds.
Oh!
Up to 12 pounds?
A two-year study showed
that Ozempic® does not
increase the risk
of major cardiovascular events
like heart attack,
stroke, or death.
Oh!
No increased risk?
♪ Oh, oh, oh, Ozempic®! ♪
Ozempic® should not be the first
medicine for treating diabetes,
or for people with
type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Do not share needles or pens.
Don't reuse needles.
Do not take Ozempic® if you have
a personal or family history
of medullary thyroid cancer,
Multiple Endocrine Neoplasia
Syndrome type 2,
or if you are
allergic to Ozempic®.
Stop taking Ozempic®
and get medical help right away
if you get a lump or swelling
in your neck,
severe stomach pain, itching,
rash, or trouble breathing.
Serious side effects
may happen,
including pancreatitis.
Tell your doctor if you have
diabetic retinopathy
or vision changes.
Taking Ozempic® with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may increase the risk
for low blood sugar.
Common side effects are nausea,
vomiting, diarrhea,
stomach pain, and constipation.
Some side effects
can lead to dehydration,
which may worsen
kidney problems.
I discovered the potential
with Ozempic®.
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! Ozempic®! ♪
Ask your healthcare provider
if Ozempic® is right for you.
Have you ever worked with Dr.
Francis?
Oh yeah, he's OK.
Just OK?
Guess who just got reinstated!
Well, not officially.
Nervous?
Yeah.
Yeah me too.
Don't worry about it, we'll
figure it out.
I'll see ya in there!
JUST OK IS NOT OK.
Especially when it comes to
your network.
AT&T is America's best wireless
network,
according to America's biggest
test.
Now with 5G E.
MORE FOR YOUR THING. THAT'S OUR
THING.
( APPLAUSE )
♪ MOVE ON UP ♪
>> Stephen: WELCOME BACK,
EVERYBODY.
FOLKS, WELCOME BACK TO OUR LIVE
SHOW FOLLOWING THE STATE OF THE
UNION.
>> FOLKS, FOR MORE THAN 30
YEARS, MY NEXT GUEST HAS
DIRECTED FILMS LIKE "DO THE
RIGHT THING," "INSIDE MAN," AND
"MALCOM X." HIS LATEST, "BLACK
KLANSMAN," IS NOMINATED FOR XIX
OSCARS,
INCLUDING BEST DIRECTOR.
PLEASE WELCOME BACK TO "THE LATE
SHOW," SPIKE LEE!
♪ ♪ ♪
( APPLAUSE )
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: WELCOME BACK.
NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
>> GLAD TO BE HERE.
GLAD TO BE HERE.
>> Stephen: NOW, DID YOU GET A
CHANCE TO WATCH ANY OF THE STATE
OF THE UNION?
>> SOME OF IT.
>> Stephen: SOME OF IT.
SOME OF IT.
>> MY THING IS DEEDS, NOT WORDS.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: SURE.
>> YOU CAN TALK ALL YOU WANT,
BUT IF YOU DON'T FOLLOW UP WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING, THEN SOMETHING'S
WRONG.
SO I'M SEEING HIM GIVING--
BRINGING UP PEOPLE WHO SURVIVED
THE HOLOCAUST, FROM
CONCENTRATION CAMPS, PEOPLE WHO
LANDED IN NORMANDY WITH THE
ALLIES TO FIGHT THE NAZIS.
BUT SOMETHING HAPPENED IN
CHARLOTTESVILLE.
( APPLAUSE )
THAT GUY HAD A CHANCE TO
DENOUNCE THE ALT-RIGHT, TO
DENOUNCE THE KLAN, TO DENOUNCE
NEO-NAZIS.
THERE'S A DISCONNECT.
( APPLAUSE )
HATE IS HATE.
AND I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU SAY WE
SHOULD ALL COME TOGETHER WHEN
YOU DEMONIZE PEOPLE.
( APPLAUSE )
YOU SAY MEXICANS ARE MURDERERS,
RAPISTS, AND DRUG DEALERS.
WE HAVE TO BUILD A WALL.
THEN, WHAT REALLY BROKE MY HEART
IS SEEING INFANTS, BABIES
SNATCHED FROM THEIR MOTHER'S
ARMS.
HOW MANY-- WHAT IS THE NUMBER
WHERE CHILDREN HAVE STILL BEEN
NOT CONNECTED WITH THEIR
PARENTS?
AND WHEN THEY PUT THAT STUFF IN
PLACE, THEY HAD NO MECHANISM TO
KEEP TRACK OF THE FAMILIES.
AND FOR ME --
>> Stephen: NOWF THEY'VE
SAID-- NOW THEY'VE SAID IT'S TOO
HARD TO RETURN THEM.
WE DON'T KNOW HOW TO DO IT.
>> YOU HAVE TO PUT SOMETHING IN
PLACE SO FAMILIES -- AND FOR ME,
I THOUGHT OF SLAVERY RIGHT AWAY.
FAMILIES BROKEN APART.
SO THIS GUY--
( APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: I NOTICE YOU'RE
NOT SAYING THE PRESIDENT'S NAME.
YOU DON'T SAY HIS NAME.
>> NO.
>> Stephen: DO YOU HAVE A
NICKNAME FOR HIM?
>> AGENT ORANGE.
( LAUGHTER )
( APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: I WANT TO GET TO
THIS "BLACKkKLANSMAN," SIX
OSCAR NOMINATIONS.
YES.
CONGRATULATIONS.
( APPLAUSE )
WE'VE GOT TO TAKE A COMMERCIAL
BREAK IN A MINUTE, SO I DON'T
WANT TO GO TO THE CLIP JUST
RIGHT NOW, BUT I DO WANT TO ASK
YOU ONE THING, DAVID DUKE
FEATURES IN THIS FILM.
>> YEAH.
>> Stephen: PROMINENTLY.
>> BOTH WAYS.
>> Stephen: BOTH WAYS.
HE WAS WORRIED THAT HE WASN'T
GOING TO BE PORTRAYED WELL IN
THIS FILM.
AND SO HE CALLED THE MAIN
CHARACTER--
>> WELL, YOU SHOULDN'T WEAR A
ROBE AND A HOOD.
>> Stephen: HE CALLED THE MAIN
CHARACTER, RON STALLWORTH, IN
REAL LIFE, AND SAID, YOU KNOW,
"I'M WORRIED HOW I'M GOING TO BE
PORTRAYED HERE.
I HAVE ALWAYS RESPECTED SPIKE
LEE."
HOW DOES IT-- HOW DOES IT MAKE
YOU FEEL?
I WILL SAY, THIS I NEVER THOUGHT
DAVID DUKE AND I WOULD AGREE ON
SOMETHING.
I HAVE ALSO ALWAYS RESPECTED
SPIKE LEE.
>> HE SAID "MALCOLM "X"" IS HIS
FAVORITE FILM.
>> Stephen: DID HE SAY WHY?
>> I WASN'T THERE.
>> Stephen: HE'S A BIG DENZEL
FAN.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
>> Stephen: I WANT TO GET INTO
IT, AND I WANT TO SHOW A
FANTASTIC CLIP OF THE MOVIE IN
JUST A MOMENT.
WE HAVE TO TAKE A BREAK AND
WE'LL BE BACK WITH MORE SPIKE
LEE.
What bad back?
Advil is... Relief that's
fast. Strength that lasts.
You'll ask...
What pain?
With Advil Liqui-Gels.
I'll take a Coke.
Is Pepsi Ok?
Is Pepsi, OK?
Is Pepsi, OK!?
[laughter]
Are puppies, OK?
Is a shooting star, OK?
Is the laughter of
a small child, OK?
Pepsi's more than, OK!
It's
Okayyyy
Okurrrr
♪ I Like It ♪
Okay, what have
we learned today?
You want a Pepsi?
I want a Pepsi.
There you go.
Okurrr. Aaahh.
I've got to come up with
my own catch phrase.
Okayyy
( ♪ )
Ready to JUVÉDERM it?
Correct age-related
volume loss in cheeks
with JUVÉDERM VOLUMA XC,
add fullness to lips
with JUVÉDERM ULTRA XC
and smooth moderate
to severe lines
around the nose and mouth
with JUVÉDERM XC.
Tell your doctor if you
have a history of scarring
or are taking medicines
that decrease the body's
immune response
or that can prolong bleeding.
Common side effects include
injection-site redness,
swelling, pain,
tenderness, firmness,
lumps, bumps, bruising,
discoloration or itching.
As with all fillers,
there is a rare risk
of unintentional injection
into a blood vessel,
which can cause
vision abnormalities,
blindness, stroke,
temporary scabs or scarring.
( ♪ )
JUVÉDERM it.
Talk to your doctor
about the JUVÉDERM
Collection of fillers.
Here's to workouts that
are working.
Special K has iron, protein and
B vitamins.
To feed your progress.
Feed your power.
Feed your change.
Dove gives you
fashion ready underarms
so you can wear anything.
From athletic tops
to zebra dresses,
and everything in between.
Enjoy 48 hour protection
and softer, smoother underarms.
With Dove antiperspirants.
( APPLAUSE )
WORD.
>> I'LL GIVE THE SIX-WORD PITCH.
>> Stephen: SIX WORDS.
THERE IT IS.
YOU WERE NOMINATED FOR BEST
DIRECTOR.
>THIS IS YOUR FIRST
NOMINATION.
>> FIRST TIME.
>> Stephen: FIRST NOMINATION
OF BEST DIRECTOR.
>> AND BEST PICTURE, TOO.
FIRST TIME.
>> Stephen: DO YOU THINK THAT
YOU'RE-- YOU'VE DONE SOME VERY
POWERFUL FILMS.
DO YOU THINK THAT YOU'RE A
BETTER FILMMAKER, OR DO YOU
THINK THE ACADEMY HAS GOTTEN
BETTER ABOUT RECOGNIZING--
>> THE ACADEMY HAS BECOME
DIVERSIFIED.
( APPLAUSE )
THE OSCARS SO WHITE WAS NOT A
GOOD LOOK FOR THEM.
AND WITH THE AFRICAN AMERICAN
WOMAN, WHO WENT TO THE BOARD OF
GOVERNORS AND SAID, LOOK, WE'VE
GOT TO-- THIS ORGANIZATION TO
REFLECT WHAT AMERICA LOOKS
LIKE."
I WOULD NOT HAVE BEEN NOMINATED
AND MANY OTHER PEOPLE OF COLOR
IF NOT FOR THE DIVERSITY THAT
CAME TO THE THE VOTING BODY.
>> Stephen: YOU THINK IT'S A
SIGNIFICANT CHANGE.
>> OH, BIG, BIG, BIG.
( APPLAUSE )
( CHEERS )
>> Stephen: THE MOVIE ITSELF,
THE MOVIE ITSELF RESONATES WITH
OUR OWN TIME.
THERE ARE ACTUALLY REFERENCES TO
THE PRESIDENT-- THE PRESENT AND
THE PRESIDENT-- IN YOUR MOVIE.
ESPECIALLY WITH PEOPLE LIKE
GOVERNOR NORTHAM IN VIRGINIA.
DO YOU WISH IT DIDN'T RESONATE
SO MUCH FOR OUR PRESENT TIME?
>> YOU MAKE A WISH YOU KNOW,
BUT, YOU KNOW, WE LIVE WHERE WE
LIVE.
BUT THE GUY TO SAY IT WAS HIM,
THE NEXT DAY IT WASN'T HIM.
"IT WASN'T ME."
WHAT'S THE NAME OF THAT SONG?
♪ ♪ ♪
"IT WASN'T ME."
SO IT'S LUNY TUNES NOW.
♪ ♪ ♪
IT'S LUNY TUNES.
SO IT'S LUNY TUNES NOW.
>> Stephen: HE DID ADMIT HE
IT'S LUNY TUNES.
HAD DONE A MICHAEL JACKSON
>> Stephen: HE DID ADMIT HE
IMPRESSION.
HAD DONE A MICHAEL JACKSON
>> AND HE PUT SHOE POLISH ON HIS
IMPRESSION.
FACE.
>> AND HE PUT SHOE POLISH ON HIS
>> Stephen: BUT HE SAID ONLY A
FACE.
LITTLE, SPIKE LEE.
>> Stephen: BUT HE SAID ONLY A
>> NOT BUYING IT.
LITTLE, SPIKE LEE.
>> Stephen: NOT BUYING IT?
>> NOT BUYING IT.
>> Stephen: ME, NEITHER.
>> IT'S CRAZY.
I WANT TO SAY, THOUGH, WHAT YOU
DO 0 VERY IMPORTANT BECAUSE
YOU'RE GETET THE WORTH OUTSIDE.
( APPLAUSE )
>> Stephen: THANK YOU, AND
THANK YOU FOR YOUR ART, SHARING
IT WITH US.
VERY NICE OF YOU TO SAY.
>> YOU CALL B.S. ON THIS STUFF,
MAN.
COME ON.
( APPLAUSE ).
>> Stephen: YOU'RE MY FAVORITE
GUEST!
♪
It hasn't always
been easy, has it?
♪
There have been days
when you doubted yourself.
♪
And days when you
were ready to quit.
♪
But you didn't.
Because you had the courage to
venture into something powerful.
Education.
If I leave you with just
three words of advice:
never...stop...growing.
[cheering]
[ music playing ]
♪ Here Comes the Sun ♪
You, all of you.
How you live. What you love.
[ laughter ]
That's what inspired us
to create America's
most advanced Internet.
Internet that
puts you in charge.
[ chattering ]
That protects what's important.
That handles everything
[ group cheering ]
and reaches everywhere.
This is beyond WiFi.
This is xFi.
Simple. Easy. Awesome.
Xfinity.
The future of awesome.
Ok I'll admit. I didn't keep my
place as clean as I would like
'cuz I'm way too busy.
Who's got the time to chase
around down dirt, dust and hair?
So now, I use Heavy Duty Swiffer
Sweeper and Dusters.
For hard-to-reach places, Duster
makes it easy to clean.
It captures dust in one swipe.
Ha! Gotcha!
And Sweeper Heavy
Duty cloths lock away
twice as much dirt and dust.
It gets stuff deep in the
grooves other tools can miss.
Y'know what? My place... is a
lot cleaner now.
Stop cleaning. Start Swiffering.
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.
What would she do without me?