>> STORIES OF SURVIVING DEATH.
>> IT WAS MAGNIFICENT AND
FRIGHTENING AT THE SAME TIME.
>> VIVID DETAILS OF WHAT THEY
SAW.
>> THIS BEAUTIFUL GARDEN.
>> THIS RIVER OF LIGHT.
>> AND A MEDIUM THAT UNRAVELS
THE ANSWERS THEY NEED TO HEAR.
DR. OZ: WHY DO YOU THINK YOU
WERE SENT BACK?
>> PLUS, FILTHY FEBRUARY.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE HOW DIRTY
THESE EVERYDAY ITEMS ARE.
DR. OZ: 10 TIMES MORE GERMS THAN
YOUR TOILET.
>> COMING UP NEXT.
♪
DR. OZ: SEASON 10 STARTS NOW.
TODAY, PEOPLE WHO SURVIVED DEATH
AND SAY THEY CROSSED OVER TO THE
OTHER SIDE, TO A PLACE WHERE FEW
HAVE GONE, WHERE SCIENCE HAS YET
TO EXPLAIN.
TWO STORIES, ONE THAT COULD
HAPPEN TO ANY OF US, A NEAR
FATAL CAR ACCIDENT, AND ANOTHER
THAT DEFIES THE ODDS, BEING
STRUCK BY LIGHTNING.
TWO SURVIVORS HAVE COME TODAY TO
GET ANSWERS ABOUT WHERE THEY
WENT, WHAT THEY SAW, AND WHY
THEY WERE SENT BACK TO SHARE
THEIR STORY.
THEY'VE ASKED FOR THE HELP OF AN
UNLIKELY SOURCE.
TRICIA SAYS THE DAY SHE ALMOST
DIED STARTED OFF LIKE ANY OTHER
NORMAL DAY.
TRICIA: IT WAS A NORMAL DAY.
I WAS DRIVING TO THE AUSTIN 10K,
WHEN OUT OF NOWHERE A CAR WAS
BARRELING TOWARDS ME AND I HAD
PRETTY MUCH A HEAD ON COLLISION.
I WAS RUSHED TO THE HOSPITAL.
I HAD BROKEN MY NECK AND WAS
GOING TO NEED EMERGENCY SPINAL
SURGERY.
I HAD LOST FEELING IN ONE OF MY
LEGS.
I WENT INTO SURGERY AND THE NEXT
THING I KNEW I WAS OUTSIDE OF MY
BODY.
THE MONITOR FLATLINED.
I WAS DEAD.
IT WAS LIKE, OH MY GOD.
I DID NOT WANT TO BE IN THAT
ROOM ANYMORE, SO I LEFT.
EVENTUALLY I TRANSITIONED INTO A
DIFFERENT ROOM.
I BELIEVED THIS ROOM TO BE THE
BEGINNING OF HEAVEN.
DR. OZ: TRICIA JOINS ME NOW.
YOU DESCRIBED A SOUND NO ONE
WANTS TO HEAR, A FLATLINE, IN
THIS CASE YOURS.
HOW LONG DID YOUR HEART STOP
BEATING?
TRICIA: TWO AND A HALF MINUTES.
DR. OZ: I GATHER YOU HAD AN OUT
OF BODY EXPERIENCE.
WHAT DID YOU THINK WAS
HAPPENING?
TRICIA: I WAS AT PEACE.
I WAS FINE WITH THIS.
I WAS AGNOSTIC AT THE TIME.
I WAS SO EXCITED THAT WE GO ON.
MY SOUL CONTINUES ON, THERE'S
THIS CONSCIOUSNESS THAT
TRANSCENDS THIS PHYSICAL FORM.
DR. OZ: IT IS NICE TO KNOW IT
DOESN'T ALL END WHEN IT IS OVER.
THE RESEARCH REVEALS THAT PEOPLE
SOMETIMES SEE SPIRITS ON THE
OTHER SIDE, SOMETIMES DON'T.
DO YOU SEE ANYONE ELSE?
TRICIA: YES, I SAW THESE AMAZING
ANGELS.
I SAW THESE NINE FOOT BEINGS
THAT WERE INCREDIBLY
INTELLIGENT.
THEY WERE SENDING HEALING LIGHT
INTO MY BODY.
DR. OZ: DO YOU THEN END UP IN
HEAVEN?
WERE YOU ABLE TO SPEAK WITH GOD?
TRICIA: AFTER THAT MOMENT WHEN
THE MONITOR FLATLINED, I
TRANSITIONED INTO THIS PLACE
NEAR GOD WHERE I WAS GIVEN A LOT
OF INFORMATION AT A VERY QUICK
SPEED.
IT WAS FANTASTIC.
DR. OZ: WHAT KINDS OF
INFORMATION?
TRICIA: I WAS SHOWN DIFFERENT
THINGS ABOUT MY LIFE.
I HAD THE LIFE REVIEW THAT MANY
PEOPLE HAVE.
I SAW THAT EYE WAS NOT ALWAYS
KIND TO PEOPLE.
I WAS SHOWN THAT THEY HAD GOOD
HEARTS AND I NEEDED TO LOOK INTO
THE HEARTS OF PEOPLE TO SEE WHO
THEY ARE, NOT TO JUDGE THEM
MATERIALLY.
I LEARNED A WHOLE LOT MORE.
I TRANSITIONED INTO A HEAVENLY
LANDSCAPE.
DR. OZ: WERE YOU THE SAME AGE IN
HEAVEN AS YOU WERE ON THAT
OPERATING TABLE?
TRICIA: GOD TOLD ME TO BE LIKE A
LITTLE CHILD.
THAT SPIRIT BODY, I TRANSITIONED
WHEN I ENTERED HEAVEN AS A CHILD
OF FIVE YEARS OLD.
CHILDREN ARE VERY MUCH ALIVE,
YOU KNOW.
SO I FELT THAT WAY.
DR. OZ: WHO WAS THE LAST PERSON
YOU SAW IN HEAVEN?
TRICIA: MY GRANDFATHER WAS THERE
TO GREET ME AND HE ESCORTED ME
INTO HEAVEN.
DR. OZ: DID YOU SPEAK WITH HIM?
DID HE ASK ANY QUESTIONS?
TRICIA: HE JUST GAVE ME LOVE AND
PEACE AND COMFORT AND SAID,
WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO ON?
THE ADVENTUROUS SOUL THAT I AM,
I WAS LIKE, YES.
I STARTED FLYING TO THAT AMAZING
, BEAUTIFUL, PEACEFUL LOVE OF
GOD AND I NEVER FELT BETTER.
THERE IS NO EXPERIENCE LIKE IT.
THERE IS NO DRUG.
THERE IS NO LOVE.
THERE IS NOTHING ON EARTH LIKE
THAT.
DR. OZ: WHY DO YOU THINK YOU
WERE CHOSEN TO CROSS OVER AND
THEN BE SENT BACK?
TRICIA: GOD STOPPED ME.
I DID NOT WANT TO COME BACK.
I INSISTED THAT I STAY AND GOD
SAID NO, YOU MUST RETURN.
DR. OZ: I STILL HAVE QUESTIONS.
I KNOW YOU DO AS WELL.
SHE ASKED US TO CONNECT HER WITH
SOMEONE WHO MIGHT NOT BE ABLE TO
JUST EXPLAIN DEATH
SCIENTIFICALLY, BUT MORE
IMPORTANTLY, OFFER A SPIRITUAL
POINT OF VIEW.
I WANT TO BRING IN ANNA
RAIMONDI.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: I CAN THROW OUT IDEAS
ABOUT WHY WHEN YOUR BLOOD
PRESSURE DROPS, AND THEY WERE
OPERATING ON YOU, LOSING A LOT
OF BLOOD, AS A SCIENTIST I
UNDERSTAND THAT, BUT I'M TRYING
TO UNDERSTAND WHAT REALLY
HAPPENS WHEN WE DIE FROM A
SPIRITUAL PERSPECTIVE.
ANNA: WHEN WE FIRST PASS, WE
HANG AROUND THOSE WHO ARE
GRIEVING, BECAUSE WE WANT TO
HELP THEM AS WELL.
WHEN SOMEONE FIRST PASSES, THEY
ARE AROUND FOR ABOUT FOUR TO SIX
WEEKS, HELPING.
THEN WE TRANSITION.
WE SEE SOMEONE THAT WE KNOW TO
GIVE US COMFORT.
THERE IS STILL FEAR AROUND THE
TRANSITION.
ONCE WE UNDERSTAND THAT WE CAN
MOVE ON AND THAT WE ARE GOING TO
A PLACE WHERE WE WILL BE LOVED,
WE MOVE ON.
DR. OZ: WHERE DO WE GO WHEN WE
DIE?
TRICIA TOLD US ABOUT HEAVEN AS
SHE SIGHED.
SHE'S BEEN FAIRLY DETAILED ABOUT
WHAT HEAVEN FELT LIKE FOR HER.
ANNA: WE GO TO A PLACE THAT IS
RIGHT HERE.
THE DIMENSION IS RIGHT HERE.
WE ARE NOT UP IN THE SKY.
IT IS A BEAUTIFUL WAY TO THINK
ABOUT HEAVEN, BUT IT TRULY IS
RIGHT HERE.
WE GO TO THIS PLACE THAT IS PURE
LOVE.
DR. OZ: WE DON'T PHYSICALLY MOVE
FROM OUR BODY?
ANNA: WE DO.
THE SOUL LEAVES INTO THIS OTHER
DIMENSION.
THE BODY STAYS IN THE MATERIAL
WORLD, BUT THE SOUL MOVES INTO
THIS OTHER DIMENSION.
DR. OZ: WHICH IS ALL AROUND US.
ANNA: ALL THE TIME.
IF YOU MOVE OUT OF FEAR, YOU CAN
CONNECT TO YOUR LOVED ONES.
DR. OZ: WHEN WE COME BACK,
TRICIA IS GOING TO ASK FOR THE
ANSWERS SHE CAME TO FIND OUT.
SPECIFICALLY, A QUESTION THAT
YOU'VE THE DAY YOU SAW
YOUR GRANDFATHER.
STAY WITH US.
[APPLAUSE]
>> GROCERY STORE STATE, SO MUCH
TO CHOOSE FROM.
WE ARE GOING BEHIND THE BUTCHERS
COUNTER.
ARE YOU GETTING THE BIGGEST BANG
FOR YOUR BUCK?
PLUS --
>> WHAT DO YOU FEEL?
>> ARE YOU ADDICTED TO EXTREME
ONLINE SHOPPING?
>> WE WILL REVEAL THE WARNING
SIGNS.
>> IT IS AFFECTING THE BRAIN THE
WAY DRUGS DO.
Well, here's to first dates!
You look amazing.
And you look amazingly
comfortable.
When your V-Neck looks more
like a U-Neck...
That's when you know, it's
Half-Washed.
Try Downy Fabric Conditioner.
Unlike detergent alone, Downy
helps prevent stretching
by conditioning and smoothing
fibers,
so clothes look newer, longer.
Downy and it's done.
I know it's hard Maddie.
But I promise,
it's gonna get better.
♪ ♪
(mom giggles)
(VO) At Pro Plan,
we believe nutrition is full of
possibilities to improve
your pet's life.
We're redefining
what nutrition can do.
Because the possibility
of a longer life
and a healthy life
is the greatest
possibility of all.
Purina Pro Plan.
Nutrition that Performs.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE ARE BACK
INVESTIGATING, CAN LIFE AFTER
DEATH SURVIVORS GET ANSWERS FROM
THE OTHER SIDE?
TRISTA SAYS SHE FLATLINED FOR
TWO AND A HALF MINUTES WHILE
DOCTORS RUSHED TO SAVE HER LIFE.
SHE ASKED US TO CONNECT HER WITH
GRIEF COUNSELOR AND MEDIUM ANNA
RAIMONDI TO HELP MAKE SENSE OF
WHAT SCIENCE AND MEDICINE CANNOT
EXPLAIN.
THE ONE BIG QUESTION YOU'VE BEEN
WONDERING ABOUT SINCE YOU
SURVIVE?
TRICIA: WHEN GOD SHOWED ME THAT
RIVER OF LIGHT, I INTERPRETED
THESE LIGHTS AS SOULS THAT
NEEDED TO BE REMINDED OF GOD AND
THEIR PURPOSE AND THEIR LOVE.
I SAW THEM AS STUDENTS.
NOW THAT MY LIFE IS EVOLVING,
ARE THESE PEOPLE THAT I'M GOING
TO REACH THROUGH SPEAKING HERE?
ANNA: I DON'T THINK THEY ARE
JUST STUDENTS, BUT EVERYBODY IS
A STUDENT.
YOU ARE TEACHING THE MASSES
ABOUT YOUR EXPERIENCE.
THIS IS WAY BIGGER THAN JUST THE
PEOPLE YOU TEACH IN A CLASSROOM.
AND YOU WILL HELP THEM.
AND YOU HAVE BEEN HELPING THEM.
TRICIA: IS IT CONNECTED TO
PARTICULAR PAINS IN THEIR LIFE
THEY NEED TO OVERCOME?
ANNA: ALWAYS.
WE ALL GO THROUGH LIFE SEEKING
TO HEAL.
WITH EACH ONE, YOU WILL TOUCH
SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
DR. OZ: CAN YOU HELP ME
UNDERSTAND WHY TRICIA SAW HER
GRANDFATHER?
I'M ALWAYS AMAZED.
I'VE MET MANY ON THE SHOW OR
JUST TRAVELING AROUND, THEY SEEM
TO ALWAYS MEET PEOPLE.
WHY WOULD TRICIA MEET HER
GRANDFATHER?
ANNA: BECAUSE SHE FELT SAFE WITH
HIM.
SHE FELT COMFORT WITH HIM.
HE WAS ABLE TO EXPRESS THAT LOVE
WHEN MAYBE SHE WASN'T GETTING IT
FROM OTHER PEOPLE IN HER LIFE.
HE CAME TO SAY, I LOVE YOU, I'VE
GOT YOU.
DR. OZ: HOW DOES THAT FEEL?
TRICIA: IT FEELS AMAZING.
HE DID LOVE ME AND I DIDN'T FEEL
THAT FOR MOST OF MY FAMILY.
I CERTAINLY FELT THAT
UNCONDITIONAL LOVE AND LACK OF
JUDGMENT.
I DID FEEL INCREDIBLY PEACEFUL
WITH HIM.
DR. OZ: THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WHEN WE COME BACK, A WOMAN WHO
SURVIVED BEING STRUCK BY
LIGHTNING AND EXPERIENCED A
VERSION OF HEAVEN YOU'VE NEVER
HEARD BEFORE.
SHE ISOME
ANSWERS.
[APPLAUSE]
>> DID YOU KILL TRAVIS
ALEXANDER?
>> CONVICTED OF KILLING HER
BOYFRIEND.
WHY HER LAWYERS
Oats and oat bran
have a soluble fiber
called beta-glucan,
which can help
lower cholesterol
as part of
a heart-healthy diet.
Now it's in new
Quaker Oat Beverage,
a super-smooth
dairy alternative.
♪♪
Now it's in new
Quaker Oat Beverage,
♪ 'Cos I know what it means ♪
♪ To walk along the lonely
street of dreams ♪
♪ Here I go again on my--- ♪
You realize your vows are a
Whitesnake song?
I do.
If you ride, you get it.
GEICO Motorcycle.
15 minutes
could save you 15% or more.
♪
You're not just mom.
You're her whole world.
Don't just get away, come
together.
Save up to 30%. Hurry.
Offer ends soon.
Never ending is now even better
at Olive Garden.
All new Never Ending Stuffed
Pastas starting at $12.99.
Pick your favorite stuffed
pasta, sauce and topping.
It's all never ending.
All new
Never Ending Stuffed Pastas.
Only for a limited time,
at Olive Garden.
>> IT WAS A HOT SUMMER DAY.
I WAS ON MY PORCH, TALKING ON MY
CORDLESS PHONE.
IT STARTED TO RAIN, BUT I WAS
COVERED SO I WASN'T GETTING WET.
I HEARD SOME THUNDER RUMBLING IN
THE DISTANCE, THEN I HEARD A
LOUD CRACK.
THE LIGHTNING CAME AND HIT MY
RIGHT ARM.
I FELT THIS HORRIBLE PAIN.
AND THEN MY SPIRIT JUST PEELED
OUT OF MY BODY.
AND WHAT HAPPENED AFTER THAT WAS
BOTH MAGNIFICENT AND FRIGHTENING
AT THE SAME TIME.
DR. OZ: BEING STRUCK BY
LIGHTNING, A NEAR-DEATH
EXPERIENCE YOU DON'T HEAR ABOUT
OFTEN.
SHARON IS HERE WITH HOW SHE
ALMOST DIED AND WHAT SHE SAYS
SHE SAW.
BEFORE WE GET TO WHAT YOU SAW
WHEN YOU CROSSED OVER, WHAT DOES
IT FEEL LIKE TO BE STRUCK BY
LIGHTNING?
SHARON: IT IS A HORRIBLE PAIN.
BURNING, SEARING, HORRIFIC, JUST
A HORRIFIC PAIN.
DR. OZ: SO YOU REMEMBER THE PAIN
AND THE LIGHTNING DAMAGED YOUR
HEART, SO YOU COLLAPSED.
WHAT DID YOU SEE WHEN YOU
CROSSED OVER?
SHARON: MY SPIRIT JUST PEELED
OUT OF MY BODY AND I WENT INTO
MY HOUSE AND IT WAS MY HOUSE,
BUT NOTHING IN MY HOUSE WAS MY
STUFF, AND I HEARD OLD-TIME
RADIO PLAYING AND IT SOUNDED
LIKE SOMETHING LIKE WHAT YOU
WOULD HEAR ON THE WALTONS.
DR. OZ: LIKE A HUNDRED YEARS
AGO, 80 YEARS AGO.
SHARON: LIKE BACK IN THE 1920'S
OR 1930'S.
AFTER THE LIGHTNING HIT MY ARM,
IT TRAVELED UNDER THE HOUSE AND
BLUE THE TRANSFORMER IN FRONT OF
THE HOUSE, SO WE DIDN'T HAVE ANY
POWER.
DR. OZ: SO THERE COULDN'T HAVE
BEEN ANY MUSIC IN THE HOUSE.
SHARON: NO, WE WERE WITHOUT
POWER.
I KNEW THAT I HAD BEEN STRUCK BY
LIGHTNING, BUT I DIDN'T KNOW I
WAS DEAD YET, SO I WAS REALLY
CONFUSED ABOUT WHAT WAS GOING
ON.
APPARENTLY I WAS A GHOST.
DR. OZ: DID YOU TRANSITION FROM
THIS OLDER VERSION OF YOUR HOUSE
WITHOUT YOUR STUFF IN IT TO
HEAVEN?
YOUR EXPERIENCE IS DIFFERENT
FROM WHAT I HEAR FROM MANY WHO
HAVE CROSSED OVER.
SHARON: AFTER ABOUT TWO OR THREE
MINUTES OF THIS PERIOD OF --
THIS WEIRD PERIOD, THERE WAS
THIS PRESENCE THAT APPEARED.
IT WAS A HUGE LOVING PRESENCE
AND IT JUST FILLED ME FOR LOVE
THIS UNBELIEVABLE LOVE LIKE I'VE
NEVER EXPERIENCED IN MY LIFE.
I WENT FROM BEING IN THIS HOUSE
THAT I KNEW WAS MY HOUSE AND
DIDN'T HAVE ANYTHING IN IT THAT
BELONGED TO ME, TO GOING INTO
THESE BEAUTIFUL CLOUDS.
I DIDN'T GO UP OR DOWN.
I WENT SIDEWAYS.
WE MOVED VERY QUICKLY THROUGH
THESE PINK AND GOLD CLOUDS.
AT THE END, I WAS IN THIS
BEAUTIFUL GARDEN.
IT WAS THE MOST MAGNIFICENT
GARDEN I'VE EVER SEEN IN MY
LIFE.
THE COLORS WERE SO RICH AND
VIBRANT.
THE PINKS WERE PINKER AND THE
REDS WERE REDDER.
DR. OZ: AND YOU SAW PEOPLE
THERE.
SHARON: YES.
WHEN I FIRST GOT INTO THE
GARDEN, THESE TW YOUNG MEN
GREETED ME.
AT FIRST I THOUGHT THEY WERE
ANGELS, BUT THEN IT HIT ME, THEY
WERE MY BROTHERS WHO HAD DIED AS
BABIES.
THEY WERE FULLY GROWN AND THEY
LOOKED JUST LIKE MY DAD.
I HAD MY LIFE REVIEW AND IT WAS
LIKE WATCHING AN OLD-FASHIONED
MOVIE.
IT WAS EVERYTHING FROM THE TIME
I WAS BORN UNTIL THE TIME I
DIED.
DR. OZ: WHY DIDN'T YOU STAY
THERE?
SHARON: I DIDN'T REALLY HAVE A
CHOICE.
I HAD TO COME BACK.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
DR. OZ: LET'S TALK ABOUT THAT.
SHARON SAYS SHE HAS LINGERING
QUESTIONS.
LET ME BRING BACK ANNA RAIMONDI.
THIS STORY, ELEMENTS ARE
RECURRENT, ELEMENTS ARE
DIFFERENT.
HOW DO YOU MAKE SENSE OF IT?
I'M CURIOUS ABOUT WHY SHE WAS
SENT BACK.
ANNA: SHE WAS SENT BACK FOR THE
SAME REASON, TO TELL HER STORY.
IT MAY NOT BE STANDING AT A
PODIUM.
IT MAY BE IN COMMUNITY.
ARE YOU VERY RELIGIOUS?
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE IT ALSO
MOVES THROUGH RELIGION.
WHO IS KATHLEEN, CATHERINE, AND
MARY?
SHARON: MY MOTHER.
ANNA: IS YOUR GRANDMOTHER
CATHERINE?
I KNOW THESE ARE SEPARATE
PEOPLE.
THEY ARE VERY MUCH AROUND YOU ON
YOUR JOURNEY.
AND ALSO TRYING TO HEAL YOU.
THEY ARE VERY MUCH AROUND A
LITTLE BOY.
DO YOU HAVE A SON OR A GRANDSON?
SHARON: GRANDSON.
ANNA: HIS NAME BEGINS WITH A C O
R --
SHARON: CONNOR.
ANNA: THEY ARE VERY MUCH AROUND
HIM.
THEY ARE TRYING TO GIVE HIM
CLARITY, TRYING TO MAKE YOU SEE
THINGS MORE CLEARLY AS WELL.
HER EXPERIENCE WAS A LITTLE BIT
DIFFERENT, BUT I ALSO FEEL LIKE
IT IS A DIFFERENT KIND OF FROM
A.
WHO IS GARY?
SHARON: MY DAD.
ANNA: HE IS LIVING?
SHARON: YES.
ANNA: THEY ARE SAYING, I LOVE
HIM.
DOES HE LIVED CLOSE TO YOU?
IT IS IMPORTANT THAT YOU STAY
AROUND HIM.
HE'S STILL GRIEVING.
HE'S OK, THOUGH.
DR. OZ: I CAN'T EVEN BEGIN TO
UNDERSTAND HOW YOU KNOW THIS.
WE DON'T FEED INFORMATION TO
YOU.
BUT I KNOW THAT YOU'VE TALKED TO
MANY AND THEY ALL FEEL THE SAME
SENSE OF AWE THAT I HAVE.
SHARON, AS YOU TRY TO MAKE SENSE
OF WHY THIS HAPPENED TO YOU, HOW
DOES IT AFFECT YOU?
SHARON: I AGREE WITH WHAT SHE'S
SAYING.
I PROMISED GOD WHEN I WAS A
LITTLE GIRL THAT I WOULD TAKE
CARE OF MY PARENTS IN THEIR
OLDER YEARS.
I WAS A CAREGIVER FOR MY MOTHER
FOR THE LAST SIX YEARS OF HER
LIFE.
SHE HAD ALZHEIMER'S.
I TOOK CARE OF HER WHEN SHE DIED
AND I TOOK CARE OF MY DAD FOR A
WHILE AFTER HER DEATH.
HE'S DOING VERY WELL.
HE'S VERY HAPPY NOW.
DR. OZ: YOUR TASK IS TO KEEP
DOING THAT.
ANNA: I SEE YOUR MOTHER IN A
CHURCH, BY THE WAY.
SHARON: SHE PASSED AWAY.
ANNA: SHE'S PRAYING.
ARE THEY CATHOLIC?
IT LOOKS LIKE A CATHOLIC CHURCH
AND SHE'S LIGHTING CANDLES.
SHE WANTS YOU TO NEVER BE
AFRAID.
DR. OZ: GOOD ADVICE GOING
FORWARD.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: YOU CAN HEAR LOTS MORE
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: I LOVE GETTING TO TALK
WITH YOU ON MY SHOW EVERY DAY,
BUT WHEN THE CAMERAS STOP
ROLLING, THE CONVERSATION IS NOT
OVER.
I STILL HAVE A LOT I WANT TO
TALK ABOUT.
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
-We're doing karaoke later,
and you're gonna sing.
-Jamie, this is your house?
-I know, it's not much,
but it's home.
Right, kids?
-Kids?
-Papa, Papa!
-[ Laughs ]
-You didn't tell me
your friends were coming.
-Oh, yeah.
-This one is tiny like a child.
-Yeah, she is.
Oh, but seriously,
it's good to be surrounded
by what matters most --
a home and auto bundle
from Progressive.
-Oh, sweetie,
please, play for us.
-Oh, no, I couldn't.
-Please.
-Okay.
[ Singing in Spanish ]
-Please.
-Okay.
APPLE PODCAST OR WHEREVER YOU
GET YOUR PODCAST.
>> POLICE OFFICER HERE.
I'M GOING TO GRAB A OF GENES SO
YOU CAN TEST THEM.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: IT IS FILTHY FEBRUARY.
IT IS NOT JUST ME.
WE ASKED OUR WHOLE AUDIENCE TO
BRING IN THEIR GENES -- JEANS SO
WE CAN DO A GERM TEST.
THERE'S A LOT.
SOME OF THEM ARE CLEAN.
SOME NOT SO MUCH.
WE DECIDED TO SEE JUST HOW
FILTHY THEY ARE.
THAT WAS THE PURPOSE HERE.
TO FIND THE ANSWER TO THE BIG
QUESTION, HOW OFTEN SHOULD YOU
BE WASHING THESE JEANS?
THE RESULTS ARE COMING UP AND
TWO PEOPLE IN OUR AUDIENCE STOOD
OUT, THE CLEANEST AND THE
DIRTIEST.
WHO ARE YOU?
SEE 58, COME DOWN.
72, COME DOWN.
LET'S SEE YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: HOW ARE YOU?
WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
ADRIENNE AND BETHANY.
ARE YOU NERVOUS?
>> A LITTLE.
DR. OZ: LET ME SEE YOUR GENES.
CAN I TELL THE DIFFERENCE?
A LITTLE DIFFERENT FROM EACH
OTHER.
SOMEONE HAS TO GO FIRST.
WHO THINKS THEY ARE THE DIRTY
ONE?
THAT WASN'T HARD.
[LAUGHTER]
>> IT WASN'T AT ALL.
DR. OZ: YOUR FIRST NAME IS
BETHANY, RIGHT, AND YOU THINK
YOU ARE PRETTY CLEAN?
I'M GOING TO GO FIRST.
EVERYONE ELSE IS VERY RELIEVED
THEY ARE NOT UP HERE.
MY JEANS SCORED 320.
REMEMBER, A NUMBER THAT IS A
LOT LESS THAN THAT, ONE HAD A
SCORE OF 35.
ONE OF YOU HAD A SUPER DIRTY
511.
THAT PAIR BELONGED TO ADRIENNE.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> THAT IS WHAT I THOUGHT.
DR. OZ: WHAT IS GOING ON WITH
THESE GENES -- JEANS?
>> IN MY DEFENSE, I'M GOING TO
PLEAD MY CASE RIGHT NOW, I WORK
FROM HOME.
I DON'T HAVE TO LEAVE VERY
OFTEN.
WHEN I THROW MY JEANS ON, EVERY
NOW AND THEN, AND I READ A STUDY
SOMEWHERE THAT YOU SHOULDN'T
WASH YOUR JEANS TOO OFTEN.
DR. OZ: WHERE DID YOU READ THAT
ARTICLE?
>> I DON'T KNOW, BUT I WISH I
KNEW RIGHT NOW.
SO I WASH THEM EVERY 3, 4 --
DR. OZ: TO MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER,
I GOT A 360.
THAT WASN'T MUCH BETTER.
BETHANY, YOUR GENES WERE CLEANER
THAN ADRIENNE'S, THEN MINES,
THEN EVERYBODY ELSE.
EVERY PAIR OF JEANS I'M LOOKING
AT WAS DIRTIER THAN YOURS.
HOW OFTEN DO YOU WASH YOURS?
>> WHENEVER I WEAR THEM, THEY GO
INTO THE WASH IMMEDIATELY AFTER.
DR. OZ: I WANT TO SEE IF YOU ALL
DO THIS.
I WANT TO KNOW HOW OFTEN YOU
WASH YOUR JEANS.
60% WASH YOUR JEANS BETWEEN
SECOND AND FOURTH WHERE.
MOST OF YOU, RIGHT, THAT IS
UNBELIEVABLE.
I CAME ACROSS A FAIR AMOUNT OF
INTERESTING RISKS THAT MIGHT BE
THERE IF YOU DON'T WASH YOUR
JEANS ENOUGH.
BUT NOT THE ONES YOU THINK.
THE BIGGEST ISSUE, YOU LOOK AT
ALL THE JEANS, MANY DIFFERENT
BRANDS, THEY ALL HAVE THE SAME
POTENTIAL RISK.
ROUGHLY 60% OF YOU ARE CHANGING
YOUR JEANS OUT AFTER 2, 3, 4
WEARS.
I'M ONE OF THE GUYS OVER HERE,
SAME AS YOU, IF I WEAR IT FOR AN
HOUR OR TWO, I'M NOT GOING TO
WASH MY JEANS.
BUT HERE'S THE RISK THAT PEOPLE
DIDN'T REALIZE.
YOU PROBABLY SAY TO YOURSELF THE
GERMS ARE ON THE OUTSIDE, RIGHT?
>> NOT LIKE IT IS ON THE INSIDE.
DR. OZ: I SAY THAT TOO,
ABSOLUTELY.
THEY CAN'T GET TO ME.
BUT HERE'S THE CATCH.
WHEN YOU DON'T WASH YOUR JEANS,
THIS FABRIC STARTS TO STRETCH.
THEY BECOME VERY COMFORTABLE.
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOUR PANTS ARE
A LITTLE LOOSE?
DON'T YOU FEEL GOOD ABOUT LIFE?
YOU ARE LOSING WEIGHT, RIGHT?
YOU COULD EAT A LITTLE EXTRA
BECAUSE THE JEANS ARE LOOSE ON
YOU.
WHO CARES ABOUT THE SCALE?
THAT IS WHY WE HAVE TO WASH OUR
JEANS EVERY THREE OR FOUR TIMES,
BECAUSE OTHERWISE THEY STRETCH
FURTHER OUT AND WE ARE
SABOTAGING OUR DIETS.
I THANK YOU FOR YOUR HONESTY.
I'M GOING TO BRING IN AN EXPERT.
CAROLYN FORTE IS HERE FROM GOOD
HOUSEKEEPING TO FIND OUT EXACTLY
HOW TO WASH YOUR JEANS.
YOU HEARD FROM THE AUDIENCE.
WHAT IS THE IDEAL?
YOU ACTUALLY TEST THESE THINGS.
CAROLYN: WE TEST JEANS AND
FABRICS.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS YOU WANT THEM
CLEAN, BUT YOU ALSO WANT THEM
LOOKING GOOD.
WE SAY EVERY FOUR TO FIVE
WEARINGS.
YOU WANT THEM TO LOOK GOOD, BUT
YOU WANT THEM TO BE CLEAN.
DR. OZ: YOU COULD GET AWAY WITH
FOUR OR FIVE TIMES.
CAROLYN: YOU COULD.
IF YOU HAVE STAINS OR YOU ARE
SWEATING IN THEM, YOU NEED TO
WASH THEM.
DR. OZ: WHAT ABOUT THIS ISSUE OF
FREEZING THE GERMS, KILLING THEM
BY FREEZING THEM?
I PUT SOME IN HERE.
PEOPLE PUT THEM IN HERE NEXT TO
THE FROZEN CARROTS.
THEY ARE NICE AND CHILLY.
CRYOTHERAPY.
WHY DOESN'T THAT WORK?
CAROLYN: BECAUSE THE BACTERIA
ISN'T KILLED BY FREEZING IT.
LIKE IN YOUR FOOD, BACTERIA
DOESN'T GET KILLED WHEN YOU
FREEZE IT, IT JUST GOES DORMANT.
ONCE YOU PUT THEM BACK ON, THEY
COME BACK UP TO TEMPERATURE,
THAT BACTERIA COMES TO LIFE
AGAIN.
THE ONLY WAY TO CLEAN YOUR GENES
IS TO WASH THEM.
DR. OZ: THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: NEXT, OUR INVESTIGATION
CONTINUES WITH DRY CLEANING.
FIND OUT WHAT OUR GERM TEST
UNCOVERED.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: NEXT, DORINDA AND JOHN
FROM THE REAL HOUSEWIVES ARE
HERE WITH THE INSIDE SCOOP ABOUT
DRY CLEANING.
ARE THEY REALLY CLEANING THEM?
WHAT IS JOHN'S NICKNAME, BY THE
WAY?
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
I use this
every day
But is Beth's soap
as clean rinsing as Dove?
My soap's still leaving
plenty of things behind
But Dove is cleaner rinsing
My soap,
...Dove.
Made with 1/4
moisturizing cream...
Dove cleans and cares
beautifully.
Welcome to our
Lipton Tea Factory
where the Sun soaks the leaves
with 4,000 hours of sunshine...
...before we pick them
at the peak of freshness,
for a smooth, refreshing taste
and aroma
in every cup of Lipton.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE ARE BACK WITH OUR
FILTHY FEBRUARY INVESTIGATION.
HOW FILTHY ARE YOUR DRY CLEANED
CLOTHES, AND WHAT REALLY HAPPENS
AFTER YOU DROP THEM OFF?
WE ARE ABOUT TO REVEAL WHAT OUR
GERM TEST UNCOVERED.
HERE IS THE CLEANEST COUPLE THAT
I KNOW, REAL HOUSEWIFE DORINDA
MEDLEY AND JOHN MAHDESSIAN.
COME ON OUT.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: YOU LOOK SPARKLING.
HOW ARE YOU?
SO, JOHN IS A THIRD-GENERATION
DRY CLEANER.
PASSIONATE ABOUT REMOVING
STAINS.
CORRECT ME IF THIS RUMOR IS MADE
UP, BUT SOMEONE SAID YOU
ACTUALLY SPELLED WINE ON YOUR
BEAUTIFUL GIRLFRIEND.
DORINDA: WE HAVE THESE ACCIDENTS
ONCE IN A WHILE.
WE WERE DOING A DEMONSTRATION.
TO TAKE OUT A STAIN, NOT A CUP
OF WINE.
JOHN: I WAS SUPPOSED TO POUR A
LITTLE BIT.
SHE SAID, NOW WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?
I SAID, I HAVE TO GET FIVE MORE
STAIN KITS.
DR. OZ: VERY SUAVE.
DORINDA: ACTUALLY, THERE'S A
LITTLE SECRET.
I HAD TO RUN TO THE BACK OF THE
STORE AND PUT ON SOMEONE'S DRESS
TO DO THE COMMERCIAL.
JOHN: BUT IT ALL CAME OUT.
DR. OZ: WHAT IS THE MOST
SURPRISING THING YOU LEARNED
ABOUT DRY CLEANING?
DORINDA: THE MOST SURPRISING
THING I LEARNED IT IS NOT JUST
ABOUT DRY CLEANING.
IT IS ABOUT STORING AND
PRESERVING AND INVESTMENT.
SHE HAS COLLECTIONS FROM ANNA
WINTOUR.
DR. OZ: THERE'S A LOT OF
MISCONCEPTIONS ABOUT DRY
CLEANING.
WE TOOK A POLL.
HOW MANY OF YOU THINK THE DRY
CLEANERS ACTUALLY CLEAN YOUR
CLOTHES?
THINK ABOUT THAT.
70% OF YOU THINK DRY CLEANERS
DON'T CLEAN YOUR CLOTHES
THOROUGHLY.
HOW DO YOU CLEAN IT WITHOUT
GETTING WET?
WE SET UP A GERM EXPERIMENT TO
FIND OUT IF YOUR CLOTHES ARE
REALLY CLEAN.
WE HAD SOME OF OUR VIEWERS BRING
IN DIFFERENT ARTICLES OF
CLOTHING.
WE MEASURED THE GERM SCORE.
THEN WE SENT THE CLOTHES TO
DIFFERENT DRY CLEANERS.
ARE YOU READY FOR THE RESULTS?
ONE-OF-A-KIND EXPERIMENT.
IF IT DOES WORK, I WANT TO
UNDERSTAND HOW YOU DO THIS
MAGIC.
HERE'S HOW THE GERM SCORE WORKS.
BELOW 50, THAT IS DORINDA
QUALITY.
ABOVE 50, WE WILL SAY IT IS
DIRTY.
MORE IS WORSE.
BEFORE WE SENT THE CLOTHES OFF,
THERE WAS A VARIED RANGE, BUT
THEY WERE ALL CONTAMINATED
BETWEEN 95 AND 430.
WE SWAPPED THEM AGAIN AFTER THE
DRY CLEANING AND HERE'S WHAT WE
FOUND.
WE GOT ALL THE CLOTHES BACK.
THE GERM SCORES WERE UNDER 50.
THEN THE QUESTION COMES, WHAT IS
GOING ON?
WHAT DO THEY DO WHEN THEY
DRYCLEAN YOUR CLOTHES?
WALK US THROUGH THE PROCESS, HOW
YOU ACTUALLY GET STUFF CLEAN.
WE DROP IT OFF.
WE ARE HERE.
WHAT HAPPENS?
JOHN: BASICALLY, WHAT WE DO IS
WE REMOVE EVERY TYPE OF STAIN.
DRY CLEANING USUALLY TAKES OUT
OILY TYPES OF GREASY STAINS.
DORINDA: THAT IS UNIQUE TO YOU.
JOHN: ANY TYPE OF STAIN,
PERSPIRATION, YOU WANT TO
ERADICATE THEM BEFORE THE
CLEANING PROCESS.
THEN IT IS CLEANED USUALLY IN A
SOLVENT OR OTHER TYPE OF ORGANIC
SOLVENT.
DR. OZ: SO EVEN THOUGH IT IS
CALLED DRY CLEANING, IT GETS
WET?
JOHN: DRY CLEANING IS A SOLVENT
THAT IS NOT WATER.
THEN IT GOES THROUGH A CLEANING
PROCESS WITH A DETERGENT, AND IT
DRIES IN THE SAME CYCLE.
DR. OZ: SO AFTER ALL THAT, IT
LOOKS LIKE THIS WHEN WE GET IT
BACK.
DORINDA: HERE IT IS.
JOHN: IT ALWAYS COMES BACK IN A
PLASTIC.
YOU ARE SUPPOSED TO REMOVE THE
PLASTIC, LET IT AIR EIGHT.
DR. OZ: STAND NEXT TO ME.
THIS IS WHAT THEY LOOK LIKE WHEN
THEY COME BACK.
HERE'S THE CONCERN.
I WANT TO BE CLEAR ABOUT WHETHER
THIS IS REAL.
PEOPLE ARE SAYING THERE ARE
DIRTY NEUROTOXINS WHEN YOU USE
DRY CLEANING.
TO ALL THE DRY CLEANERS USE
THIS?
JOHN: IT WAS A STANDARD IN THE
INDUSTRY.
A LOT OF DRY CLEANERS ARE MOVING
TOWARD A GREEN METHOD, USING A
WATER-BASED METHOD WITH
DETERGENT.
THERE'S ALSO NATURAL FLORA
CARBONS, LIKE A HYDROCARBON,
WHICH ARE SAFER TO USE.
THERE'S OPTIONS.
YOU SHOULD ASK YOUR CLEANER.
DR. OZ: THIS CHEMICAL IS
ASSOCIATED WITH A NEUROTOXIN, SO
YOU GET DIZZINESS, LOSE
COORDINATION, LONG-TERM EXPOSURE
CAN CAUSE COMA, MAYBE EVEN
DEATH.
YOU DON'T SEEM AS CONCERNED
ABOUT IT, BUT WE SHOULD AVOID
IT?
JOHN: IF YOU CAN AVOID IT, I
WOULD RECOMMEND THAT.
DR. OZ: AND NOBODY SHOULD HAVE
THESE BAGS IN THEIR HOME.
WE REACHED OUT TO THE NATIONAL
CLEANERS ASSOCIATION FOR A
COMMENT, BUT THEY DECLINED TO
PROVIDE A RESPONSE.
JOHN, YOU SAY THERE'S ANOTHER
TRICK.
YOU MIGHT BE ABLE TO SHARE WITH
US.
SPECIFICALLY ABOUT WINE, WHICH
SEEMS TO FIND ITS WAY ONTO
DORINDA'S CHEST A FAIR BIT.
DORINDA: AND LIPSTICK.
JOHN: IN TERMS OF REMOVING
STAINS, THERE'S THREE
CATEGORIES.
ONE THAT COMES FROM THE EARTH,
ONE THAT COMES FROM THE BODY,
AND THE THIRD IS OIL MATTER,
COOKING GELS, THINGS LIKE THAT.
FROM THE EARTH, FROM THE BODY,
AND OIL.
SO WE HAVE ONE OF DORINDA'S
BIRTHDAY STAINS.
SO WE ARE GOING TO DO A HOME
REMEDY.
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW EASY
IT IS TO REMOVE A STAIN.
DR. OZ: DO IT RIGHT.
JOHN: IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WHAT WE HAVE HERE, A HOME REMEDY
IS ONE PART DETERGENT, VINEGAR,
TWO PARTS WATER.
IF IT IS SMALL, YOU CAN USE A
Q-TIP.
WHAT I'M GOING TO DO IS GET THIS
IN.
IF THERE'S ANY EXCESS, YOU WANT
TO TEMPE UP.
SEE, IT IS RIGHT THERE.
DORINDA: ABSORBENT CLOTH.
JOHN: YOU ALWAYS WANT TO PUT A
CLOTH UNDERNEATH IT.
THEN YOU WANT TO TAKE THIS.
NOTICE THE STAIN IS DISAPPEARING
RIGHT NOW.
DR. OZ: WHAT IS THE WORD YOU
USED?
DORINDA: TAMP IT.
DR. OZ: I'VE NEVER HEARD THE
WORD BEFORE.
JOHN: YOU CAN SEE IT GO INTO THE
ABSORBENT CLOTH.
DR. OZ: I LIKE THIS.
JOHN: THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
IN STAIN REMOVAL IS TIME.
THE SOONER YOU CAN TREAT A STAIN
PROPERLY, THE SAFER IT IS.
THAT IS WHY I HAVE ONE OF THESE
PROFESSIONAL STAIN REMOVAL KITS
THAT I HAVE GIVEN TO EVERYONE IN
THE AUDIENCE.
[APPLAUSE]
JOHN: ANYONE OUT THERE THAT
WANTS ONE, YOU CAN GO TO
STAINKIT.COM AND USE DR. OZ AS A
PROMO CODE AND EVERYONE GETS 20%
OFF.
COMPLEMENTARY SHIPPING.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
DORINDA: WE DIDN'T NICE.
[APPLAUSE]
JOHN: ONE STAIN AT A TIME.
DR. OZ: WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
HE'S GOOD.
[APPLAUSE]
SOME
ANSWERS.
[APPLAUSE]
>> DID YOU KILL TRAVIS
ALEXANDER?
>> CONVICTED OF KILLING HER
BOYFRIEND.
WHY HER LAWYERS
♪ Before I head
out the door ♪
♪ It's what I'm lookin' for ♪
♪ Today's the Daisy I do ♪
♪ Daisy it's true ♪
♪ Before I get on the move ♪
♪ I grab my special food ♪
♪ Today's the Daisy I see ♪
♪ the difference in me ♪
♪ Today's the Daisy for cottage
cheese (cottage cheese) ♪
♪ Today's the Daisy! ♪
To most, he's
Phil Mickelson...
..pro golfer.
To me, he's...
...well, Dad.
So when his
joint pain from
psoriatic arthritis
got really bad, it scared me.
And what could that pain mean?
Joint pain could
mean joint damage.
ENBREL helps
relieve joint pain...
...helps stop irreversible
joint damage...
and helps skin get clearer.
ENBREL may lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious, sometimes
fatal events...
including infections,
tuberculosis...
lymphoma, other cancers,...
nervous system and
blood disorders...
and allergic
reactions have occurred.
Tell your
doctor if you've
been some place where
fungal infections are common.
Or, if you're
prone to infections,
have cuts or sores,
have had hepatitis B,
have been treated
for heart failure...
or if you have
persistent fever...
bruising, bleeding, or paleness.
Don't start ENBREL...
if you have an
infection like the flu.
Since ENBREL...
Dad's back to being... Dad.
Visit Enbrel.com...
and use the Joint
Damage Simulator
to see how your joint
damage could be progressing.
Ask about ENBREL.
ENBREL.
FDA approved for
over 16 years.
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WE ARE BACK WITH OUR
FILTHY FEBRUARY INVESTIGATION.
WE ARE PUTTING EVERYDAY
HOUSEHOLD ITEMS UNDER A
MICROSCOPE TO FIND THE FIVE
SURPRISING THINGS DIRTIER THAN
YOUR TOILET.
THESE THINGS ARE DIRTIER THAN
NOW IT IS TIME TO REVEAL THE
RESULTS OF OUR FILTHIEST
EXPERIMENT YET.
HERE TO HELP COUNT DOWN IS MY GO
TO TESTER, RHENOTHA, WHO KNOWS
ABOUT THIS STUFF.
WE GOING THROUGH FIVE THINGS.
REVEAL THE NUMBER FIVE ITEM THAT
IS DIRTIER THAN YOUR TOILET.
RHENOTHA: THE NUMBER FIVE THING
IS THE KITCHEN SINK.
DR. OZ: THE KITCHEN SINK?
RHENOTHA: THE KITCHEN SINK IS
NASTY.
DR. OZ: THE BACTERIA EAT THE
FOOD PARTICLES THAT YOU WASH OFF
YOUR DISHES.
RHENOTHA, SHE'S THE GOTO PERSON
ON THIS.
THERE'S AN EASY HACK TO MAKE
SURE YOU'VE GOT A SPARKLING
CLEAN -- MAY I GET YOUR
ASSISTANCE?
THIS IS HOW THEY GLOVE YOU IN
THE OPERATING ROOM.
RHENOTHA: MY NURSING ASSISTANT,
THANK YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: SO, THE SINK IS HERE.
JUST WASHING IT A LITTLE BIT
DOESN'T WORK.
RHENOTHA: YOU HAVE TO GET IN
HERE WITH BAKING SODA.
YES, BAKING SODA.
YOU NEED TO SPRINKLE IT ALL OVER
YOUR SINK.
LET THE DUST FLY.
YOU WANT TO MAKE SURE YOU GET IT
IN AND GET IT CLEAN.
LET THAT SIT FOR ABOUT FIVE
MINUTES.
YOU WANT TO GET A SOFT TOWEL AND
GO IN A CIRCULAR MOTION.
THE REASON YOU WANT TO DO A
CIRCULAR MOTION IS BECAUSE IT
DOESN'T CREATE SCRATCHES OR
ABRASIONS IN YOUR SINK.
DR. OZ: IT IS SHINING YOUR
STAINLESS STEEL.
RHENOTHA: THERE YOU GO.
DR. OZ: NUMBER FOUR ITEM DIRTIER
THAN YOUR TOILET, THE COFFEE
RESERVOIR.
YOU MIGHT REMEMBER WE REVEALED
SHOCKING THINGS ABOUT YOUR
FILTHY COFFEE POT.
IT CAN BE PRETTY DIRTY.
IF YOU ARE WORRIED ABOUT
BACTERIA, TAKE VINEGAR WITH
WATER, PUT HALF OF IT IN THE
WATER RESERVOIR, CLOSE, AND
BREWIS.
30 MINUTES.
RUN THE WATER THROUGH.
DO THIS ONCE A MONTH.
ONCE A MONTH WHEN YOU ARE
WATCHING TV, DONE.
NUMBER THREE, PET BOWLS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT?
[LAUGHTER]
RHENOTHA: DR. OZ, I'M SURE IT IS
A NASTY SITUATION GOING ON
THERE.
DR. OZ: THE SAME THINGS YOU ARE
GOING TO USE FOR OUR NEXT
PROBLEM, YOU ARE GOING TO USE TO
CLEAN THIS.
VERY SIMPLE ITEM.
NUMBER TWO ON OUR LIST IS YOUR
TOOTHBRUSH HOLDER.
RHENOTHA: EWW!
DR. OZ: DYMON IS HERE AND SHE
SWABBED HER HOUSE AND FOUND THAT
HER TOOTHBRUSH HOLDER HAD 10
TIMES MORE GERMS THAN HER TOILET
SEAT.
10 TIMES MORE.
ANY IDEA HOW THAT HAPPENED?
>> NO IDEA AT ALL.
I JUST MOVED INTO THE APARTMENT
A COUPLE MONTHS AGO.
MAYBE IT WAS THERE.
[LAUGHTER]
DR. OZ: I HAVE A MORE PLAUSIBLE
EXCUSE, THAT WE ALL HAVE
TOOTHBRUSH HOLDERS THAT ARE
DIRTY.
WHEN WE FLUSH OUR TOILET, THE
LID AND THE SEAT, THAT
AEROSOLIZATION OF BACTERIA FROM
THE TOILET GOES ALL OVER THE
ROOM.
A SOLUTION YOU ARE GOING TO
REMEMBER THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
IT IS --
RHENOTHA: IT IS THE NATURAL
CLEANING PAD.
YOU NEED THESE.
DR. OZ: EXPLAIN THAT.
RHENOTHA: ALL YOU DO IS PLOT
THEM IN A BOWL OF WATER.
DR. OZ: SEE THE BUBBLES?
RHENOTHA: THE LITTLE
EFFERVESCENCE GOING ON.
PLACE THIS INSIDE HERE.
WHERE ARE MY GLOVES FOR THIS?
DR. OZ: I DON'T KNOW.
[LAUGHTER]
RHENOTHA: AFTER ABOUT 30
MINUTES, IT SHOULD BE CLEAN.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: BUT YOU HAVE TO LOOK FOR
THE INGREDIENTS, HYDROGEN
PEROXIDE AND BAKING SODA.
IT IS SIMPLE AND EASY TO DO.
NOW WE ARE DOWN TO NUMBER ONE,
WHICH ALL OF US HAVE PROBLEMS
WITH.
THE FILTHIEST ITEM IN YOUR HOME
IS THE DISH SPONGE.
RHENOTHA: DISGUSTING.
DR. OZ: WE'RE GOING TO GET UP
CLOSE ON THIS THING.
YOU SEE THE LITTLE KNOCKS AND
CRANNIES?
THAT CAN HARBOR BACTERIA.
AND THE MOISTURE, IT IS PERFECT
FOR BACTERIA.
OPEN YOUR MOUTH.
[LAUGHTER]
DR. OZ: YOUR TONGUE IS, THANK
GOODNESS, CLEANER THAN THAT
SPONGE.
ARE YOU READY FOR WHAT WE FOUND?
>> LET'S JUST DO IT.
DR. OZ: WE FOUND BACTERIA WHICH
IS NOT DANGEROUS, BUT IT IS
FOUND IN ANIMALS, SO SOMEHOW BAD
STUFF GOT IN THERE.
THERE IS A LOT OF STUDIES
SHOWING THAT TO GET IT OFF, WE
HAVE TO PUT IT IN THE MICROWAVE,
BUT IT DOESN'T SEEM TO WORK.
RHENOTHA: BUT YOU KNOW WHAT DOES
WORK, GOOD OLD WHITE VINEGAR.
SUBMERGE YOUR SPONGE IN SOME
WHITE VINEGAR.
I THINK IT IS ABOUT FIVE
MINUTES.
[LAUGHTER]
DR. OZ: DON'T MAKE THE SAME
MISTAKE TWICE.
RHENOTHA: SOAK IT FOR
FIVE-MINUTE AND IT SHOULD BE
GOOD AS NEW.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: THIS IS 99% EFFECTIVE AT
GETTING RID OF BACTERIA.
WE'RE GOING TO PUT THESE ON
DOCTOROZ.COM.
SHARE THEM WITH YOUR FAMILY,
MAYBE EMBARRASS THEM.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: WHAT DO YOU FEEL?
>>
Oats and oat bran
have a soluble fiber
called beta-glucan,
which can help
lower cholesterol
as part of
a heart-healthy diet.
Now it's in new
Quaker Oat Beverage,
a super-smooth
dairy alternative.
Now it's in new
Quaker Oat Beverage,
60% of women wear
the wrong size pad
and can experience leaks.
You don't have to.
With Always My Fit,
try the next size up
and get up to 20% better
coverage day or night.
Because better coverage
means better protection.
Always
I AM TOTALLY BLIND.
AND NON-24 CAN MAKE ME SHOW UP
TOO EARLY... OR TOO LATE.
OR MAKE ME FEEL LIKE
I'M NOT REALLY "THERE."
TALK TO
YOUR DOCTOR,
AND CALL
844-234-2424.
Stouffer's Lasagna With Meat &
Sauce
has two times the beef of the
leading meat sauce lasagna.
That's double the tender ground
beef
baked into every cheesy,
mouthwatering bite.
When it comes to irresistible
taste,
more is always more.
Stouffer's.
Show me The Crown.
Show me Homecoming.
more is always more.
Baby sloth videos on YouTube.
Amy, do you uh mind giving
someone else a turn?
Oh yeah I made myself a
little comfortable here.
I got a pizza for Amy!
Yes, that's me!
Xfinity lets you search
Netflix, Prime Video,
and YouTube
with the sound of your voice.
And I don't have my wallet, so.
That's Simple.
Easy. Awesome.
Get started with Xfinity
Internet, TV and Voice for
$79.99 a month for 2 years,
plus ask about 4K Ultra HD.
Click, call or visit
a store today.
♪
You're not just mom.
You're her whole world.
Don't just get away, come
together.
Save up to 30%. Hurry.
Offer ends soon.
[APPLAUSE]
DR. OZ: TODAY, THE NUMBER ONE
THING YOU CAN DO TO LIFT YOUR
MOOD.
NEW STUDIES SAY THAT ALL YOU
HAVE TO DO IS TAKE THAT WALK
DOWN MEMORY LANE.
NOSTALGIA CAN BE THE MISSING
LINK TO HAVING A POSITIVE
OUTLOOK ON LIFE.
IT CAN ALSO HELP US COUNTER
SADNESS.
AFTER DOING EXPERIMENTS,
RESEARCHERS SAY THERE WAS A LINK
BETWEEN SAVORING SPECIAL MOMENTS
AND ABILITY TO BOOST YOUR
SEROTONIN LEVELS AS YOU SEE AN
IMAGE FROM YOUR PAST THAT MAKES
YOU SMILE.
HERE ARE TWO PHOTOS.
THE FIRST IS A PICTURE THAT WAS
TAKEN AT MY WIFE'S BIRTHDAY
PARTY.
MOMS DON'T GET CELEBRATED
ENOUGH.
TO BE ABLE TO GET HER AND TALK
ABOUT HER, ESPECIALLY WITH THE
PEOPLE SHE LOVES, WAS FABULOUS.
THAT IS A GREAT EXAMPLE.
THE SECOND PICTURE, I ALWAYS
LAUGH ABOUT.
MY DAUGHTERS HUDDLING.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MANY OF YOU
CALL FOOTBALL PLAYS.
IT DOESN'T TAKE THAT LONG AND NO
ONE SMILES.
THEY ACTUALLY SAY IT HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH FOOTBALL, BUT THEY
CLAIM THEY WERE CALLING A PLAY.
BUT I LEARNED A LOT ABOUT MY
DAUGHTERS BY PLAYING SPORTS WITH
THEM, SO THAT PHOTO IS IN MY
OFFICE.
ANGELIQUE HAS A PHOTO TO SHARE
WITH US.
IS THIS YOUR DAUGHTER?
ANGELIQUE: IT IS A PHOTO OF HER
IN THE CAR.
DR. OZ: MY GOODNESS.
SO CUTE.
WHAT IS THE MEMORY IT BRINGS
BACK?
ANGELIQUE: SHE HAD REALLY FULL,
CURLY HAIR.
WE ALWAYS HAD TO KEEP AN EYE ON
HER.
NEVER HAD FEAR FOR ANYTHING.
DR. OZ: SHE STILL HAS CURLY
HAIR.
STILL FEARLESS?
ANGELIQUE: SHE'S MY CRAZY ONE.
DR. OZ: STILL CRAZY?
>> A LITTLE.
DR. OZ: IN A GOOD WAY.
I WILL TAKE THAT.
TAKE A MOMENT TODAY AND LOOK AT
SOME OLD PHOTOS AND SHARE THEM
WITH PEOPLE YOU CARE ABOUT.
TOGETHER, CHANGE IS HAPPENING.
OUR JOURNEY IS JUST BEGINNING.
[APPLAUSE]
[CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY THE
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE,
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTION CONTENT AND ACCURACY.
VISIT NCICAP.ORG]
♪
Oats have a soluble fiber
called beta-glucan,
which can help lower cholesterol
when part of a
heart-healthy diet.
What's more, these oats
have no artificial flavors,
preservatives or added colors.
Now that's something
to celebrate.
♪♪
When cravings hit, hit back.
Choose Glucerna, with
slow release carbs
to help manage blood sugar, and
start making everyday progress.
Glucerna.
>>> COMING UP RIGHT NOW ON "PAGE
SIX TV" LIVE -- HAPPY
VALENTINE'S DAY.
AND PRAISE THE LORD.
CARDI B'S RETIREMENT IS OVER.
AFTER TWO DAYS OFF THE GRAM, THE
SUPERSTAR IS BACK WITH A
BOMBSHELL ANNOUNCEMENT.
AND SINGER RYAN