All fit, in the palm of your
hand.
#1 stain and odor fighter, #1
trusted.
It's got to be Tide.
>> Announcer: LIVE FROM
NEW YORK CITY, IT'S
"THE WENDY WILLIAMS SHOW."
♪ ♪
NOW, HERE'S KEKE PALMER!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Keke: HEY!
HI, EVERYONE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING
HERE!
I'M SO HAPPY THAT YOU GUYS ARE
HERE, I'M SO HAPPY!
SAY HELLO TO MY COHOSTS, MY
STUDIO AUDIENCE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HOW Y'ALL DOING?
>> Audience: HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> Keke: AND WE WANT TO SEND
LOVE TO WENDY.
I'M SO SAD THAT YOU'RE NOT HERE,
BUT I'LL BE GETTING BETTER.
I THINK YOU FOR LETTING ME TAKE
OVER YOUR SHOW TODAY!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
LET'S GET STARTED.
IT'S TIME FOR SOME "HOT TOPICS"!
A [CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
OKAY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
ALL RIGHT, SO, JUSTIN BIEBER AND
HAILEY BALDWIN ON THE COVER OF
"VOGUE" MAGAZINE.
THEY REALLY DO LOOK BEAUTIFUL,
THEY DO!
I LOVE YOUNG MARRIAGE!
I'M OFF HER YOUNG MARRIAGE.
THEY GET THE BABIES OUT, I'M
HERE FOR IT ALL.
BUT IT WAS REALLY GREAT ARTICLE.
IT TALKED ABOUT GETTING MARRIED,
THE PROCESS.
JUSTIN TALKS ABOUT WHY HE
STEPPED AWAY FROM MUSIC, WHICH I
REALLY CAN RELATE TO.
WE BOTH GREW UP IN THE INDUSTRY.
I REMEMBER WHEN HE WAS ON, AFTER
HE GOT SIGNED.
[APPLAUSE]
HE TALKED ABOUT HOW IT SO HARD.
GROWING UP IN THE ENTERTAINMENT
INDUSTRY IS DIFFICULT BECAUSE
YOUR ONLY FOCUS HAS BEEN YOUR
CAREER, TO THE POINT THAT YOU
DON'T THINK ABOUT ALL THE OTHER
THINGS ABOUT LIFE.
RELATING TO PEOPLE, WHO YOU WANT
TO BECOME A WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IN YOUR DOWN TIME.
YOU NEVER GET THE TIME TO REALLY
DEVELOP IT.
SO I WAS GLAD THAT HE SAID,
"LOOK, I KNEW I NEEDED TO TAKE
THIS TIME.
THAT'S WHAT I WANTED TO DO."
AND I'M REALLY HAPPY FOR HIM.
[APPLAUSE]
HE ALSO TALKS ABOUT HOW SEX
BECAME AN ADDICTION FOR HIM.
I CAN ALSO RELATE TO THAT.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
I'M JUST KIDDING!
[LAUGHTER]
HE ALSO TALKED ABOUT THAT.
HE SAID, "LOOK, I REALIZE THIS
IS A PROBLEM FOR ME.
I WANT TO STOP IT."
AND HE FEELS HIS REWARD WAS HIS
BEAUTIFUL MARRIAGE.
I'M GLAD HE IS SELF-AWARE.
GOOD FOR THEM.
I'M GLAD FOR THEM.
[APPLAUSE]
HALEY ALSO TALKED ABOUT HOW THE
SOCIAL MEDIA TOOLS KEPT WANTING
TO SEE THEM FAIL.
Y'ALL, I JUST NEED TO KNOW --
WHY DON'T THESE TROLLS EVER TAKE
A DAY OFF?
[LAUGHTER]
THEY NEVER TAKE A DAY OFF!
MY QUESTION IS, WHY DON'T WE
MAKE IT TO WHERE PEOPLE GET ON
SOCIAL MEDIA AND THEY HAVE TO
CONNECT TO THEIR SOCIAL SECURITY
NUMBER?
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
THAT WAY THERE ARE CONSEQUENCES!
THE MORNING, TO POST, IT'S GOING
TOWARD YOUR CREDIT SCORE!
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
OKAY?
EVEN THOUGH IT'S ALREADY AT 500,
[LAUGHTER]
THIS IS WHAT I LOVE -- THE WAY
THAT YOUNG PEOPLE ARE PARTYING.
WHEN HE WAS IN LIGHT OF THIS
PAST WEEKEND, HE WENT TO THE
CLUB AND SAID THAT NOBODY WAS
DANCING AND EVERYONE STOOD
AROUND LOOKING AT THEIR PHONES.
AS A YOUNG PERSON THAT HE'S
TALKING ABOUT, I CAN AGREE THAT
THE EXEC WHO WOULD HAPPEN.
I'M SICK OF IT!
WHEN I WAS GROWING UP, BEING AT
THIS ADULT AGE, I EXPECTED IT TO
BE LIKE "SAVE THE LAST DANCE."
[LAUGHTER]
I EXPECTED BEING CLUB GOING BACK
AND FORTH.
[APPLAUSE]
THAT'S NOT THE ENERGY.
MY THING IS, IF THAT'S A DATED
CONCEPT, WE NEED TO GO BACK TO
THAT ERA.
I WANT TO HAVE FUN IN THE CLUB
AND DANCE WITH SOMEBODY!
YOU KNOW?
[APPLAUSE]
DIDDY ANNOUNCE THAT HE'S GOING
TO BRING DANCING BACK.
HE SAID HE'S GOING TO HAVE THE
DIDDY DANCING PARTIES.
I'M READY FOR THEM.
I'VE BEEN TO A DIDDY PARTY,
YELL!
YOU AIN'T BEEN TO A PARTY IF YOU
AIN'T BEEN TO A P DOT DIDDY
PARTY!
I'M TELLING YOU
NEXT WE HAVE ARIANA GRANDE.
LOOK AT -- YOU GUYS, SHE WAS
ASKED THE OTHER DAY HOW SHE FELT
ABOUT HER EX DATING KATE
BECKINSALE.
SHE REPLIED, "THEY ARE SO CUTE!"
AND THOUGH THEY ARE THINKING SHE
THROUGH SHADE.
IT'S A LOSE-LOSE SITUATION.
FIRST OF ALL, THEY WERE BEING
SHADY ASKING HER THAT.
WHAT HAS SHE GOT TO SAY ABOUT
THIS MAN LIVING ON THE LIVING
HIS LIFE QUESTION WHICH IS
LIVING HER LIFE, AS WELL.
IF SHE WOULDN'T HAVE SAID
ANYTHING, THEY WOULD HAVE SAID
SHE WAS BEING BETTER.
MAYBE SHE REALLY THINKS THEY'RE
CUTE AND LET'S MOVE ON.
LEAVE THESE PEOPLE ALONE.
OKAY.
NOW, MICHAEL B. JORDAN -- HE
SAYS HE WENT TO THERAPY AFTER
PLAYING THE RUTHLESS VILLAIN AND
BLACK PANTHER.
HE SAYS THAT HE SPENT SO MUCH
I'M ISOLATING HIMSELF FOR THAT
ROLE THAT IT WAS HARD TO GET OUT
OF THE VILLAIN MIND-SET WHEN THE
CAMERAS WERE OFF.
I CAN RELATE TO THIS, BECAUSE I
PLAY THE CHARACTER THIS LAST
YEAR -- I GUESS IT WAS A COUPLE
OF YEARS AGO.
[APPLAUSE]
I PLAYED THE CHARACTER, HER NAME
IS WEDNESDAY.
IT WAS A MOVIE TITLED "PIMP,"
AND IT WAS A VERY INTENSE ROLE.
I NEEDED TO TAKE A BREAK OR DO
SOME WORK HOW MANY TYPE OF
STUFF, BECAUSE THAT WASN'T ME,
LOVE!
[LAUGHTER]
I REMEMBER HEARING AS A KID,
DENZIL L OR SEAN PENN, ANY OF
THESE PEOPLE WOULD SAY
, "I NEED TO TAKE A BREAK AFTER
PULLING THIS DEEP, DRAMATIC
GROWTH."
AND I WOULD NEVER UNDERSTAND IT.
BUT WHEN YOU GO INTO THESE TYPES
OF CHARACTERS THAT ARE SO
DRASTICALLY DIFFERENT FROM YOU,
IT'S VERY MUCH NEEDED.
SO I'M GLAD THAT
MICHAEL B. JORDAN SEEKING CARE
OF HIMSELF.
[APPLAUSE]
YOUR EMOTIONS DO NOT KNOW THAT
YOU ARE KIDDING.
OKAY?
OKAY.
SO, KATY PERRY'S STYLIST IS IN
HOT WATER.
ACCORDING TO "THE BLAST," BACK
IN 2017      2017 SHE ALLEGEDLYD
18 PIECES OF JEWELRY FOR THE
GRAMMY AWARDS BUT ALLEGEDLY ONLY
RETURNED 14 PIECES.
THE JEWELER IS NOW SUING HER
STYLIST FOR $120,000.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
CHILD, YOU BETTER BE CAREFUL
WITH THESE STYLISTS.
[APPLAUSE]
OKAY?
I'VE BEEN DEALING WITH THESE
STYLISTS FOR YEARS.
SOMETIMES YOU GIVE IT BACK TO
THEM AND THEY KEEP IT.
SO YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
TO THAT JEWELRY!
AS A KID, WHEN THEY WOULD GIVE
ME $15,000, $100,000 JEWELRY, I
SAID, "KEEP IT, BELOVED.
I'M GOOD."
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO BE
RESPONSIBLE FOR SOMETHING I'M
NOT GOING TO PAY FOR.
IF I'M NOT GOING TO BUY IT, IF
IT'S GETTING LOST, I DON'T WANT
HAVE TO DO WITH THE
RESPONSIBILITY.
I HOPE THAT ALL GETS WORKED OUT,
BECAUSE THAT'S A HIGHER BILL.
[APPLAUSE]
GIVE ME SOMETHING FROM THE
BEAUTY SUPPLY.
OKAY?
SO, PAM ANDERSON'S SON, BRANDON
LEE, DROPPED OUT OF COLLEGE
AFTER ONLY TWO WEEKS AND HIS MOM
WAS PISSED.
HE SAID WHEN HE SHOWED UP WITH
HIS BAG, SHE TOLD HIM TO "GET
THE [BLEEP] OUT OF HERE."
SOME PEOPLE WILL SAY THAT I'M IN
THE EXTREME MILLENNIAL FOR
SAYING THIS, BUT COLLEGES AND
FOR EVERYBODY.
I STRONGLY AGREE WITH THAT.
[APPLAUSE]
I REALLY BELIEVE THAT.
HERE'S THE THING.
THE FIRST OF ALL, THE COLLEGE
DEBT ISSUE.
IT'S REALLY AN ISSUE!
IT REALLY IS!
PEOPLE GO TO SCHOOL TO GET
DEGREES, AND THEY COME OUT OF
SCHOOL AND THEY CAN'T DO
ANYTHING WITH THEM TO EVEN PAY.
HOW CRAZY IS THAT?
[APPLAUSE]
YOU GO TO SCHOOL TO GET A
DEGREE, TO GET A JOB, TO PAY FOR
YOUR DEBT, BUT YOU CAN'T GET ONE
SO YOU ARE JUST INTO THAT.
THAT'S THE NUMBER ONE ISSUE.
THE NUMBER TWO ISSUE IS THAT NOT
EVERY PASSION YOU HAVE CAN BE
VALIDATED BY A DEGREE OR A
CERTIFICATE.
[APPLAUSE]
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
IF YOU WANT TO BE A
CHOREOGRAPHER, SPEND YOUR HOME
HUSTLING IN THE DESERT
COMMUNITY.
IF YOU WANT TO BE A PAINTER,
FIGURE OUT HOW TO PUT TIME INTO
THAT.
I FEEL LIKE SCHOOL APPLIES MOST
PEOPLE WHO WANT TO BE A DOCTOR
OR PSYCHOLOGIST, THINGS OF THAT
SORT.
I'M SAD HIS MAMA CUSSED HIM OUT,
BUT...
[LAUGHTER]
MAY BE NEEDED TIME TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT HIS PASSION WAS.
[APPLAUSE]
BUT, GET INTO THIS.
HE ENDED UP WORKING AT A
SMOOTHIE PLACE, LIVING ON HIS
FRIEND'S COUCH, WHEN HE STARTED
DOING MODELING JOBS.
SO, LOOK AT THAT!
[APPLAUSE]
GO AHEAD, BRANDON!
WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
GUYS.
UP NEXT WE ARE BREAKING DOWN
WHAT TO EXPECT AT THIS YEAR'S
GRAMMY AWARDS.
SO, GRAB A SNACK AND COME ON
BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Keke: THE GRAMMY'S ARE THE
BIGGEST NIGHT OF MUSIC.
HERE TO BREAK IT ALL DOWN, IT'S
POP-CULTURE EXPERT CHRIS
WEATHERSPOON!
HAD LOW!
>> Chris: IT'S AMAZING!
YOUR OUTFIT IS OVER!
EVERY TIME, IT'S A KEKE, YELL!
>> Keke: ALICIA KEYS IS THE
FIRST WOMAN TO HOST AND FORTUNE
YEARS?
SPEAK IS THE FIRST
TIME WE ARE HAVING A WOMAN HOST
AND FORTUNE NEWS.
THE LAST TIME WAS QUEEN LATIFAH
IN 2005.
SHE'S THE PERFECT PERSON BECAUSE
SHE AND BY SO FEMALE EMPOWERMEN
EMPOWERMENT.
ALICIA KEYS IS REALLY TRYING TO
SHOW FOLKS A DIFFERENT SIDE.
SHE HAS THIS YOUTUBE CHANNEL
WHERE SHE'S TAKING YOU TAKING
YOU BEHIND THE SCENES FROM WHEN
SHE FIRST FOUND OUT SHE WAS
HOSTING.
TELL HER HUSBAND WHILE HE'S
LAYING IN BED, TELLING HER KIDS
ALSO.
SHE REALLY WANTS US TO SEE THAT
SHE CAN BE A LITTLE BIT MORE
AMPED UP.
>> Keke: MISS ALICIA!
NOT THAT SHE'S GONE, BUT I'M
GLAD SHE'S BEING MORE INTO THE
FAMILY VIBE.
SO I'M VERY GLAD I'M GOING TO
GET TO SEE HER OUT.
>> Chris: AND I'M GLAD THEY
ARE CHOOSING HER.
ONE, SHE'S AN R&B LIVES THAT
DON'T NEGLIGENT.
SHE HAS WON 15 GRAMMY AWARDS.
SHE KNOWS WHAT IT'S LIKE TO BE
ON THAT SPEECH.
YOU HAVE SO MANY NEWCOMERS.
>> Keke: I HAVE TO ASK YOUR
OPINION ABOUT THE SPIRIT HOW DO
YOU FEEL ABOUT J.LO DOING --
>> Chris: THIS ONE IS VERY
CONTROVERSIAL.
PROBABLY THE MOST CONTROVERSIAL
TOPIC HEADING INTO THE
GRAMMY AWARDS.
JENNIFER LOPEZ PERFORMING A
MOTOWN TRIBUTE.
THERE WILL BE A LOT OF TRIBUTES
THROUGHOUT THE YEAR.
BUT THE BIG ONE ON SUNDAY NIGHT,
IT'S BEEN ANNOUNCED THAT J.LO
WILL BE PERFORMING IT.
NO WORD IF YOU WILL BE JOINED
WITH ANYONE.
BUT IT'S INTERESTING BECAUSE YOU
HAVE THESE ICONS LIKE GLADYS
KNIGHT AND LIONEL RICHIE AND
SMOKEY ROBINSON, THEY WERE
SIGNED TO MOTOWN.
THEY COULD DO THE TRIBUTE.
>> Chris: NO SHADE TOWARD
J.LO, BECAUSE I'M A HUGE FAN.
I LOVE HER.
BUT I DON'T THINK SHE WOULD HAVE
BEEN MY FIRST CHOICE AND
THINKING OF MOTOWN.
WHAT ABOUT JAZMINE SULLIVAN?
>> Chris: "FANTASIA," THE LIST
GOES ON.
I GET THEY WANT SOME ANYMORE
CURRENT AND YOUNGER, BUT YOU
HAVE BOYS TO MEN WHO WERE ALSO
SIGNED TO MOTOWN.
I'M A LITTLE BIT SURPRISED.
I'M HOPING SHE CALLS EVERYONE
SHE KNOWS.
"GIRL, WILL YOU HAVE      COME E
WITH ME?"
BECAUSE YOU NEED SOMEBODY BLACK
WITH HER.
IF SHE NEEDS ME, I'LL BE OUT
THERE!
I WILL DO A DOO-WOP IN THE
BACKGROUND, I AIN'T SCARED!
I WILL DO IT!
>> Keke: ARIANA GRANDE, SHE
CANCELED HER PERFORMANCE.
I'M VERY SURPRISED BY THAT.
>> Chris: I HOPE WE HAVE A TEA
KETTLE, BECAUSE I'M GOING TO
GIVE YOU BUNCH OF TEA RIGHT NOW.
HERE WE GO.
ARIANA GRANDE ON THE GROUND TO
COVER ALBUM CAME OUT TODAY.
SHE HAS THE NUMBER ONCE IN THE
COUNTRY RIGHT NOW WITH "SEVEN
RINGS."
IT'S MY JAM.
SO SHE WAS SCHEDULED TO PERFORM
AT THE GRAMMYS, BUT DECIDED TO
PULL OUT DUE TO ARTISTIC
DIFFERENCES.
SHE WANTED HER FROM THE WHOLE
ENTIRE SONG, "SEVEN RINGS."
BUT THEY SAID NO AND THEY
ALLOWED HER TO DO SEVEN RINGS
BUT ONLY IF SHE DID A MEDLEY OF
THEIR CHOOSING AFTERWARDS.
AND SHE SAID "THANK U, NEXT."
LORDE WAS NOMINATED FOR ALBUM OF
THE YEAR, BUT INSTEAD OF DOING A
SON OF A PROBLEM THEY WANTED HER
TO PERFORM A TRIBUTE TO TOM
PETTY.
SHE SAID, "I'M GOING TO BE PETTY
AND NOT DO ANYTHING."
AND SHE DIDN'T PERFORM.
BUT I'M CURIOUS.
NUMBER ONE, BECAUSE YOU KNOW
ARIANNA.
IS IT EASY TO WORK WITH CUSTOMER
QUIT SHE SHE LIKE TO WORK WITH?
>> Keke: I LOVE HER, WE DID
"SCREAM QUEENS" TOGETHER.
ME AND HER GO WAY BACK.
AS AN ARTIST, IT ALL GOES BACK
TO WHAT YOU PUT IN YOUR BRAIN.
EVERY PRECIOUS WITH THAT.
ONCE IT'S THERE, IT'S THERE.
THEY WERE ASKING HER TO DO
SOMETHING SHE STRONGLY DIDN'T
AGREE WITH.
I FEEL LIKE, "GIRL, YOU BETTER
GO AHEAD."
IT'S GOOD BECAUSE YOU ACTUALLY
SAID, "THIS IS THE GRAMMYS BUT
THEY DON'T WANT ME TO SHOWN IN
THE WAY I WANT TO BE SHOWN."
AND TO SAY NO TAKES A LOT OF
STRENGTH.
MOST PEOPLE WILL SAY, "IT'S THE
GRAMMYS, THEY DO WHAT I GOT TO
DO."
IMAGINE GETTING A HUGE PLATFORM
LIKE THAT IN DOING SOMETHING
THAT YOU WEREN'T HAPPY WITH.
THAT'S WORSE.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Chris: I AGREE.
AS LONG AS SHE WAS DOING HER OWN
SONGS -- AGAIN, HER ALBUM IS OUT
TODAY AND PROBABLY WILL BE
NUMBER ONE THIS WEEKEND.
I WOULD HAVE GONE OUT THERE AND
DID "THANK U, NEXT."
>> Keke: THAT'S THE GAG!
[APPLAUSE]
WHO ARE YOU EXCITED TO SEE
PERFORM?
>> Chris: CARDI B, CARDI B,
CARDI B, YELL.
[APPLAUSE]
I LIKE TO SAY, "IN CARDI WE
TRUST."
THINK BACK TO LAST YEAR, SHE HAD
A LITTLE MOMENT WITH BRUNO MARS.
BUT NOW SHE IS NOMINATED FOR
FIVE GRAMMY AWARDS AND SHE MIGHT
MAKE HISTORY, THE ALL.
SHE COULD BE THE FIRST WOMAN TO
WIN THE BEST RAP ALBUM EVER IN
THE HISTORY OF THE GRAMMYS.
IF SHE WINS OUT A WORD, I MIGHT
CRY.
>> Keke: I SHOCKED.
I THOUGHT MAYBE LIL KIM HAD ONE.
I GUESS NOT.
>> Chris: SHE WOULD BE THE
FIRST WANT TO WIN IT.
SHE HAS WORKED SO HARD THIS
YEAR, SHE DID THE PEPSI THING
FOR HALFTIME.
ALONG WITH YOUR GIRL, DOLLY
PARTON, YOUR FORMER COSTAR WHO
I'M IN LOVE WITH.
PLEASE TEXT OR AFTER THIS AND
SAY I'M YOUR BIGGEST FAN.
SHE HAS BEEN NAMED THE MUSIC
CARES PERSON OF THE YEAR.
SHE WILL BE JOINED ON STAGE BY
KATY PERRY, CASEY MUSGRAVE.
ALSO LITTLE BIG TOWN.
>> Keke: MILEY ISN'T
PERFORMING WITH HER?
>> Chris: NO, SHE HAS A SOLO
PERFORMANCE.
>> Keke: THAT'S HER GODMOTHER!
>> Chris: YOU BETTER COME UP
WITH THE FAMILY TO!
AND I'M EXCITED FOR DIANA ROSS
[APPLAUSE]
SHE'S GOING TO BE PERFORMING.
SHE TURNED 75 ON MARCH 26.
>> Keke: 75?
WAIT A MINUTE.
75 AND LOOKING LIKE THAT?
[APPLAUSE]
>> Chris: WE NEED A POINTER TO
GO OVER THE WORK THAT SHE HAS
NOT HAD DONE!
BECAUSE I DON'T SEE ANY WORK
DONE!
THAT'S A NATURAL, FIERCE 75.
BUT SHE IS CELEBRATING HER
BIRTHDAY ON THE GRAMMY AWARDS,
DURING A MEDLEY OF ALL HER SONGS
FROM MOTOWN.
WHICH WILL BE AMAZING.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Keke: THEY HAVE TO BE
JOINING HER TOGETHER SOME WAY
WITH THE MOTOWN.
>> Chris: I'M PROUD OF THE
GRAMMYS.
OFTEN TIMES THEY OVERLOOK THE
LEGENDS AND FOCUSED TOO MUCH ON
THE YOUNGER SINGERS.
BUT I THINK ABOUT PEOPLE LIKE
HER AND TINA TURNER, AND THE
ONES THAT REALLY PAVED THE WAY
FOR THESE YOUNGER ARTISTS.
I'M PROUD OF Y'ALL FOR GIVING
THEM A "NO" MOSH
!
>> Keke: I'M HAPPY WE WILL GET
MORE HIP-HOP RECOGNITION AT THE
WORDS.
IT REMINDS ME OF HOW
ROCK 'N' ROLL WAS BACK IN THE
DAY.
WHAT I'M SAYING?
ROCK 'N' ROLL WAS UNDERGROUND.
PEOPLE DIDN'T REALLY WANT TO BE
BOTHERED WITH IT.
THEN IT BECAME THE BIGGEST THING
EVER.
THAT REALLY IS WHAT HAPPENED
WITH HIP-HOP.
IT WAS UNDERGROUND.
[APPLAUSE]
AND NOW IT'S THE BIGGEST GENRE
OF MUSIC OUT RIGHT NOW.
IT INFLUENCES EVERY KIND MUSIC.
THEY SHOULD BE GETTING THEIR
SHOT AT THE GRAMMYS.
>> Chris: YOUR PREACHING!
KENDRICK LAMAR IS NOMINATED FOR
EIGHT AWARDS.
HE'S LEADING THE PACK ACROSS ALL
GENRES.
"BLACK PANTHER," THE MOVIE, THE
SOUNDTRACK.
IT'S A GIFT THAT KEEPS ON
GIVING.
ALSO, TRICK IS NOMINATED FOR
ALBUM OF THE YEAR, A RECORD OF
THE YEAR.
I HAVE ONE QUESTION.
KIKI, DO YOU LOVE ME?
ALSO, CHILDISH GAMBINO NOMINATED
FOR FIVE AWARDS.
YOU FEEL THIS SHIFT IS DUE TO
ARTISTS LIKE JAY-Z AND KANYE WHO
SPOKE OUT AGAINST THE GRAMMYS IN
THE PAST?
>> Keke: ISAAC IT'S HARD FOR
THEM TO DID DIE WITH THE
CULTURE'S DOING.
YOU CAN'T DENY WHAT IS SO
OBVIOUS.
WHAT WAS THAT LEONARDO
DiCAPRIO WOULD BECOME "THE
GREAT GATSBY?"
WHERE JAY-Z WAS IN THE
SOUNDTRACK?
YOU HAVE THINGS LIKE THAT
HAPPENING ANY RELAYS INFLUENCES
GLOBAL.
SO YOU HAVE TO APPRECIATE THE
PEOPLE WHO CREATED IT.
>> Chris: CAN WE DO HIP-HOP
ALBUM COST MIKE I WILL POP OFF.
I'LL DO IT.
>> Keke: LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
SNUBS.
>> Chris: THE QUEEN BEE AND
JAY-Z, THEY'VE BEEN STUMPED IN A
BIG WAY.
THEY PUT OUT THEIR ALBUM,
"EVERYTHING IS LOVE," BUT
APPARENTLY EVERYTHING IS NOT
LOVE AS GRAMMYS.
THEY WERE NOT NOMINATED FOR THE
BIG THREE CATEGORIES.
>> Keke: CAN I SAY SOMETHING
CRAZY?
PEOPLE WILL BE LIKE, "WHOA."
FIRST     FIRST WELCOME AWARDS T
EVERYTHING.
YOU ALWAYS NEED AN ACCOLADE.
YOU DO WHAT YOU DO BECAUSE YOU
LOVE IT.
BUT IF YOU FEEL THAT YOU GO TO
AN AWARD SHOW EACH AND EVERY
YEAR TO BE SNUBBED OR WHATEVER
YOU MAY FEEL, DON'T GO.
DON'T GO!
[APPLAUSE]
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
IF YOU FEEL THAT WAY, YOU FEEL
LIKE YOU ARE NOT BEING
RESPECTED -- WE HAVE SEEN IT
TIME AND TIME AGAIN.
WITH THE OSCARS, WITH THE
GRAMMYS.
SPECIFICALLY, PEOPLE OF COLOR
ARE ALWAYS FEELING AS THOUGH,
"HEY, I'M NOT GETTING THE
RESPECT OF RECOGNITION I DESERVE
WHEN I HAVE THE FANS IN THE
AUDIENCE.
IT'S ALL HERE, IT'S ALL RIGHT
THERE."
THEN DON'T GO.
GO TO WHERE YOU ARE SUPPORTED.
[APPLAUSE]
GO TO THE NAACP AWARDS.
GO TO THE BET AWARDS.
>> Chris: YOU ARE SO RIGHT.
I THINK JAY-Z PROBABLY HAD AN
AHA MOMENT.
HE WAS NOMINATED FOR EIGHT
AWARDS AND DIDN'T GET ONE OF
THEM.
AND BEYONCE, A COUPLE YEARS
BACK, "LIMITED" CHANGE MY LIFE
AND IT DIDN'T GET ALBUM OF THE
YEAR.
ADELE SAID "THIS IS THE REWARD."
BUT SHE WAS OVERLOOKED IN THE
BIG WAY.
GIVE THE PERSON WHO GOT THE
SNUBBED IS NICKI MINAJ.
WE LOVE HER ALBUM, HE WENT
PLATINUM, BUT SHE HAS BEEN KNOWN
THIS YEAR FOR HER BELIEFS
INSTEAD OF HER BEATS.
I THINK SHE'S AN ICON.
SHE TRAIL BLAZED.
I THINK SHE WILL BE BACK IN
FUTURE YEARS.
>> Keke: I LOVE NICKI.
[APPLAUSE]
THAT KILLS ME.
THERE IS SO MUCH MORE THAT ME
AND YOU COULD GO BACK AND FORTH
ABOUT.
>> Chris: WE COULD KIKI ON AND
ON, Y'ALL!
>> Keke: I THINK YOU SO MUCH
FOR BEING HERE.
[APPLAUSE]
YOU CAN WATCH THE GRAMMY AWARDS
THE SUNDAY NIGHT AT 8:00 ON CBS.
UP NEXT, THE HOTTEST CELEBRITY
MAKEUP TRENDS.
STAY TUNED!
A [CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
There's the same old way
to smooth, and there's
new Fructis Sleek Shot,
our first in-shower styler.
Just mix the shot
with shampoo,
power up with lather.
Five times
smoother hair,
half the time.
Skip the flat iron.
New Fructis
Sleek Shot.
By Garnier,
naturally!
New Fructis
Sleek Shot.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Keke: HERE TO SHOW US THE
HOTTEST LIBERTY MAKEUP TRENDS
THE SEASON, OUR FRIEND, NATALIE.
I CHANGE FOR YOU!
>> Natalie: YES!
YOU ARE SERVING A LITTLE COLOR
BLOCK ACTION!
>> Keke: CALVIN KLEIN, YOU
KNOW!
>> Natalie: SHE KNOWS IT!
A BEAUTIFUL WARDROBE, WITH THE
TICKET TO THE MAKEUP.
>> Keke: OF COURSE WE DO.
WITH THESE KINDS OF CELEBRITY
TRENDS, THEY ARE EASY TO DO.
LET'S TALK ABOUT CARDI B.
SHALL BE CUSTOMER WHO DOESN'T
LOVE A LITTLE CARDI B COST TO
MARKET SHE LOVES A LITTLE POP OF
COLOR.
>> Keke: SHE LIKES TAKING
CHANCES FOR MAKEUP, YEAH.
>> Natalie: MAY BE SOME OF US
WANT TO DO A LITTLE POP OF
COLOR, A SMOKY EYE.
IT'S A LOT.
IT'S A BIG COMMITMENT.
NOT EVERYBODY CAN COME IN A
FULL-COLOR BLOG OUTFIT.
RIGHT?
BUT IF YOU WANT TO DO A LITTLE
POP, LET'S START WITH A LITTLE
EYELINER.
JUST LIKE CARDI DID.
HE WILL TAKE A GREAT GREEN, LIKE
KILLMONGER DID, AND YOU WILL
JUST TAKE IT AND DO IT ON THE
BOTTOM.
THAT WAY IT DOESN'T TURN INTO
THIS
ENORMOUS SMOKY EYE.
HAVE YOU DONE ONE?
>> Keke: I LIKED IT.
IT DEPENDS WHAT IS, IF YOU DON'T
TOO MUCH.
TO THINK THAT UNDERLINED BLACK
IS NECESSARY?
OR IS IT ON ITS OWN?
>> Natalie: IS ALL ABOUT WHAT
YOU ARE FEELING.
IT'S A GREAT LITTLE VIBE.
IF YOU CAN CARRY IT, GO FOR IT!
A LITTLE POP OF COLOR.
[APPLAUSE]
TAKE A LITTLE BIT OF MAY BE A
GREEN EYE SHADOW.
GIVE IT A LITTLE EXTRA, AND YOU
ARE SERVING IT UP.
IT LOOKS SO PRETTY ON YOU!
>> THANK YOU.
>> Natalie: ANOTHER QUICK TIP
I WANTED TO TELL YOU.
IF YOU WANT TO DO A LITTLE BIT
OF THE PINK ON THE I LIKE CARDI
DID, YOU DON'T HAVE TO BREAK THE
BANK.
JUST USE SOME BLUSH.
I'M SAVING YOUR PENNIES, TOO!
ALL RIGHT?
THAT'S HOW WE DO.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE VAMP BEAT
WHIP.
LADY GAGA.
OH, YES.
SHE CAN DO NO WRONG RIGHT NOW!
THAT LIP IS SO POPULAR.
>> Keke: OUT AND ABOUT YOU
GUYS BUT SOMETIMES I'M SCARED TO
GO TO DARKER MY LIPS.
>> Natalie: MISS WENDY DOESN'T
LOVE A DARK LIP, BUT SHE'S NOT
HERE RIGHT NOW!
I LOVE YOU, WENDY!
IF YOU WANT TO MAKE IT A LITTLE
MORE MODERN -- WE HAVE DONE THIS
GREAT, DEEP LIP ON CHANEL.
HERE'S A TRICK.
WANT TO MAKE IT AN OMBRE EFFECT.
YOU DON'T DO THE LIP LINER LIKE
WE DID IN THE 90s, Y'ALL.
WE ARE RELIANT THE WHOLE LIP
WITH BLACK.
I DID ALL THE TIME IN SCHOOL.
>> Keke: AND JUST A BUNCH OF
LIP GLOSS.
WE ALL REMEMBER.
>> Natalie: I'M SURE HE LOOKED
GREAT ON YOU, BUT NOT EVERYBODY
ELSE IN THE WORLD.
WHAT WE WILL DO IS TAKE IT AND
JUST DO IT ON THE OUTER CORNERS
OF THE MOUTH.
WHAT THAT'S GOING TO DO IS NOT
ONLY GIVE YOU THAT GREAT OMBRE
EFFECT, Y'ALL, BUT IT'S ALSO
GOING TO -- HOW DO YOU SAY IT,
MAKE YOUR LIPS LOOK FULLER?
SHE DOESN'T NEED HER LIPS TO
LOOK FULLER, BUT FOR THE REST OF
THE WORLD OUT THERE WHO DO WANT
THAT POUTY LIP -- TAKE THAT
BRUSH AND BLEND IT SO IT'S A
BEAUTIFUL OMBRE EFFECT.
AND HERE'S ANOTHER LITTLE CREEK
SECRET.
TWO MORE THINGS FOR THE VAMP YOU
LIP PEOPLE.
YOU WANT TO TAKE A LITTLE BIT OF
A SHIMMER.
AND YOU PUT IT RIGHT IN THE
CENTER.
THERE!
>> Keke: THAT LOOKS BEAUTIFUL!
>> Natalie: YES, MISS THING!
>> Keke: THAT GAVE HER MORE OF
A GLOW.
>> Natalie: GIVES MORE OF A
GLOW, YOUR LIPS LOOK BIGGER.
HERE'S ONE MORE TRICK.
IF YOU WANT TO DO THE VAMP LIP,
MY SUGGESTION WITHOUT TO HAVE A
SHINY FACE.
THEN YOU LOOK CRAY-CRAY.
HE STEPPED OUT OF THE CLUB A
LITTLE TOO LATE.
YOU KNOW THE LOOK.
ANYWAY, WE WANT TO TAKE A GREAT
MODIFIER.
SOMETHING THAT WILL BE
INVISIBLE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE TOO DRY AND
ASHY.
IS THAT GORGEOUS?
THAT WAY YOU WILL HAVE THAT
BEAUTIFUL FRESH DELICIOUS LOOK.
>> Keke: LOOK HOW BEAUTIFUL
SHE IS!
THEM BROWS, THOSE EYES!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Natalie: THAT IS YOUR
LADY GAGA LIP.
FAST AND EASY.
>> Keke: LET'S GET INTO THIS
LAST TREND.
>> THERE IS A LITTLE LADY NAMED
MISS ANGELA BASSETT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
DO YOU KNOW HER?
>> Wendy: I DO, I DO!
>> Natalie: I THINK YOU MOM!
EVERYBODY SAYS, "ANGELA
BASSETT'S RETURN!"
SO I TAKE IT AS A COMPLIMENT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Natalie: THAT FACE, LOVE
IT!
YOU REALLY DO RESEMBLE HER.
THE CHEEKBONES.
THAT'S WHAT THIS IS ALL ABOUT.
THESE ARE SENSATIONAL CHEEKS.
A.K.A., CHEEKBONES FOR THE GODS.
OKAY?
EXACTLY.
WHEN YOU ARE DOING YOU ARE
HIGHLIGHTING IN YOUR CONTOURING,
WHICH, BY THE WAY, YOURS IS
LOOKING EXTRA FABULOUS.
>> Keke: THANK YOU, JEREMY!
>> Natalie: I WANT YOU TO
REMEMBER TWO THINGS.
THE LETTER SEE, AND THE NUMBER
THREE.
SEE, THREE
THAT'LL BE OR HIGHLIGHT.
YOU WANT TO TAKE THE HIGHLIGHT
AND YOU WANT THE SEE, AROUND
YOUR EYES.
YOUR HIGHLIGHT IS GOING TO GO
LIKE SO.
AND THEN THE CONTOUR, THAT IS
THE 3.
THAT'S THE SECRET.
WE WILL DO, YOU START IN THE
CENTER OF THE FOREHEAD LIKE SO.
AND YOU ARE GOING TO CREATE A
NUMBER OF 3.
ON THE FACE.
OKAY?
>> Keke: THAT LOOKS GREAT.
>> Natalie: HERE'S THE
TRICK -- YOU WERE GOING TO MAKE
A FISH FACE.
DO THIS.
>> Keke: MM-HMM, I LOVE A FISH
FACE, ON THE!
I WILL GIVE IT TO YOU DAY AND
NIGHT!
>> Natalie: EVEN GETTING YOUR
MAKEUP DONE!
THAT'S WHAT THIS IS ABOUT.
THAT'S WHERE YOU WILL
CONCENTRATE THAT DARKNESS.
YOU SEE HOW WE ARE GIVING IT TO
YOU RIGHT THERE?
THAT'S HOW WE DO IT.
>> Keke: HONEY IS BEAT!
AT >> Natalie: HERE'S ANOTHER
TRICK.
IF YOU'VE BEEN EATING TOO MANY
FRENCH FRIES LIKE YOURS TRULY
AND YOU NEED A LITTLE SOMETHING
HOW YOU WANT TO GET RID OF THE
FULLNESS UNDER HERE, THAT TURKEY
NECK -- NOTHING YOU HAVE ONE,
HONEY, DON'T WORRY -- WE WANT TO
TAKE IT AND GO RIGHT DOWN THERE.
AND THAT WILL GIVE YOU
COMPLETELY THE MOST SCULPTED AND
FIERCE -- SO IF YOU WANT TO LOOK
LIKE A MRS. KEKE --
>> Natalie: OR LIKE A MESS AND
NATALIE!
>> Natalie: STOP IT!
[APPLAUSE]
THIS IS THE WAY TO DO IT.
FAST AND EASY FOR ME IS ALL
ABOUT LOOKING FRESH AND LOOKING
LIKE YOU.
>> Keke: WHICH ONE IS YOUR
FAVORITE?
YOU'VE GOT TO CHOOSE, GIRL!
>> Natalie: I LOVE A SCULPTED
CHEEK.
THAT'S WHAT IT'S ABOUT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Keke: I WANT TO GET INTO
THIS REQUEST.
LOOK AT THESE RINGS!
THEY WERE GIVING ME LIFE THE
ENTIRE TIME!
>> Natalie: MORE IS MORE.
>> Keke: THANK YOU, NATALIE,
AT OUR BEAUTIFUL MODELS.
FOR MORE INFORMATION ON THESE
TRENDS GO TO WendyShow.com.
UP NEXT, TWO AUDIENCE MEMBERS GO
HEAD-TO-HEAD IN A GAME OF
GRAMMAR EACH OF YOU FOR A HUGE
PRICE.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Keke: WELCOME BACK!
IT'S TIME TO PLAY GRAMMY SLAMMY.
I WILL BE ASKING TWO AUDIENCE
MEMBERS QUESTIONS ABOUT THE
GRAMMYS, AND WHOEVER WINS GETS A
BIG PRIZE!
COME ON DOWN, Y'ALL!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
COME ON COME OUT FIT!
I'M SEEING YOU WITH THIS
LIME GREEN TYPE OF VIBE, YOU'VE
GOT THE RED AND THE BELT.
YES, GIRL!
WHERE ARE YOU FROM, WHAT DO YOU
DO?
>> I AM ORIGINALLY FROM
JONESBORO, ARKANSAS, .
>> Keke: A SOUTHERN GAL!
>> BORN AND RAISED, YES.
BUT NOW I LIVE IN QUEENS!
>> Keke: DO YOU LIKE NEW YORK?
>> I LOVE IT.
I LIVE IN ASTORIA AND I'VE LIVED
THERE FOR ABOUT EIGHT YEARS NOW.
>> Keke: WHERE ARE YOU FROM,
WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> I'M ARIEL, I'M FROM ARIEL,
NEW JERSEY.
I'M THE QUEEN OF MY OWN TOWN!
I'M A DIGITAL STRATEGIST.
I LOVE DIGITAL MEDIA.
>> Keke: I LOVE DIGITAL MEDIA!
>> I'VE GOT A CARD FOR YOU, GIR
GIRL.
>> Keke: I GOT A NEW SISTER
TODAY, Y'ALL!
>> HEY, BOO-BOO!
>> Keke: YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE PLAYING FOR?
>> THAT'S WHY WE'RE HERE!
>> Wendy: YOU'RE PLAYING TO
WIN A TRIP TO THE GRAMMY AWARDS!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> LETS GO!
>> Keke: THANKS TO OUR FRIENDS
AT HOTEL PLANNER.COM.
THERE ARE NUMBER ONE IN GROUP
TRAVEL AND THEY'VE GOT THE BEST
RATES ON HOTELS ALL OVER THE
WORLD.
THEY ARE PROVIDING ROUND-TRIP
AIRFARE, A TWO NIGHT HOTEL STAY,
AND TWO TICKETS TO MUSIC'S
BIGGEST NIGHT.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN TO THE
GRAMMYS?
JAN WILL GO TO THE!
ARE YOU READY TO PLAY?
WHEN WE READ TO THE RULES.
THE FIRST PLASTIC DOME I PERSON
TO DO THE BUZZER GETS TO ANSWER
THE QUESTION PAID WAIT TILL I'M
DONE READING THE ENTIRE QUESTION
ON THE CHOICES.
NO CLEANING, AND DON'T BE ALL
HELP THEM!
IF YOU GET IT WRONG YOUR
OPPONENT CAN GUESS.
LET'S PLAY.
WHO IS THE MOST NOMINATED FEMALE
ARTIST IN GRAMMY HISTORY?
BEYONCE, A DELL, OR CAREY?
[BUZZER]
BOTH OF YOUR HANDS ARE ON IT!
>> I THINK IT WAS ME!
>> Keke: ALL     ON THREE BOTH .
>> MOST NOMINATED FEMALE ARTIST
IN GRAMMY HISTORY.
OKAY, YOU KNOW -- I'M A BEYONCE
FAN.
I'M IN THE BEEHIVE AND I LIVED
THERE.
BUT BEYONCE AND ADELE, THEY DID
THAT THING.
BUT I'M GOING TO GO WITH BEYONC
BEYONCE.
>> Keke: THAT'S CORRECT!
>> "ALL THE SINGLE LADIES!"
BECAUSE THERE IS STILL HOPE FOR
ME.
IT'S THE BEGINNING OF THE GAME.
>> Keke: WHICH ARTIST CAME TO
THE 2011 GRAMMYS AND A GIANT
EGG.
[BUZZER]
MADONNA, KANYE WEST, OR
LADY GAGA?
>> OKAY, WHICH ARTIST CAME TO
THE 2011 GRAMMYS IN A GIANT EGG?
LADY GAGA!
BECAUSE YOU KNOW SHE CRAZY!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Keke: YOU'RE GOING TO LET
HER SMASH YOU LIKE THAT?
>> THERE IS STILL HOPE.
I'M NOT GIVING UP.
>> Keke: HOW MANY POUNDS AS A
GRAMMY AWARD WAY?
1 POUND, 6 POUNDS, OR 10 POUNDS?
[BUZZER]
>> WHICH ONE IS IT?
>> Audience: REL
!
>> I'M GOING TO GO WITH -- AND
THIS IS TOUGH, THIS IS TOUGH.
I'M GOING TO GO WITH 6 POUNDS!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Keke: ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
>> IT'S OKAY, GIRL.
>> I DON'T GIVE UP EASILY.
I'M STILL HERE, I'M STILL HERE!
>> Keke: WHO IS THE YOUNGEST
GRAMMY WINNER EVER?
RIHANNA, LEANNE RIMES, OR
JUSTIN BIEBER?
>> I KNOW THIS WHEN!
IF YOU DON'T, I DO!
>> I'M GOING TO GO WITH
LEANN RIMES, JUST BECAUSE!
>> Wendy: ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
THIS IS CRAZY.
IS SHE PSYCHIC?
J.LO OR IN INFAMOUS GREEN DRESS
TO THE GRAMMYS.
WHO DESIGNED IT?
ARMANI, MARK JACOBS, OR VERSACE?
WE HAVE TO LET HER THROUGH
SOMEHOW!
>> ME ABOUT!
I'M TO GO WITH --
>> Keke: YOU BETTER GET IT,
GIRL!
2000 PAGE A LOW STRESS.
>> I'M SPLIT BETWEEN ARMANI AND
MARC JACOBS.
OH, MY GOSH, .
OKAY, THIS IS MY ONLY CHANCE.
IT'S ON THAT ANSWER, I'M GOING
WITH VERSACE.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Keke: I'M JUST GOING TO GO
WITH THIS LESSON.
AN EXTRA, WILL SEE.
WHAT YEAR WAS THE FIRST
GRAMMY AWARDS CEREMONY HELD?
1949, 1959, OR 1969?
>> 1959!
I FEEL SURE!
>> Keke: GOOD JOB, GIRL!
YOU HELD IN THERE AND I REALLY
LOVE YOUR GUMPTION.
BUT THE GAG IS, ARIEL IS THE
WINNER.
BECAUSE I'M YOUR SISTER, I'M
COMING WITH YOU!
NO, I'M KIDDING.
THANK YOU BOTH ARE PLAYING.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, YOU WERE
AWESOME.
>> THANK YOU!
>> Keke: ASK KEKE ISEKE IS NEXT!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
Live from the Starlite Lounge.
♪ One plus one equals
too little too late ♪
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]
>> YOU GOT THE MONEY?
>> IS THAT ALL YOU CARE ABOUT?
I'VE BEEN THROUGH HELL.
>> YOU CAN TELL ME LATER.
>> IT IS LATER!
HOW COME YOU'RE ALWAYS LYING TO
ME?
MA, DO YOU EVEN CARE TO ASK WHAT
HAPPENED TO ME?
>> IF YOU GOT ME OUT OF HERE, WE
CAN GO TALK ABOUT IT.
>> I'M IN TROUBLE!
BIG TROUBLE!
I SHOULDN'T EVEN BE HERE RIGHT
NOW!
YOU SITTING LOOKING AT MY BUSTED
FACE?
>> I JUST WANT TO GO HOME RIGHT
UP.
I'M SURE YOU CAN UNDERSTAND
THAT.
>> YOU SAID YOU WEREN'T DOING
MORE DRUGS.
>> WHERE YOU GOING WITH THIS?
DO YOU HAVE MORE MONEY OR NOT?
>> Keke: THAT WAS A CLIP FOR
MY NEW MOVIE.
IT'S STREAMING, YOU CAN CHECK IT
OUT NOW.
BUT THEY HAVE THE CHECK OUT MY
OUTFIT!
[APPLAUSE]
KEEP GOING!
I'M KIDDING.
NOW IT'S TIME FOR "ASK KEKE."
WHAT'S YOUR QUESTION?
>> HEY, KEKE.
HOW YOU DOIN'?
MY NAME IS MALAIKA.
I'M A FRIEND, WE'VE BEEN FRIEND
FOR TEN YEARS.
EVERY TIME WE GO OUT, SHE GETS
DRUNK AND HAS AN ALTERCATION.
SHE THROWS DRINKS AT BJ's.
>> Keke: HOW LONG HAVE YOU
BEEN FRIENDS?
>> TEN YEARS.
>> Keke: AND THIS IS SOMETHING
SHE CONTINUOUSLY DOES?
MY QUESTION IS, MY MOM ALWAYS
TELLS ME, THE TIME AND PLACE TO
SERVE.
YOU CAN NEVER SAY, I WANT TO
INVITE HER TO BE CERTAIN EVENTS
BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW HOW SHE
MIGHT ACT.
OR, YOU CAN PRETTY MUCH SAY TO
HER, "LOOK, THIS IS HOW I FEEL
THAT WE'VE BEEN DOING, GIRL.
AS A FRIEND, I DON'T WANT YOU
LOOKING CRAZY OR GETTING INTO
TROUBLE.
I'M NOT JUDGING YOU, BUT GIRL,
WE DON'T GOTTA GET ANGRY WITH
NOBODY!"
[APPLAUSE]
WHATEVER YOU DO, DON'T TEXT IT.
SAY IT IN PERSON, GIRL.
I'VE RUINED A FEW RELATIONSHIPS
TEXTING THESE COMBOS.
MAKE SURE YOU TELL HER.
[APPLAUSE]
HI, HOW ARE YOU?
>> HI, KEKE.
I'M TIFFANY.
HOW YOU DOIN' COSTA McKAY WAS
A CHRISTMAS PARTY, I WAS
RELIEVED BY BEING WITH THIS CUTE
GUY.
HE WAS 6'3".
LATER ON I FOUND OUT THAT MY
BEST FRIEND HOOKED UP WITH HIM
BEFORE.
SHE SAID IT WAS COOL, BUT I
FIGURE IT'S KIND OF WEIRD.
SHOULD I CONTINUE PURSUING HIM
OR SHOULD I JUST QUIT IT?
>> Keke: HAVE YOU BEEN TALKING
SINCE YOU MET AT THAT PARTY?
>> YEAH.
>> SO THERE'S A CONTINUE TO
PROVIDE THAT IT COULD GO
SOMEWHERE.
WHEN YOU ASK YOUR FRIEND, DID
YOU HEAR AT HOME AND SHE SAID IT
WAS IT OVERTAXED?
>> SHE'S FINE WITH ME BUT SHE
DOESN'T LIKE HIM.
HE'S A FRIEND WHEN SHE THINKS
THAT HE'S JUST GOING TO USE ME.
BUT I DON'T KNOW.
>> Keke: IT DOESN'T MEAN HE'LL
DO IT WITH YOU.
ANYWAY, IF YOU ASK YOUR FRIEND
AND SHE HAS TOLD YOU THAT SHE
DOESN'T SAY ANYTHING -- THAT
SHE'S NOT COMFORTABLE WITH IT
AND HE RESPECTED HER ENOUGH TO
ASK IT, HOPEFULLY SHE SAID WHAT
SHE MEANT AND SHE MEANT WHAT SHE
SAID.
YOU CAN'T HOLD ON FOR HER.
SHE ALREADY SAID IT SO ENJOY NEW
POSSIBLE GUIDE.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Keke: WE DOING IT LIKE
THIS?
YES!
>> MY NAME IS ARLENE.
MY QUESTION, BEFORE YOU CAN TELL
YOU, I'M GOING TO TELL YOU THE
SCENARIO.
I MET A GUY AT A PARTY LAST
MONTH.
HE IS SO FINE.
LIKE WINE.
WE'VE BEEN TALKING FOR A LITTLE
WHILE OR WHATEVER.
I GOT HIS INSTAGRAM.
I JUST WANT TO NO, IS IT OKAY TO
ASK HIM OUT ON A DATE?
>> Wendy: I DON'T LIKE WHEN
PEOPLE TRY TO SEE HOW GUYS OR
GIRLS SHOULD BE.
YOU CAN BE CASUAL AND JUST SAY,
"HEY, WANT TO CATCH A MOVIE?"
YOU CAN JUST SAY, "IT DOESN'T
HAVE TO BE NO MORE THAN THAT.
[APPLAUSE]
HEY, GIRL.
>> HI, KEKE!
MY NAME IS AMANDA.
HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> Keke: I'VE GOT TO BE MIXED
THAT SOMEHOW.
HOW YOU DOIN'?
[LAUGHTER]
>> I'VE GOT AN EX-BOYFRIEND,
HE'S REALLY NICE.
HE ALWAYS REACHES OUT AND CALLS
ME, BUT MY BOYFRIEND DOESN'T
LIKE IT AND DOESN'T WANT ME TO
TALK TO HIM AT ALL.
WHO'S RIGHT?
>> Keke: WHEN YOU'RE IN A
RELATIONSHIP, I FEEL LIKE YOU
HAVE TO RESPECT WHATEVER THE
OTHER PERSON'S BOUNDARIES ARE
WITHIN REASON.
YOU GET WHAT I'M SAYING?
IF YOU REALLY LOVE THE GUY THAT
YOU'RE WITH, YOU RESPECT HIM --
HAVE YOU BEEN TOGETHER A WHILE?
>> FOUR YEARS.
>> FOR USE WITH THEIR CURRENT
GUIDE.
DID YOU TELL HIM THAT YOUR
BOYFRIEND -- DID YOU TELL HIM
THAT, LET HIM KNOW?
"NOTHING AGAINST YOU, BUT THIS
IS MAKING MY RELATIONSHIP
UNCOMFORTABLE."
HAVE YOU THOUGHT OF DOING THAT?
>> I TOLD HIM, BUT...
>> Keke: BUT HE KEPT GOING?
WHO BROKE UP WITH WHO?
>> I BROKE UP WITH HIM.
>> Keke: GIRL, WE'VE GOT TO
GO.
BECAUSE HE'S TRYING TO SABOTAGE!
NO, LOVE!
[APPLAUSE]
IF YOU'RE HAPPY WITH THE GUY YOU
ARE WITH, RESPECT HIS WISHES AND
TRY TO BACK OFF OF IT.
ALL RIGHT?
YES!
MORE "ASK A KEKE" IS N KEKE" IS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
Never ending is now even better
at Olive Garden.
With all new
Never Ending Stuffed Pastas
starting at just $12.99.
Pick your favorite
stuffed pasta
like our new
Stuffed Ziti Fritta,
with your choice of
sauce and topping...
then try another
delicious combination.
Plus unlimited
salad and breadsticks.
It's all never ending.
Here's to more from
beginning to endless.
All New Never Ending Stuffed
Pastas starting at $12.99.
Only for a limited time,
at Olive Garden.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Keke: WE ARE BACK.
TIME FOR MORE "ASK KEKE."
WHAT'S YOUR QUESTION?
>> HEY, KEKE, HOW YOU DOIN'?
MY NAME IS DANIELLE.
I HAVE A BROTHER ABOUT FIVE AND
HALF YEARS YOUNGER THAN ME.
EVERY TIME YOU'RE TOGETHER WE
ARGUE AND BICKER.
MY QUESTION IS, HOW CAN WE BUILD
OUR RELATIONSHIP SO WE DON'T
ARGUE AND BICKER?
THE ONE THAT'S A HARD ONE.
I HAVE YOUNGER SIBLINGS, AS
WELL.
THERE SEVEN YEARS YOUNGER.
WHEN YOU GET FIVE TO SEVEN
THERE'S A GENERATIONAL GAP.
A LOT OF THE TIMES THE THINGS
YOU THINK ABOUT AND WHERE YOU
ARE IN YOUR LIFE ARE TWO TOTALLY
DIFFERENT THINGS.
WHEN IT COMES TO THE YOUNGER
SIBLINGS, SOMETIMES YOU'VE GOT
TO BE PATIENT.
SOMETIMES YOU REALLY WANT TO LET
ME KNOW BUT THEMSELVES, BUT THEY
HAVEN'T REACHED THE MATURITY
LEVEL TO RELIEVE AND GATHER WHAT
THEY ARE SAYING.
I WOULD SAY, TAKE IT EASY ON
THEM.
BE A LITTLE BIT MORE PATIENT.
TRY TO MAKE YOURSELF AVAILABLE
TO THE SINK SEASON TWO.
IF IT'S THAT IMPORTANT TO YOU.
YOU ARE THE OLDER ONE, SO YOU
HAVE TO BE MORE MATURE.
[APPLAUSE]
>> THANK YOU!
>> HEY, KEKE!
MY NAME IS BARBARA.
HOW YOU DOIN'?
I'VE BEEN WITH MY FIANCE FOR TEN
YEARS, ENGAGE FOR TWO.
RECENTLY I'VE BEEN TRYING TO
MAKE WEDDING PLANS BUT HE KEEPS
ON BRUSHING THEM OFF.
NOW HE'S TELLING ME HE DOESN'T
WANT TO GET MARRIED BUT HE WANTS
TO STAY TOGETHER.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
>> Keke: YOU BEEN TOGETHER FOR
TEN YEARS?
WHEN HE PROPOSED TO YOU --
>> I PROPOSE TO HIM.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
>> Keke: WHAT I'M GETTING AT
IS THAT MARRIAGE IS A HARD LINE
FOR YOU?
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT YOURSELF,
YOU REALLY WANT TO    TO BE MAR?
>> YES.
>> Keke: THEN YOU HAVE TO MAKE
A DECISION.
BECAUSE YOU BEEN WITH THIS
PERSON FOR TEN YEARS, GIVE HIM
TEN YEARS OF YOUR LIFE.
YOU PROPOSED IT TO HIM, WHICH
SHOWS IT WAS MORE SOMETHING YOU
WANT TO DO THAN I AM.
AND HE'S BEING HONEST WITH YOU,
LETTING HIM KNOW THAT HE DIDN'T
PROPOSE.
AND WHEN YOU PROPOSE, HE LET YOU
KNOW THAT IT'S NOT REALLY WHAT
HE WANTS.
SO YOU HAVE TO ASK YOURSELF --
IS IT OKAY?
IS THE COMPANIONSHIP WITH THIS
PERSON MORE IMPORTANT THAN WHAT
I REALLY TRULY WANT?
IT'S ALL ABOUT BOUNDARY LINES.
IF THIS IS A HARD LINE FOR YOU,
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO.
[APPLAUSE]
>> THANK YOU.
>> Keke: IT'S A HARD ONE.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
Change will come.
But this hair color thing.
I've got that figured out.
Garnier Nutrisse.
The #1 Nourishing Color Crème,
with avocado, olive and
shea oils.
Nourishes while you color.
For the rich color you expect.
Join the millions who have
chosen Nutrisse.
Nourished hair.
Better Color.
Hy-a-luronic Acid.
It's in here.
New from Revitalift:
Derm Intensives
Hyaluronic Acid Serum
With our highest concentration
of Hyaluronic Acid
Visibly plumps skin
and reduces wrinkles.
Bounce back!
New Revitalift Hyaluronic
Acid Serum
From L'Oreal.
Stouffer's Lasagna With Meat &
Sauce
has two times the beef of the
leading meat sauce lasagna.
That's double the tender ground
beef
baked into every cheesy,
mouthwatering bite.
When it comes to irresistible
taste,
more is always more.
Stouffer's.
[phone ringing]
Remember the way we
used to do things?
Hey man...
Like connect with friends?
Dig it!
Or get in shape?
Or sell a house
and pay a real estate
agent a big commission.
[crash]
At Redfin, we charge
you a 1% listing fee.
And because Redfin.com is
America's #1 brokerage site
our agents get more
eyes on your home
so you sell for
thousands more
than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin Agent.
than the one next door.
♪ ♪
>> Keke: I WANT TO THANK
TODAY'S GUESTS, AND MY COHOST,
THE STUDIO AUDIENCE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
YOU ARE AWESOME!
ON MONDAY, SHERRI SHEPHERD'S
GUEST HOSTING.
THAT'S MY GIRL, WE DID BROADWAY
TOGETHER.
YES!
I LOVE YOU GUYS FOR HANGING OUT
WITH ME.
I LOVE YOU HAVE A FABULOUS
WEEKEND.
WE WILL SEE YOU NEXT TIME ON
"WENDY"!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> IT IS FRI-YAY, AND TODAY ON
"GIRL CHAT," A GIRL SCOUT
REMIXES