Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
♪ ARE YOU READY Y'ALL
TO HAVE SOME FUN
♪ FEEL THE LOVE TONIGHT
DON'T YOU WORRY
♪ WHERE IT IS YOU COME FROM
IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT
♪ IT'S THE LATE, LATE SHOW ♪
>> Reggie: LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
ALL THE WAY FROM WELLINGTON,
WISCONSIN, RHODE ISLAND, GIVE IT
UP FOR YOUR HOST, THE ONE, THE
ONLY JAMES CORDEN!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
HOW ARE YOU?
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
♪ ♪ ♪
THANKS FOR COMING TO SEE US.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
THANK YOU.
HELLO, GOOD EVENING, AND WELCOME
TO THIS, THE "LATE, LATE SHOW."
WE HAVE A FUN ONE FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, GUYS.
LET'S GET INTO IT.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU SAW THIS,
THERE IS YET ANOTHER TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION TELL-ALL BOOK ON
THE WAY.
IT COMES OUT NEXT TUESDAY.
IT'S FROM A FORMER WHITE HOUSE
COMMUNICATIONS AIDE AND IT'S
CALLED "TEAM OF VIPERS."
( LAUGHTER )
SO, I'M GUESSING IT MIGHT NOT BE
TOO FLATTERING, I IMAGINE.
( LAUGHTER )
IN ONE SECTION THE FORMER
INSIDER DESCRIBES THE WHITE
HOUSE AS BEING "ABSOLUTELY OUT
OF CONTROL."
NOW, I'M NOT EVEN A WHITE HOUSE
INSIDER.
I COULD HAVE TOLD YOU THAT.
( LAUGHTER )
WHERE'S MY BOOK DEAL.
CAN'T I WRITE A BOOK?
ACCORDING TO THE AUTHOR, FORMER
HOUSE SPEAKER PAUL RYAN ONCE
ATTEMPTED TO EXPLAIN A HEALTH-
CARE BILL TO TRUMP WHEN THE
PRESIDENT SUDDENLY GOT UP,
WALKED OUT OF THE BRIEFING AND
BEGAN WATCHING TELEVISION IN
ANOTHER ROOM.
( LAUGHTER )
NOW, I HAVE HEARD PAUL RYAN
SPEAK, OKAY, AND I NEVER THOUGHT
I WOULD SAY THIS, I HAVE TO SIDE
WITH TRUMP ON THIS ONE.
( LAUGHTER )
HE'S BORING.
MOVING ON, AMAZON JUST MADE A
BIG ANNOUNCEMENT.
THEY'RE NOW LAUNCHING A SELF-
DRIVING DELIVERY ROBOT NAMED
SCOUT.
WE'VE GOT A VIDEO OF HIM HERE.
TAKE A LOOK.
LOOK AT THIS, THAT IS SCOUT
THERE.
( LAUGHTER )
AMAZON DESIGNED IT TO DELIVER
PACKAGES DIRECTLY TO YOUR DOOR
STEP, RIGHT.
NOW, I'M SORRY, IF THERE IS A
SCOUT COMING DIRECTLY ON TO MY
FAMILY'S PROPERTY, SHE BETTER BE
SELLING COOKIES.
( LAUGHTER )
OKAY, CAN WE SEE THAT ROBOT
AGAIN?
IT LOOKS LIKE A ROOMBA WHO HAS
BEEN SPENDING TOO MUCH TIME AT
THE GYM.
( LAUGHTER )
AMAZON SAYS THEIR DELIVERY ROBOT
IS THE SIZE OF A SMALL COOLER,
WHICH I CAN ONLY IMAGINE IS BAD
NEWS IF ARE YOU ORDERING A LARGE
COOLER.
( LAUGHTER )
SO THIS IS REALLY EXCITING FOR
PEOPLE-- THIS IS EXCITING-- WOW,
THAT REALLY RIPPLED AROUND THE
WHOLE ROOM DIDN'T IT?
( LAUGHTER )
THIS IS EXCITING FOR ANY OF
THOSE PEOPLE WHO STEAL PACKAGES
OFF OF FRONT PORCHES.
YOU KNOW, NOW YOU WILL GET A
FREE ROBOT!
( LAUGHTER )
AND THIS IS INTERESTING.
A BRAND NEW STUDY FROM BY OXFORD
UNIVERSITY CONCLUDED SCREEN
TIME-- YOU NOW TIME SPENT IN
FRONT OF AN iPAD  OR AN Iphone
OR A TELEVISION-- IS NOT HARMFUL
TO KIDS.
YEAH, SO IF YOU ARE A PARENT
WITH SMALL CHILDREN AND YOU'RE
WATCHING THIS SHOW RIGHT NOW,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
GO AND WAKE YOUR KIDS UP.
( LAUGHTER )
GET THEM IN FRONT OF THE TV NOW.
BUT CONTRARY TO WHAT MANY PEOPLE
WOULD HAVE THOUGHT, IT TURNS OUT
SPENDING A LOT OF TIME ON YOUR
PHONE ISN'T HARMFUL.
THIS IS GREAT NEWS FOR YOUNG
KIDS AND PRESIDENT TRUMP.
( LAUGHTER )
THIS IS A BIG RELIEF FOR PARENTS
OUT THERE.
IT REALLY IS.
UNFORTUNATELY MOST OF THE
PARENTS DIDN'T HEAR THE NEWS
BECAUSE THEY WERE TOO BUSY JUST
SCROLLING THROUGH INSTAGRAM.
( LAUGHTER )
SHE'S GOT AN iPAD, IT'S FINE.
AND FINALLY HERE'S A STORY WE
HAVE BEEN FOLLOWING OUT OF
ALASKA.
A COW IN ANCHORAGE ESCAPED FROM
HER PEN DURING A RODEO, AND HAS
MANAGED TO EVADE CAPTURE FOR THE
LAST SIX MONTHS.
( LAUGHTER )
OR TO PUT IT ANOTHER WAY, THE
WORLD'S LONGEST RODEO HAS NOW
BEEN GOING ON FOR SIX MONTHS.
( LAUGHTER )
OFFICIALS CAN'T BELIEVE THE COW
HAS MANAGED TO EVADE THEM FOR
THIS LONG, BUT THE OWNER SAYS HE
ISN'T SURPRISED, DESCRIBING THE
COW AS A "REAL GO-GETTER."
HE KNEW RIGHT AWAY BECAUSE THE
COW SHOWED UP ON THE FIRST DAY
OF RODEO IN A POWER SUIT AND
NOTEBOOK LABELED "GREAT IDEAS."
( LAUGHTER )
YOU CAN UNDERSTAND THOUGH WHY
THE COW DOESN'T WANT TO BE
CAUGHT.
THIS IS THE POLICE SKETCH LOCAL
AUTHORITIES HAVE RELEASED TO THE
MEDIA.
( LAUGHTER )
SHALL WE HAVE A LOOK AND SEE WHO
OUR GUESTS ARE ON THE SHOW
TONIGHT?
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
IN THE RED ROOM, HE IS A MULTI-
AWARD-WINNING ACTOR, PERFORMER
AND AUTHOR YOU KNOW FROM "A
SERIES OF UNFORTUNATE EVENTS,"
THE WILDLY TALENTED, THE ALWAYS
CHARMING, NEIL PATRICK HARRIS IS
HERE TONIGHT!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
HEY, NEIL.
>> OH, HI.
>> James: HOW ARE YOU?
>> HI, JAMES, HOW IS IT GOING?
>> James: SO YOU ARE OUTSIDE THE
ROOM, AND NOT INSIDE THE ROOM.
>> OH, YEAH, YEAH, I WAS JUST
TRYING TO GET A SENSE OF THE
PLACE.
>> James: YEAH, NICE, OKAY,
GOOD.
>> I WASN'T NOT IN YOUR OFFICE.
( LAUGHTER )
>> James: YOU SEE, I NEVER
THOUGHT YOU WERE IN MY OFFICE
UNTIL YOU JUST SAID YOU WEREN'T
IN MY OFFICE.
>> OH, YEAH, NO, I WAS IN YOUR
OFFICE.
( LAUGHTER )
I LIKE ALL THE STUFF THAT'S ON
YOUR DESK.
WHAT IS THAT ONE-- WHY DO YOU
HAVE THAT ONE THING?
>> James: NEIL PATRICK HARRIS,
EVERYBODY!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
AND IN THE BLUE ROOM, A
HILARIOUS COMEDIAN, ACTOR AND
WRITER, KNOW FROM "BROOKLYN
NINE-NINE" AND HER BRILLIANT
NETFLIX SPECIAL, ONE OF THE
GREATS, THE INCREDIBLE, THE
STUNNING, CHELSEA PERETTI IS
HERE TONIGHT.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
HEY, CHELSEA, HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M GOOD, THANK YOU.
>> James: HOW IS IT GOING?
>> REALLY GOOD, FEELING SOLID
ABOUT THE SHOW TONIGHT.
BACK TO YOU.
( LAUGHTER )
>> James: WE CAN GO LIVE TO
CHELSEA PERETTI WHO IS IN THE
BLUE ROOM, CHELSEA WHAT IS
HAPPENING?
>> NOT MUCH, I'M JUST BACK HERE
REALLY EXCITED TO DO THE SHOW
( LAUGHTER )
>> James: THAT'S CHELSEA
PERETTI, LET'S HEAR FROM REGGIE
WATTS.
REGGIE, WHAT IS HAPPENING OVER
THERE?
>> Reggie: JUST CURRENTLY
SITTING DOWN HERE ADMIRING THE
CONVERSATION BETWEEN THE TWO OF
YOU.
>> James: THANKS, REG.
THANKS, CHELSEA.
THANKS, REG.
>> Reggie: BACK TO YOU.
( LAUGHTER )
>> James: THANKS, CHELSEA.
>> NO PROB!
>> James: THANKS, REG.
>> Reggie: CHELSEA OUT.
>> James: JAMES OUT.
CHELSEA PERETTI, EVERYBODY!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
AND IN THE PURPLE ROOM WE HAVE A
VERY FUNNY STANDUP COMEDIAN,
WE'RE THRILLED HE IS HERE, YOU
KNOW FROM COMEDY CENTRAL AND IN
JUST A LITTLE WHILE HE WILL BE
OUT HERE PERFORMING FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
IT'S ADAM NEWMAN IS HERE THIS
EVENING.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
HEY, ADAM, HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> HEY, JAMES, HOW ARE YOU?
I'M JUST PREPARING FOR MY SET
TONIGHT.
( FART NOISE )
( LAUGHTER )
>> James: WOW.
BECAUSE I'VE SEEN YOU LIVE
BEFORE, YOU DIDN'T DO A LOT OF
THIS SORT OF STUFF.
>> NO, I'M TRY SOME NEW STUFF, I
THINK IT'S GOING TO BE ALL
RIGHT.
( FART NOISE )
( LAUGHTER )
>> James: ADAM NEWMAN,
EVERYBODY.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
ARE YOU READY?
>> Reggie: NEWMAN.
>> James: HE'S REGGIE WATTS, I'M
JAMES CORDERN, THIS, THIS IS THE
"LATE, LATE SHOW."
ROLL THE TITLES.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
♪ THE LATE, LATE SHOW, OH, OH
THE LATE, LATE SHOW, OOH
THE LATE, LATE SHOW
♪ THE LATE, LATE SHOW, OH, OH
♪ OH, OH
THE LATE, LATE SHOW
IT'S THE LATE, LATE SHOW ♪
>> James: IT CERTAINLY IS.
SO, WE'VE BEEN DOING THIS SHOW
FOR OVER THREE YEARS NOW AND
OVER THAT TIME MORE AND MORE
PEOPLE COME UP TO ME, THEY ASK
HOW WE DO THINGS AROUND HERE.
AND THEY WANT TO KNOW THINGS,
WHICH IS WHY WE CREATED OUR NEXT
BIT, THIS IS "AUDIENCE Q & A."
>> Reggie: ♪ AUDIENCE Q AND A
QUESTIONS FROM THE AUDIENCE ♪
>> James: OKAY, SO IF YOU HAVE
GOT A QUESTION, IF THERE IS
ANYTHING YOU WOULD LIKE TO KNOW,
JUST PUT YOUR HAND UP.
WHO'S GOT A QUESTION THAT WOULD
LIKE TO KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT THE
SHOW?
LET'S GO WITH THIS MAN, THIS
GENTLEMAN HERE WHO LOOKS
SUSPICIOUSLY LIKE HE COULD BE MY
LOVE CHILD.
( LAUGHTER )
HOW ARE YOU?
>> HI, JAMES.
I'M SO GOOD, IT'S AMAZING TO BE
HERE, LIKE, I'M SUCH A BIG FAN
OF THE SHOW, I LOVE EVERYTHING
YOU DO, SO THIS IS AMAZING.
>> James: THANK YOU.
OH, THAT'S VERY SWEET.
>> I WAS JUST WONDERING, WHAT IS
YOUR FAVORITE COLOR?
( LAUGHTER )
>> James: MY-- I THOUGHT WERE
YOU GOING TO ASK A MORE PROFOUND
QUESTION.
MY FAVORITE, THAT'S ALL YOU WANT
TO KNOW?
>> YES.
>> James: BLUE?
I GUESS, YOU KNOW, THE SKY'S
BLUE, THE OCEAN'S BLUE... THESE
LITTLE EYES YOU CAN SEE ARE
BLUE, BLUE, THAT IS MY FAVORITE
COLOR.
ANYONE ELSE GOT A QUESTION?
THE LADY HERE, A QUESTION, GO
FOR IT, WHAT IS YOUR QUESTION?
>> HI, JAMES.
WHICH SHADE OF BLUE DO YOU
PREFER?
( LAUGHTER )
LIKE LIGHT BLUE, NAVY BLUE.
>> James: THIS ISN'T REALLY WHY
WE DO THIS BIT.
IT IS NOT MEANT TO BE ABOUT,
LIKE, I AM GIVING YOU AN
OPPORTUNITY TO ASK QUESTIONS
ABOUT ANYTHING, YOU KNOW,
HOSTING THE SHOW, PRODUCING A
SHOW LIKE THIS, BUT ROYAL BLUE,
I WOULD SAY, DEEP, THAT IS NAVY
BLUE, ISN'T IT?
ROYAL BLUE, I WOULD SAY THAT.
OKAY, WHO HAS GOT A DECENT
QUESTION, LIKE A DECENT, YES,
THE GENTLEMAN HERE WITH THE
BEARD.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU HAVE A
SENSIBLE QUESTION.
GO FOR IT.
>> HI, JAMES, THIS IS ACTUALLY A
QUESTION FOR NEIL PATRICK HARRIS
( LAUGHTER )
>> James: RIGHT, WELL, HE
ISN'T... HE'S NOT-- THIS IS--
THAT IS NOT WHAT THE-- THAT'S MY
JOB.
WILL BE OUT THERE LATER AND I
WILL BE ASKING HIM QUESTIONS.
THESE ARE QUESTIONS FOR ME.
OKAY?
NEIL PATRICK HARRIS ISN'T HERE,
HE IS UP IN THE DRESSING ROOM
GETTING READY FOR THE SHOW,
OKAY?
SO, THERE'S NO WAY WE COULD DO
IT.
>> NO, I'M HERE.
>> James: NEIL PATRICK HARRIS--
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
OKAY.
NEIL IS, TURNS OUT, NEIL, WHAT
ARE YOU DOING DOWN HERE?
>> I JUST WANTED TO SOAK UP THE
ATMOSPHERE, YOU KNOW, BEFORE I
CAME ON, JUST GET A SENSE OF THE
ROOM.
>> James: WELL, YOU HAVE BEEN ON
THE SHOW QUITE A FEW TIMES.
OKAY, WELL, YOU'RE HERE NOW.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE BOTHERED
WITH QUESTIONS LIKE THIS, OKAY?
SO YOU DON'T WANT THIS SORT OF
STUFF SO YOU CAN GO BACK IT.
>> I DON'T MIND.
HE CAN ASK ME A QUESTION.
>> James: OKAY, GREAT, LET'S
FIND OUT IF HIS FAVORITE COLOR
IS GREEN OR RED, OR WHATEVER, GO
FOR IT, OKAY.
>> HI, NEIL, HI.
SO I'M IN CONSTANT AWE OF THE
WAY THAT YOU ARE ABLE TO SWITCH
EFFORTLESSLY BETWEEN THE STAGE
AND THE SCREEN.
BUT WHAT I WOULD LOVE TO KNOW IS
WHEN YOU ARE PREPARING FOR A
THEATRICAL ROLE IS IT A VERY
DIFFERENT PROCESS TO WHEN YOU DO
A PIECE OF TELEVISION OR FILM?
>> James: RIGHT, YOU COULD HAVE
ASKED ME THAT.
( LAUGHTER )
I--  I 'VE DONE THOSE THINGS.
THAT IS-- I COULD HAVE-- DOESN'T
MATTER.
NO, IT DOESN'T MATTER, GO ON.
>> James: THAT COULD HAVE BEEN--
NEIL, GO FOR IT, NEIL.
>> THAT'S ACTUALLY A WONDERFUL
QUESTION.
>> James: IT IS A GOOD QUESTION.
>> THE ANSWER IS MY PREPARATION
IS PRETTY MUCH THE SAME.
I DO EVERYTHING I CAN TO FULLY
INHABIT EACH OF THE CHARACTERS
THAT I PLAY REGARDLESS OF THE
MEDIUM, I'LL DO THAT DOWN TO THE
VERY LAST DETAIL, WHICH CAN BE
KIND OF HARD TO SHAKE OFF, YOU
KNOW.
>> James: OKAY, THAT IS A GREAT
ANSWER.
A BIT PRETENTIOUS BUT THAT'S
OKAY.
( LAUGHTER )
NEIL PATRICK HARRIS, EVERYBODY.
THERE WE GO.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
I THINK YOU'VE GOT A SENSE OF
THE ROOM NOW.
THAT WAS LOVELY.
A NICE TREAT, A NICE TREAT.
OKAY, OKAY.
LET'S REFOCUS THE ROOM, OKAY?
LET'S REFOCUS.
WHO, ANYONE, WHO AS GOT A
QUESTION FOR ME ABOUT THE SHOW,
ABOUT-- YES, YES, THE LADY JUST
HERE IN THE BLACK TOP, YEAH, GO
FOR IT.
>> HI, JAMES.
>> James: HI.
>> SO, WATCHING THE SHOW IT IS
CLEAR YOU ARE A MAN OF
IMPECCABLE TASTES.
>> James: THANKS VERY MUCH.
>> SO, I WAS JUST WONDERING,
WHAT IS YOUR SECOND FAVORITE
COLOR?
>> James: OH, MY GOD, IS THIS A
JOKE?
>> NO.
>> James: WHAT IS MY SECOND
FAVORITE-- WHAT AM I, FIVE?
( LAUGHTER )
WHO HAS A SECOND FAVORITE COLOR?
CAN WE MOVE ON FROM THE COLOR
THING, PLEASE, AND JUST DO A
THING ABOUT THE SHOW?
WHO HAS GOT A PROPER QUESTION, I
REALLY JUST WANT-- YES, YES, THE
LADY HERE, I SHOULD HAVE GONE TO
YOU AT THE START.
WHAT IS YOUR QUESTION?
GO FOR IT.
>> THIS IS ANOTHER QUESTION FOR
NEIL.
>> James: OH FOR ( BLEEP ).
( LAUGHTER )
NEIL'S NOT HERE, DID YOU NOT
SEE?
HE WAS HERE AND THEN HE WALKED
OFF AND HAS GONE TO HIS DRESSING
ROOM.
>> NO, NO, NO, I'M STILL HERE--
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: WHAT--
>> HI.
( LAUGHTER )
>> James: YOU LITERALLY WENT
THAT WAY.
HOW DID YOU END UP-- IT DOESN'T
MATTER, IT IS WONDERFUL, WHAT'S
THE-- WHAT IS THE QUESTION?
>> NEIL, I'M YOUR BIGGEST FAN.
>> OH, THANKS.
>> BUT I HAVE TO ASK, WHAT'S
BEEN THE BIGGEST CHALLENGE
HOSTING THE TONY AWARDS?
>> James: OH FOR-- I HOSTED THE
TONY AWARDS!
YOU COULD HAVE ASKED ME THAT!
I'VE HOSTED THE TONYS!
>> JAMES, I THINK I'M A LITTLE
MORE QUALIFIED TO ANSWER THAT
QUESTION.
I HAVE HOSTED THE TONY AWARDS
FOUR TIMES.
>> James: YEAH, BUT I HOSTED
THEM A LOT MORE RECENTLY THAN
YOU HAVE, SO.
>> YES, BUT I ALSO WON A TONY.
>> James: I HAVE WON A TONY!
I HAVE WON A TONY!
>> HAVE YOU?
( LAUGHTER )
>> James: YES!
YOU WERE THE HOST WHEN I WON IT!
( LAUGHTER )
>> THERE WERE A LOT OF PEOPLE
THAT WON TONYS THAT DAY.
( LAUGHTER )
>> James: RIGHT, OKAY, OKAY, TO
ANSWER YOUR QUESTION, AND I'LL
TAKE IT, IT'S GREAT.
OKAY?
HOSTING THE TONYS IS GREAT, WE
BOTH AGREE, WHO ELSE HAS A
QUESTION?
YES, YES, YES, THIS MAN WITH THE
GLASSES RIGHT HERE, YES, WHAT IS
YOUR-- WHAT IS YOUR QUESTION.
>> UM, NEIL, YOU ARE--
>> James: OH, MY--
>> --ONE OF THE MOST TALENTED
PEOPLE IN THE WORLD.
>> James: YEAH, ONE OF, ONE OF,
ONE OF.
THERE ARE A FEW OF US, SO.
>> YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN DANCE,
YOU CAN ACT.
SO, I WAS JUST WONDERING, WOULD
YOU EVER CONSIDER HOSTING A LATE
NIGHT SHOW LIKE THIS ONE?
( LAUGHTER )
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> YOU KNOW, HONESTLY, THAT IS A
VERY, VERY INTERESTING QUESTION,
IT WOULD PROBABLY BE A LITTLE
BIT OF A STEP DOWN FOR ME.
( LAUGHTER )
BUT I CERTAINLY THINK, HONESTLY,
I THINK THAT I COULD DO IT
BECAUSE I WOULD JUST DO ALL OF
THE THINGS THAT I DO ALREADY,
BUT I WOULD DO THEM IN A MUCH
SMALLER WAY.
( LAUGHTER )
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> James: SMALL--
>> YEAH, LESS PRESSURE.
>> James: LESS PRESSURE-- LESS
PRESSURE?
WELL, LET'S SEE IF YOU CAN DO IT
NOW, OKAY, BECAUSE THERE ARE
OBVIOUSLY PEOPLE HERE WHO ARE
MORE INTERESTED IN YOU ANYWAY,
SO GO FOR IT.
GO ON, YEAH, GO!
>> NO.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: YEAH, YEAH.
>> NO, NO.
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
I WON'T TAKE OVER.
>> James: WELL, ARE YOU GOING TO
HAVE TO, YOU KNOW WHY?
>> WHY.
>> James: BECAUSE I QUIT, OKAY?
( BOOING )
NO, I QUIT!
NO, NO ( BLEEP ) OFF!
NO!
I'M DONE!
THIS IS OVER!
I AM UP TO HERE WITH THIS
( BLEEP ).
( LAUGHTER )
NIGHT AFTER NIGHT AFTER NIGHT,
COMING THROUGH THAT CURTAIN--
OH, YOU WANT ANOTHER TRUMP JOKE,
SITTING AT A DESK, DOING A DESK
PIECE, GOING OUT SINGING IN THE
CAR WITH ( BLEEP ) BRITNEY
( BLEEP ) SPEARS, I'M DONE, I'M
DONE, OKAY!
IT'S OVER!
I'M OUT, OKAY, YOU WANT TO KNOW
MY FAVORITE COLOR?
THAT'S MY FAVORITE COLOR, OKAY?
( LAUGHTER )
THAT'S MY FAVORITE COLOR.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
SCREW YOU, SCREW YOU AND SCREW
YOU, OKAY?
I'M OUT!
GET ME OUT OF HERE!
GET OUT OF HERE.
I'M DONE.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> ALL RIGHT THEN, WHEN WE COME
BACK I'LL BE TALKING TO CHELSEA
PERETTI AND WE'LL GET A SNEAK
PEEK AT MY AMAZING DAY WITH THE
HARLEM GLOBETROTTERS.
STICK AROUND FOR MORE "LATE,
LATE SHOW" WITH ME, NEIL PATRICK
HARRIS.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
♪ ♪ ♪
(Burke)
At Farmers, we've seen almost
everything,
so we know how to
cover almost anything.
Even Rooftop Parking.
Strange forces at work?
Only if you're referring to
gravity-and we covered it.
Talk to Farmers.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
Julie means more to me
than anything.
And I wanted to ask you
Before I ask her
May I have your permission
to marry her?
You're marrying her and
her whole world
Shop Neil Lane diamond
engagement rings...
...at KAY.
Shop Neil Lane diamond
engagement rings...
Do you want ready to wear
clothing without all the hassle?
You can, with Bounce Dryer
sheets.
We dried one shirt without
Bounce,
and an identical shirt using
Bounce.
The Bounce shirt has fewer
wrinkles, less static,
and more softness and
freshness.
Bounce out wrinkles, Bounce out
static.
NEW Theraflu PowerPods.
The cold and flu fighting
machine.
You put in your machine.
Press the button to brew up
powerful relief.
To defeat your toughest
cold and flu symptoms fast.
NEW Theraflu PowerPods.
Press. Sip. Relief.
You've tried moisturizer
after moisturizer
but one blows them
all out of the water.
Hydro Boost
from Neutrogena®.
With hyaluronic acid
to plump skin cells
so it bounces back.
Neutrogena®
♪ ♪
We all care about amazing taste.
That's why we've been making
the best mayonnaise
for over 100 years.
Hellmann's.
We're on the side of food.
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: WELCOME BACK.
LET'S MEET OUR GUESTS TONIGHT.
SHE STARS ON "BROOKLYN NINE-
NINE," PLEASE WELCOME CHELSEA
PERETTI.
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: HE STARS IN "A SERIES
OF UNFORTUNATE EVENTS," PLEASE
WELCOME NEIL PATRICK HARRIS.
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: THANK YOU FOR BEING
HERE.
THANK YOU FOR COMING TO SEE US.
WE'RE SO THRILLED THAT YOU'RE
HERE.
NOW, CHELSEA, THIS IS YOUR FIRST
TIME HERE ON THE SHOW.
>> IT'S CRAZY, RIGHT?
>> James: WE'RE SO THRILLED
YOU'RE HERE, BUT YOU AND REGGIE,
YOU GO WAY BACK.
HAVE YOU SPENT ANY TIME TOGETHER
RECENTLY?
>> NO, BECAUSE... LAST TIME WE
DID, LIKE, REGGIE DID SOMETHING
REALLY MESSED UP.
>> James: SOUNDS-- CERTAINLY
SOUNDS LIKE THE REGGIE I KNOW.
YEAH, WHAT HAPPENED?
>> IT WAS LIKE, IT WAS REALLY
FREAKY, HE REALLY MESSED WITH
ME, HE HAS A TESLA.
>> James: YES.
>> AND WE WERE HANGING OUT, JUST
GETTING A COFFEE, SOMETHING VERY
CASUAL, NO STRINGS ATTACHED.
( LAUGHTER )
AND WE'RE JUST, AND ALL OF A
SUDDEN HE JUST STOPS THE CAR AND
IT'S LIKE SILENT, SO YOU ALMOST
DON'T EVEN NOTICE IT.
>> James: UH-HUH.
>> AND THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN HE'S
TRYING TO SHOW ME THE FEATURE
WHERE IT GOES FROM LIKE 0 TO 100
REAL QUICK.
>> James: YEAH, WHAT'S IT
CALLED?
INSANE MODE?
>> Reggie: LUDICROUS.
>> James: LUDICROUS MODE.
>> PERFECT NAME, BECAUSE I HAD
MY FEET ON THE DASH BOARD, LIKE
I WASN'T EXPECTING IT.
>> James: SURE.
>> ANYWAY, I WAS ENRAGED.
>> James: YEAH.
( LAUGHTER )
>> GREAT FEATURE I GUESS, FOR
WHAT?
>> James: AND YOU LIVE IN LOS
ANGELES, WHEN DO YOU EVER GET TO
TRAVEL MORE THAN 100 FEET?
>> YEAH, IT'S STOP AND GO
TRAFFIC.
>> James: HE DID THE SAME TO ME.
HE WENT "CHECK THIS OUT" AND MY
WHOLE FACE JUST WENT.
( LAUGHTER )
>> YEAH, SO AT LEAST HE SAID
"CHECK THIS OUT."
( LAUGHTER )
BECAUSE-- FOR ME IT WAS JUST A
LULL IN CONVERSATION, I'M LIKE
YOU HEARD BIRDS CHIRPING AND
THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN--
( LAUGHTER )
VERY SCARY.
>> James: WELL, WE'RE THRILLED
THAT HE DIDN'T PUT YOU OFF BEING
HERE.
NOW, NEIL I WANT TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING WHICH I HAVE
EVER NEVER HAD THE EXPERIENCE
OF, BUT I'M INTERESTED IN.
YOU WERE RECENTLY SUMMONED FOR
JURY DUTY.
>> I WAS.
YOU--
>> James: NO, IT'S NEVER
HAPPENED TO ME.
HOW DID IT GO?
>> IT WAS PRETTY EXCITING.
I TRIED TO GET OUT OF IT.
>> James: YES.
>> I ASSUMED THAT WHEN YOU GET
THE THING THAT SAYS YOU HAVE TO
GO THAT THEY SEND THAT TO
EVERYBODY, LIKE SPAM.
>> James: RIGHT.
>> AND THAT THEY JUST HOPE THAT
PEOPLE END UP GOING SO I DIDN'T
GO, AND I WAS ACTUALLY WORKING
ON "A SERIES OF UNFORTUNATE
EVENTS" IN CANADA SO I HAD AN
ACTUAL EXCUSE AND FINALLY THEY
SENT ME A SUMMONS I WILL GO TO
JAIL IF I DON'T ACTUALLY DO
THIS, SO I WENT.
>> James: WOW.
>> AND I SERVED MY JURY DUTY,
AND I MET WITH SOME LAWYERS AND
THERE WAS A CASE ABOUT ASBESTOS
AND THEY HAD TO QUESTION
EVERYONE.
AND I HAD TO RAISE MY HAND AND
SAY, I HAD TO TALK TO THEM ONE-
ON-ONE AND SAY I COULDN'T GO
BECAUSE THIS VERY WEEK I WAS
FLYING TO LOS ANGELES TO BE ON
THE JAMES CORDEN SHOW AND
THEREFORE I WOULDN'T BE
AVAILABLE FOR THE SECOND HALF OF
THE WEEK.
AND THEY SAID, WELL, THAT'S A
PROBLEM BECAUSE THIS IS AN
ACTUAL PROFESSIONAL OPPORTUNITY
AND YOU CAN'T USE WORK AS AN
EXCUSE.
YOU CAN ONLY USE FAMILY
SITUATIONS AS AN EXCUSE.
>> James: RIGHT.
>> AND HE SAID "DO HAVE ANY
FAMILY THAT'S GOING TO BE IN
LOS ANGELES WHILE YOU ARE
THERE?"
AND I SAID "YES, JAMES CORDEN IS
MY SECOND COUSIN."
( LAUGHTER )
AND HE SAID GREAT, YOU'RE FREE
TO GO.
>> James: OH, WOW!
>> SO I DIDN'T HAVE TO SERVE AT
AN ACTUAL JURY OR AGAIN FOR SIX
MORE YEARS.
SO, THANK YOU.
( APPLAUSE )
>> James: YOU'RE MORE THAN
WELCOME.
>> WITHOUT YOU NONE OF THIS
WOULD HAVE HAPPENED.
>> James: I HAVE NEVER GOT ONE
OF THE SUMMONS THING, HAVE YOU
EVER DONE IT.
>> I JUST DID, I HAD PUT IT OFF
ALSO FOR BREAST FEEDING.
>> I TRIED THAT.
I TRIED THAT, IT DIDN'T WORK.
>> YEAH, SO I PUSHED IT AND
PUSHED IT AND THEN AT A CERTAIN
POINT, THEY'RE LIKE SURELY
YOU'RE DONE.
>> James: YEAH.
( LAUGHTER )
SO I WENT IN, BUT THEN I ALSO--
>> YOUR NAME IS SHIRLEY?
>> YEAH, SHIRLEY, LEGALLY, MY
NAME IS SHIRLEY.
BUT THEN I WAS LIKE, WHY AM I
FIGHTING THIS?
THIS SHOULD BE A GREAT HONOR.
>> James: YES, YEAH.
>> TO RESHAPE THE JUDICIAL
SYSTEM THROUGH MY JUDGEMENT.
>> YEAH.
>> James: SURE, YEAH.
>> SO I SAID-- I HAD NO CHOICE--
SO I WENT IN AND IT WAS JUST A
HUGE ROOM OF PEOPLE COUGHING AND
I--
( LAUGHTER )
I WAS IN A PANIC.
SO I WENT AND SAT OFF TO THE
SIDE AND I ACTUALLY WOUND UP
WORKING ON THIS SCRIPT THAT I'M
WRITING, VERY L.A. VERSION OF
JURY DUTY.
THEN I RAN INTO A FRIEND AND WE
WENT OUT TO LUNCH AND IT WOUND
UP BEING THE MOST SOCIAL DAY
I'VE HAD, YOU KNOW, JUST LIKE
ONE OF THE BEST DAYS OF MY LIFE.
>> James: OH!
>> YEAH.
>> James: THERE YOU GO, WHAT A
TREAT.
WELL, NOTHING TO FEAR.
>> WHO KNEW?
>> James: NOTHING TO FEAR.
>> NO, IT WAS GREAT.
>> James: THAT'S WONDERFUL.
NEIL I HAVE TO CONGRATULATE YOU
ON SEASON THREE OF "A SERIES OF
UNFORTUNATE EVENTS."
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> THANK YOU.
>> James: I LOVE THE SHOW.
IT'S VERY POPULAR NOW.
>> THANKS.
>> James: NOW, THIS IS IT?
YOU'RE DONE, YOU HAVE SHOT THEM
ALL.
ARE YOU GOING TO MISS PLAYING
THIS CHARACTER?
>> I WILL, YEAH, I'M JUST SUPER
STOKED.
I HAVE GOTTEN TO DO A TV SERIES
IN THE PAST AND I THINK THERE'S
SOMETHING GREAT ABOUT DOING
SOMETHING ON NETFLIX THAT IS ON
SORT OF THE STREAMING MEDIA VIBE
FOR REAL.
I FEEL LIKE "A SERIES OF
UNFORTUNATE EVENTS" GETS TO BE
MORE OF A PIECE OF ART, IF THAT
MAKES ANY SENSE.
>> James: FOR SURE.
>> IT'S NOT A SHOW YOU KEEP
CHURNING OUT EPISODES THAT YOU
HOPE CONTINUES AND GET TO DID IT
FOR ANOTHER SEASON.
IT WAS ALWAYS GOING TO BE THREE
SEASONS TO COVER THE 13 BOOKS
THAT DANIEL HANDLER WROTE.
AND SO, THOSE BOOKS ON AN ACTUAL
BOOKSHELF I THINK THESE EPISODES
CAN HOLD UP ON A VIRTUAL
BOOKSHELF.
AND THE DESIGN OF IT IS REALLY
FANTASTIC AND IT'S FOR KIDS BUT
NOT JUST FOR KIDS.
>> James: YEAH.
>> BARRY SONNENFELD IS THE HEAD
BEHIND IT AND I PLAYED OLAF WHO
IS A TOTAL ( BLEEP ).
( LAUGHTER )
>> James: WELL, YOU'RE SO GREAT.
SO MANY DIFFERENT STRANDS OF
CHARACTERS.
IT'S REALLY BRILLIANT.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT A CLIP FROM
"A SERIES OF UNFORTUNATE
EVENTS."
SEASON THREE IS STREAMING RIGHT
NOW ON NETFLIX.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> NOT IN THE FORM OF A SONG.
>> I'M INNOCENT.
>> VERY WELL.
>> I'M SO INCREDIBLY INNOCENT
THAT THE WORD INNOCENT SHOULD BE
WRITTEN ON MY FACE.
THE "I" WOULD STAND FOR "I'M
INNOCENT."
THE "N" WOULD STAND FOR "NOTHING
WRONG," WHICH IS WHAT I HAVE
DONE.
THE "A" WOULD STAND FOR--
>> THAT'S NOT HOW YOU SPELL
INNOCENT.
>> I'M SURE SPELLING DOESN'T
COUNT.
>> SPELLING COUNTS.
>> WELL THEN INNOCENT SHOULD BE
SPELLED O-L-A-F BECAUSE THAT IS
HOW I PLEAD.
>> James: STICK AROUND, MORE
WITH THESE TWO WHEN WE COME
BACK.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
♪ ♪ ♪
No more excuses
with Cologuard.
We all make excuses for the
things we don't want to do.
But when it comes to
colon cancer screening...
I'm not doin' that.
I eat plenty of kale.
Ahem, as I was saying...
...with Cologuard,
you don't need an excuse...
All that prep?
No thanks.
That drink tastes horrible!
But...there's no
prep with Cologuard...
I can't take the
time off work.
Who has two days?
And I feel fine -
no symptoms!
Everybody, listen!
All you need is a
trip to the bathroom.
If you're 50 or older
and at average risk,
Cologuard is the
noninvasive option
that finds 92%
of colon cancers.
You just get the
kit in the mail,
go to the bathroom,
collect your sample,
then ship it to the lab!
This is your year!
Own it!
Cologuard is not right
for everyone.
It is not for high
risk individuals,
including those with a
history of colon cancer
or precancer, IBD, certain
hereditary cancer syndromes,
or a family history
of colon cancer.
Ask your doctor if Cologuard
is right for you.
Covered by Medicare and
most major insurers.
♪(oh oh oh oh)
It's taking over.♪
Ask♪There's no escape...♪ard
is right for you.
♪...You better get moving. Ready
or not♪
♪...It's about to go down here
it comes now♪
♪...Get ready (oh oh oh oh), Get
ready♪
♪...Moving. Ready or not♪
♪...Get ready (oh oh oh oh)♪
New Galaxy. Free Buds.
Music to your ears.
Get free Galaxy Buds when you
pre-order Galaxy S10 or S10+.
Chili's 3 for $10 presents
our signature
sirloin steak.
Aged to perfection
and served with
a starter and drink
for just $10.
Out with the cousins
and Aunt Nancy,
who's politely described
as a "free spirit."
Together We Chili's.
How's your cough?
I'm good. I took 12-hour Mucinex
and sent it far away.
Hey buddy, have you seen a
nice woman with a cough?
Woahhh!
Mucinex DM releases fast and
lasts 12-hours, not 4.
Send coughs far away all day.
(ding)
Hey, who are you?
Oh, hey Jeff, I'm a car thief...
What?!
I'm here to
steal your car because,
well, that's my job.
What?
What??
WHAT?!
(laughing)
What??
WHAT?!
What?!
[crash]
WHAT?!
Haha, it happens.
And if you've got
cut-rate car insurance,
paying for this could
feel like getting robbed twice.
So get Allstate...
and be better protected
from Mayhem...
like me.
♪
>> ATTENTION SQUAD!
PUT YOUR HANDS TOGETHER FOR THE
LONG ANTICIPATED REUNION OF
D.D.C.
>> D.D.C.!
>> D.D.
>> C!
>> WHAT IS HELL IS THE D.D.C.?
>> I DON'T KNOW, BUT I LOVE IT!
>> THE D.D.C. IS THE DOPE DEMO
CREW.
OUR 20 YEAR HIGH SCHOOL REUNION
IS TONIGHT AND THE PARTY IS 90s
THEMED SO WE ARE DRESSING THE
WAY WE DID BACK THEN A.K.A.
HELLA FRESH.
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: THAT WAS A CLIP FROM
"BROOKLYN NINE-NINE" WHICH AIRS
THURSDAYS AT 9:00 ON NBC.
CONGRATULATIONS ON THE SHOW.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> THANK YOU.
>> James: SO WONDERFUL.
ON TONIGHT'S EPISODE, ON
TONIGHT'S EPISODE YOU ANNOUNCE
THAT YOU ARE LEAVING THE "NINE
NINE."
NEXT WEEK IS GOING TO BE YOUR
LAST EPISODE.
>> IT IS, YEAH.
>> James: HOW DO YOU FEEL?
EMOTIONAL FILMING FINAL SHOWS?
>> YOU'RE MAKING ME FEEL ALARMED
ABOUT IT, BUT I ALREADY KNOW.
>> IS THAT FOR REAL OR IS THAT
JUST A PLOT LINE?
>> James: NO, IT'S FOR REAL.
>> REALLY?
WOW, THAT SUCKS.
>> I KNOW, BUT YOU KNOW, LIFE IS
FULL OF SO MANY TWISTS AND
TURNS.
>> James: FOR SURE.
>> YOU EVER THOUGHT ABOUT IT
THAT WAY?
>> James: OH YEAH, BIG TIME.
BUT HOW DID YOU FEEL FILMING
THESE LAST EPISODES?
>> IT WAS KIND OF EMO. AT TIMES.
( LAUGHTER )
BUT YOU KNOW, ALSO IT'S A COMEDY
SO YOU ARE ABLE TO LAUGH THROUGH
THE TOUGH SPOTS, YOU KNOW.
>> James: SURE.
>> BUT DEFINITELY ME AND ANDY
WERE LIKE IN THIS SCENE, AND WE
HAD FOR SOME REASON PROBABLY
BECAUSE WE ARE COMEDIANS AND
DIDN'T TALK ABOUT OUR FEELINGS,
WE DIDN'T TALK ABOUT THEM SO
THEY WE WERE IN THE SCENE AND
OUR CHARACTERS WERE PROCESSING
IT AND WE MIGHT HAVE PUT A
LITTLE TOO MUCH DRAMA INTO IT.
BUT IT WAS GOOD, IT WAS VERY
SWEET, AND THEN PEOPLE WERE
GETTING VERKLEMPT AND STUFF.
>> James: BUT YOU WILL POP BACK
IN AT CERTAIN POINTS.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> James: IT'S NOT THE END-END.
>> NO, MAN, UNLESS THE WORLD
ENDS WHICH FEELS INCREASINGLY
POSSIBLE.
>> James: FOR SURE.
( LAUGHTER )
>> YEAH.
>> James: THERE IS NO DENYING
THAT.
>> THAT PUTS IT ALL IN
PERSPECTIVE.
>> James: NOW, NEIL, YOU AS WE
ALL KNOW YOU HAVE WON MANY, MANY
AWARDS, YOU HAVE HAD A
REMARKABLE CAREER.
ALTHOUGH ONE OF THE BIGGEST
THINGS YOU MAY HAVE WON, WHICH I
REALLY THINK IS INCREDIBLE, IS
YOU WON A GUACAMOLE OFF AT THE
HOME OF "SURVIVOR" HOST JEFF
PROBST.
WHICH HONESTLY IS SOMETHING I
WOULD NEVER THOUGHT I WOULD SAY
OUT LOUD.
>> YEAH.
>> James: HOW DO YOU WIN THIS?
>> I TRY AND PUT THAT SENTENCE
INTO AS MANY CONVERSATIONS AS I
POSSIBLY CAN.
>> James: FOR SURE.
>> JEFF PROBST LOVES THE GAMES,
AS YOU KNOW.
HE HOSTS THEM AND HE HAS GAME
NIGHT SOMETIME.
AND THIS IS YEARS AGO, BUT HE
INVITED US AND SAID AS AN ADDED
CHALLENGE, EVERYONE BRING
GUACAMOLE AND WE WILL HAVE A
SORT OF GUACAMOLE OFF.
I AM FROM SMALL TOWN NEW MEXICO,
YO.
GUACAMOLE IS IN MY BLOOD.
>> James: SO, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IT'S A TASTE TEST?
>> TASTE TEST, PEOPLE BROUGHT
THEIR DIFFERENT GUACAMOLES,
DIDN'T SAY WHOSE WAS WHOSE, I
THINK THEY PUT THEM INTO THIS
SAME SORT OF CONTAINERS.
>> SO, YOU HAD TO GUESS WHICH
CAUCASIAN MADE THE GUACAMOLE?
( LAUGHTER )
>> I THINK IT WAS A MIXED GROUP,
I WILL HAVE YOU KNOW, MADAME.
>> I'M SORRY, THAT WAS
PRESUMPTUOUS, THAT WAS
PRESUMPTUOUS.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE BROUGHT CRAZY
ONES LIKE WEIRD MANGO GUAC WITH
CRICKETS AND...
>> James: OH, NO, NO, NO, NO.
>> MY GRANDMA USED TO PUT
CHOPPED UP HARD BOILED EGG IN
HER GUAC AND WAS SO 50s NASTY.
>> James: THAT IS BAD NEWS.
BUT YOU HAVE SOME INTERESTING
EATING HABITS I WANT TO TALK TO
YOU ABOUT BECAUSE YOU RECENTLY
POSTED A PHOTO ON THE INTERNET
ABOUT HOW YOU EAT CAKE.
>> YES.
>> James: AND IT TURNED OUT TO
BE VERY CONTROVERSIAL.
IT MADE MAJOR NEWS, OKAY.
SO "PEOPLE" MAGAZINE WROTE
"CHELSEA PERETTI HAS POLARIZED
THE INTERNET WITH HER CAKE-
EATING METHOD."
>> YES.
>> WHAT?
>> James: "THE TODAY SHOW" RAN A
SEGMENT SAYING "IS THERE A RIGHT
WAY TO EAT CAKE?
CELEBS TWEET SPARKS A DESSERT
DEBATE."
AND THEN "TIME MAGAZINE."
>> WHAT?
( LAUGHTER )
>> James: WROTE "A SHOCKING
APPROACH TO EATING CAKE HAS
SPARKED AN IMPORTANT VIRAL
DEBATE FOR OUR TIMES."
>> IMPORTANT!
>> James: NOW, HERE IS THE POST.
YOU PUT "THIS IS HOW I EAT CAKE,
NOT THAT INTO FROSTING," OKAY.
>> YEAH.
ANYONE?
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: DON'T LIE.
>> THAT'S MY SECTION RIGHT
THERE.
>> James: WERE YOU SURPRISED
ABOUT THIS OUTRAGE?
>> NO, I THINK EVERYTHING I DO
IS VERY IMPORTANT.
( LAUGHTER )
NO, BUT I DID, YOU KNOW, I ONCE
FAMOUSLY ALSO SAID THAT PIZZA IS
OVERRATED, SO THIS--
>> James: OKAY, NOW, WAIT.
>> WHO IS WITH ME?
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: NOW, LISTEN.
>> EVEN STILL.
>> James: HANG ON.
I WILL JOKE WITH YOU ABOUT THIS.
>> I KNOW, BECAUSE IT'S A CULT,
PIZZA IS A CULT.
>> IT'S THE CULT OF THINGS THAT
ARE ( BLEEP ) DELICIOUS!
>> James: YES.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> SOMETIMES.
SOMETIMES.
>> James: BUT CAN I ASK, WHY NOT
GET A CAKE SANS FROSTING, WHICH
IS FRENCH FOR NONE?
>> HERE IS THE THING I SAID NOT
THAT INTO FROSTING.
YOU WILL SEE ON THE LEFT A BIT
OF FROSTING WAS EATEN.
IT WAS TAKEN A BIT OUT OF, WELL,
NOT OUT OF CONTEXT IT WAS JUST
TAKEN INCORRECTLY BECAUSE I
CLEARLY ATE SOME OF THE
FROSTING, IF YOU GET--
>> James: YOU LIKE A LITTLE DAB.
>> A DAB.
>> James: LIKE A SOY SAUCE ON A
SUSHI.
>> YES, HAVE A LITTLE TASTE, BE
REFINED, I DON'T LIKE A TWO INCH
THICK, HARD--
( LAUGHTER )
I DON'T LIKE--
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
GUYS, GUYS-- BUT I DON'T LIKE
WHEN IT'S LIKE A CHUNK OF
BUTTER.
>> James: NO, I'M WITH YOU ON
THAT.
>> I LIKE THOSE SOFT FROSTINGS.
I DON'T KNOW THE NAME.
>> WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS ON
CUPCAKES?
>> UM, I LIKE THEM BUT I DON'T
LIKE WHEN THEY ARE HARD.
WHOOO, GIRL!
>> James: WHAT ABOUT--
>> HERE'S WHAT I WILL SAY.
HERE IS A GREAT THING I LEARNED
WITH THE CUPCAKE, IT IS NOT
UNIQUE HOW PEOPLE DO IT, BUT YOU
TAKE OFF THE WRAPPER AND RIP OFF
THE BOTTOM HALF AND SET IT ON
THE TOP AND THEN FLIP THE WHOLE
THING OVER AND IT IS SORT OF
LIKE A CUPCAKE SANDWICH.
>> OKAY, YOU KNOW I THOUGHT WERE
YOU GOING TO SAY.
NO, I THOUGHT WERE YOU GOING TO
SAY YOU TAKE THE WRAPPER OFF
BECAUSE THERE IS WHAT I DO, AND
WIPE OFF HALF OF THE FROSTING.
THAT IS WHAT I DO.
I JUST DON'T LIKE TOO MUCH.
IT IS TOO INTENSE, PEOPLE GO TOO
FAR, LIKE DEATH BY CHOCOLATE.
IT'S LIKE, ALL RIGHT, WE DON'T
NEED TO DIE.
( LAUGHTER )
I'VE BEEN WATCHING, TO PANDER,
ONE OF THOSE BRITISH, LIKE,
BAKING SHOWS?
>> James: "THE GREAT BRITISH
BAKING SHOW."
SINGLE GREATEST SHOW ON TV.
>> IT IS A GREAT SHOW, BUT THE
DESSERT, THEY WILL BE LIKE "YOU
HAVE TO DO A CLASSIC ENGLISH
TRIFLE" OR LIKE "POUGHKEEPSIE
SOMETHING."
I DON'T KNOW THE NAMES, BUT ALL
THESE CLASSIC DESSERTS AND THEN
THEY ARE JUDGING THEM SO CLOSELY
THAT IT IS LIKE ALL THE
DESSERTS, TRADITIONAL ENGLISH
DESSERT ARE KIND OF GROSS.
DON'T YOU THINK, A LOT OF THEM?
>> James: NO.
I WOULD DISAGREE WITH YOU.
LIKE WHAT?
>> LIKE EVERYTHING ON THAT SHOW.
( LAUGHTER )
>> James: ON THE BAKEOFF?
>> LIKE, I REALIZE WATCHING IT,
I'M LIKE, I MEAN THIS IS SO
ENTERTAINING, IT IS GRIPPING.
BUT, BUT I DON'T WANT TO TRY ONE
BITE.
>> James: OH, COME ON.
SOME OF RAJUL'S SHOWSTOPPERS,
YOU WOULD TAKE A FORK OF RAJUL
SHOW STOPPER.
>> NO.
>> James: YES, YOU WOULD.
>> I DID THE GIRL WITH THAT
BRIGHT PINK BLUSH.
>> James: YES, I LOVED HER.
I TELL YOU WHAT I WOULD LOVE TO
SEE: YOU AS A JUDGE.
>> I WOULD LOVE IT!
>> James: STICK AROUND.
MORE WITH THESE TWO WHEN WE COME
BACK.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
♪ ♪ ♪
wing you?
For adults with moderately
to severely active
Crohn's disease,
STELARA® works differently.
Studies showed
relief and remission,
with dosing every 8 weeks.
STELARA® may lower your
ability to fight infections
and may increase your risk
of infections and cancer.
Some serious infections
require hospitalization.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor if
you have an infection
or flu-like symptoms or sores,
have had cancer, or
develop new skin growths,
or if anyone in your house
needs or recently
had a vaccine.
Alert your doctor of new
or worsening problems,
including headaches, seizures,
confusion and vision problems.
These may be signs of a rare,
potentially fatal
brain condition.
Some serious allergic reactions
and lung inflammation
can occur.
Talk to your doctor today,
and learn how
Janssen can help you
explore cost support options.
Remission can start
with STELARA®.
I can't believe it.
That we just
hit the motherlode
of soft-serve ice cream?
I got cones,
anybody wants one!
Oh, yeah!
Get ya some!
No, I can't believe how
easy it was to save hundreds
of dollars on my car
insurance with GEICO.
Ed!
We struck sprinkles!
[cheers]
Believe it.
GEICO could save
you fifteen percent
or more on
car insurance.
GEICO could save
you fifteen percent
Lobsterfest is on at Red Lobster
With the most lobster dishes
of year
Like Lobster Lover's Dream
With butter-poached, creamy
and roasted lobster.
Or new crispy, coconutty
Lobster in Paradise.
New Ultimate Lobsterfest
Surf & Turf is here too.
It's time to Lobsterfest,
so hurry in.
Went to Ancestry, I put in the
names of my grandparents first.
It gave me a leaf
almost right away.
Within a few days,
I went from knowing
almost nothing to holy crow,
I'm related to
George Washington.
I didn't know that using
Ancestry would be so easy.
Introducing high-rise
Rockstar 24/7 denim
now with sculpt.
Hurry in to Old Navy for
all jeans on sale
up to fifty percent off.
With kids from eight dollars,
adults from fifteen dollars,
only at Old Navy.
WHY ARE ALL THESE BUSINESS
OWNERS SO EXCITED?
WE'RE GOING TO COMCAST.
IT'S AHEAD OF THE GAME,
AHEAD OF THE CURVE.
COMCAST BUSINESS IS FOR ME.
IT'S SWITCH AND SAVE DAYS
AT COMCAST BUSINESS.
RIGHT NOW, GET FAST,
RELIABLE INTERNET
FOR $49.95 A MONTH
AND SAVE $600 A YEAR.
JUST ONE MORE WAY WE TAKE
YOUR BUSINESS BEYOND.
BUT HURRY, SWITCH AND
SAVE DAYS ENDS APRIL 7TH.
I CAN'T WAIT TO GO HOME
AND TELL EVERYONE ABOUT IT.
I JUST WANNA GET IT RIGHT NOW.
GUESS WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
(LAUGHING)
CALL TODAY.
COMCAST BUSINESS.
BEYOND FAST.
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: WELCOME BACK.
REGGIE, DO YOU HAVE A QUESTION
FOR ANY OF OUR GUESTS THIS
EVENING?
>> Reggie: YES, I DO.
TONIGHT'S QUESTION GOES TO...
( DRUM ROLL )
NEIL PATRICK PERETTI.
>> INTERESTING.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> Reggie: OKAY, SO IF YOU GUYS
WERE, IF YOU GUYS WERE KIND OF
BLACKED OUT FOR SOME REASON LIKE
NATURALISTIC REASONS AND YOU
WOKE UP AND YOU COULD SMELL A
REALLY INTENSE, KIND OF LIKE A
PERFUMIC VINYL NYLON SMELL, BUT
YOU COULDN'T REALLY SEE VERY
WELL AND YOU HEARD KIDS PLAYING
IN THE DISTANCE, WHERE DO YOU
THINK YOU WOULD BE?
>> NOW I'M STARTING TO GUESS
YOUR BASEMENT.
( LAUGHTER )
DOES THAT FEEL RIGHT?
>> THAT'S WHAT I WAS GOING TO
SAY, TOO.
>> Reggie: OH, ACTUALLY IT'S MY
FOYER BUT I WILL TAKE IT.
>> James: IT'S SO CLOSE, BUT
CORRECT, PLEASE THANK OUR
WONDERFUL GUESTS, CHELSEA
PERETTI, NEIL PATRICK HARRIS.
WHEN WE COME BACK ADAM NEWMAN
HAS GOT SOME STAND UP COMEDY FOR
US.
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
♪
(Butcher)
We both know you're not just
looking for pork chops.
You're searching
for something more...
...red-blooded.
Right this way.
You thirst for adrenaline,
you hunger for raw power.
Well, you've come
to the right place.
The road is yours, dig in.
The Russells travel to swim
meets every Saturday.
But now... it's Thursday.
Good thing they discovered Gain
Flings.
The only detergent with
concentrated Gain,
Oxi Boost, and Febreze Odor
Remover.
Try New Improved Gain Flings.
When nighttime
nasal congestion closes in,
Breathe Right strips
are designed to simply
open your nose right back up.
♪
Breathe better. Sleep better.
Breathe Right.
Live from the Starlite Lounge.
♪ One plus one equals
too little too late ♪
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]
Hi, Ted Danson, I'm here for my
appointment
No matter who you are,
it's important to go for an
annual check-up,
and when you do remember to be
open and honest
with your doctor about how
you're feeling.
Because how you're doing
emotionally,
affects your physical health -
and vice versa
Mr. Danson, would you mind?
I love doing this
Thanks, but I just need you to
fill out the medical history.
That's embarrassing
Go in for your annual check-up,
and check in physically and
emotionally
Cigna. Together all the way.
Do I have to do the age part?
Okay
I love my babies,
love my boys.
Since I'm a truck driver,
you know there's times
that I'm gone for,
like, three weeks at a time.
Even if I'm 3,000 miles away,
I'm connected with my boys.
Every day I can
video chat with them.
I could be in the middle
of Wyoming.
Even if I'm like waaay...
out here,
I can still reach my kids.
Baby, you-- you see me?
(sons)
Hey, Daddy!
(VO)
There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best network
now comes with Apple Music on us
and $300 off our best phones.
Only on Verizon.
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: WELCOME BACK.
OUR NEXT GUEST IS A VERY
TALENTED STANDUP COMEDIAN WILL
BE PERFORMING LIVE FEBRUARY 5
THROUGH 9 AT THE ACME COMEDY
CLUB IN MINNEAPOLIS, MINNESOTA.
PLEASE WELCOME THE DELIGHTFUL
ADAM NEWMAN.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
THAT WAS MY PARENT'S WEDDING
SONG, THANKS FOR HAVING THAT
QUEUED UP, GUYS.
( LAUGHTER )
I JUST TURNED 36-YEARS-OLD AND I
DON'T HAVE A SINGLE CHEST HAIR
YET.
( LAUGHTER )
IS IT COMING?
DID I MISS IT?
LIKE, I THOUGHT I WOULD HAVE
SOMETHING BY NOW, YOU KNOW, LIKE
MY LITTLE BROTHER STARTED
GETTING IT AT LIKE 14, YOU KNOW,
MY DAD HAS IT, MY MOM HAS TONS
OF IT.
( LAUGHTER )
LIKE I THOUGHT MAYBE BY NOW I'D
HAVE SOMETHING.
I HAVE NO CHEST HAIR.
YOU KNOW WHAT I DO HAVE THOUGH,
I HAVE NIPPLES THAT LOOK LIKE
DADDY LONG LEGS, I HAVE THAT.
( LAUGHTER )
TWO LITTLE PINK DOTS WITH EIGHT
LITTLE HAIRS AROUND EACH ONE,
THAT'S NOT A VERY GOOD LOOK.
I WOULD SHAVE THEM BUT THEY WILL
COME BACK AS TARANTULAS, I KNOW
IT.
( LAUGHTER )
MY SHIRT OFF I'M LIKE A YOUNG
E.T.
( LAUGHTER )
THAT'S WHAT I'M DEALING WITH
RIGHT NOW.
GOT NO CHEST HAIR, I'M 6'2, 110
POUNDS, MEDICAL TERM FOR THAT IS
GROSS.
( LAUGHTER )
IT'S NOT GREAT UNDER THIS
SWEATER.
YOU THINK BEING THAT THIN I
WOULD HAVE SOME DEFINITION, BUT
I HAVE NOTHING.
NO ABS AT ALL AND I WANT THEM.
AND I KNOW IT'S CHEESY BUT I
LOVE ABS.
I THINK THEY ARE BEAUTIFUL AND I
PROMISE YOU I WOULD BE A
RESPONSIBLE AB OWNER, OKAY.
( LAUGHTER )
I WOULD, I WOULD, NO SHIRTLESS
SELFIES AT THE BEACH, OR
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
I WOULD TREAT ABS THE WAY THEY
ARE SUPPOSED TO BE TREATED.
THEY SHOULD BE TREATED LIKE A
FINE CHINA.
( LAUGHTER )
YOU ONLY BUST THEM OUT FOR VERY
SPECIAL OCCASIONS AND THEN
EVERYBODY EATS OFF OF THEM.
( LAUGHTER )
THAT IS WHAT I WOULD DO.
( APPLAUSE )
I THOUGHT I HAD ABS WHEN I WAS A
KID, I REMEMBER GOING TO THE
DOCTOR WHEN I WAS 16 AND THE
DOCTOR WAS LIKE "YOU NEED TO
GAIN WEIGHT AND EAT PROTEIN."
AND I WAS LIKE "I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU ARE TALKING ABOUT, I
GOT A SIX PACK."
( LAUGHTER )
AND HE WAS LIKE "YOU DO NOT HAVE
A SIX PACK, YOU ARE SO THIN YOU
CAN SEE YOUR INTESTINES THROUGH
YOUR SKIN, THAT IS WHAT THAT
IS."
( LAUGHTER )
I DO GO THE GYM THOUGH.
I GO TO THE GYM AND I WORK ON
IT, I GO TO A JUDGEMENT-FREE
ZONE GYM WHICH I APPRECIATE.
( LAUGHTER )
I THINK "NO JUDGEMENT" IS A
GREAT SLOGAN FOR A GYM.
I THINK NO JUDGEMENT IS AN EVEN
BETTER SLOGAN FOR A BUFFET AND I
WILL TELL YOU WHY.
( LAUGHTER )
WHEN I'M AT THE GYM AND I FEEL
LIKE I'M BEING JUDGED, IT IS
LIKE, I KNOW, I'M HERE TO WORK
ON IT, I KNOW.
WHEN I'M AT A BUFFET DON'T JUDGE
ME.
THE REASON I'M AT THE A BUFFET
IS BECAUSE MY FAVORITE FOOD IS
SUSHI ON A BED OF MASHED
POTATOES COVERED IN FETTUCCINI
ALFREDO.
( LAUGHTER )
WHERE ELSE AM I SUPPOSED TO GET
THAT?
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
OH, YEAH, IT'S A FAVORITE IN THE
SOUTH.
I GO TO THE GYM BECAUSE I'M 36
AND I'M SINGLE AND I THINK THIS
IS MY LAST SHOT, YOU KNOW.
( LAUGHTER )
I MAY NOT HAVE ANOTHER ONE.
I GO TO THE GYM.
I DON'T WANT TO DO DATING APPS
THIS TIME, LIKE I WANT TO MEET
SOMEBODY IN REAL LIFE, I WANT TO
MEET SOMEONE AT A BAR OR A PARTY
OR FRIEND OF A FRIEND, YOU KNOW.
BECAUSE EVERY TIME I THINK I
WILL MEET SOMEBODY I GET
CORNERED BY SOME GUY INTO THE
WORST CONVERSATION I HAVE EVER
BEEN IN.
LIKE, I WAS AT THIS PARTY WITH A
LOT OF COOL YOUNG PEOPLE I'M
GOING TO MEET SOMEBODY AND THIS
GUY LASERED IN ON ME AND WAS
LAKE "HEY, MAN, YOU KNOW THEY'RE
NOT MAKING PENNIES ANY MORE
BECAUSE THE COST IS TOO MUCH TO
MAKE EACH PENNY?"
I WAS LIKE WOW, THAT'S REALLY
BORING.
( LAUGHTER )
I WISH I WAS TALKING TO A GIRL.
I DON'T WANT TO BE IN THAT
CONVERSATION.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT APP TO
START WITH NOW, SINCE THE LAST
TIME I WAS ON DATING APPS IT'S
BEEN THREE YEARS, LAST TIME,
TINDER HAS TURNED INTO JUST LIKE
THE GROSS, DIRTY, SEX HOOKUP
SITE.
SO I LIKE THAT ONE BUT THE OTHER
ONES LIKE WHERE DO YOU EVEN
START?
( LAUGHTER )
I WENT ON ONE ONLINE DATE THAT
WENT GREAT.
IT WAS SO GOOD.
LIKE FIRST DATE, THINGS WENT
GREAT.
WE WENT BACK TO HER APARTMENT,
CLOTHES ARE COMING OFF AND SHE
STOPPED ME AND SAID "BEFORE WE
GO ANY FURTHER THERE IS
SOMETHING I HAVE TO TELL YOU."
AND THAT IS NEVER GOOD, RIGHT.
( LAUGHTER )
NOBODY HAS EVER STOPPED YOU
BEFORE THE FIRST TIME YOU SLEEP
TOGETHER TO BE LIKE "HEY, BEFORE
WE GO ANY FURTHER, SURPRISE I'M
A BILLIONAIRE, NOW GET IT."
( LAUGHTER )
RIGHT LIKE DON'T TELL ME
SOMETHING YOU DON'T WANT.
WHATEVER IT IS, I LIKE YOU A
LOT, TELL ME ANYTHING.
SHE IS LIKE I NEED YOU TO KNOW
BEFORE WE GO ANY FURTHER I'M NOT
ON BIRTH CONTROL.
I WAS LIKE, WHO CARES?
THAT IS FINE, I EXPECT TO USE
PROTECTION, I MET YOU AN HOUR
AGO.
( LAUGHTER )
YOU EXPECT TO USE CONDOMS WITH
SOMEONE YOU JUST MET.
AND I HAVE HAD MY SCARES, I
DON'T KNOW IF YOU HAVE HAD
SCARES.
I HAVE BEEN TO EMERGENCY ROOM
TWICE.
EMERGENCY ROOM BEING LIKE, WHAT
IS WRONG WITH IT?
AND BOTH TIMES THEY SENT ME HOME
WITH A BENADRYL AND SAID
"SOMETIMES THEY JUST LOOK
WEIRD."
( LAUGHTER )
I DON'T KNOW WHY PEOPLE MAKE
SUCH A BIG DEAL OUT OF CONDOMS
ANYWAY.
HAVING SEX WITH A CONDOM IS NOT
THAT BAD.
HAVING SEX WITH A CONDOM IS LIKE
DRIVING WITHOUT G.P.S., YOU
KNOW.
IT TAKES A LITTLE EXTRA
CONCENTRATION BUT I'LL GET THERE
EVENTUALLY.
( LAUGHTER )
AND EVEN IF YOU DON'T, YOU KNOW,
LIKE AT LEAST YOU WENT FOR A
NICE DRIVE.
( LAUGHTER )
THAT IS IT FOR ME, I'M OUT OF
HERE.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: ADAM NEWMAN,
EVERYBODY.
SEE HIM AT THE ACME COMEDY CLUB
IN MINNEAPOLIS.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK!
THAT WAS GREAT.
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
♪(oh oh oh oh)
It's taking over.♪
♪There's no escape...♪
♪...You better get moving. Ready
or not♪
♪...It's about to go down here
it comes now♪
♪...Get ready (oh oh oh oh), Get
ready♪
♪...Moving. Ready or not♪
♪...Get ready (oh oh oh oh)♪
New Galaxy. Free Buds.
Music to your ears.
Get free Galaxy Buds when you
pre-order Galaxy S10 or S10+.
I had this chest cold, but my
medicine kept wearing off.
(coughs)
Ah!
I missed you!
Then I discovered Mucinex.
One pill lasts 12 hours,
and I'm good.
Mucinex releases fast
and lasts 12 hours, not 4.
Let's End This.
(Thunderclap)
If your day doesn't
unfold as predicted.
Unfold this.
New Neutrogena®
Makeup Remover single.
And remove 99% of makeup.
100% rain or shine.
Neutrogena®.
♪ ♪ ♪
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> James: THANKS FOR WATCHING.
WE'LL SEE YOU SOON.
REGGIE, TAKE US HOME.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
♪ ♪ ♪
I love my babies,
love my boys.
Since I'm a truck driver,
you know there's times
that I'm gone for,
like, three weeks at a time.
Even if I'm 3,000 miles away,
I'm connected with my boys.
Every day I can
video chat with them.
I could be in the middle
of Wyoming.
Even if I'm like waaay...
out here,
I can still reach my kids.
Baby, you-- you see me?
(sons)
Hey, Daddy!
(VO)
There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best network
now comes with Apple Music on us
and $300 off our best phones.
Only on Verizon.