>> Announcer: LIVE FROM
NEW YORK CITY, IT'S
"THE WENDY WILLIAMS SHOW."
♪ ♪
NOW, HERE'S JASON BIGGS!
>> Jason: OH, YEAH!
HI IT!
YES!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
YEAH!
SAY HELLO TO MY CAR HOSTS,
STUDIO AUDIENCE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
YEAH!
HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> Audience: HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> Jason: THEY TOLD HER YOU
WOULD DO THAT!
THAT'S SO FANTASTIC SMART CAN I
DO IT AGAIN?
HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> Audience: HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> Jason: THAT IS AMAZING.
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO DON'T KNOW
WHO I AM, WHERE THE HELL HAVE
YOU BEEN FOR THE LAST 20 YEARS?
[LAUGHTER]
KIND A BIG DEAL.
I WAS IN THE "AMERICAN PIE"
FILMS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU.
JUST 20 YEARS AGO.
ALSO, "ORANGE IS THE NEW BLACK."
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU.
MY COSTAR FROM
"ORANGE IS THE NEW BLACK,"
TAYLOR SCHILLING, IS HERE TODAY.
SHE WILL BE MY GUEST, WHICH IS
AWESOME.
I WOULD JUST LIKE TO SAY A
SPECIAL THANK YOU TO WENDY FOR
HAVING ME.
[APPLAUSE]
AND TRUSTING ME.
I HOPE YOU DON'T REGRET THIS.
[LAUGHTER]
I CANNOT MAKE ANY PROMISES.
[LAUGHS]
OKAY, LET'S GET STARTED!
IT'S TIME FOR --
>> Audience: "HOT TOPICS"!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Jason: WOW.
[LAUGHS]
YOU GUYS KNOW IT'S 10:00 A.M.,
RIGHT?
[LAUGHS]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
BEFORE WE START WITH
"HOT TOPICS," CAN I GET THIS YOU
CAN PLEASE?
[HARP MUSIC]
I WOULD LIKE TO POINT OUT -- I
DON'T KNOW IF THIS IS SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD BE PROUD OF, BUT I
WOULD LIKE TO POINT OUT THAT
THESE ARE THE SAME SHOES I HAVE
WORN EVERY TIME THAT I'VE BEEN
ON THIS SHOW.
AND I NOTICED THAT LAST TIME --
SO I DID THE SHOE CAM, WITH
WENDY THE FIRST TIME I WAS HERE.
AND I CAME BACK WITH MY WIFE,
JENNY, DURING THE INTERVIEW I
SAID, "OH, MY GOSH, I HAVE WHEN
THE SHOES ON THIS SHOW BEFORE."
I FEEL LIKE THEY ARE MY LUCKY
WENDY SHOES.
AND OF COURSE THE PURPLE WENDY
SOCKS.
THE BIG NEWS OVERNIGHT IS THE
FIGHT BETWEEN OFFSET AND CHRIS
BROWN OVER 21 SAVAGE POSSIBLY
GETTING DEPORTED.
THERE'S LOTS OF MEMES GOING
AROUND, MOCKING 21.
WHICH OFFENDED HIS FANS,
INCLUDING HIS FRIEND OFFSET.
CHRIS BROWN POSTED WANT OF THE
MEMES AND OFFSET RESPONDED,
SAYING, "MEMES AIN'T FUNNY.
LAME."
THERE YOU GO.
[LAUGHTER]
JUST GIVE ME A FEW MINUTES.
I WILL SETTLE IN.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I'LL GET THERE.
WELL, CHRIS BROWN CLAPPED BACK.
HERE IS WHAT HE SAID.
I NEED A CARD FOR THIS.
HE SAID, "EFF YOU, LITTLE BOY.
BETTER WORRY ABOUT WHAT YOU GOT
GOING AND FOCUS ON YOU.
IF YOU DON'T GET YOUR -- FACE
[BLEEP] OUT MY COMMENTS.
CALL ME PERSONALLY.
YOU WANT SOME CLOUT WITH ALL
YOU'VE GOT TO DO IS PULL UP.
NO CAMERA, NO FLEXING, AND ALL
THAT!
IF YOU ARE REAL MEN, FIGHT ME.
AND ANOTHER THING, SUCK MY
BLANK."
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
WOW.
WOW!
WHAT DO YOU THINK BLANK IS?
[LAUGHTER]
OFFSET CLAPPED BACK WITH "COKE
HEAD DON'T WANT SMOKE."
I'M SORRY -- WHAT DOES THAT --
I'VE NO IDEA WHAT THAT MEANS.
NORMAN, DO YOU KNOW?
>> Norman: OFFSET IS ACCUSING
CHRIS OF ABUSING COCAINE.
HE IS BASICALLY SAYING CHRIS
SHOULDN'T WANT ANY BEEF OR
PROBLEMS.
ACCORDING TO URBAN DICTIONARY.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Jason: WELL, CHRIS
CHALLENGED OFFSET TO A FIGHT.
YEAH.
WHO DO YOU THINK WOULD WIN THAT
FIGHT?
[AUDIENCE SHOUTING]
>> Jason: HOLD ON, CLAP YOUR
HANDS IF YOU THINK CHRIS.
[APPLAUSE]
CLAP YOUR HANDS IF YOU THINK
OFFSET.
[LESS APPLAUSE]
OKAY, I GOT IT.
CHRIS.
OH, MY GOSH.
WELL, I WILL SAY THIS.
THEY WOULD BOTH KICK MY -- I
WOULD NOT GO NEAR METHANOL.
SPEAKING OF OFFSET, HIS WIFE --
CARDI B -- SHE WENT ON SOCIAL
MEDIA TO TELL FANS HOW MUCH
MONEY IT TAKES TO BE CARDI B.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> BEING AN ARTIST, LOOKING GOOD
FOR YOU, DOING ALL THIS LEAP TO
PLEASE YOU, THAT COSTS MONEY.
ME, FOR EXAMPLE, MY BILLS IS
LIKE $300,000, $250,000, EVERY
SINGLE MONTH.
I TRY TO DO IT CHEAPER, AND IT'S
NOT.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
>> Jason: OKAY, I LOVE
CARDI B.
I LOVE HOW HONEST SHE IS.
SHE IS SO REAL.
I DO.
I LOVE HER.
BUT YOU'RE NOT GOING TO GET MUCH
SYMPATHY FROM ME WHEN OR LIKE,
"LOOK, I HAVE TRIED TO GET IT
LOWER THAN $300,000 A MONTH, BUT
I JUST CAN'T, OKAY?
FORGIVE ME."
NOT QUITE RELATABLE.
THAT'S A LOT OF MONEY TO SHELL
OUT EACH MONTH.
MONTHLY.
MY WIFE AND I DO NOT SPEND
NEARLY THAT MUCH.
JUST TO GIVE YOU A LITTLE
INSIGHT, HERE IS OUR MONTHLY
EXPENSES.
A FEW, IF I MAY. BUDGET.
RENT AND UTILITIES, $10,000.
FACIALS AND MASSAGES, $2100.
WARDROBE, INCLUDING WHAT ISSUES,
$16,000.
I DIDN'T THINK HE WOULD GIVE IT
REFERENCE!
HAIR EXTENSIONS, $1500.
BIKINI WAX, $350.
MEDICARE AND PEDICURE, $600.
AND $3500 AND BOTOX TREATMENTS.
NOW, MY WIFE'S MONTHLY
EXPENSES...
[LAUGHTER]
BY THE WAY, I LOVE A GOOD MANY
PATTY
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO ARE NOT ON
THAT CAKE, GET INVOLVED.
IT'S A GREAT WAY TO TREAT
YOURSELF.
IT REALLY IS.
IT'S RELAXING, PERSONAL HYGIENE
IS KEY.
TRUST ME, EVERYONE WINS IN THIS
EQUATION.
CAN WE TALK ABOUT
"THE BACHELOR?"
I USUALLY WATCH "THE BACHELOR."
IN YEARS PAST I HAVE EVEN LIKE
TO EAT IT.
MY WIFE AND I, JENNY, WE GET
VERY INVOLVED EMOTIONALLY.
I HAVEN'T REALLY WATCHED THIS
SEASON.
I WOULD LIKE TO THINK MY KIDS
FOR THAT.
[LAUGHTER]
APPARENTLY THIS YEAR IS PRETTY
JUICY.
THE BACHELOR IS A 26-YEAR-OLD
VIRGIN.
ONE OF THE WOMEN ON THE SHOW IS
A VERY PRETTY 21-YEAR-OLD NAMED
HEATHER WHO HAD NEVER BEEN
KISSED.
>> Audience: WHAT?
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
>> Jason: DO WE BELIEVE THIS?
>> Audience: NO!
>> Jason: THANK YOU!
I WAS LIKE, "REALLY, YOU GUYS?"
AND MAKES FOR INCREDIBLE
TELEVISION, OBVIOUSLY.
I'M SURE THERE IS A WORLD WHERE
SHE HASN'T.
BUT FIRST OF ALL, SHE IS
GORGEOUS.
ANYONE SHE WANTED, SHE COULD
HAVE HAD HER PICK.
I DON'T KNOW THAT I ENTIRELY BUY
IT, BUT LET'S GO WITH IT FOR A
MOMENT.
ASSUMING THAT'S THE CASE, MONDAY
NIGHT WAS THE BIG MOMENT.
HE TOOK HER OUT ON A DATE AND
HERE IS HAPPENED.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> IT'S AMAZING.
>> [LAUGHS]
I HAVE KISSED A BOY!
[LAUGHS]
IT WAS SO GOOD!
IT LITERALLY JUST FELT SO
NATURAL!
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
>> Jason: [LAUGHS]
GUYS, GUYS!
THERE WAS LITERAL FIREWORKS!
FOR HER FIRST KISS!
THIS POOR GIRL, EVERY KISS IS
GOING TO PALE IN COMPARISON FROM
THIS DAY FORWARD.
SHE COME ON MONDAY NIGHT --
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW IT'S ALREADY
TAPED -- SHE WATCHED THE SHOW
LIVE WITH HER FAMILY.
LOOK, WHEN YOUR PARENTS AND ALL
OF AMERICA WATCH AS YOUR FIRST
KISS -- LOOK, SHE IS THERE WITH
HER PARENTS!
WATCHING HER FIRST KISS WITH HER
PARENTS!
THAT'S NOT THE REACTION I'M
GOING FOR.
I'M GOING FOR, "WHAT?
THAT IS THE WEIRDEST THING!"
MY PARENTS, MY MOM SAT NEXT TO
ME AT THE "AMERICAN PIE"
PREMIERE, FOR EXAMPLE.
[LAUGHTER]
RIGHT?
WHERE THAT HAPPENED.
BELIEVE ME, THAT WAS PLENTY
AWKWARD.
BUT THERE IS NO WAY I WANT MY
PARENTS TO SEE MY FIRST KISS.
ALTHOUGH, ACTUALLY, MY FIRST
KISS -- IF I MAY -- MY FIRST
KISS WAS WORK-RELATED.
TECHNICALLY IT WAS FILMED, SO I
WAS ON THE SHOW "AS THE WORLD
TURNS."
[APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU.
WERE THEY PART OF YOUR STORIES?
I HAD TO AUDITION FOUR DIFFERENT
GIRLS FOR THE ROLE OF MY
GIRLFRIEND IN THE SHOW.
I ALREADY HAVE THE PART, SO I
WAS AUDITIONING OVER GIRLS.
I HAD TO KISS FOUR DIFFERENT
GIRLS AND ONE DAY!
IT WAS MY FIRST TIME!
BASICALLY, MY FIRST, SECOND,
THIRD, AND FORCED KISS ALL
HAPPENED WITHIN MOMENTS OF EACH
OTHER.
I ACTUALLY RAN INTO ONE OF THE
GIRLS JUST RECENTLY ON THE
SUBWAY, AND WE SIGNED HEATHER,
AND SHE TOLD ME, "YOU KNOW
WHAT'S FUNNY, YOU WERE MY FIRST
KISS.
PEAK AND I WAS LIKE, "THAT'S
WORLD.
I'VE JUST PLENTY OF REST
BEFORE."
SO THIS PROBABLY FOOTAGE OF THAT
SUMMER.
DEVON FRANKLIN SAYS MARRIED
COUPLES SHOULDN'T WATCH PORN.
HE SAID IT CREATES AN UNREAL
EXPECTATION OF WHAT INTIMACY
LOOKS LIKE.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
I WILL TELL YOU THIS.
AFTER 11 YEARS OF MARRIAGE,
THANK GOD FOR PORN!
[APPLAUSE]
I HAVE NO PROBLEM WITH IT.
I THINK IT'S SOMETHING YOU CAN
INCORPORATE INTO THE BEDROOM,
AND THAT IT CAN BE FUN AND
GREAT.
HOW DO YOU GUYS FEEL ABOUT THIS?
ARE YOU GUYS INTO PORN AT ALL?
[APPLAUSE]
I'M SEEING SOME NOS.
I'D SAY IT'S A PRETTY EVEN
SPLIT.
SUZANNE, BRANDON --    --
>> Suzanne: HI, JASON!
YOU DOING A GREAT JOB, BY THE
WAY!
>> Jason: WHERE DO YOU LAND?
>> Suzanne: LAST NIGHT WE
ACTUALLY WATCHED SOME PORN.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
IT'S A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
WE WATCHED "TEMPTATION ISLAND"
LAST NIGHT TOGETHER.
AND THEN BRANDON HAS SOME PORN
THAT HE LIKES.
>> TO ME, THE LOVE BOAT ON ME TV
ON SUNDAY FOR TWO HOURS IS ALL I
NEED.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
>> Jason: WOW.
YOU GUYS ARE REAL KINKY.
OH, MY GOSH.
I DID ASK, AND I REGRET IT.
[LAUGHTER]
MADONNA WAS A HUGE DIVA IN A
SPIN CLASS RECENTLY.
SHE REPORTEDLY WANTED A SPECIFIC
BIKE.
SO THE STUDIO ASKED THE WRITER,
WHO WAS ALREADY ON THE BITE, IF
SHE WOULD MOVE FOR A "BIG
CELEBRITY."
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
WOULD YOU MOVE OUT OF YOUR SEAT?
YOU SAY NO, AND THEN MADONNA
WALKS IN?
AND YOU ARE LIKE -- RIGHT?
I WOULD LIKE TO THINK THAT I'D
BE LIKE, "I'M SORRY, NO, YOU
CANNOT DO THIS.
IT'S NOT COOL."
BY THE WAY, SHE CAN AFFORD A
PRIVATE LESSON.
RIGHT?
[APPLAUSE]
I WOULD PROBABLY END UP MOVING
FOR HER, AND I WOULD WANT TO SIT
BEHIND HER.
BECAUSE I WOULD WANT TO KNOW IF
HER NEW -- IS REAL OR IF SHE GOT
IMPLANTS.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
YOU GUYS.
WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU GUYS THINK THAT'S REAL?
>> Audience: NO!
>> Jason: NO WAY, RIGHT?
NOW WOULD YOU MOVE AND LET HER
SIT IN YOUR SEAT?
YOU ARE LIKE, "NO, I STILL
WOULDN'T!"
OKAY.
A MAN IN ENGLAND STARTED HIS OWN
HOUSEKEEPING BUSINESS IN THE
NUDE.
UH-HUH.
HE STARTED CLEANING HOMES NAKED
ONLY TWO WEEKS AGO, I GUESS.
AND HIS BUSINESS IS ALREADY
TAKING OFF.
HE SAYS HE DOESN'T FEEL --
[LAUGHS]
HE SAYS HE DOESN'T FEEL AWKWARD
BECAUSE HE CHATS WITH HIS
CUSTOMERS, WHO ARE MAINLY
MIDDLE-AGED WOMEN AND MEN, WHILE
HE IS CLEANING.
OKAY, I'M SORRY.
RULE NUMBER ONE.
YOU'RE GOING TO CLEAN MY HOUSE
AND THEY COULD?
YOU ARE NOT SITTING ON MY COUCH.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
THAT'S NUMBER ONE.
THAT'S THE FIRST RULE.
I MEAN...
[LAUGHS]
I LOVE THAT HE JUST STARTED THIS
TWO WEEKS AGO AND HE ALREADY HAS
WHAT APPEARS TO BE A PROMOTIONAL
INTERVIEW.
HE SAT DOWN FOR IT -- YEAH, I
MEAN, KUDOS.
I'VE GOT TO RESPECT HIS COURAGE,
I SUPPOSE.
HE SAID HE STARTED THE BUSINESS
BECAUSE HE SAW A GAP IN THE
MARKET.
[LAUGHTER]
LUCKY US.
NOW WE ALL GET TO SEE THE GAP IN
HIS MARKET!
[LAUGHTER]
HEY-O!
THERE IS MORE GREAT SHOW.
UP NEXT, FIND OUT WHAT IS
TRENDING THIS WEEK!
GRAB A SNACK AND COME ON BACK.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
I call him "RoboChild."
Hey buddy! What do you wanna
be when you grow up?
I would like to be a
TurboTax Live CPA.
Don't you want to
be something else?
Yeah RoboChild, you
could be anything!
I want to help people get
their best possible refund.
Let's just break
it down, okay?
All TurboTax Live
CPAs
are human beings
with real emotions...
you're never going to be
emotionally complex enough
for that job.
I am sad. HAHAHAHA. HAHAHAHA.
Still perfecting emotion.
TurboTax Live now with
CPA's on Demand.
It's time for some
Straight Talk.
Hallelujah,
it's tax refund time.
So what are you going to do with
all that glorious extra money?
No, not that!
Here's a better plan.
Try Straight Talk Wireless and
get 25 gigs of high-speed data
for just $45 bucks a month.
That's right, all on America's
best 4G LTE networks.
Plus, save up to 200 dollars on
a Samsung Galaxy S9
with in-store activation.
Straight Talk Wireless.
Only at Walmart.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Jason: PLEASE WELCOME OUR
FIRST GUESTS, STOPPING BY TO
FILL US IN ON WHAT IS TRENDING
THIS WEEK!
HERE FROM "POP GOES THE WEEK,"
PLEASE WELCOME BRIAN BALTHAZAR!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
NICE TO SEE YOU!
>> Brian: GOOD TO SEE YOU!
WILL HAVE A TYPE.
SIMPLE
SOME PEOPLE LIKE BLONDES,
BRUNETTES.
I LIKE BIG AND I CANNOT LIE.
B14
>> Jason: MADONNA, WHAT DO YOU
THINK CUSTOMER GRILL, NOT REAL?
>> Brian: IT'S NOT REAL.
I CAN'T IMAGINE.
JUST A LITTLE PADDING.
KIND OF SAD, ACTUALLY.
THERE IS A NEW DATING SHOW THAT
TAKES IT TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
IT'S ON MTV, IT'S CALLED "GAME
OF CLONES."
IT TAKES EMPTY STARS LIKE PAULY
D, FOLKS LIKE THAT, AND THEY ARE
GOING ON THE ACTS OF PEOPLE THAT
ALL LOOK EXACTLY THE SAME.
[LAUGHS]
MTV JUST RELEASED A VIDEO.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
>> WE FOUND SEVEN IDENTICAL
SINGLES.
>> I'M IN A JAM!
>> WE ARE ASKING THESE MTV
STARS --
>> I CAN'T LOOK YOU IN THE FACE
RIGHT NOW!
>> IS OVERLOOKED LIKE YOUR TYPE,
COULD YOU FIND YOUR ONE AND
"CLONELY"?
YOU'VE NEVER SEEN A DATING SHOW
LIKE THIS.
>> WHAT TWILIGHT ZONE AND MIGHT
AND RIGHT NOW?
>> "GAME OF CLONES."
>> Brian: INTERESTING, RIGHT?
>> Jason: IT IS KIND OF
INTERESTING.
IS THE PRODUCER ON THIS QUESTION
WHAT SHE'S THINKING YOU HAD.
20 YEARS FROM NOW, SHE'S GOT A
BUILT IN SHOW.
>> Brian: IN THIS CASE ITS
HAIR EXTENSIONS AND
BREAST IMPLANTS.
>> Jason: I FEEL LIKE THEY
WERE TO RECORD FROM TITLE.
"GAME OF CLONES, THAT'S A SHOW!
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT THE SHOW'S
BUT WE'RE GOING TO MAKE IT!"
>> Brian: BE ALTHOUGH THE
CAMERAS ARE EVERYWHERE WE ARE.
EXCEPT FOR THIS ONE GUY IN
NEW JERSEY WAS CONTRACTED TO DO
SOME WORK.
HE THOUGHT, "OH, YEAH, I'M GOING
TO GO --"
BUT HE'S TERRIBLE ABOUT IT.
HE GETS A GLASS OF WATER WITH
SOME ICE IN IT.
HE DOES KNOW CAMERAS ARE THERE.
OOPS, I'M JUST GOING TO SPILL
THE WATER!
OH, NO!
ENEMY DOES THE BIG FALL.
WHOA!
I CAN'T GET UP!
SO HE BASICALLY LAID THERE UNTIL
SOMEBODY CAME.
GOD KNOWS HOW LONG THAT TOOK.
HE PROBABLY GOT UP AND GOT A
DRINK.
>> Jason: OH, MY GOSH!
THAT LOOKS LIKE ONE OF MY FIRST
AUDITIONS.
>> Brian: IS CALLED THE
PRATFALL!
HE FILED THIS INSURANCE CLAIM,
HE WAS ARRESTED, AND HE'S IN
COURT TODAY.
I DON'T THINK IT'S GOING TO WORK
OUT SO WELL FOR HIM!
WE WILL SEE A GHOST.
>> Jason: OH, MAN.
>> Brian: THE LESSON IS,
CAMERAS ARE EVERYWHERE.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Jason: THAT'S FRAUD.
IT'S ILLEGAL.
IS IT WEIRD THAT I HAVE A LITTLE
SYMPATHY FOR THE GUY?
>> Brian: NO.
IF YOU REALLY GIVE IT HIS ALL, A
GOOD FALL, YOU BE LIKE, "OKAY,
YOU TRIED!"
>> Jason: BUT EVERYTHING ABOUT
IT IS SO SAD.
BEFORE YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE ASIDE
CUSTOMER WHAT I'M ABOUT TO SHOW
YOU.
IF YOU MILK A COW, A SCHOOL'S
COME OUT.
IT'S FREEZING RIGHT NOW.
FASHION IS ALWAYS INSPIRED BY
THE WEATHER.
AND THERE ARE THESE HUGE PUFFY
COATS.
TO GO TO TAKE A LOOK AT THEM.
THERE ARE $3,000, AND THEY ARE
SOLD OUT.
I FEEL LIKE THEY'RE A LITTLE
RIDICULOUS.
THEY LOOK LIKE THEY WOULD BE ON
WHEELS.
I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU GO THROUGH
A SUBWAY TURNSTILE IN THAT.
IF THAT'S NOT ENOUGH COVERAGE
FOR YOU, THERE'S ONE ON THE
RUNWAY THAT'S GOING TO MAKE YOU
CRAZY.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> Jason: NO!
[LAUGHTER]
COME ON!
THAT'S NOT A COACH!
>> Brian: THEY NEVER ACTUALLY
GOT THE MODEL OUT OF IT.
I WOULD SLEEP IN THAT!
>> Jason: JUST STAY IN BED,
YOU GUYS.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
>> Brian: KIND OF A FASHION
TANGENT, THERE IS A WOMAN IN THE
U.K. NAMED HOLLY.
SHE IS QUITE GORGEOUS, ACTUALLY.
HER BOYFRIEND WAS CELEBRATING
HIS BIRTHDAY.
THERE SHE IS, VA VA VOOM.
HE LOOKS REALLY DEJECTED BECAUSE
SHE GOT HIM A T-SHIRT.
HE WANT TO GO OUT WITH THE BOYS.
NOT WITHOUT THE T-SHIRT!
IT SAYS, "IF YOU'RE READING
THIS, YOU'VE BEEN LOOKING AT MY
MAN FOR TOO LONG.
THIS IS HOW IT BE LOOK AT YOU IF
I WAS HERE.
HI YOU, I'M HOLLY, HIS
GIRLFRIEND!"
[APPLAUSE]
>> Jason: THIS PHOTO DOESN'T
LOOK STAGE AT ALL.
>> Brian: WOULD YOU EVER BE
FORCED TO WEAR A SHIRT LIKE
THIS?
>> Jason: NO, JENNY MAKES ME
WEAR BOXERS THAT SAY "NICE TRY."
[LAUGHTER]
JUST IN CASE.
>> Brian: DO HAVE A PICTURE OF
THAT?
WE DON'T HAVE A PICTURE OF THAT.
[LAUGHTER]
FINALLY, WE DIDN'T ALL WATCH THE
SUPER BOWL.
EVERY YEAR THE SUPER BOWL HAS
SOMETHING THAT GOES VIRAL.
IN THIS CASE, IT WAS ADAM
LEVINE'S SHIRT.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS TANK TOP.
PEOPLE THOUGHT IT LOOKED
FAMILIAR.
I THINK OF SEEN IT MAY BE AROUND
MY HOUSE?
IS THAT A SLIPCOVER?
A HANDBAG?
A CURTAIN?
I FEEL LIKE THERE IS A BOOTH IN
TGI FRIDAY'S WITH THAT A POSTER
ON IT.
>> Jason: THE PELLET IS PRETTY
SPOT ON.
THAT'S FANTASTIC.
>> Brian: AS WE ALL NO, HAD TO
TAKE IT OFF.
THEN WE SEE HIS TATTOOS.
AND SOMEONE IS LIKE, "WAIT, IS
THAT THE CHIPOTLE BAG?"
TAKE A LOOK.
[LAUGHTER]
YOU'LL NOTICE THAT HE HAS A
CALIFORNIA TATTOO.
BY THE WAY, IF ESTATE WAS ON
MINE, IT WOULD BE ALL WONKY.
HE HAS ONE THAT SAYS
"CALIFORNIA."
THIS GUY SAID, "I LOOKED JUST
LIKE ADAM LEVINE, I'M FROM
ILLINOIS!"
TAKE A LOOK.
EXACTLY THE SAME.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
>> Jason: WHICH ONE IS ADAM?
>> Brian: IT'S SO HARD TO
TELL, RIGHT?
HARD TO TELL.
LET'S MOVE ON FROM THE ABS AND
GET TO THIS AMAZING NEW SANDWICH
FROM KFC.
I LOVE ME A CHITO.
IT'S THE KFC CHITO'S SANDWICH.
>> Jason: WENT ON MY GOSH,
THEY'RE HERE.
>> Brian: ITS CHICKEN BREAST
WITH CHITO SAUCE, MALE, ON A
BUN.
IT'S ONLY AVAILABLE IN THREE
STATES.
THEY ARE TESTING IT OUT.
EVERYBODY IN THESE STATES, GO
GET IT.
WE MADE ONE FOR US.
>> Jason: YOU MADE A SPECIAL?
OH, MY GOSH.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Brian: YOU KNOW IT'S GOING
TO BE DELICIOUS.
I'M JUST GOING TO SAY IT IT'S
AMAZING!
>> Jason: THAT IS REALLY GOOD.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING
HERE!
[APPLAUSE]
FOR MORE TRENDING STORIES LIKE
THIS, CHECK OUT POP GOES THE
WEEK.COM.
I'M SPITTING CHEETOS EVERYWHERE.
UP NEXT,
"ORANGE IS THE NEW BLACK" STAR
I'M ALEX TREBEK
HERE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50-85
AND LOOKING
TO BUY LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET,
REMEMBER THE THREE P'S.
THE THREE WHAT?
THE THREE P'S?
WHAT ARE THE THREE P'S?
THE THREE P'S OF LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET
ARE PRICE, PRICE, AND PRICE.
A PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD,
A PRICE THAT CAN'T INCREASE,
AND A PRICE
THAT FITS YOUR BUDGET.
I'M 54 AND I WAS
A SMOKER BUT QUIT.
ALEX, WHAT'S MY PRICE?
YOU CAN GET COVERAGE
FOR $9.95 A MONTH.
I'M 65, RETIRED,
AND TAKE MEDICATIONS.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
ALSO $9.95 A MONTH.
I JUST TURNED 80
AND I'M ON A FIXED INCOME.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
$9.95 A MONTH FOR YOU, TOO.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85,
CALL NOW ABOUT
THE NUMBER ONE MOST POPULAR
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE PLAN
AVAILABLE THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IT HAS AN AFFORDABLE RATE
STARTING AT $9.95 A MONTH.
THAT'S LESS THAN 35 CENTS A DAY.
YOU CANNOT BE TURNED DOWN
BECAUSE OF YOUR HEALTH.
NO MEDICAL EXAM,
NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE IS GUARANTEED,
AND THIS PLAN HAS A GUARANTEED
LIFETIME RATE LOCK,
SO YOUR RATE CAN NEVER GO UP
FOR ANY REASON.
AND WITH THIS PLAN,
YOU CAN PICK YOUR PAYMENT DATE,
SO YOU CAN TIME
YOUR PREMIUM DUE DATE
TO WORK WITH YOUR BUDGET.
OPTIONS START AT $9.95 A MONTH,
PLUS, YOU GET A 30-DAY
MONEY BACK GUARANTEE.
SO CALL NOW
FOR FREE INFORMATION.
AND YOU'LL ALSO GET
THIS FREE BENEFICIARY PLANNER,
AND IT'S YOURS JUST FOR CALLING.
SO CALL NOW.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Jason: OUR NEXT GUEST
PLAYED MY FIANCE ON
"ORANGE IS THE NEW BLACK," NOW
SHE STARTING IN THE NEW SCARY
MOVIE, "THE PRODIGY."
TAKE A LOOK.
♪ ♪
>> WHAT IS IT, WHAT HAPPENED?
WHERE?
>> HE'S IN HERE.
TO SPEAK OF IT SOUND LIKE YOU'RE
HAVING A BAD DREAM.
>> NO, NO.
HE'S IN HERE.
HE'S INSIDE HERE.
INSIDE HERE.
>> Jason: PLEASE WELCOME,
TAYLOR SCHILLING!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
I LOVE YOU!
>> Taylor: I LOVE YOU!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HI!
>> Jason: OH, MY GOD, YOU LOOK
STUNNING.
>> Taylor: DO YOU LIKE MY
SUIT?
[APPLAUSE]
>> Jason: I LOVE YOUR SUIT!
>> Taylor: I KNOW        I KNOWT
USED TO SEEING ME IN CLOSE.
>> Jason: YES, I'M USED TO THE
PRISON GARB.
FANTASTIC.
>> Taylor: THANK YOU!
>> Jason: CAN WE DO A LITTLE
SHOE CAM?
THAT WE HAVE TO DO IT.
IT'S THE RULE.
IT'S A WENDY LAW.
>> Taylor: GROSS!
MY TOES ARE SHOVED IN THERE LIKE
A LITTLE HAM OX!
[LAUGHTER]
THEY DON'T LOOK RIGHT!
THESE ARE BETTER.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Jason: THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR BEING HERE BEING HERE.
>> Taylor: THANKS SO MUCH FOR
HAVING THE!
>> Jason: OF COURSE, WE DID
"ORANGE IS THE NEW BLACK"
TOGETHER.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Taylor: WE STILL HAVE MORE
WORK TO DO!
>> Jason: I THINK I'M COMING
BACK FOR A LITTLE QUICK POP.
WHERE ARE YOU AT IN THE SEASON?
>> Taylor: WE ARE DONE.
A LOVELY ONE BACKSTAGE IS LIKE,
"HAS THAT SHALL BEEN ON TEN
YEARS NOW?"
>> Wendy: FEELS LIKE IT.
>> Taylor: SEVEN YEARS.
>> Jason: CRAZY, RIGHT?
IS IT SORT OF MIXED EMOTIONS
WITH IT ENDING?
>> Taylor: ABSOLUTELY.
I'M SO PROUD OF THE SHOW, AND WE
HAVE DONE SO MANY GREAT THINGS.
I THINK JENJI AND THE WRITERS
HAVE BROUGHT SO MANY ISSUES INTO
THE CULTURAL CONVERSATION.
AND IT'S TIME.
I THINK IT'S TIME.
>> Jason: IT'S CERTAINLY GOING
OUT ON THE HIGH NOTE.
EVERYONE THAT I'VE TALKED TO
ISN'T BUMMED THAT IT'S ENDING,
BUT ALSO FEELS LIKE IT'S IN A
VERY ORGANIC AND KIND OF HEALTHY
WAY.
>> Taylor: IT FEELS LIKE WAY.
>> Jason: AS LONG AS I LIVE, I
WILL NEVER FORGET WHEN I CAME IN
ON DISH AND WITH YOU.
YOU HAD BEEN CAST.
I CAME IN AND READ WITH YOU.
>> Taylor: I WAS JUST TALKING
ABOUT THAT, TOO!
>> Jason: I LEFT THAT AUDITION
REALLY EXCITED AND WANTING THE
PART, BUT GOING, "THIS GIRL --
THE SHOW WAS GOING TO BE
MASSIVE.
THIS GIRL IS UNBELIEVABLE."
>> Taylor: JASON!
I LOVE YOU!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Jason: I WAS LITERALLY
TALKING TO JENNY, I WAS LIKE, "I
WOULD BE PSYCHED IF I GOT THIS.
REGARDLESS, IT'S A SHOW WE ARE
GOING TO BE WATCHING."
>> Taylor: THAT'S SO MAGICAL,
REMEMBER THAT AUDITION.
I REMEMBER YOU COMING IN, HOW
GOOD YOU WERE, HOW FUN IT WAS.
AND YOU LEFT.
YOU KNOW THAT THING THAT HAPPENS
IN MAGICIANS?
I DON'T SPEND A LOT OF TIME AND
AUDITIONS IN THE PROCESS OF
CASTING.
BUT IT WAS SO EXCITING.
JASON CAME IN, IT WAS SO MAGICAL
PRAYED HE LEFT, AND IT WAS LIKE,
"WELL, THAT'S THE SHOW.
WE KNOW WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO."
[APPLAUSE]
>> Jason: IS IT CRAZY TO THINK
THAT -- LIKE, WHAT WAS YOUR
TAKE?
WHEN THE SHOW FIRST CAME OUT AND
WAS BEING MADE, IT WAS MAYBE
"HOUSE OF CARDS."
NETFLIX WAS STILL THE SORT OF --
>> Taylor: THAT THING WHERE
YOU MAIL YOUR DVDs IN AND THE
RED AND BLUE.
REMEMBER WHEN THAT WAS ALL THAT
NETFLIX WAS?
>> Jason: THIS WAS LIKE THE
SECOND SHOW.
>> Taylor: IT WAS.
I AM EVER TALKING ABOUT IT WITH
THE PEOPLE WHO WEAR -- IT WAS
LIKE A WEB SERIES.
WE TALKED ABOUT IT LIKE A WEB
SERIES.
>> Jason: OH, GREAT, GOOD LUCK
WITH THAT!
>> Taylor: I STILL DON'T KNOW
WHAT A WEB SERIES IS, BUT THAT'S
WHAT IT WAS.
IT WAS SO DIFFERENT.
I REMEMBER, I WAS COACHED THAT
FIRST SEASON BY WHOEVER DOES
THAT NETFLIX PAIRED THE
PUBLICITY PEOPLE.
TO NOT USE THE WORD "BINGE."
REMEMBER WHEN THEY TOLD US THAT?
>> Jason: THEY WERE BASICALLY
TRAINING US TO TRAIN THE
AUDIENCE THAT YOU ARE GOING TO
WATCH TV IN A NEW WAY.
>> Taylor: YEAH.
IT WAS SO WILD.
AND NOBODY KNEW HOW TO PROCESS
THE IDEA THAT ALL OF THE
EPISODES WOULD COME OUT AT ONCE.
AND IT WAS A DIFFERENT -- IT WAS
JUST A DIFFERENT TIME.
>> Jason: YEAH.
SO CRAZY.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Taylor: YES.
>> Jason: NOW, I WOULD LIKE TO
DO -- IF YOU DON'T MIND -- PLAY
A LITTLE GAME.
>> Taylor: OH, GOD, JASON.
OKAY, I'M READY.
>> Jason: I KNOW YOU HATE
GAMES.
[LAUGHS]
>> Taylor: I KNOW YOU HATE
FUN!
>> Jason: YOU HATE FUN, SO
WERE GOING TO HAVE SOME FUN.
[LAUGHS]
WOULD YOU MIND COMPARING ME --
COMPARE ME TO SOME OF YOUR OTHER
ON-SCREEN COSTARS.
SO, LOWER PRE
LAURA PREPON.
WE HAVE A PHOTO?
THERE'S YOU AND LAURA.
>> Taylor: OH, GOD.
>> Jason: THERE'S YOU AND I.
HE WAS THE BETTER KISSER?
>> Taylor: JASON!
>> Jason: DON'T WORRY.
PRETEND THEY'RE NOT HERE.
[LAUGHS]
>> Taylor: I MEAN, I DON'T
KISS AND TELL, FIRST OF ALL.
>> Jason: I CAN ALREADY TELL
THE ANSWER IS LAURA.
YOU ARE DELAYING JUST ENOUGH!
[LAUGHTER]
>> Taylor: NO IT'S NOT, YOU'RE
A GREAT KISSER!
I DON'T EVEN A MEMBER!
>> Jason: WHAT, YOU DON'T
REMEMBER?
IT'S ALL I THINK ABOUT IS OUR
FIRST KISS!
[LAUGHTER]
OH, MY GOD.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
LET'S MOVE ON, PLEASE.
>> Taylor: IT WAS A LONG TIME
AGO!
IT'S NOT EVEN REAL KISSING ON
CAMERA, IS IT?
>> Jason: OKAY, YOU PLAYED BEN
AFFLECK'S WIFE IN "ARGO."
[APPLAUSE]
I THINK THE PICTURE ANSWERS THIS
QUESTION.
WHO IS THE BETTER ACTOR?
[LAUGHTER]
THERE IS BEEN WITH HIS -- WHAT
KIND OF WORD IS THAT?
IT'S LIKE A -- WHAT IS THAT,
FROM A FILM FESTIVAL OR
SOMETHING?
WHAT'S THAT, AND OSCAR?
DON'T EVEN.
AND THERE'S ME WITH THE MTV
MOVIE AWARD FOR BEST ACTOR.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Taylor: [LAUGHS]
THAT'S A GREAT PHOTO!
>> Jason: RIDICULOUS.
THIS IS A GOOD ONE.
I THINK YOU'LL BE ABLE TO ANSWER
THIS ONE VERY QUICKLY.
YOU HAD A LOVE SCENE WITH THE
ZAC EFRON IN "THE LUCKY ONES."
[APPLAUSE]
WHO HAS THE BETTER BODY?
[LAUGHTER]
>> Taylor: JASON!
JUST REVELING IN BEING ALIVE.
>> Jason: YOU KNOW JUST LOVING
LIFE.
LOVING MY BODY!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Taylor: YES!
LOVE YOUR BODY, JASON!
>> Jason: STAY BODY POSITIVE!
>> Taylor: IT'S VERY TRUE.
I LOVE IT.
WHO TOOK THAT PICTURE?
>> Jason: I PUT ON A SELFIE
STICK.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Taylor: LET ME GET A
PICTURE OF THE WATERFALL.
>> Jason: "HONEY, THERE'S A
WATERFALL.
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO."
CAN WE TALK ABOUT YOUR DOG?
>> Taylor: YES, LET'S CONTINUE
TO EXPLOIT MY ANIMAL."
SHE IS SO CUTE!
>> Jason: HOW OLD IS SHE NOW?
>> Taylor: LIKE A YEAR AND A
HALF.
>> Jason: CHI'S ONSET OF THE
TIME, RIGHT?
ISH?
>> Taylor: SHE GETS VERY
EXCITED IN MY DRESSING ROOM
SOMETIMES.
SOMETIMES IT'S BEST FOR HER TO
BE AT HOME.
THERE ARE SO MANY DOGS.
AND HAIR AND MAKEUP, EVERYBODY
HAS A DOG.
>> Jason: BUT NONE OF THE DOGS
TALK.
YOU ARE TEACHING TANK TO TALK?
>> Taylor: I DON'T KNOW AND
MORE HARNESSING HER NATURAL
ABILITIES TO SAY CERTAIN THINGS.
I'M NAMING WHAT SHE CAN ALREADY
DO.
>> Jason: CAN WE SEE THE VIDEO
VIDEO?
>> Taylor: I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU.
[DOG SAYING "I LOVE YOU"]
THERE WE GO!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Jason: THAT'S IMPRESSIVE!
IF I EVER GUESSED-HOST
WENDY WILLIAMS AGAIN, I WOULD
LIKE TANK TO BE MY GUEST.
THIS IS A LITTLE SEGMENT WITH
TANK.
I HAVE QUESTIONS.
>> Taylor: IT'S HER.
NOT THAT IT MATTERS.
>> Jason: I SAID HER!
CAN WE TALK ABOUT YOUR NEW
MOVIE?
YOU'RE STARTING IN THIS HORROR
MOVIE, "THE PRODIGY."
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WHICH LOOKS RIDICULOUSLY SCARY.
CAN YOU PLEASE --
>> Taylor: IT'S TRULY VERY
SCARY.
>> Jason: WHY?
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
>> Taylor: IS A HORROR
MOVIE -- HORROR MOVIES ARE
REALLY FUN.
BUT THIS -- IT'S TERRIFYING.
I HAVE SEEN IT TWICE NOW WITH
AUDIENCES, AND THERE ARE MOMENTS
WHERE PEOPLE JUST SCREAM SO MUCH
THAT THERE ARE BITS OF DIALOGUE
THAT GET LOST.
I'M LIKE "EVERYBODY COME I NEED
TO LISTEN TO THE MOVIE!"
>> Jason: IS THIS YOUR FIRST
HORROR MOVIE?
>> Taylor: YES.
>> Jason: IT SEEMS LIKE SO
MUCH FUN.
>> Taylor: IT IS REALLY FUN TO
READ THE SCRIPT IS REALLY GOOD.
IT'S AS FUN AS I THOUGHT IT
WOULD BE.
YOU REALLY JUST GET TO PLAY
PRETEND, THE CIRCUMSTANCES ARE
SO HEIGHTENED.
>> Jason: WHAT ARE YOU AFRAID
OF?
>> Taylor: UHHHHHHHHHH...
>> Jason: COME ON COME OF THIS
MOMENT IS GOING TO GO VIRAL.
SAY SOMETHING GOOD.
>> Taylor: I'M AFRAID OF REAL
THINGS.
I'M AFRAID OF SHARKS.
I WAS ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE THAT
GOT TOTALLY SCREWED UP BY SEEING
"JAWS."
I'M NOT ALONE IN THAT.
I KNOW THAT A LOT OF --
>> Jason: WELL, YOU WERE THREE
WHEN YOU SAW IT.
>> Taylor: SOMEBODY REALLY
MESSED UP ON THE CHILD-REARING
END.
THE BODY BOARD MOMENTS, WHERE
IT'S UNDERNEATH AND THE MUSIC,
AND ALL THE SUDDEN --
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE?
ABANDONMENT...
A LIFE ON LIVED -- KNOW WHAT I
MEAN?
NOT REACHING THEIR FULL
POTENTIAL.
NOT FULLY EXPRESSING YOURSELF AS
A HUMAN.
>> Jason: [LAUGHS]
JUST, YOU KNOW.
X ESSENTIAL.
JUST TERRIFIED OF LIFE.
[LAUGHTER]
TAYLOR, I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
HER NEW MOVIE, "THE PRODIGY,"
HITS THEATERS TOMORROW.
CHECK IT OUT.
UP NEXT I AM TAKING AUDIENCE
QUESTIONS.
KEEP IT HERE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Jason: WE ARE BACK, AND IT
IS TIME FOR "BIGGS ISSUES!"
WHAT'S YOUR ISSUE?
>> HI, JASON PAID MY NAME IS
CHERRY.
HOW YOU DOIN'?
I LOVED YOU IN THE MOVIE
"AMERICAN PIE."
I LOVE THE MOVIE BECAUSE IT
SHOWED HOW MUCH YOU LOVE --
>> Jason: HOLD ON, LET'S LET
THEM CLAP FOR A MINUTE.
[APPLAUSE]
>> I LOVE THE MOVIE, IT SHOWED
US HOW MUCH YOU LOVABLE HIGH.
SHOULD I
BRING FOOD INTO THE BEDROOM TO
SPICE THINGS UP?
>> Jason: WOW.
I MEAN -- LISTEN, YOU DO YOU PAY
WHATEVER YOU WANT TO INCLUDE
PREJUST MAKE SURE YOUR PARTNERS
INTO IT, AS WELL.
AS LONG AS YOU ARE
COMMUNICATING, IF YOU ARE BOTH
ON THE SAME PAGE, YOU GUYS CAN
DO WHATEVER YOU WANT IN THE
BEDROOM.
IT [CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU.
HI!
I'M DOING THIS, BUT I DON'T NEED
TO DO THAT.
I THINK YOU JUST NEED TO DO IT.
BUT DON'T TOUCH MY MICROPHONE.
[LAUGHTER]
>> SPICY!
HI, I'M ASHLEY.
>> Jason: WHAT'S YOUR ISSUE?
>> HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> Jason: HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> I'VE BEEN WITH MY BOYFRIEND
FOR TEN YEARS.
HE GETS UPSET WHEN I GO
SOMEWHERE AND DON'T TELL THEM
I BE REPORTING TO HIM
LIKE HE'S DADDY?
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
>> Jason: NEED I SAY MORE?
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT -- NO.
THAT'S THE LAST THING YOU WANT
TO DO.
I'M TELLING YOU, DON'T -- THAT'S
JUST GOING TO BE BAD.
THAT'S GOING TO TRIGGER YOU.
IF YOU HAVE STUFF, IT'S THE
WHOLE THING.
NO, STAY AWAY FROM THAT.
YOU DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
>> AMEN.
[APPLAUSE]
I GUESS THAT'S IT!
UP NEXT, A SPECIAL BOND THE
SCENES LOOK AT HOW I TRAINED TO
FILL IN FOR WENDY!
-Ah, the old crew!
Remember when we all used to go
to the cafeteria
and just chow down midday?
-You mean, like, lunch?
-Come on. Voted
"Most Likely to Help People
Save $668 When They Switch."
-At this school?
-Didn't you get caught
in the laminating machine?
-Ha. [ Sighs ]
-"Box, have a great summer.
Danielle."
Ooh.
Danielle, control yourself.
I'd like to slow it down here
with a special discount
for a special girl.
Danielle, this one's for you.
with a special discount
for a special girl.
I'm a concrete mason.
I had severe fatigue, went to
a doctor.
Became diagnosed with
Hodgkin's lymphoma.
I had to put my trust in
somebody.
We recommended chemotherapy,
and then a stem cell transplant.
When his disease progressed,
I thought that he would be a
good candidate
for immunotherapy
to unleash his immune system
against the cancer.
I'm back to working hard.
I've honestly have never felt
this great.
The evolution of cancer care
is here.
Learn more at cancercenter.com
appointments available now.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Jason: WELCOME BACK!
YOU KNOW I WAS PRETTY NERVOUS
ABOUT TRYING TO FILL WENDY'S
ISSUES, OBVIOUSLY.
LUCKY FOR ME, MY WIFE JENNY WAS
THERE TO HELP WITH ME INTO
SHAPE.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
THURSDAY.
GREAT, BY.
YOU KNOW HOW WENDY WILLIAMS IS
HAVING GUEST HOSTS THIS WEEK?
>> COME THEY WANT ME TO DO IT?
[LAUGHTER]
>> NO, THEY JUST CALLED.
THEY WOULD LIKE TO KNOW IF --
>> WE WOULD DO IT TO GET A?
I MEAN, I'M BUSY, BUT I COULD --
>> NO.
I LOVE YOU.
NO, THEY WANT TO KNOW IF I WILL
DO IT.
>> ALONE?
>> YEAH!
>> YOU KNOW THE SHOW?
>> YEAH, WENDY WILLIAMS!
>> YOU KNOW "HOT TOPICS"?
GRAB A SNACK, HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> I'M DOING GREAT!
>> NO, HOW YOU DOIN'.
SHE SAYS THAT.
>> HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> WE HAVE SOME WORK TO DO.
YOU HAVE TO BRING THEM OUT ON.
BRING IN THE HANDS.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU LIKE A CAT?
>> WENDY IS KNOWN AS THE POPE OF
POP CULTURE.
>> AMEN.
I'M LIKE THE NUN OF NEWS.
THEY GO RIGHT.
SO, HOUSEWIVES.
CAN YOU NAME THE CITY'S?
>> THE "REAL HOUSEWIVES" --
SEATTLE?
>> NO, NOT ONE.
>> TALLAHASSEE?
>> NO.
AGAIN.
MAYBE THAT'S A PORN YOU WATCH,
THAT'S NOT A "REAL HOUSEWIVES" "
HEY, WENDY!
MY NAME IS MONICA, I'M AN
INTERN, AND MY BOSS HAS ASKED ME
TO GO OUT TO DINNER.
WISHED I DO?
>> GIRL...
[LAUGHTER]
GET THAT A FREE MEAL >> THAT'S
NOT GOOD.
KIM KARDASHIAN IS TO KRIS JENNER
AS BLAC CHYNA IS TO...
>> BANGKOK BETTY?
LADIES AND JUDGMENT, PLEASE
WELCOME MY FIRST GUEST.
NICOLE -- SCHERZINGER.
LET'S GIVE IT UP FOR SAOIRSE
RONAN!
PASS.
>> YOU CAN'T PASS, YOU HAVE TO
INTERVIEW HIM!
>> I WILL SAY GO TO A DIFFERENT
SHOW, BECAUSE I CAN'T PRONOUNCE
HER NAME.
>> FIRST, JESSICA.
PHARAOH SHADE.
JUST THROW IT.
PHARAOH SHADE AT SOMEBODY
BETTER.
>> HOW YOU DOIN'?
WHAT THE [BLEEP] IS THAT?
>> WHAT DOES ARIANA GRANDE THINK
HER TATTOO SINCE?
>> SEVEN RINGS.
>> AND WHAT DOES THAT ACTUAL
SAY?
>> JAPANESE BARBECUE FINGER.
>> HOW YOU DOIN'.
>> MY NAME IS JENNY, I'VE BEEN
MARRIED FOR 11 YEARS.
LATELY MY HUSBAND AND I HAVEN'T
BEEN HAVING AS MUCH SEX AS WE
USE TO.
>> 11 YEARS?
I MEAN, I'M SURPRISED YOU'RE
HAVING SEX AT ALL.
[LAUGHS]
>> I'M DONE.
>> DON'T TOUCH MY MICROPHONE!
>> I'M DONE!
>> TONY, TRINA, TASTY, TO WANT
TO, TAMAR.
BOOM!
>> [PRONOUNCING DIFFICULT NAMES]
>> YASSSS, KWEEN!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
IT'S A BETTER CHOICE.
I'VE GOT TO GO.
>> WELL, WHAT DO WE THINK?
>> YEAH, YOU LOOK GOOD.
>> THAT'S A LITTLE SHADE.
I SEE WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
[CLEARS THROAT]
HOW YOU DOIN'?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Jason: SPECIAL THANKS TO MY
WIFE, JENNY, FOR ALL OF THE
HELP!
I LOVE YOU.
WE DID IT, BABY.
"WHAT THE FLICK"'S NEXT!
UGH, ANOTHER DELAY...
BUT... YOU KEEP BOUNCING
LIKE I'M A BOUNCY CASTLE!
OH YEAH!! 5 STOPS, 0 LEAKS.
WE'RE CRUSHING THIS COMMUTE!
HUGGIES LITTLE MOVERS.
OUR BEST FITTING DIAPER
THAT FITS LIKE A HUGG.
HUGG ON.
♪♪
You guys hungry?
>> Jason: HEY, WE ARE BACK AND
IT'S TIME TO PLAY WITH THE
FLICK!
WITH ME AND OUR PLAYER.
WHAT IS YOUR NAME!
>> I'M FROM WASHINGTON, D.C.
HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> Jason: HOW YOU DOIN'?
[LAUGHS]
OKAY, WE WILL SHOW YOU A PHOTO.
FIRST WE WILL SHOW YOU THE PHOTO
FROM A MOVIE, AND YOU HAVE TO
GUESS THE TITLE.
PRETTY SIMPLE.
DON'T MESS THIS UP.
[LAUGHTER]
HERE'S THE PHOTO.
♪ ♪
WOULD YOU LIKE ANY HINTS?
>> I'M GOING TO NEED A HAND.
>> THIS IS A COMEDY STARRING
JACK BLACK, AMANDA PETE, AND
MYSELF.
NEIL DIAMOND MAKES A CAMEO.
ONE MORE HINT -- FRIENDS TRY TO
SAVE MY CHARACTER FROM MARRYING
HIS CONTROLLING GIRLFRIEND.
SOMEONE JUST SAID "TEN THINGS I
HATE ABOUT YOU."
AND THAT IS WRONG.
[LAUGHTER]
>> IS IT SAVING SILVERMAN?
>> YES!
CONGRATULATIONS, YOU WON A 60
MINUTE MASSAGE AT HAVEN SPA!
NICE WORK!
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK AFTER
THIS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
APPLSE]
Stouffer's Lasagna With Meat &
Sauce
has two times the beef of the
leading meat sauce lasagna.
That's double the tender ground
beef
baked into every cheesy,
mouthwatering bite.
When it comes to irresistible
taste,
more is always more.
Stouffer's.
I'M ALEX TREBEK
HERE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
more is always more.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50-85
AND LOOKING
TO BUY LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET,
REMEMBER THE THREE P'S.
THE THREE WHAT?
THE THREE P'S?
WHAT ARE THE THREE P'S?
THE THREE P'S OF LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET
ARE PRICE, PRICE, AND PRICE.
A PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD,
A PRICE THAT CAN'T INCREASE,
AND A PRICE
THAT FITS YOUR BUDGET.
I'M 54 AND I WAS
A SMOKER BUT QUIT.
ALEX, WHAT'S MY PRICE?
YOU CAN GET COVERAGE
FOR $9.95 A MONTH.
I'M 65, RETIRED,
AND TAKE MEDICATIONS.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
ALSO $9.95 A MONTH.
I JUST TURNED 80
AND I'M ON A FIXED INCOME.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
$9.95 A MONTH FOR YOU, TOO.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85,
CALL NOW ABOUT
THE NUMBER ONE MOST POPULAR
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE PLAN
AVAILABLE THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IT HAS AN AFFORDABLE RATE
STARTING AT $9.95 A MONTH.
THAT'S LESS THAN 35 CENTS A DAY.
YOU CANNOT BE TURNED DOWN
BECAUSE OF YOUR HEALTH.
NO MEDICAL EXAM,
NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE IS GUARANTEED,
AND THIS PLAN HAS A GUARANTEED
LIFETIME RATE LOCK,
SO YOUR RATE CAN NEVER GO UP
FOR ANY REASON.
AND WITH THIS PLAN,
YOU CAN PICK YOUR PAYMENT DATE,
SO YOU CAN TIME
YOUR PREMIUM DUE DATE
TO WORK WITH YOUR BUDGET.
OPTIONS START AT $9.95 A MONTH,
PLUS, YOU GET A 30-DAY
MONEY BACK GUARANTEE.
SO CALL NOW
FOR FREE INFORMATION.
AND YOU'LL ALSO GET
THIS FREE BENEFICIARY PLANNER,
AND IT'S YOURS JUST FOR CALLING.
SO CALL NOW.
>> Jason: WELL, I HAD SUCH A
GREAT TIME TODAY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, WENDY.
TOMORROW, ACTRESS KEKE PALMER IS
GUEST HOSTING.
I LOVE YOU ALL FOR WATCHING
TODAY!
THANK YOU, THANK YOU!
WILL SEE YOU NEXT TIME ON
"WENDY."
MWAH!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
(birds singing,
insects trilling)
SHELDON:
It's nice to get back to nature.
Why don't I do this more often?