>> Announcer: LIVE FROM
NEW YORK CITY, IT'S
"THE WENDY WILLIAMS SHOW."
♪ ♪
NOW, HERE'S NICK CANNON!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Nick: WHAT'S UP, Y'ALL?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> Audience: HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> Nick: YOU KNOW WHAT?
[LAUGHS]
I'VE GOT TO SAY, Y'ALL WAS RIGH
RIGHT.
EVERY DAY, I'VE BEEN SUPER
ENERGETIC, SCREAMING AT THE TOP
OF MY LUNGS, AND A PLAYER DONE
LOST HIS VOICE.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
BUT I DID NOT LOSE MY ENERGY!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
IT'S SO GOOD TO BE HERE WITH THE
FAMILY.
FAMILY, WHERE WE AT?
>> Audience: WE LOVE THAT!
>> Nick: THAT'S WHAT I'M
TALKING ABOUT.
I LOVE Y'ALL, I LOVE BEING HERE.
IT AIN'T GOING TO STOP.
THIS UNFORTUNATELY IS MY LAST
DAY.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
BUT I'VE GOT TO GO GET MY MOVIE
STAR ON, Y'ALL!
I'M MAKING AN ACTION MOVIE IN
DUBAI!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
TRÈS LOOK LIKE A MOVIE STAR?
GO AHEAD, GET THE WHOLE OUTFIT.
I LOOK LIKE A RINGLEADER RIGHT
NOW.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
BUT YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO HAVE
SOME MORE GREAT GUEST HOSTS
UNTIL THE QUEEN RETURNS, MISS
WENDY!
[APPLAUSE]
I'M GOING TO BE WATCHING FROM
DUBAI.
Y'ALL JUST KEEP THE ENERGY
GOING.
WITHOUT FURTHER ADO, I GUESS NOW
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO DRINK SOME
TEA WHILE I'M TALKING ABOUT THE
TEA!
IT'S "HOT TOPICS," Y'ALL!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
YEAH!
I LOVE IT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
IT IS TIME.
SIT ON DOWN, RELAX.
WE ABOUT TO GET IN EVERYBODY'S
BUSINESS RIGHT NOW.
HOW HAVE Y'ALL BEEN ENJOYING THE
"HOT TOPICS"?
THEY'VE BEEN GOOD?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I TRIED TO KEEP IT REAL THOUGH.
I DON'T LIKE TO BE NASTY.
I HAVE NO MALICIOUS INTENT OR
ANY OF THAT, BUT I'VE GOT TO BE
HONEST, Y'ALL.
THAT'S WHAT PEOPLE WANT, RIGHT
CUSTOMER YOU WANT TO HEAR THE
REAL
TODAY WE'RE GOING TO TALK ABOUT
TWO THINGS THAT I'VE BEEN
AVOIDING TALKING ABOUT, BUT I'VE
GOT TO TALK ABOUT IT.
ONE THING, WE'RE JUST GOING TO
GET RIGHT TO IT.
MY HIT SHOW, SEASON 13, "WILD N'
OUT" ."
[AUDIENCE CHANTING]
BUT, GUESS WHO'S ON THIS WEEK?
BOW WOW AND -- I HAVE BEEN
REALLY TRYING TO AVOID TALKING
ABOUT THIS ALL WEEK BECAUSE
THESE TWO BEAUTIFUL INDIVIDUALS
ARE MY PERSONAL FRIENDS.
AND COLLEAGUES.
I HAVE KNOWN BOW OUT SINCE HE
WAS A LITTLE PUP.
[LAUGHTER]
KIYOMI IS A "WILD N' OUT" GIRL.
THERE'S US HANGING OUT BACKSTAGE
AFTER THE SHOW.
THAT'S ME AND KIYOMI, MOMENTS
EARLIER.
IT'S UNFORTUNATE AND IT'S SAD,
BECAUSE THEY WERE ARRESTED OVER
THE WEEKEND AFTER GETTING INTO A
PHYSICAL FIGHT.
I'M JUST SAYING, THERE IS
NOTHING FUNNY ABOUT
DOMESTIC VIOLENCE WHATSOEVER ON
EITHER SIDE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
THERE SHOULD BE NO DOUBLE
STANDARD EITHER WAY.
I REACHED OUT, KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
TO BOTH OF THEM.
BECAUSE IT'S A REAL LEGAL
MATTER, THEY'VE GOT TO GO TO
COURT AND STUFF.
NEITHER ONE OF THEM ACTUALLY
WANTED TO SPEAK ON THE ACTUAL
EVENTS THAT HAPPENED, BECAUSE
THEY HAVE BEEN ADVISED -- I
SPOKE TO KIYOMI.
BOW WOW STILL AUNT CALLED ME.
HE SUPPOSED TO BE MY FRIEND!
HE'S SENDING ME SENDING        D
ALL THAT.
YOU AIN'T GETTING NO CHRISTMAS
PRESENT THIS YEAR!
[LAUGHTER]
YOU'RE GOING TO GET A STATEMENT!
THIS IS MY MAN.
I'VE KNOWN HIM FOREVER, AND WE
ALWAYS HAVE FUN.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, TAKE A LOOK
AT THIS WEEK'S CLIP FROM
"WILD N' OUT" TO SEE HOW WE PLAY
WITH EACH OTHER.
>> YO.
I SAW YOUR PAYCHECK FOR YOUR
SHOW.
YOU KNOW IT AIN'T REAL.
COME WORK FOR ME.
YOU KNOW WE GET THAT BREAD FOR
REAL.
SIGNED THAT DEAL.
NO, DON'T YOU REACH!
SEAT DON'T ASK THAT YOUR
BLACK -- DOWN AND WATCH THE
TEACHER TEACH!
>> Nick: HE SEEMED A LITTLE
AGGRESSIVE!
[APPLAUSE]
RIGHT?
WHERE WAS ALL THAT THIS WEEKEND?
THIS IS WHERE I'VE GOT TO STICK
UP FOR BOTH OF MY FRIENDS.
BECAUSE IT'S A LITTLE -- THE
RUMORS IS CRAZY OUT THERE RIGHT
NOW.
I DID SOME INTEL AND SOME
RESEARCH.
THERE IS A RUMOR OUT THERE THAT
THE FIGHT WAS OVER KIYOMI
FLIRTING WITH SHAQUILLE O'NEAL.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
KIYOMI MUST NOT HAVE A TYPE AT
ALL, RIGHT?
[LAUGHTER]
LOOK AT THE SIZE DIFFERENCE!
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
IT WOULD TAKE TWO BY WHILES AND
ONE KEVIN HART TO EQUAL THAT.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
I DON'T REALLY NO, AND REALLY,
IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS WHAT
THE ALTERCATION WAS ABOUT.
BUT THERE IS A BUNCH OF
DIFFERENT STORIES GOING ON.
I HAVE TO ASK Y'ALL, FAMILY DOES
YOU GOT TO HELP ME OUT WITH
THIS.
WHEN YOU HAVE TWO FRIENDS -- I'M
PRESENT BOTH OF THEM -- AND I
DON'T WANT TO TAKE SIDES.
THIS IS A VERY SERIOUS MATTER.
I WANT TO TALK TO BOTH OF THEM.
I DIDN'T EVEN WANT TO TALK ABOUT
IT ON THE SHOW.
I GET IT, BUT THE MAN IN ME
WANTS TO INSTANTLY PROTECT THE
WOMAN.
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I BELIEVE NOBODY SHOULD PUT
THEIR HANDS ON A WOMAN
REGARDLESS.
I TELL MY SON ALL THE TIME,
"NEVER PUT YOUR HANDS ON A
WOMAN."
I DON'T CARE WHAT THE SITUATION
IS.
[APPLAUSE]
THERE IS NO REASON.
BUT THE REFEREE IN ME...
[LAUGHTER]
LOOK, I'M CONCERNED FOR BOW WOW!
WE NEED SOME JUSTICE FOR BOW WO
WOW!
THIS HAS BEEN A HOT TOPIC I'VE
BEEN TRYING TO AVOID, BUT I LIKE
TO TALK ABOUT THE NOT TOPICS,
TOO.
THE THING WE ARE NOT TALKING
ABOUT IS THAT NOBODY SHOULD BE
PUTTING THEIR HANDS ON ANYONE,
REGARDLESS OF GENDER.
[APPLAUSE]
WHEN YOU'VE GOT TO GO ALL THE
WAY TO VIOLENCE FOR WHATEVER
REASON, I JUST CAN'T CONDONE
THAT.
I DON'T WANT TO BE PREACHY OR
NONE OF THAT, BUT Y'ALL GOING TO
HAVE TO START MEDITATING OR
SOMETHING.
GIVE IT TO JESUS.
[APPLAUSE]
BECAUSE BOW OUT -- BOY, WE GOING
TO HAVE TO START A FUND FOR BOW
OUT.
GET A LITTLE BOW WHILE SHOULDER
FOR BRUISED BROTHERS OR
SOMETHING.
[LAUGHTER]
BOW WOW, CALL ME.
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I WISH HIM THE BEST.
I TOLD YOU, DON'T MESS WITH THEM
"WILD N' OUT" GIRLS.
THEY DO DRESS!
I GOT THEM FROM THE ISLAND WHERE
WONDER WOMAN IS FROM!
I ONLY HIRE POWERFUL QUEENS,
Y'ALL.
SPEAKING OF POWERFUL QUEENS,
ANOTHER THING THAT'S BEEN IN THE
NEWS -- WHICH I FIND PRETTY
FASCINATING -- CHRIS PRATT, WE
ALL NO, JUST CELEBRATED HIS
ENGAGEMENT TO
ARNOLD SCHWARZENEGGER'S
DAUGHTER.
CATHERINE SCHWARZENEGGER.
BUT WHAT HE CHOSE TO DO -- I
AIN'T MAD AT HIM.
HE CELEBRATED BY GOING TO A
STRIP CLUB.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
MY ONLY THING IS, HE WENT BY
HIMSELF.
HE DIDN'T BRING HIS FIANCEE WITH
HIM.
WHY DOES SHE GET LEFT OUT OF THE
FUN?
IT IN A JOKING WAY, THIS IS
WHERE CHRIS MIGHT HAVE TOOK IT A
LITTLE TOO FAR.
HE EVEN JOKINGLY SAID TO A
STRIPPER THERE AT THE STRIP
CLUB -- HE ASKED HER TO MARRY
HIM INSTEAD.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
I KNEW Y'ALL WASN'T GOING TO
FEEL THAT.
I DON'T THINK ARNOLD IS GOING TO
FEEL THAT, EITHER.
THE TERMINATOR GON' WHOOP YOUR
--  , CHRIS!
"YOU DON'T DISRESPECT MY
DAUGHTER!"
I GOT YOUR BACK, PLAYER.
I'VE BEEN IN THE STRIP CLUB,
TOO, AND THAT BRINGS THEM AFTER
MONEY OUT OF YOU.
"I NEED TO PROPOSE TO HER, PAY
SOME TUITION, SOMETHING!"
I GET IT.
IF ARNOLD GOT PROBLEMS WITH IT,
YOU TELL THEM TO CALL ME.
YOU CAN HAVE A STRIPPER.
HE HAD THE MAID, WHAT'S THE
DIFFERENCE?
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
DID I GO TOO FAR?
>> Suzanne: NO, I LOVE THAT
YOU BROUGHT UP MILDRED!
>> Nick: I HAD TO BRING UP
MILDRED!
SHE PROBABLY BE TWERKING AND
PUSHING THE BROOM, TOO!
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
[LAUGHTER]
THIS IS THE THING -- AGAIN, GET
TO THE NOT TOPIC REAL QUICK, I
THINK WE ARE IN SUCH A
PROGRESSIVE TIME AND A TIME OF
STRENGTH AND TRUE LIBERATION FOR
WOMAN
WOMEN THAT WE SHOULD STOP
LOOKING DOWN ON STRIP CLUBS.
THAT'S NOT A BAD THING.
THEY'RE MAKING MONEY, GETTING
THROUGH SCHOOL.
[APPLAUSE]
I DONE.
PLENTY TUITION.
IT'S A RESPECTABLE ENVIRONMENT.
THEY SHOULD BE HAVING BIBLE
STUDY IN THE STRIP CLUBS NOW.
DROPPING IT LOW FOR JESUS.
I'VE SEEN IT.
[LAUGHTER]
I HAVE SEEN IT.
I'M JOKING AROUND, BUT I
HONESTLY BELIEVE -- WHAT'S THE
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN STRIPPERS AND
VICTORIA'S SECRET MODELS?
ONE IS JUST A CASH UPFRONT
BUSINESS.
[LAUGHTER]
I TRULY BELIEVE THAT.
WE WILL HAVE A WHOLE NIGHT AND
GLORIFY THESE OTHER WOMEN
WALKING UP AND DOWN THE RUNWAY
IN THEIR UNDERWEAR.
MY SON IS LOOKING AT THE
MAGAZINE AT THE HOUSE.
BUT THERE IS NO DIFFERENCE.
SO I'M NOT GOING TO JUDGE, TO
ALL THE STRIPPERS, IF YOU NEED
ME, CALL ME.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
AND THE VICTORIA'S SECRET
MODELS, TOO!
IF Y'ALL NEED ME, CALL ME, TOO.
I'M AVAILABLE.
[LAUGHTER]
AND EVERYTHING REALLY
INTERESTING IN THE NEWS, AND I'M
A HUGE FAN.
I'M PROUD OF THIS BROTHER.
HE HAS HAD QUITE THE JOURNEY.
HIS SPIRIT IS SO STRONG.
DMX WAS RELEASED FROM PRISON.
[APPLAUSE]
TWO WEEKS AGO.
I LOVE IT.
MAN.
I LOVE THAT BROTHER RIGHT THERE.
HE'S BEEN THROUGH SO MUCH, AND
HAS PREVAILED, OVERCOME SO MANY
OBSTACLES.
AND HE JUST ANNOUNCED THAT HE'S
GOING BACK ONTO HER
A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE ISSUES WITH
THIS.
A LOT OF FANS ARE SAYING THAT,
YOU KNOW IT'S TOO SOON AND IT'S
NOT GOOD FOR HIS SOBRIETY.
EXACTLY!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
DMX OWED THE GOVERNMENT LIKE
$2 MILLION.
WHAT ELSE HE GOT TO GET OUT
THERE AND MAKE IT MONDAY
CUSTOMER HE'S GOT TO GET A JOB
!
[APPLAUSE]
WHAT OTHER JOB IS DMX GOING TO
DO?
YOU WON'T SEE DMX AT
McDONALD'S.
"WE'LL COME TO McDONALD'S, HOW
CAN I TAKE YOUR ORDER?
WHAT?
I CAN'T HEAR YOU!"
HE'S GOING TO A CROSSING GUARD?
DMX OUTSIDE THE SCHOOL?
"STOP, DROP, SHUT IT DOWN BEFORE
YOU GET SHOT!"
[AUDIENCE SINGING SONG]
Y'ALL ARE HILARIOUS!
I WOULD HIRE DMX AS MY
ACCOUNTANT, THOUGH.
HE WILL PROTECT THE MONEY, FOR
REAL.
"HEY, YO, DOUG.
YOUR DIVIDENDS, YOU GOT TO GET
THAT REVENUE.
[BARK]
"MY MAN!
BUT DMX HAS GOT 15 KIDS AND NINE
BABY MAMAS.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
I SALUTE YOU!
BE FRUITFUL AND MULTIPLY, THAT'S
WHAT WE ARE ON THE EARTH FOR.
THAT'S WHAT JESUS SAID, I THINK.
YOU MAD THAT HE GOT ALL THEM
KIDS?
THAT'S A LEGACY!
>> Audience: WOW.
>> Nick: SHE SANG "WOW."
ALL I'M SAYING, THAT MAY NEED TO
TAKE CARE OF HIS KIDS SO WE CAN
GET BACK TO WORK DOING WHAT HE
LOVES AND WHAT WE LOVE HIM FOR.
[APPLAUSE]
ONE OF THE GREATEST
REPRESENTATIVES TO DO IT, AND I
PRETTY SURE IT IS EXTREMELY
THERAPEUTIC FOR HIM TO BE UP
THERE WITH HIS FANS, GETTING
THAT LOVE, AS HIS HEALING
PROCESS OCCURS.
SO WE'RE GOING TO SUPPORT YOU,
DOG MAN X.
WE WITH YOU, MAN.
GET THAT MONEY!
[BARKING]
THAT WAS FUNNY.
HE WAS LIKE "WHAT?"
I LOVE IT, MAN.
THAT'S CULTURE RIGHT THERE.
THIS IS A LITTLE WEIRD BUT,
AGAIN, I DON'T JUDGE.
I JUST PUT OUT THERE.
DID YOU SEE THAT HUGE HARRY
STYLES FACE TATTOO?
WE TALKED ABOUT IT.
SHE PUT IT ON HER FACE.
THEY TALKED ABOUT ON THE SHOW,
IT WENT VIRAL.
WELL, IT TURNS OUT IT WAS FAKE.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
[APPLAUSE]
SHE FINESSED US, AND I LOVE IT!
I LOVE THE FINESSE!
SHE IS ACTUALLY A SINGER.
KELSEY CARTER ADMITTED IT WAS A
PUBLICITY STUNT TO PROMOTE HER
NEW SONG CALLED "HARRY."
SHE RELEASED THE WHOLE VIDEO
BECAUSE SHE PUT OUT A SONG.
SHE WAS SAYING SHE WAS GOING FOR
IT HER DOG PASSED AWAY, AND SHE
REVEALS -- "I'M A FAN OF
HARRY STYLES," AND SHE MADE A
SONG CALLED "HARRY."
SHE MADE A WHOLE VIRAL VIDEO.
"HOWEVER OFF THE ENTIRE WORLD
FOR $300."
SHE EXPLAINED HOW SHE WOKE UP
ONE MORNING AND TO GET MORE
ATTENTION ON HER SONG SHE
PRETENDED SHE HAD A TATTOO ON
HER FACE.
I SALUTE YOU!
[APPLAUSE]
THE NOT TOPIC HERE IS THE THINGS
THAT WE DO AS PEOPLE IN A
SOCIETY TO GET ATTENTION AND
SOCIAL MEDIA AND ENTERTAINMENT.
I'M GUILTY.
[LAUGHTER]
I GOT A TATTOO OF A POP STAR,
WELL.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
BUT MINE WAS REAL!
I COULDN'T JUST WASH THAT OFF
WITH NO DOVE SOAP!
[LAUGHTER]
THAT WAS LEFT, RIGHT THERE,
THOUGH.
PEOPLE ASKED ME, "WHY DID YOU DO
IT?"
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO BUY MARIAH
CAREY?
ATE A ROCK BIG ENOUGH TO PROVE
MY LOVE!
SO I WAS LIKE, "BABY, I'M GOING
TO PUT YOUR NAME ON MY BACK."
AND SHE STILL GOT MY BACK TO
THIS DAY!
WE ARE THE CLOSEST OF FRIENDS.
WE ARE RAISING SOME AMAZING KIDS
TO GIVE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
JUST BECAUSE -- I ADDED TO IT,
OF COURSE.
BECAUSE I HAD TO ADD SOME MORE.
THAT'S MY KIDS, ANGELS, THAT'S
JESUS.
IT'S A WHOLE FAMILY.
THE HOLY SPIRIT IS COVERING UP
"MARIAH."
BUT IT'S STILL THERE!
IT'S LIKE A COLLAGE.
I'VE GOT SOME MORE ROOM, TOO!
MY LEGS IS FREE.
I TOLD Y'ALL, I'M GOING TO PUT
HALLE BERRY AND NAOMI RIGHT
HERE.
I WILL GET RIHANNA RIGHT HERE.
IT'LL ALL WORK OUT.
ARE Y'ALL TATTOO PEOPLE?
I CAN'T BLAME ANYBODY, BECAUSE
I'M TATTED UP.
WHO'S GOT TATS IN HERE?
[APPLAUSE]
WOULD YOU EVER GET A SIGNIFICANT
OTHER TATTOOED ON YOU?
>> Audience: NO!
>> Nick: SO I'M THE ONLY FOOL
IN THE BUILDING PRAY [LAUGHTER]
I DO IT AGAIN.
I DO IT AGAIN AND AGAIN.
THAT'S WHAT LOVE IS ABOUT.
[APPLAUSE]
THE YOUNG GIRL, THE " "CASH ME
OUSSIDE" GROUP.
I AIN'T MAD AT HER.
TAKE A LOOK AT WHAT SHE'S DOING
NOW.
>> I'M A BAD KID THAT MY MOM
CAN'T CONTROL PART I WENT FROM
SLEEPING ON THE FLOOR IN A
TRAILER TO HAVING A GOLD RECORD
IN SIX MONTHS.
I'VE GOT TO GO UP MANAGERS A
BODYGUARD.
MY MOM -- THEY THINK I'M YOUR
BABY.
THEY DON'T WANT ME TO GO UP TO
HIM BUT TIME.
>> SHE'S A LITTLE [BLEEP]
[BLEEP].
>> SHE'S NEVER HAD A FATHER IN
HER LIFE.
SHE'S BECOME LIKE MY TEAM HQ.
>> I GIVE UP EVERYTHING FOR YOU!
>> WHAT DID YOU GIVE UP?
>> Y'ALL REALLY WANT TO KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I'M HERE TO [BLEEP] TELL YOU!
>> Nick: SUZANNE, I'M NOT MAD
AT THIS!
YOU DON'T LIKE THIS?
I KNOW YOU ARE A MOM.
>> Suzanne: YOUNG GIRLS ARE
LOOKING UP TO THIS AND I DON'T
APPROVE OF THAT.
>> Nick: YOU MAY NOT AGREE
WITH THIS, BUT I WANT TO KEEP IT
REAL.
I WOULD RATHER MY DAUGHTER BE
GOING THIS DIRECTION THAN THE
KYLIE JENNER DIRECTION.
THAT JUST ME.
THIS GIRL MAY HAVE A BAD MOUTH,
SHE NEED SOME GUIDANCE, SHE
NEEDS A WHOOPING.
BUT AT THE SAME AGE, KYLIE
JENNER WAS GETTING
PLASTIC SURGERY.
SHE GOT A MAKEUP LINE, SHE'S
GOTTA MAKE UP LINE.
THEY ARE BOTH MAKING MONEY OFF
OF SOCIETY'S EXPECTATION OF
YOUNG GIRLS.
THERE'S TWO DIFFERENT WAYS.
BUT IF I HAVE TO CHOOSE, I WANT
MY DAUGHTER TO GET OUT THERE AND
BE ALLOWED MOUTH AND TALK.
BECAUSE THEN I CAN SAY IS ABOUT
DISCIPLINE AND RESPECT.
BUT WHEN HE GETS THAT OF THE
WORLD WHERE THERE ARE THINGS
THAT I CAN'T CONTROL, BECAUSE
SOCIAL MEDIA IS CONTROLLING
EVERYTHING -- AS A PARENT, I'M
JUST SAYING, SUZANNE...
IF I HAD TO CHOOSE.
BECAUSE I CAN FIX BAD BHABIE
WITH A BAD BHELT.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
I'LL GIVE YOU A PERFECT EXAMPLE.
A LOT OF PEOPLE GOT MAD AT ME ON
SOCIAL MEDIA BECAUSE I LET MY
KIDS -- WE BE CUTTING UP WHEN WE
GET TOGETHER.
WE DO "YO MAMA" JOKES AND OF
ITSELF.
BUT IT'S FUN!
NOT THEY MAMA.
BUT WE DO "YO MAMA" JOKES PRAYED
I WILL TALK ABOUT MY SON,
MOROCCAN.
THIS IS MY SON WITH HIS JOKE.
SPEAK OKAY.
WHAT WAS THAT?
OH, YEAH.
YO MAMA SO STUPID, SHE PUT AN
iPAD IN THE BLENDER TO MAKE
APPLE JUICE!
[LAUGHTER]
>> Nick: STUPID MAMA!
YOU KNOW EIGHT NO DOUBLE
STANDARDS.
IT'S EQUAL, WE DON'T JUST DO
MAMA JOKES.
WE DO DIRTY JOKES, TOO.
LOOK AT MY DAUGHTER, MUNRO.
GO AHEAD AND SHOW THAT ONE.
>> ALBRIGHT, MUNRO.
WE KEEP TALKING ABOUT MAMA'S.
WHAT ABOUT DADDY'S?
SPEAK OKAY.
YOUR DADDY IS SO OLD, WHEN THEY
SAID "LET THERE BE LIGHT," HE
WAS THERE TO FLICK ON THE LIGHT
SWITCH.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
THAT'S FUNNY!
AND PEOPLE SAY, "YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE THEM," THEY UNDERSTAND.
THEY'RE EMPOWERED, THEY KNOW THE
JOKE IN THE END THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN HUMOR AND BEING REAL.
THEY RESPECT ME AS A PARENT.
ONE THING IN MY HOUSE, I WANT
THEM TO SPEAK FREELY INTO
EVERYTHING THEY WANT TO DO
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT THEIR
PARENTS DO.
BUT I WANT TO FOCUS ON
EDUCATION.
[APPLAUSE]
IT STARTS SUPER YOUNG.
THEY'RE SO MUCH GOING ON A
SOCIETY, I WANT TO INFORM THEM
AND EMPOWER THEM SO I'M NOT
HIDING ANYTHING FROM THEM.
SO THE CLOSER -- I STARTED THEM
AS BABIES, Y'ALL.
MY 7-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER WAS
TUTORING MY ONE AND A
HALF-YEAR-OLD.
CHECK THIS OUTCOME IS EDUCATION.
THIS IS AMAZING TO ME.
>> WHAT DOES THIS SAY?
>> POLAR BEAR.
>> WAVE.
>> WHAT DOES THIS SAY?
>> GOOD JOB, MAN!
>> Nick: HE'S NOT EVEN TWO YET
YET!
IT'S ABOUT EMPOWERING YOUR YOUNG
PEOPLE.
EDUCATE THEM.
IT'S A TOUGH WORLD OUT THERE.
I DON'T WANT TO JUDGE ANYBODY,
BECAUSE PARENTING IS A DIFFICULT
THING.
I DON'T HAVE ALL THE ANSWERS.
JUST INFORM THEM AND GIVE THEM
UNCONDITIONAL LOVE.
THAT'S WHERE IT IS.
[APPLAUSE]
'S GOT MORE GREAT SHOW!
UP NEXT, RAPPER AND ACTIVIST, MY
BROTHER, KILLER MIKE IS HERE,
Y'ALL!
SO GRAB A SNACK AND COME ON
BACK!
A [CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: WELCOME BACK, WELCOME
BACK!
STILL TRYING TO GET MY VOICE
BACK.
I'M NURSING IT WITH THIS TEA.
Y'ALL GOT ME DOING DMX
IMPRESSIONS AND STUFF.
I'M NOT GOING TO HAVE A VOICE
WHEN I GET TO DUBAI!
RIGHT NOW I'M SUPER EXCITED
BECAUSE I'M BRINGING OUT
SOMEBODY NOT ONLY WHO I ADMIRE,
WHO I'M A FAN OF, BUT I CONSIDER
A BROTHER.
OUR FIRST GUEST IS A
GRAMMY-NOMINATED RAPPER AND
SOCIAL ACTIVIST.
AND FELLOW OUTSPOKEN VOICE IN
THE COMMUNITY, IN THE STRUGGLE.
HIS NEW SHOW ON NETFLIX IS
CALLED "TRIGGER WARNING WITH
KILLER MIKE."
TAKE A LOOK.
>> I'M TRYING TO INTRODUCE
PEOPLE TO NEW CONCEPTS.
KILLER MIKE!
♪ ♪
I WANT TO KNOW HOW DIFFICULT IT
IS TO TRULY LIVE IN THE BLACK
ECONOMY.
NO RACISM, BUT YOU ARE ASIAN AND
I'M ONLY SPENDING MONEY IN THE
BLOOD COMMITTEE FOR THE NEXT
THREE DAYS.
YOU AIN'T BLACK.
I COULD GO BUY T-SHIRT.
>> THIS FEELS A LITTLE BIT MORE
CORPORATE.
>> YEAH.
>> I HAVEN'T WORKED WITH A GANG
BEFORE.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME FOR
EVERYTHING.
>> Nick: HILARIOUS AND
INFORMATIVE!
PLEASE WELCOME, MICHAEL RENDER.
AK, KILLER MIKE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Nick: NOW, THE BROTHER
RIGHT HERE ISRAEL WITH IT.
ONE OF THE HOTTEST RAPPERS IN
THE GAME.
COMING OUT OF ATLANTA.
[APPLAUSE]
WE'VE GOT TO BREAK DOWN A LITTLE
BIT.
YOU'RE GOING TO SCARE SOME OF
THE FOLKS.
I SAY KILLER MIKE, THEY'RE LIKE,
"KILLER MIKE?
COULD HE BE MORE LIKE FRIENDLY
MY?"
>> Mike: MY NAME IS MICHAEL
RENDER.
I'M NAMED FOR MY DAD AND I HAVE
A DAUGHTER NAMED FOR ME.
ACTUALLY WON A GRAMMY A LOT OF
YEARS AGO.
[APPLAUSE]
WE LOST LAST YEAR, THOUGH.
I'M ONE HALF OF THE GROUP CALLED
RUN THE JEWELS, AND I'M A
BEAUTIFUL WOMAN NAMED SHAYNA'S
HUSBAND.
THANK Y'ALL FOR HAVING ME.
>> Nick: THAT'S A BEAUTIFUL
THING!
THE KILLER CAME FROM KILLING
THEM IN BATTLES, RIGHT?
>> Mike: I WAS 15 YEARS WILL
PREVAIL AND FIVE, SIX, SEVEN,
EIGHT GUYS.
I WAS KILLING THEM.
MY NICKNAME WAS SKUNK.
I GOT STOOD UP AND SAID, "YO,
THAT KID IS A KILLER, HE'S
KILLING Y'ALL."
AND NOBODY CALLED ME MIKE AFTER
THAT.
>> Nick: KEEP KILLING IT, MAN.
YOU'RE KILLING IT OUT THERE
RIGHT NOW.
>> Mike: I APPRECIATE YOU,
MAN.
YOUR FAN, BROTHER.
JUST IN TERMS OF BEING
OUTSPOKEN.
>> Nick: THAT'S LOVE.
>> Mike: I APPRECIATE.
>> Nick: I'VE GOT TO GET YOU
ON THE PODCAST SO WE CAN GET
REAL DEEP!
ONE OF THE THINGS I ADMIRE AND
RESPECT ABOUT YOU EVERY TIME WE
GET TOGETHER, YOU ARE OUR
FAMILY-ORIENTED MEN PREVIEW OF
YOUR COMMUNITY COMMUNITY.
YOU'VE BEEN MARRIED FOR     TO E
OR 13 YEARS.
[APPLAUSE]
THAT'S SUCCESS RIGHT THERE!
YOU GOT YOUR QUEEN WITH YOU.
>> Mike: SHE HATES THAT
PICTURE.
I THINK SHE LOOKS HOT.
[APPLAUSE]
SHE'S PROBABLY GOING TO HATE ME
LATER FOR THAT PHOTO BEING USED,
BUT I TOLD HER THAT SHE IS
BAYWATCH BEAUTIFUL.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
>> Nick: THERE IT IS!
SHE'S ALSO EXTREMELY POWERFUL,
EXTREMELY INTELLIGENT.
YOU ACTUALLY WANTED TO MAKE A
PURCHASE, A CAR PURCHASE.
THE DODGE DEMON, WHICH IS A LOT
OF MONEY.
SHE SHIPPED ON THE PURCHASE AND
TOLD YOU TO INVEST?
>> Mike: THERE WERE TWO
THINGS.
I WANTED A DODGE DEMON.
I SAVED UP FOR LIKE A YEAR, I
WAS GOING GET ONE.
AND MY GOOD FRIEND T.I. CALLED
ME AND SAID THAT THERE IS A
RESTAURANT FOR SALE IN OUR
NEIGHBORHOOD CALLED BANKHEAD
SEAFOOD.
AND I SAID, "OH, WELL, I GUESS
IT WILL BE GETTING THAT DEMON."
LATER, I WAS LIKE, "I'VE GOT A
QUARTER MILLION DOLLARS, ALL MY
FRIENDS ARE BUYING ROLLS-ROYCE
TRUCKS.
MAYBE I SHOULD, TOO."
AND SHE WAS LIKE, "NO, DUMMY.
WE'RE GOING TO BUY AN APARTMENT
BUILDING."
>> Nick: A WISE WOMAN.
>> Mike: THE BUILDING WE
BOUGHT IS WORTH TRIPLE WHAT IT
WAS WORTH WHEN WE BOUGHT IT.
[APPLAUSE]
WITH A QUARTER MILLION DOLLAR
INVESTMENT, SHE MAY BE ABOUT
500,000 EXTRA DOLLARS.
>> Nick: WOW.
THAT'S A QUEEN RIGHT THERE!
THAT'S BEING EQUALLY YOKED!
>> Mike: AND SHE'S SHAVED BIG
ON IG.
>> Nick: FOLLOW THE GREEN.
NOT ONLY DO YOU HAVE APARTMENT
BUILDINGS, RESTAURANTS, YOU HAVE
A LOT OF PROPERTY AND BUSINESSES
IN YOUR COMMUNITY IN GEORGIA.
AND THE SUPER BOWL THIS PAST
WEEKEND WAS THERE.
EVERYBODY KNOWS, I TOOK THE
STANCE.
IF IT'S ME AND KAEP, I WAS WITH
HIM FOR REAL.
WE HAD CHINESE VEGAN FOOD.
I CHOSE TO STAY HERE.
I CAME BACK TO GET READY FOR THE
SHOW.
>> Mike: THEY MISSED YOU.
I WAS LIKE, "SORRY, GIRLS, WE
ARE PROTESTING."
[LAUGHTER]
>> Nick: VERY FUNNY.
WE DON'T SHARE THE EXACT SAME
OPINION, BUT WE WANT THE SAME
OUTCOME.
I WANT TO KNOW HOW YOU FEEL
ABOUT THE SUPER BOWL COMING TO
YOUR CITY AND ALL THE THINGS
THAT WERE GOING ON THERE.
>> Mike: FIRST OF ALL, THERE
ARE MANY ROADS TO FREEDOM.
WE CAN ALL MEET EACH OTHER THEY
PAID DURING THE CIVIL RIGHTS
CAMPAIGN, MARTIN KING WAS LOOKED
AT AS SUSCEPTIBLE TO THE WHITE
STRUCTURE HERE.
IF YOU LOOK AT THOSE BROTHERS,
MALCOLM, THEY WERE LOOKED AT AS
MORE RADICAL.
BUT THEY WANTED THE SAME THING.
BASIC HUMAN RIGHTS FOR US.
FOR ME, AND MATTERS OF BLACK
PEOPLE CHOOSING TO WORK ON THE
SUPER BOWL, I'VE BEEN HAVING TO
CRITIQUE, I HAVE CRITICISM,
BECAUSE I LIVE IN ATLANTA.
I SAW WHAT IT DID FOR A SECOND
I'M GOOD.
BECAUSE OF THERE'S LOT OF BLACK
BUSINESS OWNERSHIP, IN
PARTICULAR AFRICAN-AMERICAN
WOMEN -- I SAW RESTAURANTS
THRIVE.
EVEN THE STRIP CLUB I WENT TO
HIS BLACK-OWNED.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: EXCEPT FOR THE ONE
ASIAN STRIPPER IN THE SHOW!
>> Mike: I SHOWED HER LOVE
LATER.
[LAUGHTER]
YOU CAN'T HAVE A SUPER BOWL IN
ATLANTA AND NOT HAVE OUTKAST
PRESENT, SO BIG BOI WAS
APPROPRIATE.
YOU CAN DO IT WITHOUT HAVING
GLADYS KNIGHT PRESENT.
I DON'T WANT CIVIL RIGHTS TO
FORCE US TO BE THERE, I DON'T
WANT THEM WIPED AWAY.
I WAS PROUD OF ATLANTA BECAUSE
WE MANAGED TO DISAGREE AND STILL
BRING INCOME TO THE WORKING
CLASS PEOPLE.
THEY WALKED AWAY WITH MORE
MONEY.
[APPLAUSE]
SMALL BUSINESSES WALKED AWAY.
>> Nick: I'VE GOT TO SALUTE
IT.
>> Mike: AND WE GOT THE JAM.
SO I THINK MAROON 5 DESERVES A
SALUTE FOR WE DID.
MY GROUP, RUN THE JEWELS, WE
OPENED UP FOR THE FOO FIGHTERS
THE DAY BEFORE TOM MORELLO CAME
OUT AND PLAY.
SO PEOPLE PROTESTED.
THERE WAS A MURAL OF
COLIN KAEPERNICK THAT GOT TORN
DOWN.
ARTISTS CAME TOGETHER THE NIGHT
BEFORE.
SEVEN.
>> Nick: ALL OVER THE CITY OF
ATLANTA.
AND COLIN LOVED IT, HE REPOSTED
ALL OF THEM.
I FELT LIKE THE NFL HEARD OUR
VOICE IS LOUD AND CLEAR.
AND THE RATINGS -- IT WAS THE
LOWEST IN TEN YEARS.
I THINK WE BOTH GOT WHAT WE
WANTED OUT OF THIS WHOLE THING.
[APPLAUSE]
THESE ARE THE TYPE OF TOPICS
THAT YOU DISCUSS AND DEAL WITH
ON YOUR NEW NETFLIX SHOW,
"TRIGGER WARNING WITH
KILLER MIKE."
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
ALL THE WAY DOWN TO THE STRIP
CLUB!
EPISODE -- I LOVE ALL THE
EPISODES I'VE SEEN THUS FAR, BUT
THE ONE THAT YOU WANTED TO ONLY
SPEND YOUR MONEY IN THE BLACK
COMMUNITY -- IT WAS SO DIFFICULT
FOR YOU THAT YOU HAD TO SLEEP ON
THE BUS BENCH!
>> Mike: ON A PARK BENCH IN
ATHENS!
>> Wendy: YOU COULDN'T EAT,
YOU COULDN'T GET OF THAT --
[LAUGHTER]
AT IT SO DIFFICULT BECAUSE THERE
AREN'T ENOUGH BLACK-OWNED
BUSINESSES.
TELLING THEM ABOUT THAT.
>> Mike: WHITE PEOPLE TAKE
MARIJUANA FROM MEXICANS.
I COULDN'T EVEN SMOKE BECAUSE
MARIJUANA IS --
BUT AFTER THAT --
>> Nick: YOU COULDN'T FIND NO
JAMAICANS?
>> Mike: I COULDN'T FIND ONE
JAMAICAN!
[LAUGHTER]
THIS IS THE THING.
INDIVIDUALLY, AS
AFRICAN-AMERICANS, SEVEN YEARS
OR TEN YEARS AFTER SLAVERY WE
HAD ALREADY AMASSED LAND AND
WEALTH DONE BETTER FOR
OURSELVES.
BY THE TIME 1907 CAME AROUND,
OUR UNIVERSITY WAS GREATER AND
MORE BLACK REALTORS IN HARVARD
AND YALE.
BECAUSE THEY COULD TAKE TRADE.
TO ME, IT'S ABOUT BEING
ECONOMICALLY RESPONSIBLE.
THEN AS A COMMUNITY, DOING THAT.
THAT HELPS THE LARGER COMMUNITY.
IF THE BLACK COMMUNITY IN
AMERICA IS STRONG FINANCIALLY
AND ECONOMICALLY COME THE
GREATER COMMUNITY BECOME STRONG.
HOW DOES THAT WORK?
WELL, IF YOUR COMMUNITY IS
CHARGING $2.50 OR $3.50 FOR GAS,
AND IT'S A CORPORATE, LARGE GAS
STATION, I DO HAVE A SMALL GAS
STATION THAT COULD GIVE YOU
BETTER PRICING -- LOCALLY,
REGIONALLY, OR AS WE SAY, BLACK.
BECAUSE I LIVE NEAR BLACK
PEOPLE.
SEEKING GOING TO MAKE MEDIA TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF THOSE RESOURCES AND
JOIN IN.
OUR COMMUNITY IS STRONG, THE
GREATER COMMUNITY STARTED.
I'M NEVER EXCUSING PEOPLE WHEN I
SAY BLACK OR BY BLACK.
I WANT TO CODY.
I WANT VANILLA, CHOCOLATE,
STRAWBERRY.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: MAN, WHEN ARE YOU
RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT, MAN?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
A TRUE SCHOLAR AND LEADER.
THINK FOR BEING HERE, BROTHER.
WE'RE GOING TO CONTINUE THIS.
"TRIGGER WARNING WITH
KILLER MIKE."
SEE IT, IT'S AN AMAZING SHOW.
STREAMING ON NETFLIX NOW.
UP NEXT, I WILL PLAY THE DATING
GAME WITH 320 WATCHES.
KILLER MIKE, YELL!
I
Live from the Starlite Lounge.
♪ One plus one equals
too little too late ♪
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]
>> Nick: ANOTHER MONSTER
PERFORMANCE!
>> I LOVE YOU, MONSTER!
[AUDIENCE CHANTING "MONSTER!"
>> HE CAN MOVE!
>> LET ME HELP YOU BECOME A
MONSTER.
LIMITED WILL BE HERE.
THIS IS REAL LOVE HER, ALSO NIC!
>> Nick: THAT WAS A CLIP FOR
MY NEW HIT SHOW,
"THE MASKED SINGER."
HAVE YOU BEEN WATCHING IT?
EVERYWHERE I GO, THAT'S ALL
PEOPLE ARE TALKING TO ME ABOUT.
I LOVE IT, BUT I WAS TIRED OF
PEOPLE SAYING "IT WAS THE
MONSTER?
"Y'ALL GOING TO FIND OUT.
IT COMES ON TONIGHT, SO MAKE
SURE Y'ALL CHECK IT OUT.
[APPLAUSE]
YOU'VE BEEN WATCHING IT, YOU
SEEN IT?
>> Suzanne: , YEAH, I SAW IT.
>> Wendy: YOU THINK YOU KNOW
THE PEOPLE ARE?
>> Suzanne: YEAH, MAYBE.
I WILL LET YOU KNOW AFTER THE
SHOW WHAT I THINK.
>> Nick: PEOPLE TALK ABOUT.
SINCE I AM HERE AND I'M SINGLE,
I THOUGHT I WOULD FLIP IT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WHAT BETTER WAY TO FIND A DATE
THAN TO PLAY "THE MASKED DATING
GAME?"
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WHERE WE HAVE LADIES WEARING A
MASK.
I'M GOING TO REALLY GO ON A
DATE.
I'M GOING TO FIND IT, JUST LIKE
THE STRICT DATING IMPROVEMENT
PAID BUT INEQUITABLY THEY ARE.
THEY WILL REVEAL THEIR IDENTITY
AT THE END.
WITH STUDENT.
Y'ALL READY TO PLAY?
[APPLAUSE]
ANNOUNCER, LET'S MEET BACHELOR
NUMBER ONE!
>> Announcer: OUR FIRST
BACHELOR IS LINDA, A
PROFESSIONAL MAKEUP ARTIST FROM
EL SALVADOR WHO HAD A CRUSH ON
NIXON'S "DRUM LINE."
JUST LIKE A REAL UNICORN, SHE IS
A RARE FIND.
YOU DON'T WANT TO LOSE HER ONCE
YOU'VE GOT HER.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: ALL RIGHT, WITH THE
UNICORN.
THERE IS SOME FINENESS UP UNDER
THERE.
I CAN TELL.
LET'S MEET BACHELOR NUMBER TWO!
>> Announcer: OUR SECOND
BACHELOR IT IS THE DATA, A HOT
JAMAICAN FROM BROOKLYN WHO ISN'T
AFRAID TO SAY IT LIKE SHE MEANS
IT.
SHE CAN BE SWEET, BUT SHE ISN'T
AFRAID TO WALK ON THE WILD SIDE.
BE CAREFUL, NICK.
THIS CAT WILL MAKE YOU PURR ALL
NIGHT LONG.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: MAKE ME PURR ALL
NIGHT LONG?
I HEARD THAT, JADA!
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S MEET BACHELOR NUMBER
THREE.
>> Announcer: OUR LAST
BACHELOR IT IS CHARLIE, A MODEL
FROM LOS ANGELES WHO IS
ATTRACTED TO NICK'S MIND, BODY,
AND SOUL.
THIS INDEPENDENT WOMAN KNOWS
EXACTLY WHAT SHE WANTS, AND NO
ONE IS BEATING THIS BUNNY IN A
RACE TO NICK'S HEART.
[APPLAUSE]
SP ONE OH!
A BUNNY, A CAT, AND A UNICORN.
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS GOING TO GET
INTERESTING.
Y'ALL READY FOR THE FIRST
QUESTION?
[APPLAUSE]
ARE ALL ABOUT FIRST IMPRESSIONS.
BACHELOR NUMBER ONE, TELL ME
SOMETHING ABOUT YOURSELF THAT
WILL IMPRESS.
>> NICK, I'M A TRUE LATINA.
I WORK HARD, I LOVE HARD, I PLAY
HARD.
I'M LIKE A DRUG.
ONCE YOU GET A TASTE OF THIS,
YOU WON'T LET GO.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: THAT'S -- THAT'S
IMPRESSIVE AND SCARY ALL AT THE
SAME TIME!
I'M ALL ABOUT THE LATINA!
MUY CALIENTE, ME GUSTA, TE QUIE
RO MUCHO!
BUT I DON'T WANT NO DRUGS, I'M
DRUG-FREE.
BACHELOR NUMBER TWO, SAME
QUESTION.
>> HONESTLY, NICK, I'M VERY
UPFRONT ABOUT WHAT I WANT.
IT'S UP TO YOU WHETHER YOU LIKE
IT OR NOT, SO...
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
I'M GOING TO HAVE FUN, BUT I
DON'T PLAY NO GAMES.
>> Nick: IT'S YOU AND BECOME
ALL RIGHT!
I'M NOT MAD AT THAT.
BACHELOR NUMBER THREE COME US IN
QUESTION.
HOW WOULD YOU IMPRESS ME CLOSE
TO MEXICO NICK, YOU'RE EXACTLY
MY TYPE.
YOUR CHARMING, YOU ARE SEXY, AND
YOU GOT A GOOD SENSE OF STYLE.
SO I KNOW THAT IF YOU PICK ME
I'M DEFINITELY GOING TO BE A
GOOD ACCESSORY ON YOUR ARM.
>> Nick: KILLING YOU WITH THE
COMPLIMENTS!
I LIKE THAT.
THAT'S IMPRESSIVE.
THIS IS GOING TO BE TOUGH.
BACHELOR NUMBER ONE, YOU KNOW
I'M ALWAYS TRAVELING.
WOULD YOU DROP EVERYTHING TO GO
BE WITH ME?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I LOVE TO TRAVEL.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO SEE THE
WORLD.
IF I'M WITH YOU, WHAT ELSE DO I
NEED?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Nick: ALL RIGHT.
WELL, MAYBE I'M TRYING TO TRAVEL
BY WRITING A UNICORN!
YOU NEVER KNOW!
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
SEE, YELLED TO GET THERE!
IT'S A FAMILY SHOW!
PEGASUS.
NEVER MIND.
[LAUGHTER]
BACHELOR NUMBER TWO, I HAVE A
LOT OF FEMALE FANS.
HOW WOULD YOU HANDLE IT?
>> THAT SOUNDS LIKE A PARTY, TO
BE HONEST.
THE MORE THE MERRIER.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
I'M VERY OPEN!
I'M VERY OPEN INTO BRINGING
SOMEONE INTO OUR RELATIONSHIP.
>> Nick: I LOVE A PARTY.
BACHELOR NUMBER THREE.
EVERYONE KNOWS, I HAVE THREE
CHILDREN.
I'VE GOT TO KEEP IT ALL THE WAY
REAL.
I WOULD YOU FEEL ABOUT THEM
BEING MY NUMBER ONE PRIORITY?
THEY ARE FIRST.
>> NICK, I HAVE A DAUGHTER
MYSELF.
SO I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE TO PUT
YOUR CHILDREN FIRST.
I ALSO UNDERSTAND THE BALANCE
BETWEEN A CAREER, RAISING A
FAMILY, AND ALSO BEING IN A
RELATIONSHIP.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Wendy: OUR KIDS COULD PLAY
TOGETHER!
GOOD ANSWER.
THIS IS MY LAST QUESTION.
I HAVE A NEW SINGLE FEATURING A
FEW RAPPERS.
WHEN I HIT THE TRACK, I'VE --
YOU'LL HAVE GOT TO HAVE SIMPLY
BECOME UNITS OF RHYTHM.
YOU NEED TO MOVE IT.
I NEED YOU TO SHOW ME SOME
MOVES.
BACHELOR NUMBER ONE, PUT A
LITTLE ETCHING ON!
WHOM WENT THE TRACK, LET'S GET
IT TO IT!
♪ ♪
>> Nick: ALL RIGHT!
THERE WAS SOMETHING THERE!
SHE HAD ME, SHE WAS DROPPING
LOW.
PICKED IT BACK UP.
BACHELOR AT NUMBER TWO, YOU ARE
NEXT!
HIT THE MUSIC!
♪ ♪
>> Nick: BACHELOR NUMBER
THREE, EUROPE!
LET'S KEEP IT GOING, DJ!
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THAT WAS IMPRESSIVE!
BACHELORETTE NUMBER -- WHO DO
YOU THINK I SHOULD PICK?
SHOUT OUT TO THE HULA-HOOP!
I DON'T KNOW.
UP NEXT, I'M GOING TO PICK MY
BACHELORETTE!
KEEP IT RIGHT HERE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
Stouffer's Lasagna With Meat &
Sauce
has two times the beef of the
leading meat sauce lasagna.
That's double the tender ground
beef
baked into every cheesy,
mouthwatering bite.
When it comes to irresistible
taste,
more is always more.
Stouffer's.
>> Nick: ALL RIGHT, Y'ALL.
I'M BACK WITH MY MASKED
BACHELORETTE.
GIVE IT UP FOR HER.
AND I CHOOSE...
BACHELORETTE NUMBER TWO!
COME ON OVER HERE, QUEEN.
BEFORE REVEAL WHO BACHELORETTE
NUMBER TWO IS, LET'S REVIEW OUR
OTHER BEAUTIFUL QUEENS.
BACHELOR NUMBER ONE?
TAKE OFF YOUR MASK!
[APPLAUSE]
CAN I DO MORE THAN ONE?
PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> Nick: AMAZING.
NUMBER THREE, REVEAL YOUR MASK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
Y'ALL MAKE SOME NOISE FOR THEM!
[APPLAUSE]
I LIKE BUNNIES AND UNICORNS.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT, I THINK I
MAKE THE RIGHT DECISION.
OF COURSE THEY WERE BEAUTIFUL,
BUT I'VE GOT A FEELING MY
WINTER -- TAKE OFF YOUR MASK,
BABY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
OH, YES!
WE REALLY GOING TO DINNER!
WERE GOING TO THE LONGBOAT HOUSE
RESTAURANT CENTRAL PARK.
THIS HAS PROBABLY BEEN THE MOST
AMAZING HOSTING JOB I'VE EVER
HAD!
I LOVE "THE MASKED SINGER," BUT
I DON'T GET GIRLFRIENDS ON
"THE MASKED SINGER."
I ONLY GET EXTRA FRIENDS THERE.
"THE MASKED SINGER," TONIGHT AT
9:00 ON FOX.
CHECK US OUT.S OUT.
"LOOSE CANNON" IS NEXT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
RISK OF
>> Nick: IF YOU ARE IN
NEW YORK CITY AND YOU WANT TO BE
A PART OF STUDIO AUDIENCE, THE
TICKETS ARE FREE!
GO TO WendyShow.com.
COME HANG WITH US, Y'ALL.
WE WILL BEWE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
Got it?
Got it.
Nooooo...
Quick, the Quicker Picker Upper!
Bounty picks up messes quicker
and is 2x more absorbent.
Bounty, the Quicker Picker
Upper.
>> Nick: ALL RIGHT, BEFORE I
SHOW I HIT THE STREETS TO PLAY
"HOT TOPICS" FOR CASH.
GO TO WendyShow.com TO CHECK
IT OUT, Y'ALL.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪AUSE]
♪ ♪
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
>> Nick: YOU KNOW I HAD SUCH A
GREAT TIME POSTING.
DID Y'ALL HAVE FUN?
I HAD MY SUPER OUTFIT ON.
DID YOU LIKE MY OUTFIT TODAY?
I'VE GOT TO GO.
TOMORROW, THE VERY FUNNY JASON
BIGS WILL BE GUEST HOSTING.
Y'ALL WILL HAVE A GREAT TIME
PRAY I WILL BE WATCHING.
WE WILL SEE YOU NEXT TIME, Y'AL
Y'ALL.
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
"THE