>> Announcer: "THIS WEEK" WITH
GEORGE STEPHANOPOULOS STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
>>> COUNTDOWN TO COHEN.
>> MICHAEL COHEN'S TESTIMONY?
>> NO, NO.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP'S FORMER
FIXER SET TO PULL BACK THE
CURTAIN ON HIS TIME WITH TRUMP
BEFORE THREE COMMITTEES IN
CONGRESS.
COHEN SAYS HE'LL TELL THE TRUTH
ABOUT TRUMP AFTER YEARS OF LIES.
HE'S COOPERATING AGAIN WITH
PROSECUTORS IN NEW YORK.
WILL THIS NEW TESTIMONY POSE A
THREAT TO PRESIDENT TRUMP EVEN
AFTER ROBERT MUELLER COMPLETES
HIS INVESTIGATION?
THAT AND MORE WITH HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE CHAIR ADAM SCHIFF,
OUR LEGAL EXPERTS DAN ABRAMS AND
ALAN DERSHOWITZ AND ANDREW
McCABE WHOSE NEW TELL ALL IS
DRAWING FIRE FROM TRUMP.
>>> AND --
>> THERE HAS BEEN NO NUCLEAR
TESTING, NO MISSILES, NO
ROCKETS.
>> NO SIGNS YET THAT NORTH KOREA
IS READY TO GIVE UP ITS NUCLEAR
ARSENAL.
WILL A SECOND MEETING WITH KIM
JONG-UN BRING REAL PROGRESS?
INSIDE ANALYSIS WITH OUR PANEL
OF EXPERTS INCLUDING THE
AMBASSADOR WHO NEGOTIATED WITH
NORTH KOREA, BILL RICHARDSON.
>>> PLUS, BERNIE IS BACK.
>> AND OUR 2016 POLITICAL
CAMPAIGN BEGAN THE REVOLUTION.
NOW IT IS TIME TO COMPLETE THAT
REVOLUTION.
>> HIS STAYING POWER SHOCKED THE
POLITICAL WORLD IN 2016.
HIS NATIONAL MOVEMENT IS A
FUND-RAISING JUGGERNAUT.
CAN HE STAY IN THE CYCLE OF THE
WIDE OPEN RACE FOR THE WHITE
HOUSE?
OUR ROUND TABLE WEIGHS IN ON
WHAT'S AT STAKE IN 2020, THE
ISSUES AT PLAY AND WHO IS MAKING
HEADWAY.
WE'LL BREAK DOWN THE POLITICS,
SMOKE OUT THE SPIN.
THE FACTS THAT MATTER THIS WEEK.
>>> GOOD MORNING AND WELCOME TO
"THIS WEEK."
IT'S A BIG WEEK AHEAD FOR THE
PRESIDENT ON TWO VERY DIFFERENT
FRONTS.
TOMORROW HE BOARDS AIR FORCE ONE
FOR VIETNAM, THE SITE OF HIS
SECOND SUMMIT WITH KIM JONG-UN
WHO IS ON HIS WAY TO HANOI.
YOU SEE HIM THERE ON HIS ARMORED
TRAIN ARRIVING IN CHINA
YESTERDAY.
JUST AS TRUMP TRIES TO STRIKE A
NUCLEAR DEAL WITH KIM JONG-UN,
MICHAEL COHEN WILL TAKE THE
WASHINGTON SPOTLIGHT.
THREE DAYS OF HEARINGS ON
CAPITOL HILL INCLUDING
BLOCKBUSTER PUBLIC TESTIMONY IN
THE HOUSE ON WEDNESDAY.
COHEN'S LAWYER SAYS HE'S
PREPARED TO REVEAL DAMNING
DETAILS OF HIS YEARS AS TRUMP'S
ATTORNEY AND FIXER.
PROMISING A CHILLING PORTRAIT OF
THE PRESIDENT.
IT COMES AS COHEN CONTINUES TO
COOPERATE WITH PROSECUTORS
OFFERING LEADS, AND INSURANCE
REGULARITIES AT THE TRUMP
ORGANIZATION.
AND THAT INVESTIGATION IN NEW
YORK'S SOUTHERN DISTRICT, JUST
ONE OF SEVERAL PROBES POISED TO
CHALLENGE THE PRESIDENT WELL
BEYOND THE END OF ROBERT
MUELLER'S WORK.
WE START WITH THE MAN LEADING
ONE OF THOSE INVESTIGATIONS, THE
CHAIR OF THE HOUSE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE CONGRESSMAN SCHIFF.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US THIS
MORNING.
>> THANK YOU.
>> MICHAEL COHEN APPEARING
BEHIND CLOSED DOORS ON THURSDAY.
WHAT DO YOU HOPE TO LEARN FROM
HIM YOU DON'T ALREADY KNOW?
>> A GREAT DEAL STARTING WITH
WHY THE FALSE STATEMENTS BEFORE
OUR COMMITTEE WHEN HE FIRST
APPEARED.
DID THEY GO BEYOND WHAT HE TOLD
US ABOUT MOSCOW TRUMP TOWER INTO
OTHER AREAS AS WELL?
WHO WOULD HAVE BEEN AWARE OF THE
FALSE TESTIMONY THAT HE WAS
GIVING?
WHAT OTHER LIGHT CAN HE SHED NOW
THAT HE'S COOPERATING ON ISSUES
OF OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE OR
COLLUSION?
WHAT MORE COULD HE TELL US ABOUT
THE TRUMP TOWER NEW YORK MEETING
OR ANY OTHER ISSUES RELEVANT TO
OUR INVESTIGATION.
WE THINK HE HAS A LOT TO OFFER.
>> HOW ABOUT THE FINANCES OF THE
TRUMP ORGANIZATION?
YOU HAVE SUGGESTED THAT'S THE
NEW FRONT IN YOUR COMMITTEE'S
INVESTIGATION.
>> WELL, THIS IS SOMETHING,
GEORGE, AS YOU KNOW, I HAVE BEEN
CONCERNED ABOUT FOR TWO YEARS
NOW.
WE WEREN'T REALLY PERMITTED TO
EXPLORE IT IN GREAT DETAIL WHEN
THE REPUBLICANS WERE RUNNING THE
COMMITTEE, BUT WE KNOW ALREADY
AND MICHAEL COHEN IS PIVOTAL TO
THIS, THE PERIL OF IGNORING OR
OBSERVING THIS RED LINE OF THE
PRESIDENT'S AND IGNORING THE
FINANCIAL ISSUES.
WHAT WE HAVE LEARNED TO DATE
ABOUT MOSCOW TRUMP TOWER IS
CHILLING AND THAT IS AS DONALD
TRUMP WAS CAMPAIGNING FOR
PRESIDENT, EVEN WHEN IT BECAME
THE PRESUMPTIVE NOMINEE OF THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY AND HE WAS
TELLING THE COUNTRY HE HAD NO
BUSINESS DEALINGS WITH RUSSIA,
HE WAS PRIVATELY THROUGH HIS
ORGANIZATION SEEKING THE
KREMLIN'S HELP TO WHAT MAY HAVE
BEEN THE MOST LUCRATIVE DEAL OF
HIS LIFE, EVEN REPORTEDLY
OFFERING AN INDUCEMENT TO PUTIN
TO MAKE IT HAPPEN AND AT THE
SAME TIME, TALKING ABOUT
REMOVING SANCTIONS ON RUSSIA.
THAT'S SOMETHING VERY IMPORTANT
TO THE RUSSIANS AND THAT IS
DEEPLY COMPROMISING.
WHETHER IT'S CRIMINAL OR NOT,
IT'S DEEPLY COMPROMISING OF OUR
NATIONAL SECURITY, SO THOSE
ISSUES HAVE TO BE PROBED AND
THEY INCLUDE MONEY LAUNDERING AS
WELL.
>> IF IT TURNS OUT AS THE
PRESIDENT HAS SAID SO MANY TIMES
THAT HE DID NOT COLLUDE WITH THE
RUSSIANS TO INTERFERE IN THE
ELECTION, BUT, IN FACT, HE WAS
PURSUING THIS TRUMP TOWER AT THE
SAME TIME, IF THAT'S NOT
CRIMINAL, DOES MUELLER HAVE A
RESPONSIBILITY TO REPORT IT OR
NO?
>> HE DOES HAVE A RESPONSIBILITY
TO REPORT IT AND, IN FACT, IF
YOU TAKE THE POSITION, AND I
THINK IT'S A FLAWED ONE, BUT IF
YOU TAKE THE POSITION THAT THE
PRESIDENT CANNOT BE INDICTED AND
THE ONLY REMEDY FOR IMPROPER,
ILLEGAL OR OTHER CONDUCT IS
IMPEACHMENT, THEN YOU CANNOT
WITHHOLD THAT INFORMATION FROM
CONGRESS.
THAT CANNOT BE ALLOWED TO BE THE
CASE.
BILL BARR HAS COMMITTED IN HIS
TESTIMONY TO MAKING AS YOUMUCH
THE REPORT PUBLIC AS HE CAN, AND
THE REGULATIONS WILL MAKE IT
ALL.
AND WE INSIST ON IT BECOMING
PUBLIC AND WE INSIST ON THE
UN
UNDERLYING EVIDENCE BECAUSE
THERE IS CERTAIN EVIDENCE IN THE
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE THAT WE
CAN'T GET ANY OTHER WAY.
THE SEARCHES WERE CONDUCTED FOR
EXAMPLE OF ROGER STONE AND PAUL
MANAFORT.
THERE IS NO OTHER WAY TO GET THE
INVEST THAT WAS SEIZED EXCEPT
THROUGH THE DEPARTMENT AND WE
CAN'T TELL THE COUNTRY FULLY
WHAT HAPPENED WITHOUT IT.
>> WILLIAM BARR MAY HAVE A
DIFFERENT VIEW ABOUT WHAT THOSE
REGULATIONS REQUIRE THAN YOU DO.
THEY COULD ALLOW HIM TO RELEASE
THE ENTIRE REPORT, BUT UNDER
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT REGULATIONS,
OFFICIALS HAVE SAID THAT IF YOU
DECLINE TO PROSECUTE SOMEONE,
THE UNDERLYING EVIDENCE SHOULD
NOT BE RELEASED.
>> BUT GEORGE, THE DEPARTMENT
HAS VIOLATED THAT POLICY
REPEATEDLY, AND EXTENDEDLY -- TO
A GREAT EXTENT OVER THE LAST TWO
YEARS.
I HAVE HAD THIS CONVERSATION
WITH ROD ROSENSTEIN AND OTHERS
DOWN AT THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
AS THEY TURNED OVER THOUSANDS
AND THOUSANDS OF PAGES OF
DISCOVERY IN THE CLINTON E-MAIL
INVESTIGATION AND THERE WAS NO
INDICTMENT IN THAT
INVESTIGATION, THAT THIS WAS A
NEW PRECEDENT THEY WERE SETTING
AND THEY WERE GOING TO HAVE TO
LIVE BY THIS PRECEDENT WHETHER
IT WAS A CONGRESS CONTROLLED BY
THE DEMOCRATS OR REPUBLICANS.
SO THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
ABIDE BY THIS, AND I THINK ALSO
QUITE SEPARATE APART FROM THE
PRESIDENT AS THEY HAVE ALREADY
SAID IS THE INTENSE PUBLIC NEED
TO KNOW HERE WHICH I THINK
OVERRIDES ANY CONSIDERATION.
>> YOU SEE THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT IS GOING TO HAVE TO
LIVE BY THIS PRECEDENT, BUT WHAT
IF THEY DON'T?
WHAT IF THEY SAY NO?
WHAT PGSOPTIONS DO THEY HAVE?
>> WE WILL SUBPOENA THE REPORT
AND BRING BOB MUELLER IN TO
TESTIFY BEFORE CONGRESS AND TAKE
IT TO COURT IF NECESSARY.
AND IN THE ENDS, I THINK THE
DEPARTMENT UNDERSTANDS THEY'RE
GOING TO HAVE TO MAKE THIS
PUBLIC.
I THINK BARR WILL ULTIMATELY
UNDERSTAND THAT AS WELL.
BARR COMES INTO THIS JOB WITH
TWO STRIKES AGAINST HIM.
HE APPLIED FOR THE JOB BY BE
DEMONSTRATING A BIAS AGAINST THE
MUELLER INVESTIGATION.
THAT'S PART OF THE REASON HE WAS
HIRED.
HE HAS ALSO NOT BEEN COMMITTED
TO FOLLOWING THE ADVICE OF THE
ETHICS COMMITTEE.
IF HE WERE TRY TO WITHHOLD ANY
PART OF THIS REPORT, THAT WILL
BE HIS LEGACY AND IT WILL BE A
TARNISHED LEGACY.
I THINK THERE WILL BE IMMENSE
PRESSURE NOT ONLY ON THE
DEPARTMENT, BUT ON THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL TO BE FORTHCOMING.
>> YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT PUBLIC
PRESSURE.
ARE YOU PREPARED TO TAKE THE
ADMINISTRATION TO COURT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WE'RE GOING TO GET TO THE BOTTOM
OF THIS, AND WE SHARE THIS
INFORMATION WITH THE PUBLIC, AND
IF THE PRESIDENT IS SERIOUS
ABOUT ALL OF HIS CLAIMS OF
EXONERATION, THEN HE SHOULD
WELCOME THE PUBLICATION OF THIS
REPORT.
>> THE PRESIDENT HAS SAID NO
COLLUSION MANY TIMES AS I SAID.
YOU SAID MANY MONTHS AGO THAT
YOU HAVE ALREADY DEVELOPED
EVIDENCE OF COLLUSION.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN THAT FROM ROBERT
MUELLER.
DO YOU HAVE ANY EVIDENCE AT ALL
THAT THE PRESIDENT COLLUDED?
>> GEORGE, THERE IS AMPLE
EVIDENCE OF COLLUSION OF THE
CAMPAIGN, AND IT'S VERY MUCH IN
THE PUBLIC RECORD, AND IT'S
EVERYTHING FROM WHAT WE HAVE
SEEN RECENTLY ABOUT PAUL
MANAFORT MEETING WITH SOMEONE
LINKED TO RUSSIAN INTELLIGENCE
AND SHARING POLLING DATA, AND
NOT TOP LINE DATA.
NOT THIS IS WHY WE THINK TRUMP
IS GOING TO WIN DATA, BUT RAW
DATA, COMPLICATED DATA.
WE HAVE SEEN EVIDENCE OF ROGER
STONE IN COMMUNICATION WITH
WIKILEAKS.
WE HAVE SEEN THE PRESIDENT'S SON
HAVING A SECRET MEETING AT TRUMP
TOWER THAT WAS PRESENTED TO HIM
AS PART OF THE RUSSIAN
GOVERNMENT'S EFFORT TO HELP THE
TRUMP CAMPAIGN.
HIS ACCEPTANCE OF THAT HELP IS
INTERESTING.
GETTING THAT -- ALL OF THIS IS
EVIDENCE OF COLLUSION AND THERE
IS MUCH, MUCH MORE.
WHETHER THAT WILL AMOUNT TO A
CRIMINAL CONSPIRACY THAT COULD
BE PROVED BEYOND A REASONABLE
DOUBT, WE'LL HAVE TO WAIT FOR
BOB MUELLER TO TELL US, BUT NOT
TO SEE WHAT IS PLAINLY IN FRONT
OF US MEANS YOU BASICALLY DON'T
WANT TO SEE THE EVIDENCE OF
COLLUSION BECAUSE IT IS QUITE
ABUN TANT.
>> CONGRESSMAN SCHIFF, THANK YOU
FOR YOUR TIME.
LET'S BRING IN DAN ABRAMS AND
ALAN DERSHOWITZ, AUTHOR OF "THE
CASE AGAINST," AND LET'S TALK
ABOUT WHAT I WAS TALKING ABOUT
WITH CONGRESSMAN SCHIFF RIGHT
THERE.
HE SAYS THAT BILL BARR IS UNDER
TREMENDOUS PRESSURE TO RELEASE
WHATEVER HE'S -- WHATEVER
MUELLER HAS REPORTED PUBLICLY.
IT'S NOT CLEAR THAT BARR AGREES
WITH THAT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
BARR HAS MADE IT VERY CLEAR THAT
HE'S GOING TO RELEASE AS MUCH AS
HE CAN, BUT HE HAS PUT CAVEATS
ON THAT, AND THE QUESTION WILL
BE FOR EXAMPLE, HOW MUCH
INFORMATION IN THERE POTENTIALLY
COULD BE A NATIONAL SECURITY
THREAT?
AND I THINK YOU NEED TO SEPARATE
OUT THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN THE
REPORTED SELF AND THE UNDERLYING
INFORMATION BECAUSE YOU HEARD
CONGRESSMAN SCHIFF THERE TALKING
ABOUT SOME OF THE UNDERLYING
INFORMATION.
THAT'S GOING TO BE HARDER TO
GET.
>> EVEN THOUGH IT WAS ALL
RELEASED IN THE CLINTON
INVESTIGATION?
>> CORRECT.
YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER THAT THE
CURRENT SPECIAL COUNSEL LAW WAS
A RESPONSE TO THE CLINTON
INVESTIGATION MEANING THERE WERE
CONCERNS ABOUT HOW MUCH --
>> BILL CLINTON INVESTIGATION.
THE HILLARY CLINTON --
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
IN RESPONSE TO THE BILL CLINTON
INVESTIGATION, THIS IS A
RESPONSE TO THAT LAW.
ON THE HILLARY CLINTON
INVESTIGATION, LOOK.
I DON'T THINK THERE IS A DIRECT
COMPARISON BETWEEN THE HILLARY
CLINTON INVESTIGATION AND THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL INVESTIGATION.
I DO THINK THAT THERE IS A MUCH
STRONGER ARGUMENT TO SAY THAT A
SPECIAL COUNSEL INVESTIGATION
OUGHT TO BE MADE PUBLIC EVEN IF
THERE IS NO PROSECUTION, THAT
THE DECISION MAKING PROCESS FOR
THEM, THAT THE REPORT SHOULD BE
MADE PUBLIC EVEN IF IN TYPICALLY
IN THE DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE,
YOU WOULDN'T RELEASE INFORMATION
RELATED TO AN INVESTIGATION THAT
WAS NOT PROSECUTED.
>> WHAT'S YOUR SPOPS RESPONSE T,
ALAN?
>> I THINK THAT'S EXACTLY THE
ISSUE.
DEMOCRATS WERE APPROPRIATELY
FURIOUS.
I WAS AMONG THEM WHEN COMEY
AFTER SAYING THAT HE WAS NOT
GOING TO INDICT HILLARY CLINTON,
THEN WENT ON TO GIVE HIS OWN
OPINION AS TO HER WRONGDOING,
AND THE QUESTION IS, IS THERE A
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN COMEY WHO DID
WRONG?
EVERYBODY NOW ACKNOWLEDGES THAT,
AND A SPECIAL COUNSEL WHO HAS
HAD A BROADER MANDATE TO
INVESTIGATE.
LET'S BE REALISTIC.
IN THE END, EVERYTHING IS COME
OUT.
THERE ARE NO SECRETS.
IN THE END, IT'S ALL GOING TO
COME OUT AND IN THE END, AS I
SAID FROM DAY ONE, IT ONE OF SO
MUCH BETTER IF WE HAD A
NONPARTISAN, INDEPENDENT
COMMISSION LIKE THEY HAVE IN
ENGLAND AND IN ISRAEL, LIKE WE
HAD AFTER 9/11, GETTING TO THE
WHOLE TRUTH IN A NONPARTISAN
WAY.
THE AMERICAN PUBLIC IS NOT GOING
TO TRUST DEMOCRATIC CONTROL OF
THE HOUSE.
>> LET ME STOP YOU.
>> THEY'RE NOT GOING TO TRUST
THE REPUBLICAN-CONTROLLED
SENATE.
>> MUELLER IS ABOUT AS
NONPARTISAN AS YOU COULD HAVE
FOUND, ISN'T HE?
>> IF HIS INFORMATION IS NOT
RELEASED TO THE PUBLIC AND IT
THEN GOES TO CONGRESS TO CONDUCT
THE INVESTIGATION, I THINK THERE
WILL BE A QUESTION OF
CREDIBILITY.
LOOK.
I THINK AND I HAVE SAID FROM DAY
ONE THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
GREATEST VULNERABILITY LIES NOT
WITH THE MUELLER REPORT, BUT
WITH THE SOUTHERN DISTRICT OF
NEW YORK AND WITH THE NEW YORK
ATTORNEY GENERAL'S OFFICE, AND
WITH OTHER PROSECUTORIAL ARMS
THAT CAN LOOK INTO CONDUCT
UNRELATED TO COLLUSION TO
RUSSIA, BUT CONDUCT PRECEDING
HIS PRESIDENCY AND THAT'S WHERE
PROBLEMS CAN COME UP IN THE
FUTURE.
THIS MAY BE JUST THE BEGINNING.
THE MUELLER REPORT MAY BE JUST A
ROAD MAP GIVEN TO CONGRESS AND
GIVEN TO OTHER PROSECUTORS THAT
WILL CONTINUE THESE
INVESTIGATIONS UNTIL THE END OF
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>> WE MAY BE HAVING A MUELLER
STRATEGY IN PLAIN SIGHT.
EVERY INDICTMENT HE HAS LAYS OUT
IN GREAT DETAIL WHAT HE THOUGHT
HAPPENED.
IN THE MEANTIME, THINGS THAT HE
THINKS MAY BE A BIT BEYOND HIS
SCOPE, HE SIPHONS OFF TO OTHER
PROSECUTORS.
>> RIGHT, AND I THINK ALAN IS
RIGHT THAT POSES AN ENORMOUS
DANGER TO HIM IN THE OFFICE.
YOU CAN'T JUST SAY THE SOUTHERN
DISTRICT OF NEW YORK IS OUT TO
GET ME AND THE EASTERN DISTRICT
OF NEW YORK IS OUT TO GET ME AND
VIRGINIA IS OUT TO GET ME, ET
CETERA.
THAT'S A TOUGH ARGUMENT TO MAKE,
BUT WHEN YOU LOOK AT --
>> I AGREE.
>> SOME OF THE DOCUMENTS THAT
HAVE BEEN FILED LIKE IN THE
MANAFORT CASE, AND THE ROAD MAP,
YOU HAVE TO ASK THE QUESTION AND
THE BIG PICTURE, WHY IS SO MUCH
REDACTED?
WHY ARE THEY STILL NOT ALLOWING
THE PUBLIC TO SEE SO MUCH
RELATED TO THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION?
WHY ISN'T MICHAEL COHEN BEING
ALLOWED TO TESTIFY IN PUBLIC
ABOUT THE RUSSIA INVESTIGATION?
>> HE'S ONLY GOING TO BE TALKING
ABOUT OTHER INVESTIGATIONS.
>> TEN OTHER TOPICS NOT RELATED
TO RUSSIA.
IF THERE IS NOTHING ELSE THAT'S
GOING TO COME OUT, WHY ARE THEY
REDACTING SO MUCH?
>> 800 PAGES FROM ROBERT MUELLER
YESTERDAY IN THE MANAFORT
SENTENCING MEMO, YET NOTHING
ABOUT THE UNDERLYING THINGS HE
MAY HAVE BEEN LYING ABOUT.
HIS MEETINGS WITH VARIOUS
RUSSIANS AND THEY SAY THE
REDACTIONS WERE FOR ONGOING
INVESTIGATIONS AND UNCHARGED
INDIVIDUALS.
THAT DOES SUGGEST MORE TO COMP.
>> OH, ABSOLUTELY.
I HAVE NO DOUBT ABOUT THAT.
I THINK THESE REDACTIONS ARE A
CLUE TO WHAT MAY BE HINTED AT.
LOOK.
ALSO I THINK WE ARE SEEING NOW
AN EFFORT TO TAMP DOWN
EXPECTATIONS FROM THE MUELLER
REPORT ITSELF.
I THINK WE'RE BEING TOLD, DON'T
EXPECT SMOKING GUNS.
DON'T EXPECT DYNAMITE IN THE
REPORT.
THE REPORT IS GOING TO BE THE
BEGINNING OF SOME OTHER
INVESTIGATIONS COMING DOWN THE
LINE SO I THINK THERE IS A
COMBINATION.
DON'T EXPECT TOO MUCH FROM THE
MUELLER REPORT ITSELF, BUT THE
MUELLER REPORT MAY LEAD TO
GREATER INVESTIGATIONS BY A
VARIETY OF OTHER INSTITUTIONS SO
THIS -- THE MUELLER REPORT IS
NOT GOING TO MARK THE END OF THE
INVESTIGATION.
I THINK THAT'S THE MESSAGE WE'RE
HEARING.
>> SO MUCH REPORTING ON THE
MUELLER REPORT.
IT'S UNFOUNDED BECAUSE ROBERT
MUELLER ISN'T TALKING AND THERE
HAS BEEN RATHER AGGRESSIVE
BACKGROUNDING GOING ON
SUGGESTING THAT THE MUELLER
REPORT WILL BE AN ANTI-CLIMAX.
>> YEAH, AND LOOK.
THE EXPECTATION GAME IS CRITICAL
WHEN IT COMES TO PUBLIC
PERCEPTION, BUT WHETHER IT'S A
SUMMARY, WHETHER IT'S A DETAILED
ACCOUNTING, DON'T FORGET WE
ALREADY HAVE A LOT OF
INFORMATION, AND I'M NOT JUST
TALKING ABOUT WHAT CONGRESSMAN
SCHIFF WAS TALKING ABOUT, BUT
THE INDICTMENTS THAT CURRENTLY
EXIST.
WHEN PEOPLE WANT TO NE WHAT
HAPPENED LEADING UP TO THE 2016
ELECTION, YOU HAVE TO START BY
READING THE INDICTMENTS.
YOU HAVE TO START BY READING THE
INDICTMENTS OF THE RUSSIANS AND
THEN ASK YOURSELF, OKAY.
WAS ANYONE ELSE CONNECTED TO
THEM, AND THAT'S WHAT THEY'RE
TRYING TO PIECE TOGETHER STILL.
WHEN YOU HAVE PAPADOPOULOS
LYING, FLYNN LYING ABOUT RUSSIA.
YOU HAVE GOT MANAFORT LYING, ET
CETERA.
YOU HAVE TO ASK YOURSELF,WHY ARE
ALL THESE PEOPLE NOT TELLING THE
TRUTH?
THE ANSWER MAY SIMPLY BE, YOU
KNOW, LOOK.
I WANTED TO DISTANCE MYSELF FROM
IT.
I DIDN'T WANT TO GET IN TROUBLE
IN CONNECTION WITH THIS THING,
BUT THERE ARE STILL CRITICAL
QUESTIONS THAT ARE UNANSWERED.
THERE IS A TON OF REDACTED
MATERIAL, AND, YOU KNOW, I
THINK -- WE'RE GOING TO SEE SOME
ANSWERS.
>> WE'RE WAITING FOR ROBERT
MUELLER.
>> LET'S REMEMBER THOUGH.
>> GO AHEAD.
>> INDICTMENTS ARE DIFFERENT
THAN CONVICTIONS AND A LOT OF
THIS IS INDICTMENTS AND REMEMBER
TOO.
WE'RE GOING TO SEE A REBUTTAL
REPORT FROM THE TRUMP TEAM.
I THINK THE AMERICAN PUBLISHER
WILL WITHHOLD FINAL JUDGMENT
UNTIL THEY SEE BOTH REPORTS.
>> THIS WILL BE THE FIRST TIME
IN THE HISTORY OF AMERICA WHERE
A DEFENDANT OR SOMEONE WHO IS
ACCUSED OF SOMETHING GETS TO
WRITE A RESPONSE REPORT TO WHAT
AN INDICTMENT IS.
EVERY CRIMINAL DEFENDANT IN
AMERICA WOULD LOVE TO BE ABLE TO
WRITE THEIR OWN REPORT ABOUT
WHAT THEY SAY HAPPENED, BUT
THAT'S NOT THE WAY THE SYSTEM
WORKS.
>> YOU'RE CONTRADICTS YOURSELF.
THIS IS NOT JUST A YES OR NO.
YOU'RE SAYING THAT SPECIAL
COUNSEL HAVE SPECIAL OBLIGATIONS
TO RELEASE EVERYTHING.
>> YES.
>> IF THEY HAVE AN OBLIGATION TO
RELEASE EVERYTHING, THEY CAN
ALLOW A RESPONSE.
>> LET HIM RESPOND.
LET HIM RESPOND.
>> YES OR NO, YOU WOULDN'T NEED
A RESPONSE, BUT IF YOU GET A
LONG, LONG NARRATIVE, THEN
FAIRNESS REQUIRES A RESPONSE.
>> THAT'S FINE.
LET HIM RESPOND.
>> SIMULTANEOUS RELEASE OF BOTH.
>> BOTH TOO.
>> RIGHT.
YES.
>> THAT'S JUST -- THAT'S
RIDICULOUS THE IDEA THAT YOU
HAVE TO ALLOW THE OTHER SIDE IN
SOMETHING LIKE THIS, THE
OPPORTUNITY TO FILE A LONG
REPORT IN RESPONSE TO A
PROSECUTOR.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT IF
YOU JUST LIMIT YOURSELF TO
INDICTMENT OR NOT INDICTMENT,
BUT IF YOU GO BEYOND IT AND YOU
START TELLING A STORY, THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE NARRATIVE HAS TO BE
PRODUCED AS WELL.
THAT'S REQUIRED BY FAIRNESS AND
DUE PROCESS.
>> BILL CLINTON WOULD LOVE THAT.
>> NOT IN THE REGULATIONS.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, ANDREW
McCABE UP NEXT, AND THE ROUND
TABLE TAKES ON 2020.
THAT WILL BE UP NEXT.
When you retire will you
act or feel different?
Or will you just be you,
without the constraints
of a full time job?
You can grow your retirement
savings with Pacific Life
and create the future that's
most meaningful to you.
Which means you can retire,
without retiring from life.
Having the flexibility to
retire on your terms.
That's the Power of Pacific.
Ask your financial professional
about Pacific Life today.
98% of us don't get enough
omega-3s.
Which is why MegaRed Advanced
4in1
packs more omega-3 power into
one small softgel.
It supports your heart...
Brain... Eyes... And joints.
MegaRed.
Prestige creams not living up to
the hype?
One jar shatters the
competition.
Olay Regenerist hydrates skin
better than creams
costing over $100, $200, and
even $400.
Fact check this ad in Good
Housekeeping.
Olay.
For singing definitely dry mouth
has been a problem for me.
I'm also on a lot of medications
that dry my mouth.
I just drank tons of water
all the time.
It was never enough.
I wasn't sure I was going to
be able to continue singing.
I saw my dentist.
He suggested Biotene.
It feels refreshing.
My mouth felt more lubricated.
I use Biotene Rinse twice a day
and then I use the spray
throughout the day.
it actually saved my
career in a way.
Biotene really did
make a difference.
[heartbeat]
WELCOME TO FOWLER, INDIANA.
ONE OF THE WINDIEST
PLACES IN AMERICA.
AND HOME TO THREE
BP WIND FARMS.
IN THE OFF-CHANCE THE WIND
EVER STOPS BLOWING HERE...
THE LIGHTS CAN KEEP ON SHINING.
THANKS TO OUR NATURAL GAS.
A SMART PARTNER TO
RENEWABLE ENERGY.
IT'S ALWAYS READY WHEN NEEDED.
OR... NOT.
AT BP, WE SEE
POSSIBILITIES EVERYWHERE.
TO HELP THE WORLD
KEEP ADVANCING.
For the 250K service members
who transition out of the U.S.
military every year...
...one of the toughest parts
is the search for a job
that takes advantage
of the skills
you've gained while serving.
You can now search with the
phrase 'jobs for veterans'
directly on Google...
...and then enter your Military
Occupational Specialty Code.
Google brings together job
openings from across the web
that match the skills you
gained in your military role.
Just click to apply
and use your experience
to guide your future.
No matter how much you clean,
does your house still smell
stuffy?
That's because your home is
filled
with soft surfaces that trap
odors
and release them back into the
room.
So, try Febreze Fabric
Refresher.
Febreze finds odors trapped in
fabrics
and cleans them away as it
dries.
Use Febreze every time you tidy
up
to keep your whole house
smelling fresh air clean.
Fabric Refresher even works for
clothes you want
to wear another day.
Make Febreze part of your clean
routine
for whole home freshness.
This is Charlie not coughing
because he took Delsym 12-hour.
And this is Charlie still not
coughing
while trying his hardest not to
wake Zeus.
Delsym 12-hour.
Nothing lasts
longer for powerful
cough relief.
They're our parents...
neighbors... loved ones.
Living with diseases like
cancer, epilepsy,
mental health conditions
and HIV.
Maybe you're one of them.
But new Medicare rules could
deny access to the latest,
most effective therapies...
therapies that keep
them healthy.
Are Medicare cuts that save less
than one percent
worth the risk to millions of
patients?
President Trump promised
to protect Medicare...
We need him to keep his word.
>>> I THINK ANDREW McCABE HAS
MADE A FOOL OUT OF HIMSELF OVER
THE LAST COUPLE OF DAYS AND HE
LOOKED TO ME LIKE A POOR MAN'S
J. EDGAR HOOVER.
I THINK HE'S A DISASTER, AND
WHAT HE WAS TRYING TO DO IS
TERRIBLE AND HE WAS CAUGHT.
I'M VERY PROUD TO SAY WE CAUGHT
HIM.
SO WE'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS, BUT
HE -- HE IS A DISGRACED MAN.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP TAKING ON OUR
NEXT GUEST, ANDREW McCABE.
HIS NEW BOOK, "THE THREAT: HOW
THE FBI PROTECTS AMERICA IN THE
AGE OF TERROR AND TRUMP," TAKES
US BEHIND THE SCENES OF THE
LAUNCH OF THE MUELLER
INVESTIGATION.
WELCOME TO "THIS WEEK."
POOR MAN'S J. EDGAR HOOVER?
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT THAT
MEANS.
THAT'S NOT THE FIRST TIME I HAVE
HAD TO LISTEN TO THE PRESIDENT
SAY BIZARRE AND UNTRUE THINGS
ABOUT ME, SO IT'S UNFORTUNATE
THIS IS GETTING A LITTLE BIT
ROUTINE, BUT I WILL SAY, YOU
KNOW, I DON'T THINK THERE IS
ANYTHING SAD OR UNFORTUNATE
ABOUT SPEAKING TRUTH TO POWER
AND TELLING THE STORY THAT YOU
LIVED AND THE THINGS YOU SAW AND
HEARD AND THE REASONS BEHIND THE
DECISIONS YOU MADE AND THAT'S
WHAT I HAVE TRIED TO DO WITH THE
BOOK.
>> ANOTHER MAN WHO HAS A
REPUTATION, MUELLER.
YOU WORKED FOR HIM AT THE FBI.
>> I DID.
>> BASED ON WHAT YOU KNOW, AND
YOU HEARD OUR PREVIOUS
DISCUSSION.
WHAT SHOULD WE EXPECT FROM
ROBERT MUELLER?
KIND OF A NARROW BY THE BOOK
PROSECUTOR REPORTING OR SOMEONE
WHO SENSES HE HAS A BROADER
RESPONSIBILITY TO THE PUBLIC?
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S A GREAT
QUESTION, GEORGE.
I THINK FIRST AND FOREMOST WHAT
YOU CAN EXPECT FROM ROBERT
MUELLER IS AN HONEST,
INDEPENDENT ASSESSMENT OF THE
WORK THAT THEY HAVE DONE.
HOW MUCH DETAIL HE CHOOSES TO GO
INTO, TO CONVEY TO THE
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE IS A GREAT
QUESTION.
I HOPE THEY LEAN ON THE DETAILED
SIDE.
THIS IS NOT A NORMAL
INVESTIGATION BY ANY EVALUATION.
IT'S ONE THAT I THINK THE
DEPARTMENT, CONGRESS AND THE
PUBLIC HAVE ENORMOUS INTEREST IN
FINDING OUT WHAT THEY ARE.
>> IT'S COMPLICATED IN SO MANY
WAYS INCLUDING THE PRECEDENT OF
THE HILLARY CLINTON
INVESTIGATION.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> THE FBI RELEASED ALL THAT
INFORMATION ABOUT HER.
AS YOU HEARD ALAN DERSHOWITZ,
AND COMEY WAS CRITICIZED FOR
THAT.
WAS THAT THE WRONG DECISION BY
COMEY?
>> I AGREED WITH HIS APPROACH AT
THE TIME, AND INSUSINCE THE BEN
OF SOME RECONSIDERATION OF THE
THINGS WE DID, AND I THINK I'M
PRETTY CLEAR ABOUT IT IN THE
BOOK, I THINK THAT THAT DECISION
WAS NOT WELL THOUGHT.
I THINK WE UNDERESTIMATED THE
KIND OF POLITICAL TOXICITY OF
THE ENVIRONMENT THAT WE WERE
LAUNCHING OUR CONCLUSIONS INTO
AND WE OVERESTIMATED OUR ABILITY
AND JIM'S ABILITY TO CONVINCE
PEOPLE OF THE GREAT WORK WE HAD
DONE.
>> THE CASE FILE IS PRECEDENT,
AND IS IT ONE THE FBI SHOULD
FOLLOW IN THIS INVESTIGATION?
>> I'M NOT SURE JIM'S DECISION
TO ANNOUNCE IT IN JULY IS A
PRECEDENT.
HOWEVER, I THINK THAT IT IS A
VERY CONCERNING AND NOW RECENT
PRECEDENT.
THE VOLUME OF INFORMATION THAT
THE FBI TURNED OVER TO CONGRESS
IN THE WAKE OF AFTER THE
INVESTIGATION WAS CONCLUDED.
THAT IS SOMETHING THAT CONCERNED
ME GREATLY AT THAT TIME, AND I
THOUGHT, YOU KNOW, THIS IS A --
THIS IS A PRACTICE THAT WILL BE
HARD TO STEP AWAY FROM.
>> YOU MADE THE DECISION TO
INVESTIGATE THE PRESIDENT.
COMING IS SOME CRITICISM FROM
CONGRESSMAN MARK MEADOWS.
YOU SAID IT WAS BECAUSE OF
SUSPICIOUS BEHAVIOR BY THE
PRESIDENT, AND OTHER SECRET
EVIDENCE.
CONGRESSMAN MEADOWS SAYS THAT IS
AN ABUSIE OF POWER.
>> I'M NOT SURE WHAT HE'S
REFERRING TO THERE, BUT I CAN
TELL YOU THAT THE INFORMATION
THAT WAS IN OUR HANDS AT THE
TIME, MUCH OF WHICH IS PUBLICLY
KNOWN, CAUSED US GREAT CONCERN.
>> YOU SAY US, BUT THIS WAS YOUR
DECISION, RIGHT?
>> THIS WAS THE DRECOMMENDATION
FROM THE INVESTIGATIVE TEAM AND
IT WAS MY DECISION TO AUTHORIZE
THE OPENING OF THE CASE AND I
DID THAT BECAUSE AT THE TIME,
THE FACTS CLEARLY INDICATED WE
HAD BASIS TO BELIEVE THAT A
CRIME MAY HAVE BEEN COMMITTED
AND THAT A THREAT TO NATIONAL
SECURITY MIGHT EXIST.
WE HADN'T CONCLUDED EITHER OF
THOSE TWO THINGS HAD HAPPENED,
BUT WE WERE CERTAINLY IN THE
PLACE WE NEEDED TO INVESTIGATE
BOTH SIDES.
>> YOU'RE PLANNING ON FILING A
CIVIL LAWSUIT AGAINST PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
WHAT GROUNDS DO YOU HAVE TO SUE
AND WHAT DO YOU HOPE TO GET FROM
IT?
>> I CAN'T TALK IN GREAT DETAIL
ABOUT THE LAWSUIT.
I'LL LET THE PLEADINGS SPEAK FOR
THEMSELVES.
IT WILL BE AN ACTION AGAINST THE
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE PRIMARILY
AND CHALLENGING THE
CIRCUMSTANCES OF MY FIRING.
IT OF COURSE, DERIVES FROM THE
INSPECTOR GENERAL REPORT, A
REPORT I DEEPLY DISAGREE WITH,
AND IT WAS A RESULT OF A PROCESS
THAT I DON'T THINK ANYONE HAS
EVER SEEN BEFORE.
I CERTAINLY HADN'T.
EXCUSE ME.
>> DO YOU THINK THE PRESIDENT
INSPIRED THAT PROCESS?
>> THERE IS NO DOUBT IN MY MIND
THAT THE PRESIDENT'S CLEAR
DESIRE IMPACTED THAT PROCESS.
THE PRESIDENT WAS TALKING ABOUT
REMOVING ME FOR MONTHS BEFORE I
EVER INTERACTED WITH THE
INSPECTOR GENERAL.
HE MADE HIS DESIRES PERFECTLY
CLEAR ON HIS OWN TWITTER FEED.
THE INSPECTOR GENERAL DELIVERED
THAT RESULT.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> THANK YOU, GEORGE.
>> ROUND TABLE IS UP NEXT.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
to your goals and needs.
Some only call when they have
something to sell.
Fisher calls regularly so
you stay informed.
And while some advisors are
happy to earn commissions
whether you do well or not.
Fisher Investments fees
are structured so we do better
when you do better.
Maybe that's why most
of our clients
come from other money managers.
Fisher Investments. Clearly
better money management.
How's your cough?
I'm good. I took 12-hour Mucinex
and sent it far away.
Hey buddy, have you seen a
nice woman with a cough?
Woahhh!
Mucinex DM releases fast and
lasts 12-hours, not 4.
Send coughs far away all day.
Think only specialty stores have
what's new?
Olay has the hottest debut.
New Olay Clay Stick Masks,
Hydrating Facial Mist,
And Brightening Eye Cream.
Only by Olay.
Whether you were borne for more
dance-offs...
More travels...
Or more touchdowns.
Get the immune support that
gives you more.
Airborne Gummies have 50% more
vitamin-C than Emergen-C...
Plus our crafted blend of
vitamins, minerals and herbs.
Airborne.
The Russells travel to a
different swim meet every
Saturday.
But now... it's Thursday.
Good thing they discovered Gain
Flings.
The only detergent with
concentrated Gain,
Oxi Boost, and Febreze Odor
Remover.
Mmhmm. Smelling is believing.
And Gain Flings can HIYA Karate
stink too.
Try new improved Gain Flings.
98% of us don't get enough
omega-3s.
Which is why MegaRed Advanced
4in1
packs more omega-3 power into
one small softgel.
It supports your heart...
Brain... Eyes... And joints.
MegaRed.
♪♪
Ignition sequence starts.
10... 9... Guidance is internal.
6... 5... 4... 3... 2... 1...
♪♪
Do I use a toothpaste that
whitens my teeth?
Or one that's good for my teeth?
Now I don't have to choose.
From Crest 3D White.
The Whitening Therapy
Collection.
Now with Charcoal or Coconut
Oil.
It gently whitens.
Plus, it has a fortifying
formula
to protect your enamel.
Crest. Healthy, beautiful smiles
for life.
This is Charlie not coughing
because he took Delsym 12-hour.
And this is Charlie still not
coughing
while trying his hardest not to
wake Zeus.
Delsym 12-hour.
Nothing lasts
longer for powerful
cough relief.
Ahh Potluck.
These dishes will soon be yours
to scrub.
And they're not even yours.
New and improved Dawn Ultra lets
you
scrub 50% less and get done
faster.
A drop of Dawn and grease is
gone.
♪
When heartburn hits,
fight back fast
with TUMS Smoothies.
It neutralizes stomach
acid at the source.
♪TUM TUM TUM TUM♪
Smoothies.
Also available
TUMS Sugar-Free.
>>> ROUND TABLE STANDING BY AND
ALL WEEK LONG YOU CAN GET THE
POLITICS WITH BREAKING NEWS
ALERTS ON THE ABC NEWS APP.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
A WAY TO CREATE ENERGY
FROM HOUSEHOLD TRASH.
IT NOT ONLY SAVES ABOUT
80% IN CARBON EMISSIONS...
IT HELPS REDUCE LANDFILL WASTE.
THAT'S WHY BP IS PARTNERING
WITH A CALIFORNIA COMPANY:
FULCRUM BIOENERGY.
TO TURN GARBAGE INTO JET FUEL.
BECAUSE WE CAN'T LET ANY
GOOD IDEAS GO TO WASTE.
AT BP, WE SEE
POSSIBILITIES EVERYWHERE.
TO HELP THE WORLD
KEEP ADVANCING.
Whether you were borne for more
dance-offs...
More travels...
Or more touchdowns.
Get the immune support that
gives you more.
Airborne Gummies have 50% more
vitamin-C than Emergen-C...
Plus our crafted blend of
vitamins, minerals and herbs.
Airborne.
Upgrade to new Tide PODS 2.0.
And get 50% more cleaning power
In the palm of your hand,
For a powerful clean in one
step.
#1 stain and odor fighter, #1
trusted.
It's got to be Tide.
When I kept finding myself
smoking in my attic.
Dad!
Hiding when I was
supposed to be quitting.
I thought, I should try
something that works.
I should try Nicorette.
Nicorette Mini relieves
sudden cravings fast.
Anytime. Anywhere.
Nicorette Mini.
You know why. We know how.
Prestige creams not living up to
the hype?
One jar shatters the
competition.
Olay Regenerist hydrates skin
better than creams
costing over $100, $200, and
even $400.
Fact check this ad in Good
Housekeeping.
Olay.
This is Decision Tech.
It's screening technology
that helps you find a stock
based on what's trending
or an investing goal.
It's real-time insights
and information,
in your own customized view
of the market.
It's smarter
trading technology,
for smarter trading decisions.
And it's only from Fidelity.
Open an account
with no minimums today.
And it's only from Fidelity.
How's your cough?
I'm good. I took 12-hour Mucinex
and sent it far away.
Hey buddy, have you seen a
nice woman with a cough?
Woahhh!
Mucinex DM releases fast and
lasts 12-hours, not 4.
Send coughs far away all day.
>>> I WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT IN
THE YEARS TO COME, THE SAME
OPPORTUNITIES THATER THERE
FOR ME, A KID THAT GREW UP IN
THE PUBLIC SCHOOLS IN TEXAS, CAN
BE THERE FOR ANYBODY.
>> I'M IN THIS FIGHT BECAUSE I
TRULY DO BELIEVE THIS IS OUR
MOMENT.
>> I BELIEVE IT IS TIME TO
RESTORE TRUTH AND JUSTICE.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
>> YOU SEE EVERY SINGLE DAY THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS TRYING TO
UNDERMINE OUR CONSTITUTION.
>> I AM GOING TO RUN FOR
PRESIDENT.
>> WHAT'S GOING TO BE DIFFERENT
THIS TIME?
>> WE'RE GOING TO WIN.
>> FIRST VOTES ARE A YEAR AWAY,
BUT THE CAMPAIGN IN FULL SWING
THIS FEBRUARY.
LET'S TALK ABOUT IT WITH OUR
ROUND TABLE, WITH CHRIS
CHRISTIE.
HEIDI HEIDCAMP, AND OUR REPORTER
FROM "THE WASHINGTON POST."
WELCOME TO YOU.
WE HAVE OUR POLITICAL AFFAIRS
DIRECTOR, AND ALEX CASTKAS YAW
KNOWS.
LET'S START WITH BERNIE SANDERS.
HE SAYS HE'S GOING TO WIN THIS
TIME AROUND.
77 YEARS OLD AND ALREADY
TARGETED BY THE PRESIDENT AS A
DEMOCRATIC SOCIALIST, BUT 24
HOURS INTO HIS ANNOUNCEMENT OF
THAT FUND-RAISING BASE.
>> $6 MILLION IN RIGHT AWAY, AND
ANOTHER $6,000 FROM PEOPLE WHO
LE
PLEDGED TO GIVE HIM EVERY SINGLE
MONTH.
IT'S LIKE THE NETFLIX FOR
RUNNING A CAMPAIGN.
HE'S GOING TO BE A CHALLENGE
THIS TIME AROUND.
I WORKED ON HOWARD DEAN'S
CAMPAIGN.
>> AGAINST JOHN CARRIGAN.
>> AND EVERYBODY ELSE IN THE
WORLD, AND THERE WAS A SENSE IT
WAS A BATTLE FOR THE HEARTS AND
MINDS OF THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY,
BUT AT SOME POINT IN IOWA, NEW
HAMPSHIRE, EARLY ON, DEPARTMENTS
DECIDED WE DON'T WANT A
REVOLUTION.
WE WANT TO BEAT GEORGE BUSH.
BERNIE SANDERS IS GOING TO FIND
THIS TIME PEOPLE DON'T WANT A
REVOLUTION BUT THEY WANT DONALD
TRUMP.
>> BERNIE SANDERS, HIS IDEAS
HAVE BEEN ADOPTED BY MANY OTHER
CANDIDATES, MANY OTHER
DEMOCRATS, BUT THERE IS THAT
CONCERN THAT HE'S GOING TO PULL
THE PARTY TOO FAR TO THE LEFT.
>> WELL, I THINK THAT A COUPLE
OF THINGS ARE GOING TO HAPPEN.
YOU'RE GOING TO SEE PEOPLE GET
IN WHO ARE GOING TO BROADEN THE
SCOPE OF DEMOCRATIC IDEAS THAT
ARE GOING TO BE PUT ON THE
FOREFRONT, BUT TO THE POINT OF
THE MONEY, MONEY DOESN'T MATTER
AS MUCH AS WHAT IT USED TO IN MY
OPINION.
WHEN YOU STEP BACK AND TAKE A
LOOK AT KIND OF THE RECORD
CROWDS THAT EVERYBODY'S ENJOYING
IN IOWA -- I MEAN PEOPLE ARE
COMING OUT BECAUSE THEY WANT TO
EXAMINE EACH CANDIDATE AND PICK
THE CANDIDATE WHO IN THEIR MIND,
THE HIGHEST PRIORITY IS WHO CAN
BEAT THIS PRESIDENT.
>> MONEY MAY NOT MATTER, BUT THE
SIGN YOU HAVE THIS MOVEMENT
BEHIND YOU COULD.
>> IT COULD AND I DISAGREE WITH
THE SENATOR HAVING GONE THROUGH
IT A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO.
MONEY MATTERS AND WHOEVER
EMERGES OUT OF THIS WILL WIND UP
HAVING A HUGE TARGET ON THEIR
BACK WHEN THEY START TO DO WELL,
AND THEY HAVE TO HAVE THE MONEY
TO ANSWER, AND IF YOU DON'T HAVE
THE MONEY TO ANSWER, YOU'RE
GOING TO LOSE BECAUSE I LOVE ALL
THE CHARACTERIZATION OF IOWA AND
NEW HAMPSHIRE VOTERS ESPECIALLY
EARLY AS BEING SO DISCERNING AND
THEY WANT TO COME AND MEET YOU
IN PERSON.
THEY WANT TO MEET EVERYBODY IN
PERSON, BUT THEY ALSO WATCH WHAT
COMES IN THEIR MAILBOX AND WHAT
COMES OVER THE TV AND GUYS
WOULDN'T HAVE MADE THE FORTUNE
HE HAS MADE.
SANDERS WILL MATTER, BUT, YOU
KNOW, IT'S A REPUBLICAN DREAM
THAT SANDERS COULD BE THE
NOMINEE.
>> CAN I JUMP IN AND SAY IT'S
INCREASE INGLY -- THE DEMOCRATSN
CAPITOL HILL AND DEMOCRATS
JUMPING IN ON 2020 ARE BECOMING
INCREASINGLY GLARING WHERE YOU
SEE THE CANDIDATES SUPPORTING
MEDICARE FOR ALL?
THE NEW DEAL, AND FREE COLLEGE
GETTING CORPORATE MONEY IT OF
POLITICS ON CAPITOL HILL.
NANCY PELOSI IS KEEPING HER --
>> SHE'S HOLDING THE LINE
AGAINST SOME OF HER NEW MEMBERS
AS WELL THERE.
>> THEY'RE INTRODUCING IDEAS,
BUT THEY ARE NOT GOING TO BE
VOTED ON ON THE FLOOR AND THERE
IS A REASON FOR THAT, AND THAT'S
BECAUSE MOST DEMOCRATS ON THE
HILL ARE AFRAID OF THESE IDEAS
AND I THINK THEY GO TOO FAR.
>> IT'S A PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN.
POLITICS WILL JUST SWAMP PUBLIC
POLICY OVER THE COURSE OF THE
NEXT 18 MONTHS OF OR SO.
>> THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE TO BE
CAREFUL.
THAT SHOWS.
IT SHOWS.
IT SHOWS THE DIVIDE IN THE PARTY
THOUGH.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP LOVES BERNIE
SANDERS FRONT AND CENTER.
>> HE COULDN'T BE THAT LUCKY
AGAIN, COULD HE?
THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY IS GOING AS
CRAZY FAR LEFT AS REPUBLICANS
DID FAR RIGHT UNDER OBAMA, AND
IT'S A GIFT.
I MEAN, SOCIALISM DIDN'T WORK
FOR THE PILGRIMS THE FIRST TWO
YEARS HALF OF THEM DIED AND NOW
THAT'S THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY
AGENDA.
THERE ARE THREE DEMOCRATIC
PRIMARIES TO TAKE ON TRUMP AND
ALL TO HAVE THEM ARE GOING,
THERE'S THE ESTABLISHMENT
PRIMARY WITH BIDEN AND
KLOBUCHAR.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE QUAKERS?
THAT WAS THEIR MODEL.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE THE
PROGRESSIVE PRIMARY, WHICH
SANDERS HAS THE MONEY AND THE
LEAD AND YOU HAVE KAMALA HARRIS
AND CORY BOOKER FOR THE OBAMA
BLACK PRIMARY.
I THINK KAMALA HARRIS IS GOING
TO SUCCEED IN THAT ONE, AND YOU
WILL SEE BERNIE SANDERS AND
MAYBE KLOBUCHAR.
KAMALA HARRIS CAN GO BEYOND.
SHE'S BEING PEGGED --
>> I THINK THERE IS NO SUCH
THING AS THE OBAMA BLACK
PRIMARY.
I THINK KAMALA --
>> YES, THERE IS.
>> THEY ARE BOTH EXTRAORDINARY
CANDIDATES WHO CAN APPEAL.
>> THAT'S MY POINT ABOUT KAMALA
HARRIS.
I AGREE WITH, THAT BUT THAT'S --
RIGHT NOW THE DEMOCRATIC
PRIMARIES --
>> YOU'RE ALL JUDGING -- YOU'RE
ALL JUDGING THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY
IDEAS BY THE PEOPLE WHO ARE IN
NOW.
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN MICHAEL
BENNETT GETS IN?
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN CHERYL BROWN
GETS IN?
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU SEE
BLOOMBERG GET IN?
>> YOU MENTIONED JOE BIDEN.
DO YOU THINK HE'LL GET IN?
>> I DO.
I THINK THE VICE PRESIDENT WILL
FEEL A CALLING AND FEEL A
NECESSITY TO BRING THAT GRAVITAS
AND I THINK THE MINUTE HE GETS
IN, HE'S GOING TO BE THE
RECOGNIZED FRONT RUNNER.
>> THERE IS AN OPENING FOR THAT
RIGHT NOW.
>> HE HAS NAME I.D., A LOT OF
DEMOCRATIC VOTERS ARE SITTING
THERE BECAUSE THEY DON'T KNOW
THE ALTERNATIVE, BUT THE SOUL OF
THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY IS RAPIDLY
ANTI-TRUMP AND GOING CRAZY LEFT
AND BELONGS TO OCASIO-CORTEZ.
>> THAT IS WISHFUL REPUBLICAN
THINKING.
>> THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
>> WE DID IT AS REPUBLICANS.
>> ALEX, THERE ARE FOLKS WHO ARE
SITTING IN IOWA, NEW HAMPSHIRE,
SOUTH CAROLINA, CALIFORNIA,
WHICH WAS AN EARLY STATE ON
SUPER TUESDAY THIS TIME WHO ARE
WORRIED ABOUT THE EDUCATION OF
THEIR CHILDREN.
THEY ARE CONCERNED ABOUT HEALTH
CARE.
>> WHICH IS WHY WARREN IS --
>> THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS IN
WASHINGTON, D.C.
WE'RE GOING TO MOVE AWAY FROM
POLITICS.
>> LET'S GET BACK TO THIS.
LET'S GET TO WHAT'S PRACTICAL
HERE, AND WHAT CAMPAIGNS COME
DOWN TO ARE CANDIDATES.
FORGET ABOUT ALL THE IDEOLOGY
AND EVERYTHING ELSE, IT'S
CANDIDATES.
>> WHO'S GOING TO PERFORM.
>> YOU HAVE SEEN THIS, AND I
HAVE SEEN IT AND I HAVE WILL IT.
KAMALA HARRIS LEARNED THIS IN
HER FIRST WEEK WHEN SHE'S
TALKING ABOUT SMOKING POT
LISTENING TO TUPAC.
SHE SAID SHE WAS IN COLLEGE.
YOU'RE SHAKING YOUR HEAD,
PATRICK, BUT LET ME TELL YOU.
SHE HAS PROBABLY TOLD THAT B.S.
STORY IN CALIFORNIA A THOUSAND
TIMES AND NO ONE EVER CALLED HER
ON IT.
WHEN YOU RUN FOR PRESIDENT, THEY
CALL YOU ON EVERYTHING AND WHO'S
GOING TO PERFORM --
>> WHETHER THEY TELL THE TRUTH
NOW?
THAT'S A NEW STANDARD.
>> WHEN THE LIGHTS GO ON -- WHEN
THE LIGHTS GO ON, THERE IS ONLY
TWO ALTERNATIVES.
YOU EITHER SHINE OR YOU MELT.
THOSE ARE THE ONLY TWO
ALTERNATIVES FOR PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES AND WE'LL SEE WHO
DOES WHAT AND IT'S WAY TOO EARLY
TO TRY TO FIGURE IT OUT WITH
THESE FOLKS AND WHEN JOE BIDEN
IS SEEN AS THE FRONT RUNNER
WHICH I THINK HE IS IF HE GETS
IN, THIS IS A GUY WHO HAS RUN
TWICE AND HASN'T EXACTLY SHINED
BOTH TIMES HE RAN.
>> GOVERNOR, YOU KNOW A THING OR
TWO ABOUT FANCIFUL TALES.
>> OH, PATRICK.
>> BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY,
THE GOVERNOR IS RIGHT THAT THIS
REALLY IS ABOUT PERFORMANCE.
YOU SHOWED THE CLIP AT THE VERY
BEGINNING, GEORGE.
EVERY CANDIDATE WITH THE
EXCEPTION OF AMY KLOBUCHAR
STARTED EACH SENTENCE WITH I.
I BELIEVE, I FEEL.
THEY UNDERSTAND AT THE END OF
THE DAY, IT'S WHETHER PEOPLE CAN
TRUST THEIR VALUE AND THEIR
STORY.
>> SINCE THE GOVERNMENT
SHUTDOWN, THE PRESIDENT HAS HAD
SOMET
SOMETHING OF A COMEBACK
RECENTLY.
HEADING TOWARDS THE MID 40s, AND
NOT THERE YET, BUT THIS
EMERGENCY WILL BE FRONT AND
CENTER ON CAPITOL HILL THIS
WEEK.
>> RIGHT.
EXACTLY.
THE PRESIDENT THINKS THIS IS A
GOOD RE-ELECTION.
SOMETHING THAT HE CAN RUN ON AND
THAT'S GOING TO HELP HIM AND,
YOU KNOW, IT SHOWS THAT HE IS
OBVIOUSLY CATERING TO HIS BASE
AND SHE'S SHOWING HE'S PUTTING
THEM FRONT AND CENTER, BUT IN
GOING TO THAT, HE HAS SORT OF
UPENDED THE RE-ELECTIONS
POTENTIALLY OF OTHER SENATE
REPUBLICANS.
>> THEY CONTINUE WANT THIS VOTE.
>> THEY DONE, AND A LOT OF THEM
WERE PRIVATELY TELLING THE
PRESIDENT, PLEASE DON'T DO THIS.
DON'T DO THIS.
THIS IS GOING TO CREATE A
TERRIBLE PRECEDENT.
IF WE HAVE A PRESIDENT BERNIE
SANDERS SOMEDAY, IF HE'S GOING
TO DO SOMETHING WITH THE GREEN
NEW DEAL ON HIS OWN, AND CALL
THIS AN EMERGENCY, WE CAN'T HAVE
THAT.
WE'RE SEEING A LOT OF THOSE SAME
REPUBLICANS WHO PRIVATELY WERE
TELLING HIM, DON'T DO THIS, COME
OUT AND SAY THAT THEY'RE NOT
GOING TO PUSH BACK AGAINST HIM.
>> STILL HIS REPUBLICAN PARTY
AND BY THE WAY, IF THE ELECTION
WERE HELD TODAY AGAINST THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY HE'S RUNNING
AGAINST, I THINK DONALD TRUMP
WILL WIN BY MORE THAN HE WON
LAST TIME.
THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY IS GOING
CRAZY LEFT.
THE ONLY THING THAT HAS
CHANGED -- NEITHER PARTY HAS
CHANGED.
REPUBLICANS NOR DEPARTMENTS AS
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS ELECTED AND
NOW HE'S NOT THEORY, BUT HE'S
FACT.
>> THE MIDTERM ELECTION --
>> EXCUSE ME.
>> THE APROEP OCCAPROPRIATION O
FACT.
LET'S NOT FORGET THAT HAPPENED.
WOMEN IN PARTICULAR?
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU HAVE TO
UNDERSTAND.
MIDTERMS ARE A REFERENDUM ON THE
INCUMBENT.
PRESIDENTIAL YEARS ARE CHOICES
AND THE DEMOCRATS ARE OFFERING A
CHOICE OF GOING LEFT.
TRUMP IS SAYING --
>> DEMOCRATIC CHOICE IS NOT --
THAT'S WHY YOU HAVE A PRIMARY
CONTEST, ALEX.
>> TRUMP'S CHOICE IS CLEAR.
GROWTH AND LOCKING THE DOORS AT
NIGHT AND SECURITY.
THE DEMOCRATS' RESPONSE HAS NOT
BEEN ABOUT EITHER OF THEM.
IT'S BEEN ABOUT THE MOMMY BEAR
PARTY CARING AND NOURISHING,
LIKE A 1950s SITCOM.
>> SO HEALTH CARE -- HEALTH
CARE, CHILD CARE AND --
>> I'M NOT ADVOCATING.
I'M JUST TELLING YOU.
TRUMP HAS A STRONG HAND GOING
INTO 2020.
>> YOU THINK THE ECONOMY IN A
YEAR IS GOING TO LOOK LIKE THE
ECONOMY TODAY, YOU'RE WRONG, AND
THE TAX REFUND ISSUE IS REAL.
I KNOW THIS.
I MEAN, YOU'RE GOING TO SAY
WHILE THE TAXES WERE REDUCED,
PEOPLE COUNT ON THAT WE FUND AND
THEY FEEL THEY GOT SHORTCHANGED
AND THEY LOOK AT ECONOMIC AND
BUSINESS INVESTMENT THAT NEVER
MATERIALIZED.
THEY PACKAGED THIS SIGNATURE
PIECE FOR THIS PRESIDENT.
>> IT'S NOT A GREAT POLITICAL
STRATEGY.
>> AND I'M NOT HOPING FOR BAD
NEWS, BUT I THINK BAD NEWS IS
PREDICTABLE IN THIS CYCLE.
I MEAN, I'M NOT THE ONLY PERSON
SAYING THIS.
I THINK -- LOOK AT --
>> IT'S SOCIALISTS.
>> IN THE ECONOMY, IT'S
AGRICULTURE.
WE HAVE RECORD BANKRUPTCY.
>> ALEX IS COUNTING ON THAT
SOCIALISM LABEL STICKING, BUT
CHRIS, I WANT TO BRING UP A
DIFFERENT POINT INSIDE THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY.
IT SEEMS TO BE TRUMP'S
REPUBLICAN PARTY RIGHT NOW.
YOU HAD BILL WELD SAYING HE'S
GOING TO RUN AGAINST HIM.
LARRY HOGE SAID THIS.
>> I WAS JUST SWORN IN A MONTH
AGO FOR MY SECOND TERM, AND I
HAVE GOT A LOT OF WORK TO DO
HERE IN MARYLAND.
I'M BEING APPROACHED FROM A LOT
OF DIFFERENT PEOPLE AND I GUESS
THE BEST WAY TO PUT IT IS I
HAVEN'T THROWN THEM OUT OF MY
OFFICE.
>> HOW REAL IS THIS IDEA OF THE
SIGNIFICANT CHALLENGE TO THE
PRESIDENT?
>> NOT REAL.
THERE IS PROBABLY NOBODY IN
AMERICAN POLITICS WHO KNOWS
LA
LARRY HOGAN BETTER THAN I DID
BECAUSE I WENT IN THERE WHEN NO
ONE THOUGHT MARYLAND WAS
WINNABLE AND I INVESTED
$2 MILLION IN HIM AND WE GOT HIM
OVER THE FINISH LINE.
HE WON BOTH TIMES.
ONLY THE SECOND REPUBLICAN EVER
TO BE RE-ELECTED GOVERNOR OF
MARYLAND IN THE HISTORY OF THE
STATE BECAUSE HE'S A SMART
POLITICIAN, AND A SMART
POLITICIAN IS NOT BASED ON THIS
SET OF FACTS TO CHALLENGE DONALD
TRUMP IN A PRIMARY BECAUSE THESE
GUYS HAVE 80% APPROVAL RATINGS
AMONG REPUBLICANS.
WHAT LARRY IS DOING IS HE HAS
ISSUES HE CARES ABOUT AND HE'S
GOING TO USE IT AS A PLATFORM TO
SPEAK OUT ABOUT THE ISSUES TO
BRING THE PARTY BACK TOWARDS
WHERE HE IS, BUT THE IDEA THAT
LARRY HOGAN -- BILL WELD ISN'T
SERIOUS AND NO ONE TAKES HIM
SERIOUSLY, BUT LARRY HOGAN -- MY
THEORY IS HE WON'T DO IT.
>> IT'S POLITICAL SUICIDE TO DO
THAT RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS DONALD TRUMP'S PARTY
STILL.
TWO YEARS LATER.
LOOK NO FURTHER AGAIN TO THE
NATIONAL EMERGENCY.
>> IT COMES OUT AS AN
INVESTIGATION.
>> LARRY HOGAN WILL BE WITH A
WHOLE GROUP OF PEOPLE RUNNING.
>> THIS IS THE EMERGENCY
DECLARATION FOR WEEKS.
HE IGNORED THEM AND THEY'RE
BACKING OFF, AND THIS IS TRUMP'S
PARTY.
>> WHAT DOES HAPPEN WITH THESE
FOLLOW-UP INVESTIGATIONS?
WE HAVEN'T SEEN ROBERT MUELLER'S
REPORT.
AND DO YOU SENSE ANY CONCERN
AMONG YOUR COLLEAGUES THAT IF
ROBERT MUELLER FINISHES HIS JOB
AND HANDS IT OFF IF THEY'RE
GOING TO BE WARY OF GOING TOO
FAR?
>> I HOPE SO.
I THINK THEY ARE.
I THINK THEY REALIZE THAT ONE OF
THE WORST THINGS THAT CAN HAPPEN
IN MY OPINION IS IMPEACHMENT.
I THINK THAT YOU HAVE TO WIN AT
THE BALLOT BOX IN ORDER TO HAVE
A -- HAVE A REAL FUTURE FOR THIS
COUNTRY.
>> DOES THAT MEAN NO OFIN
INVESTIGATING?
>> NO BUT IT MEANS WHAT DO YOU
DO WITH THAT INVESTIGATION?
ALL OF THAT INFORMATION IS
CRITICAL AND IMPORTANT AND THE
PUBLIC NEEDS TO KNOW.
20% OF THE PUBLIC BELIEVES
WHATEVER THE PRESIDENT SAYS.
THE NEXT 20% WILL SAY, YEAH.
HE DOESN'T ALWAYS TELL THE
TRUTH.
SO WHAT?
YOU HAVE 40% SO WON'T CARE.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT THE 20% THAT
YOU HOPE YOU CAN PERPERSUADE.
>> THE PAST IS PROLOGUE.
THE YEAR BEFORE PRESIDENT NIXON
RESIGNED, 57% OF MEAMERICANS SA
TOO MUCH ATTENTION WAS BEING
PAID TO WATERGATE.
>> ARE YOU FULL SPEED AHEAD?
>> DEMOCRATS IN CONGRESS ARE
ABSOLUTELY GOING TO CONTINUE
THESE INVESTIGATIONS.
THERE'S MORE THAN ENOUGH FODDER
WHEN YOU CONSIDER EVERY
INSTITUTION THAT DONALD TRUMP
HAS TOUCHED, HAS COME INTO BEING
QUESTIONED FROM HIS CABINET
PICKS LIKE HIS CURRENT LABOR
SECRETARY TO HIS FOUNDATION THAT
HE HAD TO SHUTTER.
>> HERE'S THE THING THOUGH.
THERE BETTER BE SOME THERE
THERE.
IF THEY'RE GOING TO DECIDE TO GO
DOWN THAT ROAD -- PATRICK.
PATRICK, THIS IS A DIFFERENT
CONTEXT NOW BECAUSE WHEN YOU ARE
GET STING INTO A PRESIDENTIAL
ELECTION CYCLE, PEOPLE SEE IT AS
NOT BEING NECESSARILY
LEGITIMATE, BUT BEING POLITICAL.
EVEN MORE POLITICAL WHEN YOU
HAVE THESE CANDIDATES THAT
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO BE ABLE TO
CONTROL THEMSELVES.
>> HOW DOES THAT AFFECT YOUR
COLLEAGUES IN THE SOUTHERN
DISTRICT THAT SEEM TO HAVE THE
SERIOUS --
>> NOT A LICK.
NOT A BIT.
THEY DON'T CARE.
WHEN I WAS U.S. ATTORNEY IN NEW
JERSEY, EVERYONE USED TO REFER
TO THEM AS THE SOVEREIGN
DISTRICT OF NEW YORK.
THEY BELIEVED THEY ARE SOVEREIGN
AND THEY LISTEN TO NO ONE.
THEY BARELY LISTEN TO THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL.
THEY WILL DO WHATEVER THEY THINK
THEY NEED TO DO, AND THAT'S WHAT
I HAVE BEEN SAYING AS YOU KNOW,
FOR TEN MONTHS HERE.
THE SOUTHERN DISTRICT OF NEW
YORK INVESTIGATION IS MON
MONUMENTALLY MORE PERILOUS THAN
BOB MUELLER EVER WAS OR WILL BE.
THEY HAVE TWO TOUR GUIDES AND NO
RESTRICTION ON WHERE THEY CAN
GO.
>> THAT IS THE LAST WORD.
UP NEXT, WHAT TO EXPECT FROM
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S SECOND NUCLEAR
SUMMIT WITH NORTH KOREA'S KIM
JONG-UN.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>>> GET RID OF ALL OF THEIR
NUCLEAR WEAPONS?
>> THEY WILL.
I THINK THEY WILL.
I REALLY BELIEVE THAT HE WILL.
I HAVE GOTTEN TO --
>> DID HE TELL YOU THAT?
>> YEAH, SURE.
DE-NUKING.
HE'S DE-NUKING THE WHOLE PLACE
AND HE'S GOING TO START VERY
QUICKLY.
I THINK HE'S GOING TO START NOW.
I WOULD JUST LIKE TO SEE
ULTIMATELY DE-NUCLEARIZATION OF
NORTH KOREA.
I THINK WE WILL SEE THAT
ULTIMATELY.
I HAVE NO PRESSING TIME
SCHEDULE.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
EXPECTATIONS.
THAT'S SET FOR THURSDAY IN
VIETNAM.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE RISK AND
THE POSSIBLE REWARDS WITH OUR
PANEL OF EXPERTS, TOM BOSSERT,
FORMER TRUMP HOMELAND SECURITY
ADVISER, A FORMER CIA ANALYST,
AND THE FORMER AMBASSADOR TO THE
U.N.
LET ME BEGIN WITH YOU.
YOU SAW THE PRESIDENT SETTING
THE KPAPEXPECTATIONS.
IT'S A QUESTION MARK QUESTIONING
WHETHER THAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
IS IT A -- CAN YOU HAVE A
SUCCESSFUL SUMMIT WITHOUT A
CLEAR COMMITMENT BY THE NORTH
KOREANS, AN ACTUAL CONCRETE
ACTION TO DENUCLEARIZE?
>> I DON'T THINK IT WOULD BE
SUCCESSFUL UNLESS YOU HAVE
COOPERATION WITH MISSILES,
NUCLEAR DETONATIONS.
IT SEEMS THE PRESIDENT IS
DEFLATING EXPECTATIONS, AND
THAT'S OF CONCERN.
THE CONCERN -- BECAUSE I THINK
WHAT SHOULD COME OUT OF THIS
SUMMIT IS A FRAMEWORK FOR
NEGOTIATIONS.
MY WORRY, GEORGE, IS THIS
NEGOTIATION, THIS SUMMIT MAY BE
A DUD, THAT INSTEAD OF CONCRETE
PROGRESS ON WHAT IS IMPORTANT,
DE-NUCLEARIZATION, AND IT'S NOW
SHIFTING FROM DE-NUCLEARIZATION
ARMS CONTROL TO PEACE.
SO IMPORTANT STEPS.
RETURN OF OUR SERVICEMEN, THE
REMAINS.
MAYBE A LIAISON OFFICE, MAYBE
SOME KIND OF CONTINUED
NORTH/SOUTH COOPERATION WHICH IS
GOOD.
I THINK THE PRESIDENT DESERVES
CREDIT FOR LOWERING TENSIONS IN
THE REGION, BUT IN TERMS OF
CONCRETE ACCOMPLISHMENTS, I
DON'T THINK THIS SUMMIT IS GOING
TO PRODUCE THAT.
>> THE DUD IS ONE POSSIBILITY,
AND THERE HAS BEEN SOME CONCERN
FROM THE PRESIDENT'S ADVISERS HE
GIVES SOMETHING HE SHOULDN'T
GIVE AWAY TOO SOON SAYING A
FORMAL PEACE DECLARATION DECLAR
WAR.
>> THERE HAS BEEN A PROFOUND
SHIFT IN TALKING ABOUT PEACE,
AND I THINK THAT'S REALLY
PROBLEMATIC BECAUSE THE POINT OF
A SUMMIT BETWEEN THE TWO LEADERS
IS TO GET DISMANTLEMENT AND
NORTH KOREA TO COMPLETELY
ABANDON ITS NUCLEAR WEAPONS.
I THINK HAVING A PEACE
DECLARATION AND NORMALIZATION IS
FINE FOR TENSION REDUCTION, BUT
WE HAVE TO WONDER ABOUT HOW THAT
AFFECTS NORTH KOREA'S ACTIONS
DOWN THE LINE.
>> SHOULD THERE BE A SUMMIT NOW
GIVEN THE FACT THAT THE
PRESIDENT'S OWN NATIONAL
SECURITY JOHN BOLTON SAYS --
>> THERE HAS BEEN BACK PEDALING
AND DISHONESTY FROM THE LAST
SUMMIT WHICH IS A WATER SHED
MOMENT UNTIL TODAY, AND AT THIS
POINT, THE ONLY REASON TO HAVE
THAT SUMMIT IS FOR PRESIDENT
TRUMP TO GO IN AND GIVE A CLEAR
RE
REMINDER.
IT WILL BE A DUD IF HE TRIES TO
VARNISH THIS AS A SUCCESS
WITHOUT ANY AXCACTIONABLE ACTIV.
ANY GESTURE ON THE PART OF THE
NORTH KOREANS WILL BE A SLAP IN
THE FACE, BUT IF THE PRESIDENT
COMES OUT AND BUYS IT WHETHER
IT'S POLITICAL PRESSURE OR ON
INSTINCT TO POST A WIN, HE'S
GOING TO LOSE THE INTERNATIONAL
COALITION HE PUTS TOGETHER.
>> THE PRESIDENT HAS PUT THIS
OUT HE SAID THAT NORTH KOREA CAN
BE AN ECONOMIC POWERHOUSE UNDER
KIM I DON'TJONG-UN IF THEY JUSTP
NUCLEAR WEAPONS.
ALMOST TRYING TO INCENTIVIZE
HIM.
HE'S BANKING ON HIS PERSONAL
RELATIONSHIP WITH HIM AND HOW IT
WILL YIELD BENEFITS.
>> I THINK PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
MAKING THE MISTAKE OF MIRROR
IMAGING.
THE PRESIDENT IS FROM NEW YORK
CITY.
HE'S A BUSINESSMAN AND A REAL
ESTATE MOGUL AND HE IS SPEAKING
IN TERMS OF AS IF KIM IS ANOTHER
BUSINESSMAN, BUT KIM IS A
DICTATOR AND A HIGHLY
AUTHORITARIAN REGIME AND HE
NEEDS HIS WEAPONS FOR SURVIVAL.
NORTH KOREA IS IN THE MIDDLE OF
A VERY STRATEGIC ENVIRONMENT
AMONG THE SECOND, THIRD AND 11th
LARGEST ECONOMIES IN THE WORLD,
BUT NORTH KOREA SEES ITS
LOCATION AND ITS ECONOMIC DEP
VAGS RELATIVE AS A THREAT TO ITS
SURVIVAL.
>> HOW DO WE MAKE PROGRESS SHORT
OF NORTH KOREA GETTING RID OF
ITS WEAPONS?
WHAT KIND OF CONCRETE ACTION
COULD WE SEE FROM NORTH KOREA
THAT WOULD REALLY SIGNIFY REAL
PROGRESS THAT CAN BE BUILT ON?
>> I THINK JOHN IS RIGHT AND SO
IS TOM.
I HAVE CALLED THIS A POTENTIAL
DUD, BUT WE HAVE GOT TO CONTINUE
TALKING.
THE RELATIONSHIP --
>> NO HARM IN IT.
>> NO.
THE RELATIONSHIP OF THE TWO
LEADERS, THAT'S GOOD.
HOWEVER, THE PRESIDENT SHOULD
LISTEN TO HIS ADVISERS AND HIS
ADVISERS HAVE BEEN I THINK VERY
SPECIFIC.
WHAT I FEAR WE'RE GOING TO LOSE,
ONE, A DETAILING OF ALL THE
WEAPONS INVENTORY THAT NORTH
KOREA HAS.
I THINK WE HAVE KIND OF GIVEN UP
ON THAT.
SECONDLY, THAT WE SIMPLY SAY,
OKAY.
YOU DISMANTLE THE REACTOR,
ANOTHER MISSILE SITE THAT THEY
HAVE ALREADY DONE SEVERAL TIMES.
THAT'S A DANGER, AND IF THAT'S
THE ONLY ARMS CONTROL INITIAL
INITIATIVE THAT THEY PUSH, AND I
THINK LASTLY, MY WORRY, GEORGE,
IS THAT WE'RE GOING TO TRADE
SOMETHING WITH THE NORTH KOREANS
REALLY WANT, WHICH IS A PEACE
TREATY, IN EXCHANGE FOR SOME
LIMITED ARMS CONTROL MEASURES.
WHAT NEEDS TO HAPPEN IS
DISMANTLE SOME WEAPONS.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO DISMANTLE
ALL OF THEN.
FREEZE INTERCONTINENTAL
BALLISTIC MISSILES THAT AFFECT
JAPAN AND SOUTH KOREA.
FIND WAYS THAT THESE ARE
CONCRETE STEPS.
TIME LINES, VERIFICATION,
FRAMEWORK FOR NEGOTIATIONS.
IF IT'S JUST A BUNCH OF, YOU
KNOW, HANDSHAKES AND YOU'RE A
GOOD GUY AND WE'LL MEET AGAIN,
IT'S GOING TO BE A DUD.
>> IS THERE A WIN/WIN HERE?
>> YEAH, BUT IT'S NOT GOING TO
HAPPEN OUT OF THIS MEETING.
SO WHAT HAPPENED IN THE LAST
MEETING TOOK US BACK FROM THE
BRINK OF WAR, BUT THE
PRESIDENT -- TWO PRESIDENTS
AGREED TO TWO MUTUALLY
INCONSISTENT FUTURE OBJECTIVES.
ONE WAS NORMALIZATION BETWEEN
THE NORTH AND SOUTH AND WONE WA
DE-NUCLEARIZATION OF THE NORTH.
PRESIDENT MOON IN THE SOUTH IS
OPENING SANCTIONS AND INDUSTRIAL
COMPLEXES IN THE NORTH TO INDUCE
THEM INTO FURTHER TALKS AND THAT
WOULD FUNDAMENTALLY UNDERMINE
EVERYTHING THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
IS TRYING TO DO WITH RESPECT TO
DENUCL
DENUCLEARIZING.
IF YOU DON'T FORCE HIM, THE
NORTH WILL NOT GET RID OF THEIR
WEAPONS.
THE WIN/WIN HAS TO BE FOR THE
PRESIDENT TO CARRY THE
INTERNATIONAL GOOD WILL.
HE'S NOT REPRESENTING THE UNITED
STATES, AND NOT COME OUT WITH
THREATENING SANCTIONS.
>> THAT'S THE LAST WORD.
THAT IS ALL FOR US TODAY.
THANK YOU FOR SHARING PART OF
YOUR SUNDAY WITH US.
CHECK OUT "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT"
AND I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW ON
"GMA."