[CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
WARNER BROS. DOMESTIC TELEVISION
DISTRIBUTION]
HARVEY: WELCOME TO "TMZ LIVE."
HARVEY LEVIN HERE.
CHARLES: CHARLES HERE.
HARVEY: JUSTIN BIEBER HAS BEEN
OFF THE GRID IN TERMS OF BEING
PUBLIC FOR A YEAR NOW.
HE SAID HE WANTED TO GO
UNDERGROUND AND GET HIS LIFE
TOGETHER, AND HE DID THAT, BUT
HE HAS RESURFACED, TALKING ABOUT
THINGS IN HIS LIFE HE HAS NEVER
TALKED ABOUT BEFORE, INCLUDING
THE FACT THAT HE MADE A
DECISION, A CONSCIOUS DECISION A
YEAR BEFORE HE GOT MARRIED,, TO
BE CELIBATE.
CHARLES: THAT WHOLE TIME WHEN
JUSTIN WAS SHUTTING DOWN SAYING
HE WASN'T GOING TO BE TALKING
ANYMORE,, WE DIDN'T REALIZE AND
NOW WE KNOW, HE SAYS THAT HE WAS
TRYING TO GET CLOSER TO GOD AND
DECIDED THAT ONE OF THE WAYS HE
WAS GOING TO DO THAT WAS TO STOP
HAVING SEX.
>> IT'S REALLY INTERESTING.
HE HAD MENTIONED THAT, IN HIS
EARLY TEENAGE YEARS, THAT HE HAD
REALLY HIT ROCK-BOTTOM.
HE MENTIONED PEEING IN THE MOP
BUCKET.
THE ARREST.
CHARLES: THE EGGING AND ALL THAT
STUFF.
>> SAID THAT HE WAS SLEEPING
AROUND WITH A LOT OF WOMEN.
SEX NO LONGER BECAME
PLEASURABLE, INTERESTING TO HIM.
HE WAS ACTUALLY TAKING A LOT OF
XANAX.
HE MENTIONED HE WAS ABUSING
XANAX AS A RESULT OF ALL OF
THIS.
AND FINALLY HE SAID, YOU KNOW
WHAT, I WANT TO BE CLOSER TO
GOD.
SO HE DECIDED TO NOT HAVE SEX
ANYMORE AS A WAY TO SHOW GOD
THAT HE IS WITH HIM.
CHARLES: AND THEN HE SEES
HAILEY.
>> AND HE SAID THAT -- HE WAS
CELIBATE FOR ABOUT A YEAR.
HE BELIEVES THAT GOD REWARDED
HIM WITH HAILEY.
WHEN HE SAW HER HE IS LIKE,,
WOW, I DIDN'T REALIZE HOW MUCH
SHE MEANT TO ME, HOW GREAT SHE
MADE ME FEEL, HOW SHE COMPLETED
ME.
THEY GOT BACK TOGETHER AND
ACTUALLY WERE NOT HAVING SEX
UNTIL THEY GOT MARRIED.
HARVEY: THIS IS BIEBER JUST
OPENING UP.
HE DID AN INTERVIEW WITH
"VOGUE."
HE AND HAILEY DID AN INTERVIEW.
HE SAID, "DRUGS PUT A SCREEN
BETWEEN ME AND WHAT I WAS
DOING."
IT USED TO BE, I REMEMBER HIS
PEOPLE WOULD SAY, NOW, HE'LL
HAVE A BEER, SMOKE A LITTLE POT,
BUT HE IS SAYING IT WAS MUCH
MORE SIGNIFICANT.
MUCH MORE SIGNIFICANT THAN WHAT
HE HAD SAID.
RAQUEL: BUT XANAX IS A SERIOUS
SITUATION, SO I CAN UNDERSTAND
WHY HIS SEX HABITS CHANGED BY
DOING XANAX.
IT MAKES YOU FEEL WELL.
IT DOESN'T MAKE YOU ON THE EDGE
AND WANT TO GO.
CHARLES: THE WAY HE DESCRIBED
IT, IT WASN'T THAT HE STOPPED
HAVING SEX BECAUSE XANAX WAS
KILLING HIS SEX DRIVE.
HE MADE A CONSCIOUS DECISION
THAT HE WAS NOT GOING TO HAVE
SEX.
>> ANOTHER THING ABOUT THIS THE
REASON WHY ALL THIS CAME ABOUT,
WAS BECAUSE HE WAS DISPELLING
RUMORS THAT HAILEY WAS PREGNANT.
THAT'S WHY THEY HAD GOT MARRIED.
CHARLES: SHOTGUN WEDDING.
>> HE EXPLAINS, LOOK, I WAS
CELIBATE.
I WANTED TO HAVE SEX WITH A GIRL
I'M IN LOVE WITH.
>> HI, I'M FROM LONG BEACH,
CALIFORNIA.
I'M WITH YOU.
HE HAD ME CONFUSED, JUSTIN, ONE
MINUTE SAYING HE IS CELIBATE
BECAUSE HE WANTS TO BE CLOSER TO
GOD, THEN HE WANTS TO RUN TO
GOD, TO GET MARRIED, TO HAVE
SEX.
HARVEY: THAT MAKES IT REAL.
WE HAVE A LOT TO COVER.
CHARLES: LET'S GET TO 21 SAVAGE
AND THE DETAILS.
HARVEY: WE HAVE SOME REVELATIONS
NOW.
WE'VE GOTTEN TO THE BOTTOM.
CHARLES: WHICH REVELATION DO YOU
WANT TO START WITH?
HARVEY: WE NOW KNOW, BECAUSE WE
GOT A HOLD OF THE POLICE
REPORTS, THERE WERE ACTUALLY
THREE OF THEM LAST SUNDAY, THE
DAY THAT 21 SAVAGE AND OTHERS
WERE ARRESTED.
I GUESS ONE OF THE HEADLINES IS
THAT THEY FOUND A LOADED --
FULLY LOADED GLOCK IN THE CENTER
CONSOLE OF THE CAR THAT HE WAS
DRIVING WHEN HE WAS PULLED OVER
BY COPS.
NOW, YOU MIGHT THINK, OK, THE
GLOCK HAS SOMETHING TO DO WITH
HIS ARREST WITH ICE.
THESE POLICE REPORTS NEVER
CONNECT THE DOTS OR EXPLAIN WHY
ICE WAS THERE.
WE ARE TOLD THEY WERE THERE, BUT
THE POLICE REPORTS MENTIONED
NOTHING ABOUT ICE.
CHARLES: ATF WAS THERE.
>> THERE WAS A K-9 UNIT, A VICE
UNIT.
THEY WERE THERE FOR AN OPERATION
TO TAKE DOWN YOUNG DUTY -- YOUNG
NUDY.
21 WAS DRIVING IN A DIFFERENT
VEHICLE.
THEY SAY HE DROVE ERRATICALLY IN
FRONT OF AN OFFICER.
THAT'S WHY THEY PULLED HIM OVER
AND DISCOVERED ALL THIS.
HARVEY: WHAT'S INTERESTING IS,
IT LOOKS LIKE ATF IS THE AGENCY
THAT TOOK 21 SAVAGE INTO
CUSTODY, WHICH MAKES ME THINK IT
HAD SOME CONNECTION TO THE GUN.
CHARLES: YOU UNDERSTAND WHY ATF
IS THERE, BECAUSE THE WARRANTS.
HARVEY: WITH YOUNG NUDY.
CHARLES: IT DID INVOLVE VIOLENT
CRIMES INVOLVING GUNS.
THAT'S WHY ATF WAS THERE.
HARVEY: WHY WAS ICE THERE?
WHY AREN'T THEY MENTIONING ICE?
THEY DON'T EXPLAIN IT.
ATF IS THERE, THE ONLY FEDERAL
AGENCY THAT IS THERE, AND
SOMEHOW ICE IS BROUGHT INTO
THIS.
HARVEY: HIS PEOPLE SAY THAT WAS
NOT HIS GUN, EVEN THOUGH THE
POLICE REPORT SUGGESTS IT IS IN
THE EVIDENCE REPORT.
HIS PEOPLE ARE SAYING, NOT HIS
GUN.
THAT REALLY COMES TO THE CORE OF
WHAT THIS IS ALL ABOUT.
BECAUSE WHAT WE ARE TOLD BY
PEOPLE CONNECTED TO SAVAGE IS
THAT THEIR BIGGEST BEEF IS NOT
THAT INS IS TRYING TO DEPORT
HIM.
THEY ARE GOING TO ARGUE HE
SHOULD NOT BE DEPORTED.
THEY HAVE A GOOD CASE, I THINK,
THAT HE SHOULD NOT BE DEPORTED.
BUT THEY ARE NOT WAGING HOLY WAR
OVER THAT.
THEY ARE WAGING HOLY WAR OVER
THE FACT THAT ICE IS HOLDING
HIM IN A CELL AND NOT LETING --
LETTING HIM BOND OUT, PENDING
THE HEARING, WHICH IS WHAT THEY
TYPICALLY DO WITH OTHER PEOPLE
IN A SIMILAR SITUATION AS LONG
AS THEY DON'T POSE A THREAT TO
THE COMMUNITY OR BE A FLIGHT
RISK, AND HE IS REALLY NEITHER.
SO, WHY ARE THEY HOLDING HIM
PENDING A HEARING THAT COULD
TAKE A YEAR?
THEY ARE SO BACKLOGGED IN INS,
IT'S CRAZY.
SO, WHY ARE THEY HOLDING THIS
GUY?
WE CAN'T GET AN ANSWER FROM ICE.
WE'VE CALLED ICE.
WE'VE MADE REQUESTS.
JUST RADIO SILENCE.
THEY WILL NOT GIVE US ANYTHING
TO EXPLAIN THIS.
HIS PEOPLE ARE SAYING THERE IS
ABSOLUTELY NO JUSTIFICATION TO
HOLD THE SKY.
-- HOLD THIS GUY.
CHARLES: IT'S PRETTY OUTRAGEOUS,
BECAUSE THE PRESIDENT IS THERE
FOR HIM TO BE RELEASED.
HARVEY: ABSOLUTELY.
CHARLES: AND IF YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO RELEASE HIM, AT LEAST EXPLAIN
WHY HE IS BEING HELD.
IF YOU DON'T SAY WHY, THEN IT
LOOKS LIKE YOU ARE KEEPING A BIG
SECRET.
IT'S BAD FOR THE AGENCY AND THE
GOVERNMENT.
OBVIOUSLY, IT'S UNFAIR TO 21
SAVAGE.
HARVEY: THEY'RE JUST NOT
ANSWERING US.
THERE IS A COMPELLING CASE TO BE
MADE THAT THIS GUY HAS BEEN IN
PLAIN SIGHT OF THE ICE FOR YEARS
AND THEY KNEW WHERE HE WAS AND
THEY KNEW HE WAS APPLYING TO GET
THIS VISA TO BECOME A LEGAL
RESIDENT.
WHY SUNDAY?
WHY WAS ICE THERE?
WHY ARE THEY HOLDING HIM WITHOUT
LETTING HIM OUT?
CHARLES: WHY IS ICE NOT
MENTIONED IN ANY OF THE REPORTS
ABOUT THE ARREST?
HARVEY: AND THEY MENTION
EVERYBODY ELSE.
>> HI.
I'M FROM FAIRFIELD, CALIFORNIA.
HERE'S THE THING WITH 21 SAVAGE.
I'M NOT SURPRISED.
HE IS GOING TO CARRY A GUN FOR
PROTECTION.
WE LIVE IN AMERICA.
I'M MORE SHOCKED THAT HE HAD THE
AUDACITY TO TRY TO BECOME A
SUPERSTAR WHEN HE IS AN ILLEGAL
IMMIGRANT, BASICALLY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHO TOLD ON
HIM, BUT IT LOOKS LIKE A SNITCH
SITUATION.
HARVEY: IT LOOKS TO US, BASED ON
THE REPORTS, THAT THEY WERE ALL
AFTER YOUNG NUDY.
CHARLES: AND ENDED UP GETTING 21
SAVAGE AND ANOTHER PERSON AS
WELL.
HARVEY: BUT YOUNG NUDY DOES NOT
HAVE IMMIGRATION PROBLEMS.
WHAT'S GNAWING AT ME IS, WERE
THEY REALLY AFTER YOUNG NUDY,
BECAUSE WHY WAS ICE THERE?
CHARLES: YOU KEEP SAYING WHY WAS
ICE THERE.
I'M STILL NOT CONVINCED ICE WAS
THERE.
HAVING READ THE REPORTS, I'M NOT
CONVINCED ICE AGENTS WERE
ACTUALLY THERE.
HARVEY: WE HAVE SOURCES WITH
ATF TELLING US THAT ICE WAS
THERE.
I CAN'T -- THAT'S WHAT WE'RE
BEING TOLD.
LET'S MOVE ON.
CHARLES: ARIANA GRANDE AND PETE
DAVIDSON AND KATE BECKINSALE.
HARVEY: AND HOW SHE FEELS ABOUT
THEM.
CHARLES: THE SHE BEING ARIANA
GRANDE.
WE GOT ARIANA.
HARVEY: WHO SPOKE, A LOT.
SHE NEVER TALKS.
CHARLES: WE GOT HER IN CULVER
CITY.
SHE WAS LEAVING THE STUDIO WITH
SOME FRIENDS.
HER MOM WAAS TH -- WAS THERE.
PETE DAVIDSON AND KATE
BECKINSALE, NOW VERY PUBLICLY
OUT TOGETHER.
HARVEY: HOW DOES SHE FEEL ABOUT
THAT?
WE STARTED WITH THE GRAMMYS.
SHE IS PULLED OUT OF THE
GRAMMYS.
SHE IS NOT GOING TO PERFORM OVER
A DISPUTE.
>> WE ARE GOING TO MISS YOU NOT
PERFORMING.
WHAT IF YOU WIN AN AWARD AND ARE
NOT THERE TO RECEIVE IT?
>> YOU DESERVE THE AWARD.
>> 2 P.M. KATE BECKINSALE MAKE A
GOOD COUPLE? -- DO PETE AND KATE
BECKINSALE MAKE A GOOD COUPLE?
CHARLES: SO CUTE.
HARVEY: SHE BROKE UP WITH PETE.
THEY HAD A LOT OF ISSUES.
IT SOUNDS TO ME LIKE, IT'S VERY
ADULT.
CHARLES: YEAH.
WHICH IS NOT WHAT PEOPLE THINK
OF.
HARVEY: THE BIGGER PROBLEM IS
THIS.
THAT SHE ACTUALLY ASKED OUR
CAMERA GUY WHERE TO GET A MEAL
AROUND THERE AND HE GAVE HER THE
NAME OF A RESTAURANT THAT IS NOT
THERE.
SHE MAY HAVE GONE ON A WILD
GOOSE CHASE.
CHARLES: HE SENT HER 10 MILES
AWAY.
HARVEY: OK, TAKING A BREAK.
CHARLES: WHEN WE COME BACK, TOM
BRADY AND PRESIDENT TRUMP, WILL
THEY COME FACE-TO-FACE?
EVER SINCE THE PATRIOTS WON THE
SUPER BOWL, EVERYONE WONDERED,
WOULD TOM GO TO THE WHITE HOUSE
WITH THE TEAM?
HE DID NOT GO.
HE WAS ASKED
♪
Take a moment.
To unwrap,
and unwind...
with Lindor.
A milk chocolate shell
with a smooth,
melting center.
Crafted By the Lindt
Master Chocolatiers
whenever.
wherever.
Lindor, only from Lindt.
CHARLES: WELCOME BACK TO "TMZ
LIVE."
TOM BRADY IS, I THINK, GIVING US
A STRONG HINT AS TO WHETHER OR
NOT HE IS GOING TO THE WHITE
HOUSE.
HARVEY: I THINK IT'S A STRONG
HINT.
CHARLES: HE WAS ASKED
POINT-BLANK THIS MORNING IN
BOSTON, DOING A GILLETTE EVENT.
THEY GAVE HIM A SHAVE.
I THINK THEY DO THIS EVERY YEAR
AT THE END OF THE SEASON.
HARVEY: A REPORTER WAS
INTERVIEWING HIM.
CHARLES: TOM OPENED UP THE ROOM.
HE SAID, I WILL TAKE SOME
QUESTIONS.
THE REPORTER --
HARVEY: HE KNEW WHAT WAS COMING.
OF COURSE.
EVERYBODY IS TALKING ABOUT IT.
REMEMBER THE BACKDROP, TWO YEARS
AGO TOM BRADY DID NOT GO TO THE
WHITE HOUSE, THEN THERE WAS A
LOT OF TALK ABOUT THAT AND
DONALD TRUMP SEEMED REALLY ANGRY
AT HIM.
CHARLES: AND HE AND TRUMP WERE
FRIENDS.
HARVEY: HE HAD A MAGA HAT IN HIS
LOCKER.
NOW THE QUESTION, IS HE GOING TO
GO THIS YEAR?
>> DO YOU HAVE PLANS ON GOING TO
THE WHITE HOUSE FOR A
CELEBRATION?
TOM: NEXT QUESTION.
CHARLES: NEXT QUESTION.
DID HE SAY, "OH, MY GOD" AT THE
END?
HARVEY: HE KNEW THIS IS GOING TO
BE ASKED.
CHARLES: HE SHRUGS HIS
SHOULDERS.
HARVEY: DONALD TRUMP EXTENDED
THIS ALL IN FRENCH A WHILE AGO
-- THIS OLIVE BRANCH A WHILE
AGO, CONGRATULATING HIM BY NAME,
WHICH HE HADN'T DONE SINCE BRADY
WAS A NO-SHOW AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
TOM BRADY DID NOT RESPOND IN
KIND TO TRUMP.
EVERYBODY IS WONDERING.
GISELLE'S POSITION ON TRUMP,
WHICH HAS HARDENED --
CHARLES: TWO YEARS AGO, SHE WAS
VERY VOCAL ABOUT THE FACT THAT
SHE DID NOT LIKE HIM OR HIS
POLICIES.
HARVEY: AND IT HAS HARDENED
SINCE THEN.
>> ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY HIS
ANSWER INDICATES HE IS NOT GOING
TO THE WHITE HOUSE?
CHARLES: CORRECT.
>> I THINK YOU'RE COMPLETELY
WRONG.
CHARLES: I THINK THAT'S WHY HE
COMPLETELY SHRUGGED HIS
SHOULDERS.
YOU KNOW WHAT THE ANSWER IS.
DON'T MAKE ME SAY IT.
>> THE COUNTRY HAS NEVER BEEN
MORE DIVIDED.
WHY ANSWER THIS QUESTION
PREMATURELY WHEN YOU DON'T HAVE
TO?
ALL YOU'RE GOING TO DO IS MAKE
PEOPLE MAD, MAKE FANS MAD, MAKE
YOUR WIFE MAD.
KICK IT DOWN THE ROAD.
CHARLES: WHY WOULD IT MAKE HIS
WIFE MAD IF HE SAID I'M NOT
GOING?
>> NO, BECAUSE I THINK HE IS
GOING TO GO TO THE WHITE HOUSE
AND HE DOESN'T WANT TO TALK
ABOUT IT NOW AND HAVE TO DEAL
WITH A MAD GISELLE FOR THE NEXT
COUPLE MONTHS.
CHARLES: SO HE IS GOING TO SNEAK
OUT OF THE HOUSE ONE DAY?
HARVEY: GOING DOWN THE STREET TO
GET SOME SODA.
CHARLES: I'M GOING TO GET MILK.
>> EXACTLY.
HARVEY: BABCOCK, HE IS NOT
GOING.
CHARLES: YOU ARE RIDICULOUS.
>> I THINK THE RELATIONSHIP IS
GOOD AND HE WILL BE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
HARVEY: THERE IS NO
RELATIONSHIP.
HE HAS NEVER SAID A WORD TO
TRUMP IN TWO YEARS.
>> CAN I INTERRUPT HERE AND TAKE
YOUR SIDE?
REMEMBER WHEN TRUMP
CONGRATULATED THE PATRIOTS FOR
WINNING THE AFC CHAMPIONSHIP
GAME?
YOU KNOW WHAT HE DIDN'T DO?
HARVEY: HE DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT HE DIDN'T DO
AFTER THE SUPER BOWL?
HE DID NOT CONGRATULATE THE
PATRIOTS FOR WINNING THE SUPER
BOWL YET.
THAT HAS NOT HAPPENED.
I THINK TO BABCOCK'S DETRIMENT,
HE REACHED OUT THE FIRST TIME,
DID NOT GET A REACTION, HE SAYS,
I SEE HOW IT IS.
>> BILLY FROM DALLAS.
IT'S WISE FOR TOM BRADY NOT TO
SAY ANYTHING, BUT I HAVE TO
AGREE TO HIM NOT SAYING ANYTHING
MEANS HE DOES NOT HAVE A
DECISION.
CHARLES: WE WILL SEE, BABCOCK.
HARVEY: MOVING ON.
CHARLES: TWO VIRGINIA.
THE EMBATTLED STATE OF VIRGINIA
WHERE GOVERNOR NORTHAM --
A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE CALLING FOR
GOVERNOR NORTHAM TO STEP DOWN,
TO RESIGN AFTER A PHOTO OF HIM
IN BLACKFACE CAME OUT.
HE IS DENYING THAT THAT PHOTO IS
HIM, BUT DOES ADMIT THAT HE
ADDRESSED -- DRESSED UP AS
MICHAEL JACKSON AT ONE POINT AND
DID DARKEN HIS FACE.
ONE OF THE PEOPLE WHO CALLED FOR
HIM TO STEP DOWN IS THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL, MARK HERRING.
THE ISSUE FOR MARK HERRING IS
HE, TOO, ADMITS THAT HE AT ONE
POINT HAD GONE TO A PARTY IN
BLACKFACE, BUT HE SAYS HE WAS
DOING IT AS AN HOMAGE TO HIS
FAVORITE RAPPER AT THE TIME,
BACK IN 1980.
HIS FAVORITE RAPPER WAS CURTIS
BLOW.
SO, HOW DOES CURTIS BLOW FEEL
ABOUT THE FACT THAT THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL WAS A FAN AND TRIED TO
PAY HOMAGE TO HIM THIS WAY?
CURTIS IS JOINING US NOW, THE
LEGEND HIMSELF.
WELCOME TO "TMZ LIVE."
HOW ARE YOU DOING, MAN?
>> WHAT'S GOING ON, GUYS?
HARVEY: WE ARE THRILLED TO HAVE
YOU ON.
CHARLES: WE'VE HAD YOU ON ONCE
BEFORE.
IT WAS FOR A BETTER REASON THAN
THIS.
I'M CURIOUS HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT
IT JUST, EVERY DAY, SOMETHING
THIS.
COMES OUT OF VIRGINIA THAT IS
IT JUST, EVERY DAY, SOMETHING
MORE SHOCKING.
COMES OUT OF VIRGINIA THAT IS
TO FIND OUT THE ATTORNEY GENERAL
MORE SHOCKING.
, ONE, WAS A FAN OF YOURS BACK
TO FIND OUT THE ATTORNEY GENERAL
IN 1980 WAS A LITTLE SURPRISING
, ONE, WAS A FAN OF YOURS BACK
AND THEN SHOCKING THAT HE
IN 1980 WAS A LITTLE SURPRISING
ACTUALLY WENT IN BLACKFACE TO
AND THEN SHOCKING THAT HE
HONOR YOU.
ACTUALLY WENT IN BLACKFACE TO
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT?
HONOR YOU.
>> IT'S LIKE WHAT YOU JUST SAID.
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT?
I WAS TOTALLY SHOCKED.
>> IT'S LIKE WHAT YOU JUST SAID.
BEING THE ELDER SPOKESMAN, A
I WAS TOTALLY SHOCKED.
FATHER, A MINISTER, A HUSBAND, I
BEING THE ELDER SPOKESMAN, A
FIND IT TOTALLY OFFENSIVE AND
FATHER, A MINISTER, A HUSBAND, I
DISRESPECTFUL, DEGRADING.
FIND IT TOTALLY OFFENSIVE AND
IT'S UGLY.
DISRESPECTFUL, DEGRADING.
YOU KNOW, I'M PRAYING FOR MY
IT'S UGLY.
MAN, MR. HERRING, RIGHT NOW.
YOU KNOW, I'M PRAYING FOR MY
I THINK --
MAN, MR. HERRING, RIGHT NOW.
I'VE SEEN TRIBUTES BEFORE WHERE,
I THINK --
YOU KONW, -- KNOW, THE
I'VE SEEN TRIBUTES BEFORE WHERE,
BLACKFACE WAS NOT USED.
YOU KONW, -- KNOW, THE
LIKE MY MAN JIMMY FALLON DID
BLACKFACE WAS NOT USED.
SOMETHING WITH SHAQ A FEW YEARS
LIKE MY MAN JIMMY FALLON DID
AGO, NOT SHAQ.
SOMETHING WITH SHAQ A FEW YEARS
LEBRON JAMES.
AGO, NOT SHAQ.
IT WAS THE WASTE PAPER
LEBRON JAMES.
BASKETBALL SONG.
IT WAS THE WASTE PAPER
THEY DID A SPOOF ON MY
BASKETBALL SONG.
BASKETBALL SONG OR EVEN
THEY DID A SPOOF ON MY
ATTRIBUTE WITH JIMMY FALLON AND
BASKETBALL SONG OR EVEN
-- EVEN A TRIBUTE WITH JIMMY
ATTRIBUTE WITH JIMMY FALLON AND
FALLON AND JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE.
-- EVEN A TRIBUTE WITH JIMMY
HARVEY: I HAVE A QUESTION ABOUT
FALLON AND JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE.
THIS.
HARVEY: I HAVE A QUESTION ABOUT
WE HAVE BEEN TALKING ABOUT IT A
THIS.
LOT.
WE HAVE BEEN TALKING ABOUT IT A
DOES IT MATTER TO YOU, A, WHAT
LOT.
WAS IN HIS HEAD AND HIS HEART,
DOES IT MATTER TO YOU, A, WHAT
AND, B, DO YOU LOOK BACK AND SAY
WAS IN HIS HEAD AND HIS HEART,
THIS WAS DECADES AGO AND THAT
AND, B, DO YOU LOOK BACK AND SAY
PEOPLE TODAY LOOK AT THINGS WITH
THIS WAS DECADES AGO AND THAT
A DIFFERENT LENS, SAY, THAN THEY
PEOPLE TODAY LOOK AT THINGS WITH
LOOKED THEN, AND THEY ARE NOT AS
A DIFFERENT LENS, SAY, THAN THEY
SENSITIVE AND NOT AS EVOLVED AS
LOOKED THEN, AND THEY ARE NOT AS
THEY ARE NOW?
SENSITIVE AND NOT AS EVOLVED AS
DOES THAT MATTER TO YOU?
THEY ARE NOW?
>> OF COURSE.
DOES THAT MATTER TO YOU?
WE AS YOUNG KIDS, WE MAKE
>> OF COURSE.
MISTAKES.
WE AS YOUNG KIDS, WE MAKE
NOBODY IS PERFECT.
MISTAKES.
WE, ON A SPIRITUAL LEVEL, WE
NOBODY IS PERFECT.
NEED TO FORGIVE IN ORDER TO
WE, ON A SPIRITUAL LEVEL, WE
RECEIVE FORGIVENESS.
NEED TO FORGIVE IN ORDER TO
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT AS A
RECEIVE FORGIVENESS.
CHRISTIAN THAT WE FORGIVE EACH
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT AS A
OTHER FOR OUR MISTAKES.
CHRISTIAN THAT WE FORGIVE EACH
BUT SOMETHING LIKE THIS THAT
OTHER FOR OUR MISTAKES.
GOES ALL THE WAY BACK, AGAIN,
BUT SOMETHING LIKE THIS THAT
IT'S THE BLACKFACE.
GOES ALL THE WAY BACK, AGAIN,
IT WAS DEFINITELY A MISTAKE ON
IT'S THE BLACKFACE.
HIS PART.
IT WAS DEFINITELY A MISTAKE ON
IT'S A TEACHABLE MOMENT
HIS PART.
NOWADAYS, AND WE ALL SHOULD
IT'S A TEACHABLE MOMENT
LEARN FROM THIS.
NOWADAYS, AND WE ALL SHOULD
I THINK IT WOULD CAN FORGIVE
LEARN FROM THIS.
HIM, HE OWES SOME KINMD O-- KIND
I THINK IT WOULD CAN FORGIVE
OF RETRIBUTION OR JUST A
HIM, HE OWES SOME KINMD O-- KIND
COMMITMENT TO HELP OUT
OF RETRIBUTION OR JUST A
AFRICAN-AMERICANS, SINCE HE HAS
COMMITMENT TO HELP OUT
BEEN IN THIS SITUATION RIGHT
AFRICAN-AMERICANS, SINCE HE HAS
NOW.
BEEN IN THIS SITUATION RIGHT
HARVEY: CURTIS.
NOW.
CHARLES: TIMES CHANGE.
HARVEY: CURTIS.
HARVEY: CURTIS, IT'S GREAT
CHARLES: TIMES CHANGE.
HAVING YOU ON.
HARVEY: CURTIS, IT'S GREAT
REALLY NICE TALKING TO YOU.
HAVING YOU ON.
>> THANK YOU.
REALLY NICE TALKING TO YOU.
YOU KNOW, IT'S REALLY ALL ABOUT
>> THANK YOU.
THE LOVE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S REALLY ALL ABOUT
LOVE AGAINST HATE, AND LOVE CAN
THE LOVE.
CONQUER ALL.
LOVE AGAINST HATE, AND LOVE CAN
THIS IS A TEACHABLE MOMENT.
CONQUER ALL.
THE KIDS NOWADAYS ARE DOING
THIS IS A TEACHABLE MOMENT.
BLACKFACE, NOWADAYS.
THE KIDS NOWADAYS ARE DOING
THESE ARE THE KIDS THAT WE NEED
BLACKFACE, NOWADAYS.
TO REACH OUT TO AND TELL THEM
THESE ARE THE KIDS THAT WE NEED
THIS IS NOT RIGHT.
TO REACH OUT TO AND TELL THEM
CHARLES: AND CURTIS, TO THAT
THIS IS NOT RIGHT.
POINT, IT IS INTERESTING THAT
CHARLES: AND CURTIS, TO THAT
THIS HAS COME UP IN FEBRUARY.
POINT, IT IS INTERESTING THAT
IT IS BLACK HISTORY MONTH.
THIS HAS COME UP IN FEBRUARY.
I KNOW YOU ARE GOING TO BE
IT IS BLACK HISTORY MONTH.
SPEAKING TO SOME KIDS TODAY
I KNOW YOU ARE GOING TO BE
ABOUT BLACK HISTORY MONTH IN NEW
SPEAKING TO SOME KIDS TODAY
YORK.
ABOUT BLACK HISTORY MONTH IN NEW
>> RIGHT.
YORK.
I'M ACTUALLY IN AUGUSTA,
>> RIGHT.
GEORGIA.
I'M ACTUALLY IN AUGUSTA,
CHARLES: SORRY.
GEORGIA.
>> I'M AT THE VOORHEES COLLEGE.
CHARLES: SORRY.
I'M GOING OVER TO ANOTHER
>> I'M AT THE VOORHEES COLLEGE.
COLLEGE, DOING A COUPLE SPEAKING
I'M GOING OVER TO ANOTHER
ENGAGEMENTS ABOUT THE HISTORY OF
COLLEGE, DOING A COUPLE SPEAKING
HIP-HOP DURING BLACK HISTORY
ENGAGEMENTS ABOUT THE HISTORY OF
MONTH.
HIP-HOP DURING BLACK HISTORY
CHARLES: ALL RIGHT.
MONTH.
HARVEY: CURTIS, THANKS SO MUCH.
CHARLES: ALL RIGHT.
>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS, THANK YOU.
HARVEY: CURTIS, THANKS SO MUCH.
HARVEY: WE'RE TAKING A BREAK.
>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS, THANK YOU.
CHARLES: WHEN WE COME BACK,
HARVEY: WE'RE TAKING A BREAK.
MIGUEL IS GOING TO BE WITH US.
CHARLES: WHEN WE COME BACK,
BIG WEEKEND FOR HIM.
MIGUEL IS GOING TO BE WITH US.
HE IS UP FOR A GRAMMY, ONE OF
BIG WEEKEND FOR HIM.
THE FAVORITES TO WIN.
HE IS UP FOR A GRAMMY, ONE OF
THERE IS AN ISSUE HE HAS BEEN
THE FAVORITES TO WIN.
TACKLING FOR YEARS AND IS NOW IN
THERE IS AN ISSUE HE HAS BEEN
THE SPOTLIGHT, PARTIALLY BECAUSE
TACKLING FOR YEARS AND IS NOW IN
OF 21 SAVAGE'S ARREST.
THE SPOTLIGHT, PARTIALLY BECAUSE
IT'S ABOUT IMMIGRATION.
OF 21 SAVAGE'S ARREST.
HE HAS BEEN AT THE FOREFRONT OF
IT'S ABOUT IMMIGRATION.
THIS BATTLE, BUT HE HAS A NEW
HE HAS BEEN AT THE FOREFRONT OF
SONG WITH CALVIN HARRIS THAT
THIS BATTLE, BUT HE HAS A NEW
REALLY PUTS A SPOTLIGHT ON THE
SONG WITH CALVIN HARRIS THAT
ISSUE.
REALLY PUTS A SPOTLIGHT ON THE
I'M ALEX TREBEK
HERE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50-85
AND LOOKING
TO BUY LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET,
REMEMBER THE THREE P'S.
THE THREE WHAT?
THE THREE P'S?
WHAT ARE THE THREE P'S?
THE THREE P'S OF LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET
ARE PRICE, PRICE, AND PRICE.
A PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD,
A PRICE THAT CAN'T INCREASE,
AND A PRICE
THAT FITS YOUR BUDGET.
I'M 54 AND I WAS
A SMOKER BUT QUIT.
ALEX, WHAT'S MY PRICE?
YOU CAN GET COVERAGE
FOR $9.95 A MONTH.
I'M 65, RETIRED,
AND TAKE MEDICATIONS.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
ALSO $9.95 A MONTH.
I JUST TURNED 80
AND I'M ON A FIXED INCOME.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
$9.95 A MONTH FOR YOU, TOO.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85,
CALL NOW ABOUT
THE NUMBER ONE MOST POPULAR
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE PLAN
AVAILABLE THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IT HAS AN AFFORDABLE RATE
STARTING AT $9.95 A MONTH.
THAT'S LESS THAN 35 CENTS A DAY.
YOU CANNOT BE TURNED DOWN
BECAUSE OF YOUR HEALTH.
NO MEDICAL EXAM,
NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE IS GUARANTEED,
AND THIS PLAN HAS A GUARANTEED
LIFETIME RATE LOCK,
SO YOUR RATE CAN NEVER GO UP
FOR ANY REASON.
AND WITH THIS PLAN,
YOU CAN PICK YOUR PAYMENT DATE,
SO YOU CAN TIME
YOUR PREMIUM DUE DATE
TO WORK WITH YOUR BUDGET.
OPTIONS START AT $9.95 A MONTH,
PLUS, YOU GET A 30-DAY
MONEY BACK GUARANTEE.
SO CALL NOW
FOR FREE INFORMATION.
AND YOU'LL ALSO GET
THIS FREE BENEFICIARY PLANNER,
AND IT'S YOURS JUST FOR CALLING.
SO CALL NOW.
♪ ♪
Let's face it,
the world
could use some warmth.
♪ ♪
ANNOUNCER: TMZ HAS EVERY
FREAKING THING.
HARVEY: I HEARD IT THROUGH THE
GRAPEVINE.
>> HE LOOKS LIKE A CALIFORNIA
RAISIN, TOO.
ANNOUNCER: IT'S TMZ.
♪
CHARLES: WELCOME BACK TO "TMZ
LIVE."
MIGUEL HAS A BIG WEEKEND AHEAD
OF HIM.
HARVEY: GRAMMYS ARE SUNDAY.
CHARLES: HE IS UP FOR TWO OF
THEM, BEST R&B SONG, BEST URBAN
CONTEMPORARY ALBUM.
THE ALBUM IS THE ONE THAT A LOT
OF PEOPLE THINK HE IS DEFINITELY
GOING TO WIN, SHOULD WIN, BUT
THERE IS SOMETHING ELSE THAT IS
REALLY IMPORTANT TO MIGUEL,
ASIDE FROM AWARDS.
FOR YEARS, HE HAS BEEN VERY
VOCAL ABOUT IMMIGRATION POLICIES
AND WHAT HE SEES AS, OBVIOUSLY,
BAD IMMIGRATION POLICIES.
HARVEY: AND THIS ALL GETS
REIGNITED WITH 21 SAVAGE.
CHARLES: CERTAINLY.
IT'S ALSO REIGNITED BECAUSE
MIGUEL AND CALVIN HARRIS AND
BENNY BLANCO HAVE A SONG THAT
CAME OUT JUST ABOUT A MONTH AGO.
IT'S CALLED, "I FOUND YOU."
IF YOU HAVEN'T SEEN THE VIDEO,
YOU SHOULD WATCH THE FULL THING,
BECAUSE IT TELLS THE STORY OF A
WOMAN WHO WAS FROM HONDURAS,
CAME TO AMERICA.
SHE WAS SEPARATED FROM HER SON.
NO SPOILERS.
YOU HAVE TO WATCH IT TO SEE WHAT
HAPPENS.
BUT THIS IS A REALLY IMPORTANT
ISSUE TO MIGUEL.
HE IS JOINING US RIGHT NOW TO
TALK ABOUT THIS AND WHY HE HAS
CHOSEN TO PUT A SPOTLIGHT ON IT.
IGUEL -- MIGUEL, WELCOME TO "TMZ
LIVE."
HARVEY: THANKS FOR JOINING US.
APPRECIATE IT.
>> IT'S A PLEASURE.
HOPE YOU GUYS ARE HAVING A GOOD
DAY.
HARVEY: RIGHT BACK AT YOU.
CHARLES: THIS VIDEO WAS JUST
CAPTIVATING.
IT IS PORTRAYED AS A TRUE STORY,
RIGHT?
DID YOU MEET THE WOMAN WHO WAS
AT THE CENTER OF THIS?
>> NO, I WISH I DID.
NO.
IT FOLLOWS THE STORY OF HER
JOURNEY TO THE STATES.
HER NAME IS NILDA.
WHEN YOU WATCH THE VIDEO, YOU
REALLY GET A SENSE OF ALL OF THE
CHALLENGES THAT IT TOOK FOR HER
TO MAKE IT TO THE STATES.
AND THEN WHAT SHE IS STILL
DEALING WITH, IN ORDER TO JUST
BE WITH HER SON HERE.
IT'S KIND OF A TRAGEDY, BECAUSE
THERE ARE SO MANY PEOPLE HERE
WHO ARE DEALING WITH SIMILAR
SITUATIONS.
IT'S ACTUALLY CRAZY.
CHARLES: AND I KNOW YOU, THIS IS
NOT A NEW THING FOR YOU.
EVEN YEARS AGO, I REMEMBER YOU
HELD A CONCERT HERE IN
CALIFORNIA, ADVOCATING FOR
CHANGE IN IMMIGRATION POLICY.
>> YEAH.
YEAH.
IT WAS REALLY NICE.
I WAS AT ADELANTO, JUST OUTSIDE
OF LOS ANGELES, KIND OF TOWARDS
THE DESERT.
IT IS ONE OF THE LARGEST
ATTENTION CENTERS IN CALIFORNIA
THAT IS HOLDING, TO THIS DAY,
HOLDING PEOPLE WHO ARE
UNDOCUMENTED.
AND ARE HAVING A LOT OF TROUBLE
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT JUST WHAT
THEY ARE GOING TO DO WITH THEIR
LIVES, IF THEY ARE GOING TO BE
DEPORTED OR KEPT IN THE STATES.
IT'S A WEIRD LIMBO.
THERE ARE ALL THESE GRAY AREAS
IN TERMS OF FIGURING OUT HOW TO
GET LEGAL SUPPORT AND SO ON AND
SO FORTH.
A LOT OF THESE PEOPLE DON'T EVEN
SPEAK ENGLISH.
IT'S REALLY CRAZY, MAN.
HARVEY: MIGUEL, WE HAVE BEEN ALL
OVER THIS 21 SAVAGE ARREST SINCE
IT HAPPENED.
IT IS JUST WEIRD AND
INEXPLICABLE WHY HE IS --
CHARLES: WHY HE IS BEING HELD
STILL.
HARVEY: AND NOW OUT ON BOND.
WHAT DO YOU THINK IS BEHIND ALL
THIS?
>> IT DOES SHED LIGHT ON THIS,
HELPS PEOPLE UNDERSTAND THAT
THIS ISN'T JUST A SPECIFIC
ETHNIC GROUP THAT IS AFFECTED BY
THIS.
THERE'S PEOPLE FROM ALL OVER THE
WORLD WHO ARE HERE IN THE
STATES, WHO ARE CONTRIBUTED TO
SOCIETY, BUT, YOU KNOW, FOR
WHATEVER REASON, HAVE NOT BEEN
ABLE TO, I GUESS, OBTAIN ALL THE
PROPER DOCUMENTATION.
AND HE HAPPENS TO BE ONE OF
THESE UNFORTUNATE PEOPLE.
LOOKING AT IT ON THE POSITIVE
SIDE, IT DOES HELP SHED LIGHT TO
THE THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE WHO JUST
DON'T HAVE A VOICE.
HARVEY: IT'S SO TRUE.
IN MANY WAYS, IT IS SIMILAR TO
MEEK MILL, WHO REALLY SHED LIGHT
AS WELL.
>> RIGHT.
TAKE SHOUT OUT TO MEEK MILL,
TOO.
I KNOW WHAT HE'S DOING, PRISON
REFORM IS SUPER IMPORTANT.
CHARLES: WE SHOULD SAY WHAT YOU
ARE DOING,, YOU STARTED THE
WHILE THEY WAIT FUND, HELPING
FAMILIES THAT HAVE BEEN
DISPLACED AND THAT ARE SEEKING
ASYLUM.
THAT'S REALLY INCREDIBLE WORK
YOU ARE DOING.
>> I DIDN'T START IT, BUT IT'S
AWESOME TO BE ABLE TO CONTRIBUTE
AND HELP SHED LIGHT TO THESE
ISSUES.
WHEN WE HAVE A PLATFORM, IT'S
REALLY FULFILLING TO HELP
EDUCATE EACH OTHER, AND NOT ONLY
THAT, BUT HELP PEOPLE.
I THINK THAT'S WHAT IT REALLY
COMES DOWN TO.
HARVEY: WE DON'T HAVE TIME TO GO
THROUGH ALL THE STUFF, BUT YOU
ARE DEEPLY INVOLVED IN CIVIL
RIGHTS CAUSES ALL OVER THE
BOARD.
IT'S REALLY NICE.
HONESTLY.
ONE OF THE REASONS I LIKE YOU SO
MUCH IS THAT YOU HAVE KIND OF
GOT THIS BIFURCATED LIFE, THAT
YOU ARE AN ENTERTAINER, BUT YOU
DEVOTE HUGE AMOUNT OF TIME TO
THINGS YOU CARE ABOUT, WHERE YOU
CAN USE YOUR FAME AND YOUR
PLATFORM AND EVERYTHING ELSE.
YOU REALLY WALK THE WALK, MAN.
>> THERE ARE SO MANY MUSICIANS
AND ENTERTAINERS AND PEOPLE WHO
HAVE A SPOTLIGHT WHO DO SO MUCH
FOR CAUSES AND HAVE THEIR OWN
CAUSES.
I'VE HAD A CHANCE TO SUPPORT EVA
LONGORIA.
THERE'S A FEW FRIENDS.
ZOE.
THERE'S A LOT OF PEOPLE WHO ARE
REALLY INTO --
I CAN'T NAME THEM ALL, BUT IT'S
NICE TO BE ABLE TO DO A LITTLE
BIT HERE AND THERE.
THE MORE WE SEE THERE ARE
PROBLEMS OR ISSUES TO BE
ADDRESSED, WE ARE LOOKING FOR
OPPORTUNITIES TO ADDRESS THOSE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, MAN.
THERE'S SO MUCH TO BE DONE.
IT'S NOT ONLY ME.
EVERYONE CAN DO SOMETHING.
THAT'S WHAT IT'S ABOUT.
HARVEY: I HOPE YOU GET SOME
HARDWARE ON SUNDAY.
CHARLES: SOME GRAMMYS.
>> OH, MAN, YEAH.
IT'S A BLESSING.
YOU NEVER KNOW WITH THE GRAMMYS,
TOO.
I THINK THAT'S THE FUN PART
ABOUT IT.
BUT JUST TO BE INCLUDED IN THE
CONVERSATION I THINK IS A BIG
ENCOURAGING FACTOR.
WE ARE GOING TO DO IT ANYWAY.
CHARLES: WE'RE PULLING FOR YOU.
BEST R&B SONG, BEST URBAN
CONTEMPORARY ALBUM.
GOOD LUCK AT THE GRAMMYS.
I ENCOURAGE EVERYONE TO WATCH
THE "I FOUND YOU" VIDEO IF YOU
HAVEN'T SEEN IT YET.
IT'S A REALLY COMPELLING STORY
THAT YOU AND CALVIN AND BENNY
HAVE TOLD.
>> BIG SHOUTOUT TO BENNY AND   L
CALVIN.
THEY ARE THE ONES WHO PUT IT
TOGETHER.
CHARLES: CONGRATULATIONS.
WE HAVEN'T SPOKEN TO YOU SINCE
YOU GOT MARRIED.
CONGRATS.
WE SAW PHOTOS.
IT LOOKS GREAT.
>> MY FAVORITE PIECE OF
HARDWARE.
HARVEY: NICE.
GOOD MOVE.
CHARLES: TAKE CARE.
HARVEY: WE ARE TAKING A BREAK.
CHARLES: WHEN WE COME BACK, BLAC
CHYNA SHOULD NOT HAVE CUSTODY OF
DREAM ANY LONGER, NOT FOR NOW.
AND THAT COMES FROM HER OWN
MOTHER, WHO SAYS THAT ROB IS THE
MORE FIT PARENT RIGHT NOW.
Enamel is the white, outer
layer of your tooth surface.
The more that we can
strengthen and re-harden
that tooth surface,
the whiter their patients'
teeth are going to be.
Dentists are going
to really want to
recommend Pronamel
Strong and Bright.
It's going to give their
patients whiter teeth.
recommend Pronamel
Strong and Bright.
Eight wings for just a mere
portrait of yours truly.
Cool story, bro.
Shut up, Dave. It is a cool
story.
Only Pizza Hut has a $5 lineup
of your favorites.
Get 'em fast for just a Lincoln
each.
CHARLES: WELCOME BACK TO "TMZ
LIVE."
ET TU, MAMA?
HARVEY: ET TU, MAMA?
CHARLES: THAT'S WHAT BLAC CHYNA
MIGHT BE SAYING.
I DON'T KNOW OF SHE SPEAKS LATIN
OR NOT.
HARVEY: I WAS IMPRESSED.
CHARLES: BLAC CHYNA'S MOTHER HAS
A STRONG OPINION ABOUT WHAT'S
BEEN GOING ON IN BLAC CHYNA'S
LIFE RECENTLY.
BOTTOM LINE FOR HER IS THAT SHE
THINKS BLAC CHYNA IS NOT --
HARVEY: NOT A FIT MOM.
CHARLES: AND THAT DREAM SHOULD
BE WITH ROB KARDASHIAN.
WE TALKED TO HER ABOUT BLAC
CHYNA'S --
HARVEY: THIS IS REALLY STUNNING.
CHARLES: YOU REMEMBER BLAC
CHYNA, A COUPLE WEEKS AGO --
HARVEY: SHE WENT TO HAWAII.
ROB WAS UPSET BECAUSE SHE LEFT
DREAM WITH THE NANNY.
SHE JUST WENT OFF AND DID HER
OWN THING.
CHARLES: SHE WAS THERE WITH THIS
NEW BOYFRIEND SHE HAD.
GOT INTO A FIGHT WITH HIM.
COPS WERE CALLED.
HARVEY: A LOT OF STUFF HAPPENED.
THIS IS WHAT HER MOTHER SAID.
>> FIRST OF ALL, LET'S START OFF
WITH THIS DUDE.
HIS LITTLE [BEEP], EXCUSE THE
FRENCH, HE IS CRAZY.
YOU GOT A CHIP IN YOUR HAND.
HE IS MESSY -- SHE IS CRAZY FOR
MESSING WITH HIM.
SECOND OF ALL, YOU HAVE HIM
AROUND MY GRANDKIDS?
THAT'S CRAZY.
I DON'T THINK ANYTHING IS WRONG
WITH CHILDREN GOING TO THEIR DAD
.
IT HAPPENS IN EVERYDAY HOMES OUT
HERE IN AMERICA.
I DON'T KNOW IF THEY SHOULD KEEP
THEM, BUT I DO BELIEVE THAT, FOR
A LITTLE WHILE, THEY SHOULD --
TILL SHE PULLS THINGS TOGETHER,
BECAUSE IT'S CLEAR, IT DOESN'T
TAKE A ROCKET SCIENTIST TO SEE
SOMETHING IS TERRIBLY WRONG.
CHARLES: SHE THINKS BLAC CHYNA
HAS BAD JUDGMENT.
HARVEY: BUT THIS IS REALLY
STUNNING THAT BLAC CHYNA'S OWN
MOTHER IS SAYING SHE IS AN UNFIT
PARENT FOR NOW AND THAT DREAM
NEEDS TO BE WITH ROB BECAUSE HE
IS A MORE FIT PARENT.
RAQUEL: I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
MORESO FIT.
I THINK SHE'S GOING OFF BLAC
CHYNA'S ACTIONS BY DATING KID
BOO.
WITH HER DATING SOMEONE WHO IS A
CLONE WITH A CHIP IN HIM AND HAS
A HISTORY OF BEING A DOMESTIC
ABUSER --
CHARLES: HE HAS BEEN ACCUSED OF
DOMESTIC VIOLENCE.
HARVEY: BUT, RAQUEL, SHE IS NOT
WITH KID BOO ANYMORE.
RAQUEL: BUT HER ACTIONS, THOUGH,
OF EVEN BEING WITH A DUDE LIKE
THAT, HER MOM IS SAYING IT IS
TRICKY.
HARVEY: THIS GIVES ROB
KARDASHIAN A LOT OF AMMO IN THIS
NEGOTIATION.
RAQUEL: IT DOESN'T GIVE ANY
AMMO.
HARVEY: IT DOES.
CHARLES: IT ABSOLUTELY DOES.
RAQUEL: YOU COULD JUST BE LIKE,
I HAVE NOT TALKED TO MY MOM.
SHE IS TRIPPING.
HARVEY: YOU CAN SAY THAT, BUT --
CHARLES: HER MOTHER WOULD KNOW
HER.
HER MOTHER IS SAYING MY DAUGHTER
HAS POOR JUDGMENT.
RAQUEL: OF COURSE SHE KNOWS HER.
SHE HAD HER.
THAT'S HER KID.
BUT I THINK THAT THE OVERALL
SITUATION, BLAC CHYNA COULD BE
LIKE, YOU KNOW WHAT, ME AND MY
MOM ARE NOT HEADS UP RIGHT NOW.
WHAT YOU'RE HEARING IS JUST
TRICKY.
>> HEY, Y'ALL.
IT'S AMBER IN RICHMOND,
VIRGINIA.
HOW ARE YOU?
CHARLES: WE ARE GOOD.
>> WELL, I'M GOING TO TELL YOU
RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS THE SMARTEST THING I'VE
EVER HEARD HER SAY ABOUT HER
DAUGHTER.
YOU KNOW KID BOO DID SAY THAT HE
WAS A CLONE.
WHO WOULD WANT TO GO ANYWHERE
WITH HIM ANYWAY?
YOU NEED TO FACE IT HERE, LACK
CHINA.
-- BLAC CHYNA.
YOU ARE TRYING TO STAY RELEVANT.
YOUR DAUGHTER COMES FIRST.
WHY DID YOU PUT YOUR DAUGHTER
WITH A NANNY WITH ROB SITTING
THERE WITH HIS SOCKS THAT
HAVEN'T BEEN SELLING?
HE IS TRYING TO BE WITH HIS
CHILD.
YOU SHOULD HAVE TAKEN HER RIGHT
OVER THERE.
CHARLES: THAT WAS AN UNNECESSARY
SHOT AT ROB'S SOCKS.
HARVEY: WE'RE GOING TO MOVE ON.
CHARLES: MOVING ON TO REALLY
EXCITING NEW TAKE ON DATING
SHOWS.
BECAUSE WHEN YOU REALLY NEED TO
FIND MR. RIGHT OR MRS. RIGHT,
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO TURN TO BUT
YOUR GRANDMA, RIGHT?
HARVEY: [LAUGHTER]
CHARLES: ON JEWISH LIFE TV,
THERE IS A SHOW CALLED "BUBBIES
KNOW BEST."
THEY ARE NOT DOING IT FOR THEIR
FAMILY, BUT THE BUBBIES ARE
TRYING TO FIND LOVE FOR RANDOM
PEOPLE.
HARVEY: AND NOT JUST JEWS,
APPARENTLY.
CHARLES: THIS IS EQUAL
OPPORTUNITY.
JOINING US RIGHT NOW, THE STARS,
THE BUBBIES, SJ, BUNNY, AND
LINDA.
WELCOME TO "TMZ LIVE."
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> GREAT TO BE HERE, DARLING.
>> THE BUBBIES ARE HERE TO MAKE
EVERYBODY FIND LOVE AND THEIR
SOULMATES.
WE CAN FIX THEM UP.
HARVEY: HERE'S THE DEAL.
THE DIVORCE RATE IS ABOUT 50%.
WHY DO YOU GUYS FEEL YOU CAN DO
BETTER THAN THAT?
>> WHAT YOU MEAN?
OF COURSE WE CAN DO BETTER THAN
THAT, DARLING, BECAUSE WE ARE
BUBBIES, AND WE KNOW BEST.
HARVEY: SO, HOW DO YOU --
THERE ARE COMPANIES LIKE
MATCH.COM AND ALL THESE OTHERS
THAT HAVE PROFILES AND WHATNOT.
GIVE US SOME SENSE, BECAUSE,
LOOK, I'M A JEWISH GUY.
I KNOW WHAT YOU ARE TALKING
ABOUT, BECAUSE I'VE SEEN IT IN
MY FAMILY.
SO, EXPLAIN WHAT YOUR MO IS IN
SITTING DOWN WITH SOMEBODY
YOU'VE NEVER NECESSARILY MET
BEFORE, AND SAYING I'M GOING TO
FIGURE OUT WHO YOU SHOULD DATE.
>> WE COME FROM THE HEART.
ONE OF THE BIGGEST RULES IS LIKE
A RABBI TOLD ME.
YOU CAN HAVE YOUR WAY.
AND YOU CAN BE ALONE.
COMPROMISE.
WE TEACH THEM TECHNIQUES TO BE
ABLE TO HAVE THAT GOOD
RELATIONSHIP.
WHEN YOU HAVE AN ARGUMENT,
REMEMBER WHY YOU FELL IN LOVE
WITH THEM AND HOLD THEIR HAND.
>> ALL RIGHT.
NOW, MY PLAN IS THIS.
BECAUSE MY GRANDMOTHER WAS A
MATCHMAKER FOR BROOKLYN.
SHE USED TO SAY TO ME, SAUNDRA,
THAT'S MY REAL NAME, HERE'S THE
STORY.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT THEY LOOK
LIKE.
EVERY GARBAGE CAN HAS A COVER,
AND HE WILL MAKE UP FOR IT IN
BED.
[LAUGHTER]
HARVEY: OH, MY GOD.
CHARLES: ALL RIGHT.
I LIKE THE WAY YOUR GRANDMOTHER
SPOKE.
I'M WONDERING WHAT YOU GUYS
THINK ABOUT, I DON'T KNOW IF YOU
HEARD, JUSTIN SAID HE DID NOT
HAVE SEX FOR A WHOLE YEAR BEFORE
HE MET HIS NOW WIFE, HALEY.
>> I AGREE WITH THAT.
I THINK YOU SHOULD, LIKE, DATE
FOR A WHILE BEFORE YOU HAVE SEX.
GO OUT ON YOUR FIRST DATE SHOULD
BE A COFFEE DATE.
YOU ARE INTERVIEWING THE PERSON.
IT'S LIKE A JOB INTERVIEW,
RIGHT?
AFTER SIX WEEKS, THEN YOU CAN
HOP INTO BED.
I DON'T BELIEVE IN JUMPING INTO
BED RIGHT AWAY.
WHO KNOWS?
THIS SWIPING STUFF TODAY.
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
WHAT IS THAT ANYWAY?
DON'T OPEN THE CANDY SHOP RIGHT
AWAY.
YOU GET TO KNOW EACH OTHER.
HARVEY: SO, ONE FINAL QUESTION.
WHAT ABOUT PEOPLE WHO WANT TO
DATE, BUT DON'T WANT TO GET
MARRIED?
DO YOU PUSH MARRIAGE AS KIND OF
THE SUCCESS OR CAN YOU ACCEPT
THAT SOME PEOPLE JUST WANT TO
DATE AND NOT NECESSARILY GET
HITCHED?
>> I CAN ACCEPT ANYTHING, HONEY.
I'M FROM BROOKLYN.
WE CAN ACCEPT ANYTHING.
>>, I'M SORRY BUT I BELIEVE THAT
YOU HAVE TO PUT A RING ON IT.
CHARLES: YOU HEAR THAT?
HARVEY: THIS IS BRINGING BACK
MEMORIES.
CHARLES: HOW DID THOSE
CONVERSATIONS WORK?
>> YOUR BOTH GORGEOUS -- YOU'RE
BOTH GORGEOUS.
>> YOU ARE TAKEN.
OTHERWISE WE WOULD FIND A MATCH
FOR YOU.
HARVEY: I WENT THAT ROUTE, BUT
ANYWAY.
SHOW IS ON --
CHARLES: "BUBBIES KNOW BEST"
ON JEWISH LIFE TV.
>> HERE WE ARE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
>> "BUBBIES KNOW BEST."
[BELL RINGING]
CHARLES: I LOVE THE BELL.
YOU ALWAYS KNOW WHEN THEY'RE
COMING.
HARVEY: WE'RE GOING TO TAKE A
BREAK.
CHARLES: WHEN YOU COME BACK,
JUSSIE SMOLLETT IS BACK IN
CHICAGO.
WE'VE LEARNED MORE ABOUT HOW THE
CAST IS REACTING AFTER THIS AND
HOW PRODUCERS AND SECURITY AT
FOX STUDIOS HAS CHANGED.
On tour, every second counts.
I need great without the wait.
New Elvive
Rapid Reviver
Deep Conditioners
work fast
with no leave in time.
2x easier detangling
2x less breakage
than with a leading conditioner.
New Elvive
Rapid Revivers.
Start reviving.
Change will come.
But this hair color thing.
I've got that figured out.
Garnier Nutrisse.
The #1 Nourishing Color Crème,
with avocado, olive and
shea oils.
Nourishes while you color.
For the rich color you expect.
Join the millions who have
chosen Nutrisse.
Nourished hair.
Better Color.
CHARLES: WELCOME BACK TO "TMZ
LIVE."
THEY ARE TAKING NO CHANCES IN
CHICAGO NOW AT THE FOX STUDIOS
WHERE "EMPIRE" IS SHOT.
JUSSIE SMOLLETT IS BACK IN TOWN,
WE TOLD YOU THAT.
THEIR SECURITY IS ON HIGH ALERT,
AND THE CAST IS ALSO ON HIGH
ALERT  BECAUSE OF WHAT JUSSIE
SAID HAPPENED LAST WEEK HAS
REALLY PUT EVERYBODY ON EDGE.
>> THE FBI IS INVOLVED IN
ENFORCING THESE NEW SECURITY
PROCEDURES.
A SECURITY TEAM WAS HIRED TO GO
THROUGH ALL INCOMING MAIL.
THEY WEAR GLOVES TO MAKE SURE
THEY DON'T CONTAMINATE ANYTHING.
IF THEY SEE ANYTHING HATE MAIL
RELATED OR NEGATIVE, THEY
AUTOMATICALLY FORWARD THAT TO
THE FBI FOR FURTHER ANALYSIS AND
PROCESSING.
THEY WANT TO TRY AND FIGURE OUT
WHO SENT THAT LETTER TO JUSSIE
EIGHT DAYS BEFORE THE ATTACK IN
CHICAGO.
HARVEY: THEY ARE ASSUMING MAYBE
WHOEVER SENT THAT WOULD SEND
ANOTHER ONE AND THEY ARE TRYING
TO CONNECT THE DOTS,.
WHAT THEY DON'T KNOW IS IF
WHOEVER SENT THAT HAS ANY
CONNECTION TO THE ATTACK LAST
WEEK, BECAUSE THERE WERE SIGNS
FROM THE LETTER THAT WAS SENT
EIGHT DAYS BEFORE THAT TRACK
WITH WHAT JUSSIE SAID
HAPPENED.
CHARLES: YOU CAN SEE ON THE
LETTER THE NOOSE, THE EPITHETS,
THE WEAPON POINTED AT HIM.
THAT'S WHAT THEY ARE TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT, IF THERE IS A
CONNECTION.
>> THIS IS MY THING.
JUSSIE, I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
HAPPENING.
THE JURY IS STILL OUT ON THAT
ONE.
I'M BEGINNING TO BELIEVE, I'M
NOT SURE IF IT WAS LUCIOUS OR
COOKIE THAT MAYBE WHISPERED
SOMETHING IN HIS EAR.
WITH THAT BEING SAID, I GUESS
NEXT SEASON N "EMPIRE" IS GOING
TO BE A HIT.
HARVEY: WE ARE HEARING RUMBLINGS
THAT THEY MIGHT INCORPORATE THIS
IN THE SHOW AND THERE ARE SOME
PEOPLE WHO THINK IT'S A BAD IDEA
AND SOME WHO THINK IT'S A GOOD
IDEA.
CHARLES: INCORPORATING THE
STORYLINE.
HARVEY: OK.
IT IS TIME.
YOUR FAVORITE TIME OF THE WEEK.
CHARLES: TIM IS HERE WITH HIS
REJECTS.
TIM: I KNOW YOU GUYS BOTH LOVE
YOUR DOGS TO DEATH.
CHARLES: THAT IS TRUE.
TIM: WHAT BETTER WAY TO SHOW
THAT THAN TO GET CUSTOM SLIPPERS
MADE IT TO LOOK EXACTLY LIKE
YOUR DOGS?
CHARLES: THAT'S GOING TOO FAR.
TIM: YOU CAN SEND IN A PHOTO.
THEY MAKE ME CUSTOM -- THE
CUSTOM SLIPPERS TO BASICALLY
LOOK IDENTICAL, LIKE YOUR DOGS.
HARVEY: I DON'T WANT TO HIJACK
YOUR SEGMENT, BUT A LONG TIME
AGO, I HAD A HOUSEKEEPER WHO
GAVE ME A CHRISTMAS PRESENT, AND
IT WAS THIS WEIRD RAINCOAT.
I DIDN'T REALLY LIKE IT, BUT I
PUT IT ON.
CHARLES: HIJACKING IN PROGRESS.
HARVEY: IT WAS A RAINCOAT FOR
THE DOGS.
AND I PUT IT ON.
IT WAS SO RIDICULOUS.
CHARLES: DID IT FIT?
HARVEY: I HAD A GERMAN SHEPHERD.
GO ON, TIM.
TIM: OK.
SO, WHEN YOU GUYS LIKE A MATCH,
HOW DO YOU NORMALLY PUT IT OUT?
YOU SHAKE IT.
YOU CAN BLOW IT OUT.
WELL, THIS GUY SET THE WORLD
RECORD FOR MOST MATCHES
EXTINGUISHED BY THE GTONGUE.
HARVEY: HE IS AN IDIOT.
CHARLES: I'M NOT WORRIED ABOUT
THE FLAME, THE CHEMICALS.
HARVEY: THAT'S --
TIM: HE DID 62.
HARVEY: CAN WE SAY VERY
QUICKLYHARVEY:, THIS WILL HURT
YOU.
IT COULD REALLY ENDAGNER -- E
NDANGER YOU.
TIM, NEXT.
WE'RE DONE, TIM.
NEXT.
LAST ONE.
TIM: REMEMBER THE 5'8" A CONTEST
FINALISTS?
-- THE FIVE POTATO CONTEST
HARVEY: YES.
FINALISTS?
CHARLES: DO WE HAVE A WINNER?
HARVEY: YES.
TIM: WE HAVE A WINNER.
CHARLES: DO WE HAVE A WINNER?
HARVEY: PEOPLE DREW THE POTATO
TIM: WE HAVE A WINNER.
TO SEE WHO COULD DO THE BEST.
HARVEY: PEOPLE DREW THE POTATO
CHARLES: WHO COULD MAKE THE BEST
TO SEE WHO COULD DO THE BEST.
IMAGE.
CHARLES: WHO COULD MAKE THE BEST
THE TOP FIVE EACH GOT $500.
IMAGE.
HARVEY: THE WINNER GETS ANOTHER
THE TOP FIVE EACH GOT $500.
$2500.
HARVEY: THE WINNER GETS ANOTHER
WHO WON?
$2500.
TIM: THE WINNER IS DRAKE.
WHO WON?
CHARLES: THIS IS A POPULARITY
TIM: THE WINNER IS DRAKE.
CONTEST.
CHARLES: THIS IS A POPULARITY
OF COURSE DRAKE WON.
CONTEST.
HARVEY: I CAME IN LAST.
OF COURSE DRAKE WON.
CHARLES: I DIDN'T GET PROMPTING.
HARVEY: I CAME IN LAST.
TIM: BRITNEY FROM WALNUT CREEK,
CHARLES: I DIDN'T GET PROMPTING.
CALIFORNIA, WON.
TIM: BRITNEY FROM WALNUT CREEK,
CHARLES: YOU KNOW WHERE WALNUT
CALIFORNIA, WON.
CREEK IS?
CHARLES: YOU KNOW WHERE WALNUT
HARVEY: PARADISE IN A NUTSHELL.
CREEK IS?
>> SHE SAYS THE WINNING PRIZE
HARVEY: PARADISE IN A NUTSHELL.
MONEY IS GOING TOWARDS HER
>> SHE SAYS THE WINNING PRIZE
COLLEGE TUITION.
MONEY IS GOING TOWARDS HER
HARVEY: THAT'S GOOD.
COLLEGE TUITION.
REALLY GOOD.
HARVEY: THAT'S GOOD.
CHARLES: CONGRATULATIONS.
REALLY GOOD.
HARVEY: DRAWING ON A POTATO,
CHARLES: CONGRATULATIONS.
THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
HARVEY: DRAWING ON A POTATO,
WE HAVE ANOTHER ONE ON MONDAY.
THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
TAKING A BREAK.
WE HAVE ANOTHER ONE ON MONDAY.
OH, THANKS, TIM.
TAKING A BREAK.
CHARLES: GUYS HE IS WAITING FOR
OH, THANKS, TIM.
HIS APPLAUSE.
CHARLES: GUYS HE IS WAITING FOR
GIVE HIM HIS DUE.
HIS APPLAUSE.
HARVEY: COME ON, GUYS.
GIVE HIM HIS DUE.
CHARLES: WOW.
HARVEY: COME ON, GUYS.
A SMATTERING.
CHARLES: WOW.
WHEN WE COME BACK, WOODY ALLEN
A SMATTERING.
GOING AFTER AMAZON STUDIOS.
WHEN WE COME BACK, WOODY ALLEN
FILED A LAWSUIT FOR $68 MILLION.
GOING AFTER AMAZON STUDIOS.
WE WILL
Switch to Fios and get
entertainment delivered
to your home like no one else.
Because Fios is a 100%
fiber-optic network.
That means you'll get the
fastest internet available
and Fios TV One with amazing
4K capability,
and an advanced voice remote.
And now we'll give you a Netflix
premium plan for a full year.
So you can stream your favorite
Netflix shows
and movies in 4K on 4
devices at once.
Already have Netflix?
We'll cover the cost for one
year.
Just switch for 79.99 a month
with a two-year agreement
and get Fios Gigabit Connection
with TV and phone
with a 2-year price guarantee.
And not only will you get a
Netflix premium plan on us for a
year,
you'll be able to find Netflix
in the Fios Channel guide
and use the advanced voice
remote to launch Netflix
and easily find all the
channels,movies and shows
you love.
When you think about it,
there are so many entertaining
reasons to switch to Fios.
100% fiber-optic network.
100% phenomenal.
Go to getfios.com today.
CHARLES: WELCOME BACK TO "TMZ
LIVE."
WOODY ALLEN HAS FILED A HUGE
LAWSUIT AGAINST AMAZON STUDIOS,
$68 MILLION.
HE SAYS THEY LEFT ONE OF HIS
MOVIES JUST SITTING ON A SHELF.
IT'S CALLED "A RAINY DAY IN NEW
YORK."
HARVEY: I REMEMBER READING ABOUT
THIS MOVIE.
CHARLES: THE MOVIE IS DONE.
THEY SHOT THE WHOLE THING.
IT'S READY TO GO.
HARVEY: AND THE CAST IS SO GOOD,
YOU WOULD THINK THEY WANT TO
RELEASE THIS.
CHARLES: WOODY SAYS IN THIS
LAWSUIT THAT AMAZON PULLED OUT
LAST SUMMER.
THEY SAID WE ARE BACKING OUT OF
THIS DEAL,.
THEY ARE NOT GOING TO DISTRIBUTE
THE FILM.
HARVEY: DO WE HAVE ANY IDEA WHY?
CHARLES: A TOTAL OF A FOUR
PICTURE DEAL HE WAS POST TO BE
DOING WITH AMAZON AND THEY HAVE
RENEGED ON THE WHOLE DEAL.
HARVEY: HE THINKS IT'S RELATED
TO THE ALLEGATIONS.
CHARLES: THE ONLY THING THEY
SAID, HE SAYS IN THE LAWSUIT
THAT THEY SAID IT HAD TO DO WITH
THE RENEWED ALLEGATIONS AND
WOODY'S CONTROVERSIAL COMMENTS.
HE INSINUATES IN THE LAWSUIT
THAT IT HAS TO DO WITH --
HARVEY: DYLAN.
CHARLES: THE ALLEGATIONS HE
MOLESTED HIS DAUGHTER 25 YEARS
AGO.
>> SOME OF WHAT HE SAYS IS TRUE,
MEANING THE BASIS OF THE LAWSUIT
IS THE ALLEGATIONS.
I THINK HE HAS A GOOD CLAIM.
CHARLES: $68 MILLION FOR FOUR
MOVIES WHICH MAY NOT SOUND LIKE
A WHOLE -- HUGE NUMBER, BUT
WOODY ALLEN DOESN'T MAKE IT
BUDGET -- BIG BUDGET FILMS.
HARVEY: OK.
WHAT ELSE DO YOU WANT TO TALK
ABOUT?
>> HI.
I'M FROM HOUSTON, TEXAS.
I'M CALLING TO TALK ABOUT JUSTIN
BIEBER.
LET'S STOP TALKING ABOUT HIS
PAST.
LET'S COMMEND HIM.
365 DAYS.
YOU KNOW HOW PROMISCUOUS HE WAS
IN THE PAST.
HE IS A VERY INFLUENTIAL PERSON
FOR TEENAGERS AND YOUNG PEOPLE
LOOKING AT HIM.
THAT'S GREAT.
MAYBE THEY CAN DO IT, TOO.
STOP TALKING ABOUT HIS PAST.
THIS CAN HELP HIM WITH HIS
MARRIAGE, HIS XANAX USE, AND IT
BRINGS THEM CLOSER TO GOD.
HARVEY: ONE MORE.
>> HI, THIS IS APRIL.
I'M CHECKING IN FROM THE HOME OF
21 SAVAGE, ATLANTA.
I WANT TO LET PEOPLE KNOW I'M
VERY CLOSE TO A LOT OF PEOPLE
CLOSE WITH 21 SAVAGE.
MY NEPHEW IS ONE OF HIS
PARTNERS.
A LOT OF THESE STORIES THAT ARE
COMING OUT AS FAR AS THE GUNS
AND DIFFERENT THINGS, IT'S A LOT
OF MISUNDERSTANDING OF WHAT
EXACTLY HAPPENED.
PRAYERS ON TOP OF PRAYERS FOR 21
SAVAGE.
HARVEY: SOMETHING IS WRONG HERE.
OK, WE'RE TAKING A BREAK.
CHARLES: WHEN WE COME BACK,
GOING DOWN UNDER WITH MATT
DAMON.
I'M NOT REFERRING TO AUSTRALIA.
HARVEY: WE'RE TALKING ABOUT THE
OCEAN.
CHARLES: REPEATEDLY UNDER.
♪♪
-Morning.
-What do we got?
-Keep an eye on that branch.
Might get windy.
Have a good shift.
Fire pit.
Last use -- 0600.
I'd stay close.
Morning.
♪♪
Get ready to switch.
Protected by Flo.
Should say, "Protected
by Alan and Jamie."
-Right?
-Should it?
When you bundle
home and auto...
Run, Alan!
...you get more
than just savings.
You get 'round-the-clock
protection.
CHARLES: WELCOME BACK TO "TMZ
LIVE."
MATT DAMON AND HIS FAMILY ARE
DOWN IN AUSTRALIA.
HARVEY: THEY SPEND A LOT OF TIME
THERE.
CHARLES: MATT IS DOING WHAT
AUSTRALIANS DO, GETTING ON A
SURFBOARD.
IT'S PRETTY CLEAR HE IS NOT
AUSTRALIAN.
HARVEY: THAT'S A MOMENT IN TIME.
CHARLES: IT HAPPENED OVER AND
OVER.
HARVEY: TWICE.
CHARLES: I'M NOT SAYING I COULD
DO IT.
I ACTUALLY GIVE HIM CREDIT.
HARVEY: I'VE THE FEELING HE JUST
--
CHARLES: YOU THINK THERE IS
ACTUALLY FOOTAGE OF HIM
COMPLETLY NAILING IT.
AND THEY JUST DIDN'T SELL THAT
FOOTAGE?
HARVEY: SELECTIVE EDITING.
CHARLES: THEY WOULD WANT TO SEE
IT IF MATT DAMON COULD DO IT.
HARVEY: OK, WE WILL SEE YOU
TOMORROW.
[CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY THE
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE,
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTION CONTENT AND ACCURACY.
VISIT NCICAP.ORG]
>> I'M A LAWYER!
HVR.
You either love it
or you really love it.
>> Announcer: Alcohol and anger
were a bad mix.
>> She just continued
to keep disrespecting me.
>> Announcer: Then this party
of four
became b