What comes with
$1 soft drink
from McDonald's?
( ♪♪ )
$1 any size soft drink.
Joy included.
( ♪♪ )
[CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
WARNER BROS. DOMESTIC TELEVISION
DISTRIBUTION]
CHARLES: WELCOME TO "TMZ" LIVE.
HARVEY LEVIN HERE.
CHARLES: CHARLES HERE.
HARVEY: BILL COSBY THE GIVING
LECTURES BEHIND BARS ON
PARENTING, ON DRUG ABUSE AND ON
GETTING A JOB.
AND HE'S DRAWING HUGE CROWDS.
CHARLES: HE'S AN EXTREMELY
POPULAR MOTIVATIONAL SPEAKER
WHERE HE IS SERVING HIS TERM.
HARVEY: THIS MAY SOUND CRAZY TO
YOU BECAUSE BILL COSBY AT THE
END OF THIS TRIAL WHERE HE WAS
CONVICTED, YOU KNOW, OF DRUGGING
ANDREA CONSTANT AND ASSAULTING
HER, YOU WOULD THINK THAT PEOPLE
AREN'T LISTENING TO BILL COSBY
ANYMORE.
THEY ARE.
THEY ARE BEHIND BARS.
>> AND IT'S HAPPENING MULTIPLE
TIMES A WEEK.
THIS IS THREE, FOUR TIMES A
WEEK.
AND UP TO 100 PRISONERS WILL
ELECT TO COME TO THESE THINGS.
IT'S NOT A REQUIRED OR MANDATORY
THING.
THESE GUYS ARE COMING TO HEAR
HIM TALK.
HARVEY: YOU THINK ABOUT WHAT IS
IT THAT'S DIFFERENT BETWEEN THEM
AND PEOPLE ON THE OUTSIDE.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE IN PRISON
ESPECIALLY IF THEY'VE BEEN THERE
FOR A LONG TIME, THEY ARE LOCKED
INTO THE COSBY SHOW.
AND DIDN'T NECESSARILY CONNECT
--
CHARLES: BUT THEY KNOW WHY HE'S
THERE.
HARVEY: THAT DO I, INDEED.
BUT IT DOESN'T SEEM TO MATTER
THE WAY IT MATTERS ON THE
OUTSIDE.
>> IS HE ACKNOWLEDGING, LOOK, I
MADE MISTAKES?
BRAD: HE HAS MAINTAINED HIS
INNOCENCE AND ACTUALLY TO THE
COSBY SHOW PART, HIS REP TOLD US
WHENEVER HE IS THERE TO VISIT
BILL, A LOT OF THE PRISONERS
REFER TO HIM AS THEIR FATHER
FIGURE.
AND THAT'S WHY THEY'RE LISTENING
TO HIM THERE.
HARVEY: THERE ARE PEOPLE WHO
COMMIT CERTAIN CRIMES IN PRISON
OR COMMIT CERTAIN CRIMES ON THE
OUTSIDE AND THEY'RE LOOKED ON
WITH DISFAVOR.
IT IS THE OPPOSITE FOR BILL
COSBY.
VAN: IT'S DICEY FOR A LOT OF
REASONS.
NUMBER ONE THE CRIMES THAT BILL
COSBY IS CONVICTED OF ARE
HEINOUS AND DEPLORABLE.
AND THERE ARE CERTAIN PEOPLE WHO
LOOK AT HIM WITH SOME AFINITY.
HE WAS AN INSANELY SUCCESSFUL
PERSON.
IF YOU WERE GOING TO DEMSH A
VACUUM IF YOU WERE GOING TO
LISTEN TO SOMEBODY ON HOW TO
BECOME SUCCESSFUL OR THINGS YOU
NEED DO TO RECLAIM SUCCESS OR
START YOUR OWN, HE WOULDN'T BE A
BAD GUY TO LISTEN TO BESIDES ALL
THE OTHER STUFF, YOU DON'T WANT
TO HEAR ANYTHING COMING OUT OF
HIS MOUTH.
IF YOU'RE INSIDE, YOU MIGHT LOOK
AT IT DIFFERENTLY.
HARVEY: SO BRAD IN TERMS OF
PARENTING, HI THINK HE'S TALKING
ABOUT REBONDING?
>> YEAH, BECAUSE A LOT OF THE
GUYS HE SPEAKS TO ARE GOING TO
BE OUT ON PAROLE SOON.
IT'S ABOUT REBONDING WITH YOUR
CHILDREN AND YOUR FAMILY WHEN
YOU GET OUT.
IT'S ABT ABOUT HOW YOU INTERVIEW
FOR JOBS SO YOU'RE PROVIDED
OPPORTUNITIES THAT DON'T LAND
YOU BACK BEHIND BARS.
HARVEY: YOU KNOW, IT'S
INTERESTING THAT --
CHARLES: IT'S NOT THAT HE'S --
WHAT HE'S SAYING, I'M SURE --
CLEARLY THERE'S VALUE IN IT.
AND A LOT OF THE MEN HE'S
SPEAKING TO IN THERE CAN LEARN
SOMETHING FROM IT AND FROM HIM.
IT'S JUST WEIRD THAT IT'S COMING
FROM HIM AFTER WHAT HE WAS
CONVICTED OF.
HARVEY: BUT THE QUESTION IS --
CHARLES: WHEN YOU'RE ON THE
INSIDE, EVERYBODY IN THERE HAS
MADE A MISTAKE.
VAN: AND AT THE SAME TIME --
LISTEN, IF YOU'RE INCARCERATED
WHATEVER YOU'RE INCARCERATED
FOR, YOU WOULD HOPE THAT SOMEONE
WOULD SPEND THEIR TIME INSIDE
INCARCERATED TO DO SOMETHING
POSITIVE LIKE ANYTHING -- ANY
TOOTHPASTE YOU CAN SQUEEZE OUT
OF THE TUBE -- IT'S JUST A WEIRD
THING COMING FROM BILL COSBY
WITH THE IDEAS THAT WE HAVE IN
OUR HEAD ABOUT HIM RIGHT NOW.
CHARLES: IT WOULD BE LESS
DISTASTEFUL IF HE WERE
ACKNOWLEDGING SOME WRONGDOING
WHILE TEACHING THESE LESSONS.
AND BECAUSE HE ISN'T -- IT'S AS
IF THERE'S NO -- IF HE'S NOT
CONTRITE, THEN FOR PEOPLE ON THE
OUTSIDE IT'S JUST DIFFICULT TO
HEAR HIM BEING A LEADER.
THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
THAT'S WHAT I THINK.
THAT'S WHY THIS STORY SEEMS
WEIRD TO PEOPLE, I THINK.
>> HIS NAME IS MARQUIS JOHNSON
AND I'M FROM MILWAUKEE,
WISCONSIN.
AND SPEAKING ABOUT BILL COSBY, I
THINK IT IS VERY RARE FOR US ON
THE OUTSIDE TO HEAR OF WHAT BILL
COSBY IS DOING.
HOWEVER, I THINK IT IS VERY
BENEFICIAL TO THE INMATES THAT
ARE COMING OUT ON PAROLE DUE TO
THE FACT THAT THEY'RE GOING TO
TO COME TO THE OUTSIDE AND
REBUILD WITH THEIR FAMILY AND
REBUILD IN THEIR LIFE AGAIN.
I THINK IT IS A GOOD IDEA FOR
FWOIL BE DOING SOMETHING LIKE
THAT WHILE HE'S INCARCERATED BUT
HE ALSO NEEDS TO ADMIT TO HIS
WROTE DOINGS AS WELL.
CHARLES: MAYOR PETE BUTTIEG, WE
KNOW HE'S ACCOMPLISHED,
INCREDIBLY SMART GUY.
ROADS SCHOLAR AND SPEAKS
MULTIPLE LANGUAGES WHICH WAS ON
DISPLAY IN NEW YORK CITY.
HARVEY: SO HE'S WALKING DOWN THE
STREET.
AND THIS DUDE COMES UP TO HIM
AND THE GUY IS FROM MALTA.
AND HE IS ACTUALLY -- HE IS THE
PRESIDENT -- IT'S FUNNY ENOUGH
THAT A PRESIDENT HOPEFUL MEETS A
PRESIDENT.
HE'S THE PRESIDENT OF A MALTESE
CLUB IN NEW YORK.
THE GUY STARTS TALKING TO
BUTTIEG.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO SHOW YOU THE
WHOLE THING IN MALTESE.
>> MY PEOPLE.
[SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
>> OK.
VERY GOOD.
>> NICE.
HARVEY: IT'S NOT THE WEATHER.
CHARLES: WHAT ARE THEY TALKING
ABOUT?
HARVEY: WE KNOW BECAUSE THEY
HAVE MALTESE SPIES.
THE GUY FROM ASTORIA IS SAYING
HE'S INVITING BUTTIEG --
>> IT'S A ROUGH TRANSLATION.
HARVEY: I SPOKE TO SOMEBODY.
HE INVITED BUTTIEG TO COME TO
THE CLUB HE RUNS IN ASTORIA AND
DECIDED TO SWEETEN THE POT
SAYING IF YOU SHOW UP WE'RE
GOING TO GIVE YOU THE CAN --
IT'S A DESSERT.
WHAT'S THE NAME OF IT AGAIN?
CHARLES: IT IS CALLED PASTISI.
HARVEY: IT'S LIKE A CANOLI WITH
A SOFT CRUST INSIDE.
THEY ENDED UP TALKING AND IT
TURNS OUT THAT BUTTIEG WAS
ASKING WHERE HIS FAMILY IS FROM.
AND HE SAID THIS HIS
GRANDPARENTS WERE IN A NEARBY
TOWN AND THEY LIVE NEXT DOOR TO
A GUY NAMED ANTON BUTTIEG NOT
RELATED TO HIM BECAME PRESIDENT
OF MALTA.
SO BUTTIEG IS LIKE SMITH IN
MALTA.
IT'S KIND OF INTERESTING.
WE SHOULD SAY IN ADDITION TO
MALTESE, HE SPEAKS ITALIAN,
FRENCH, NORWEGIAN, SPANISH --
>> HE'S READ BOOKS.
HE REALLY KNOWS THEM.
HARVEY: AND HE ALSO SPEAKS SOME
ARABIC.
CHARLES: I DON'T WANT TO MAKE
THE ASSUMPTION THAT YOU KNOW
WHERE MALTA.
IS IT'S A SMALL ISLAND IN THE
MEDITERRANEAN.
IT'S BETWEEN AFRICA AND THE END
OF THE ITALIAN BOOT.
SOME PEOPLE THINK IT'S NEAR
GREECE.
IT'S NOT NEAR GREECE.
HARVEY: IT IS NEAR GREECE.
I DIDN'T SAY NEARER.
I SAID NEAR GREECE.
LOOK AT A MAP.
AND YOU'LL UNDERSTAND.
YOU WILL SEE THAT IT'S NEAR
GREECE.
CALLER: I'M CALLING FROM
CHESAPEAKE, VIRGINIA.
MAYOR PETE IS GOING TO SNEAK ON
US ALL.
HE HAD THE UNIQUE ABLE TO
CONNECT GENUINELY WITH JUST
ABOUT EVERYONE.
AND HE'S ONLY LIKE, 19?
>> YEAH, THAT'S SOME MILLENIAL
SHADE?
CHARLES: IT MIGHT HAVE BEEN.
HARVEY: LOOK, I THINK WHAT'S
FACE NATING ABOUT HIM IS THAT HE
IS A TRUE INTELLECTUAL.
IT'S INTERESTING THAT, YOU KNOW,
HOW AMERICA RECEIVES THAT.
I THEY THEY GOING TO RECEIVE IT
WELL BECAUSE YOU ALSO CAN RELATE
TO PEOPLE.
>> RIGHT.
YOU'RE SAYING THAT THERE'S
ALWAYS THE CHANGS THAT SOME
PEOPLE FEEL ALIENATED FROM THAT.
HARVEY: YOU KNOW WHO WOULD
CHANGE THAT?
JAMES HOLZERHAUR.
CHARLES: THERE YOU GO.
LET'S GET SOME DANCING.
BEYONCE AND JAY-Z'S LITTLE GIRL
SHE'S 7.
THAT'S OLD ENOUGH TO BE THE STAR
OF A DANCE RECITE -- RECITAL.
I THINK THE DANCE ACADEMY IS IN
ENGELWOOD.
SHE WAS DOING HER THING.
HARVEY: SHE'S GOOD.
CHARLES: THERE WAS ANOTHER TIME
THAT SHE'S PERFORMING TO ONE OF
BEYONCE'S SONGS "BEFORE I LET
GO."
AND I DON'T KNOW IS THAT WEIRD
FOR HER?
>> NO, IT'S NOT WEIRD FOR HER
BECAUSE THEY PROBABLY PLAY THIS
SONG ALL THE TIME IN THE HOUSE.
SHE PROBABLY LISTENS TO THE
RADIO.
EVERYBODY LOVES THAT SONG RIGHT
NOW.
THERE'S A HUGE VIRAL BEFORE I
LET GO CHALLENGE THAT I'M SURE
SHE DOES AT HOME IN HER MIRROR
WITH HER MOM.
AND SHE'S KILLING IT.
>> DO THE OTHER KIDS THINK THAT?
>> MY NIECE LOVES THIS SONG.
WHEN SHE BROUGHT IT BACK TO A
WHOLE OTHER GENERATION.
>> EASY.
>> LET THESE BABIES DANCE, MAN.
FINE.
OK.
DANCE, BABIES.
GO AHEAD.
HARVEY: CAN WE TAKE A BREAK?
OH, MY GOD.
You've tried so many
moisturizers...
but one blows them all
out of the water.
Hydro Boost with hyaluronic acid
to plump skin cells
so it bounces back...
Neutrogena®
And try our hydrating makeup.
CHARLES: WELCOME BACK TO "TMZ"
LIVE.
IF YOU'RE HALLE BERRY AND YOU
COME HOME TO YOUR FABULOUS HOUSE
ONLY TO DISCOVER -- IT'S NOT
YOUR HOUSE.
HARVEY: THIS IS MIND BOGGLING.
SO SHE LITERALLY.
THERE'S A GUY WHO TRIED TO STEAL
HALLE BERRY'S HOUSE.
STEAL HER WHOLE DAMN HOUSE, AND
--
CHARLES: HOW IN THE WORLD DO YOU
PULL OFF SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
A GUY NAMED RONALD EUGENE
GRIFFIN TRIED TO DO IT.
>> THIS IS SUCH A CRAZY STORY.
CHARLES: IT'S ACTUALLY SIMPLE.
>> THIS GUY FIRST HE COMES TO
THE HOUSE AND TRIES TO FIT ON
THE LOCKS.
THE GARDENER SAYS WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
AND HE COMES WITH A LOCK SMITH
AND THEY GET SOME OF THE LOCKS
CHANGED.
SOMEONE WHO WORKS HERE, HE SAID
I'M THE NEW OWNER OF THE HOUSE.
I HAVE A DEED HERE.
THIS GUY GOES, I'M GOING TO CALL
THE COPS TOO.
HARVEY: BECAUSE I HAVE THE DEED.
>> I MEAN, THIS IS SO CRAZY.
CHARLES: THIS IS ONE OF HALLE'S
HOMES IN THE L.A. AREA.
APPARENTLY, IT'S NOT HER MAIN
HOME.
AGAIN, AT THAT POINT RIGHT THERE
THEN TO ME THAT'S WHEN AN ALARM
SHOULD HAVE GONE OFF THAT THE
STAFFER OR WHOEVER WAS THERE AT
THE HOUSE, MIGHT MAKE A CALL TO
HALLE BERRY.
--
>> I THINK THEY DID CALL AND
CALLED THE POLICE.
THEY INVESTIGATED THIS GUY.
THEY HAD HIM ARRESTED.
>> RIGHT.
BUT THE GUY ACTUALLY FORGED A
DEED.
>> RIGHT.
THIS IS MORE COMMON THAN YOU
BELIEVE NOW.
THERE'S A WHOLE VISION THAT
DEALS JUST WITH THIS.
STEAL THE WHOLE HOUSE.
HARVEY: THIS HAS BEEN IN
CALIFORNIA WHERE ELDERLY PEOPLE
ESPECIALLY THEY GET TAKEN
ADVANTAGE OF AND IT'S DONE IN
VARIOUS DAYS WHERE A ROOFER WILL
COME AND SAY, SIGN THIS
CONTRACT, WE'LL PUT A NEW ROOF
ON AND THEY END UP FORECLOSING.
BUT THIS IS WAY MORE BOLD.
>> I MEAN, IT'S SHOCKING.
SOMEBODY DOESN'T HAVE THE STAFF
TO FIGHT BACK.
GET OUT.
IT'S MY HOUSE NOW.
>> IF IT'S A RENTAL HOUSE, YOU
GO NO.
AND YOU GET THEM OUT LEGALLY.
THEY COULD BE THERE FOR A WHILE.
>> HALLE BERRY HAS HAD ISSUES.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU REMEMBER,
BUT FOUR OR FIVE YEARS AGO, SHE
LITERALLY CAME BACK TO HER
HOUSE, GOT IN THE KITCHEN,
LOOKED OUT THE GLASS WINDOW IN
THE KITCHEN.
AND THERE'S A GUY FACING HER ON
HER PROPERTY STARING AT HER WAS
TRYING TO GET INSIDE THE HOUSE.
AND IT WAS SOMEBODY WHO
APPARENTLY HAD BEEN PERSISTENT.
SO SHE'S HAD THESE PROBLEMS
BEFORE.
BUT APPARENTLY, THE GUY DIDN'T
KNOW IT WAS HALLE BERRY'S HOUSE.
>> THIS HOUSE WAS UNDER A TRUST.
THEY HAD NO IDEA.
UNLUCKY FOR HALLE.
>> BAD LUCK FOR HIM BECAUSE HE
GOT ARRESTED.
CALLER: I'M AERIAL JONES.
I THINK IT'S WEIRD THAT YOU FIND
A RANDOM PERSON IN YOUR HOME
ESPECIALLY HALLE BERRY.
IT'S LIKE HOW -- HOW WOULD YOU
THINK YOU WOULD GET AWAY WITH
THAT?
>> THAT'S WHAT I WAS GOING TO
SAY, I CAN'T IMAGINE HOW HE DID
THIS.
BUT THE FACT THAT HE DID THIS,
MAKES YOU THINK HE COULD PULL
THIS OFF.
HARVEY: BANK ROBBERS START
STEALING CANDY AT LIQUOR STORES.
AND THEN THEY GRADUATE UP.
SO TO GO TO A REALLY NICE HOUSE
WHERE YOU KNOW THERE ARE
EMPLOYEES THERE --
>> A SMALLER HOUSE.
>> YOU'RE WONDERING HOW MANY
TIMES IS THIS HAPPENING?
AND ARE THEY GETTING PEOPLE WHO
ARE STRUGGLING OUT OF THEIR
HOUSE AND SAY GO, GO, IT'S MY
HOUSE NOW.
AND THEY DO IT.
I MEAN, IT'S CRAZY.
OK.
WE'RE GOING TO MOVE ON.
CHARLES: WE GOT SOME VIDEO NOW
OF A HUGE BRAWL THAT BROKE OUT.
MAN, IT WAS VICIOUS ON A NEW
YORK CITY STREET CORNER.
THIS IS IN SOHO.
TWO WOMEN FOR VARIOUS REASONS
ACCORDING TO WITNESSES JUST
STARTED GOING AT IT UNTIL A
HOLLYWOOD ACTOR NAMED PETER
GREEN.
YOU KNOW HIM FROM "PULP FICTION"
AND "THE MASS."
HE PLAYED ZED IN "PULP FICTION."
HE HAPPENED TO WALK BY.
AND WHILE EVERYONE ELSE WAS
WATCHING WHAT WAS GOING ON, HE
JUMPED INTO ACTION.
[BEEP]
>> HEY, STOP FIGHTING.
STOP FIGHTING.
HEY!
YOU WITH THE RED!
YO, STOP IT!
[BEEP]
[BEEP] STOP IT!
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
YOU LET THEM FIGHT?
YOU'RE A GROWN MAN.
NO, TELL YOU TO STOP FIGHTING.
>> HOW COME YOU DON'T STOP IT?
>> [BEEP] STOP IT!
CHARLES: YOU SEE THERE AT THE
END, PETER WAS TICKED OFF.
THE PEOPLE HE WAS YELLING AT ARE
NEW YORK CITY TRAFFIC AGENTS AND
WATCHING IT HAPPEN.
>> YOU CAN UNDERSTAND WHY HE
WOULD BE MAD.
WHY ARE YOU WATCHING TWO GIRLS
BEAT THE HELL OUT OF EACH OTHER.
CHARLES: THEY DO WORK FOR NYPD
AS TRAFFIC OFFICERS.
HARVEY: THESE BIKES ARE NOT
CHEAP.
AND PETER THROWS DOWN HIS BIKE.
VAN: TALL HUMAN TRAUMA AND
HARVEY IS LIKE, I'M CONCERNED
ABOUT THAT BIKE.
HARVEY: IT'S A MARKER OF HOW HE
STEPPED IN AND WAS A GOOD
SAMARITAN.
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO PICK UP A
CHARGE YOURSELF.
HARVEY: GOOD FOR HIM.
VAN: IT IS GOOD TO STEP IN.
THE TRAFFIC PEOPLE -- I DON'T
KNOW IF THEY'RE LIKE -- IF
THAT'S PART OF THEIR JOB
DESCRIPTION.
HARVEY: PROBABLY NOT.
I THINK IF THE FIGHT SPILLED
OVER AT THE CROSSWALK, THEN THEY
WOULD GET INVOLVED.
>> OR THEY COULD BE DECENT HUMAN
BEINGS.
>> A DECENT HUMAN BEING PUTS
THEMSELVES AT RISK OF GETTING
WIND OF SOMEBODY FIGHTING?
HARVEY: SPITTING ALSO?
VAN: OBVIOUSLY, Y'ALL NEVER BEEN
AROUND --
HARVEY: THERE'S A DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN BEING A GOOD SAMARITAN
AN NOT BEING DECENT.
PEOPLE DON'T WANT TO GET
INVOLVED IF IT HAPPENS.
GOOD FOR PETER GREEN.
VAN: PETER GREEN DID SOMETHING
HEROIC.
CALLER: I'M VICTORIA FROM
GREENSBORO, NORTH CAROLINA.
HE DID IT JUST SO EFFORTLESS --
EFFORTLESSLY.
HIS STATUS WENT UP 10 NOTCHES IN
MY OPINION.
HARVEY: OK.
WE'RE MOVING ON.
CHARLES: YOU WANT TO HEAR ABOUT
A COOL CAT.
HE'S GOING TO MAKE A LOT OF
MONEY AT LEAST THAT IS THE PLAN.
YOU GUYS KNOW BENJAMIN BUTTON,
RIGHT?
NOT THE MOVIE CHARACTER BUT MORE
IMPORTANTLY --
HARVEY: TAYLOR SWIFT'S FELINE.
CHARLES: HER NEWEST CAT IS NOW
OFFICIALLY PART OF THE GANG
BECAUSE SHE'S ADDED BENJAMIN TO
HER TRADEMARK.
HARVEY: HOW DO YOU GET HER TO
HER TRADEMARK?
CHARLES: IT'S BENJAMIN SWIFT.
SO NOW --
HARVEY: IT'S A NICKNAME.
CHARLES: BUT HIS TRADEMARK NAME
IS BENJAMIN SWIFT.
I GET IT.
HARVEY: HAS SHE DONE ANYTHING IN
TERMS OF MARKETING ANYTHING?
>> YES, SHE HAS.
MEREDITH AND OLIVIA HAVE BEEN
ALL OVER T-SHIRTS AND THINGS
LIKE THAT.
SO SHE HAS ALREADY ALREADY BEEN
SELLING ALL THAT MERCH.
WITH HIM IT'S GOING TO BE CUTER
EVENT AND SHE WANTS TO DO CELL
PHONE CASES, LUGGAGE.
THERE'S SO MUCH OPPORTUNITY.
WITH GRUMPY CAT PASSING AWAY,
THE CAT COMMUNITY IS OPEN.
THERE'S ABSOLUTELY A SPOT FOR A
NEW CAT COME AND TAKE OVER.
>> YOU KNOW BENJAMIN IS NOT
GOING TO MAKE MONEY.
>> NO, YOU'RE KIDDING?
>> I WANTED TO LET CHARLIE KNOW
--
>> YOU GUYS, MAYBE IT'S NOT
MAYBE HE WANTS THE FAME.
HARVEY: HE'S A CLOUD CHASE IR.
TAKING A BREAK.
DUKE'S IS FAR AND AWAY
MY FAVORITE MAYONNAISE
AND IT HAS BEEN FOR AS
LONG AS I CAN REMEMBER.
IT TASTES HOMEMADE
BUT IT'S BETTER THAN
I COULD MAKE.
FOR ANY POTATO SALAD,
YOU HAVE TO HAVE MAYO
AND YOU MIGHT AS
WELL START WITH THE BEST.
AND IT'S DUKE'S.
AND IT'S DUKE'S
(LAUGHS).
REALLY GOOD.
THE FACT THAT THEY USE
REAL EGG YOLKS AND
THERE IS NO ADDED
SUGAR, YOU CAN
ACTUALLY TASTE THAT.
OH YEAH, THERE'S MORE
DUKE'S ON THERE
THAN THERE IS BOLOGNA
(LAUGHS).
Buy One Take One is back,
starting at just $12.99,
at Olive Garden.
Join us for a NEW
favorite today.
Then bring one home
for tomorrow--on us.
Buy One Take One
For a limited time.
Only at Olive Garden.
ANNOUNCER: THIS YEAR "TMZ" GOT
EVERY FREAKING THING!
BIG EVENTS!
BIG STORIES!
BIG EVENTS.
>> SHE GAVE HIM A LAP DANCE.
>> HE HAD SWEATS ON.
THAT'S DANGEROUS!
ANNOUNCER: IT'S "TMZ"!
CHARLES: WELCOME BACK TO "TMZ"
LIVE.
MOST OF THE FACES ARE THE SAME,
BUT MAN, HAVE THEIR LIVES
CHANGED DRAMATICALLY.
TALKING ABOUT THE CAST OF "THE
HILLS."
THE REHILLS NEW BEGINNING.
YOU WILL SEE A LOT O FACES THAT
YOU KNOW.
A COUPLE OF FACES THAT HAVE NEW.
HARVEY: THEY'VE HAD A DECADE TO
GROW AND CHANGE.
THERE WAS A COME-ON.
HEIDI AND SPENCER.
THEY'RE TOGETHER.
THEY'RE MARRIED.
>> YEAH, THERE'S THAT LITTLE GUY
WHO IS ON THE SHOW WHICH IS
INTERESTING BECAUSE WE KNOW THAT
HAVING KIDS ON REALITY SHOWS
PROBLEMATIC.
>> CAN BE PROBLEMATIC.
CHARLES: JOINING US RIGHT NOW TO
TALK ABOUT ALL THAT IS SPENCER
PRATT.
WELCOME BACK TO TMTMS LIFE.
-- "TMZ" LIVE.
>> COULD I SEE YOUR GUYS' FACES?
I CAN'T SEE MY BIG HEAD LIKE
THAT.
>> WHERE ARE YOU?
>> THIS IS CRESTED BUTE MOUNTAIN
THIS IS WHERE HEIDI GREW UP.
WE'RE VISITING HER FAMILY.
>> MONTANA.
>> NO, COLORADO.
HARVEY: I DIDN'T KNOW IT WAS
COLORADO.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
HOLY SMOKES.
>> YOU HAVE TO ENJOY THE VIEW.
HARVEY: LISTEN, MAN, IT'S BEEN A
DECADE.
AND THERE WERE NO -- WHEN YOU
GUYS WERE PARTYING IN HOLLYWOOD
BACK THEN, NOBODY WAS BRINGING
BABY STROLLERS OR CAR SEATS.
SO HOW IS THIS GOING TO WORK
OUT?
>> WELL, THAT WAS A BIG DRAMA
THING FOR MY WIFE BECAUSE SHE IS
AN ATTACHMENT PARENT.
THE FIRST PART OF "THE HILL,"
SHE DOESN'T GO OUT.
SHE'S HAVING EMOTIONAL
BREAKDOWNS JUST LEAVING OUR SON
BECAUSE FOR THE FIRST TIME SHE
NEVER LEFT GUNNAR FOR LONGER
THAN A MINUTE.
THANKFULLY FOR THE HILLS, SHE
GOATS A POINT WHERE SHE CAN GO
OUT AND BE A REGULAR MOM AND HAS
A DRINK.
BUT THAT WAS VERY CHALLENGING
INITIALLY.
HARVEY: I'VE GOT A QUESTION
BECAUSE I DIDN'T KNOW THIS.
SO THIS SOUNDS LIKE A -- WAS SHE
PREVENTING YOU FROM PARENTING
BECAUSE SHE WAS DOING IT ALL THE
TIME?
THAT'S WHAT I'M HEARING.
SPENCER: I WAS THERE.
I COULD LEAVE THE HOUSE.
SHE WAS MORE EXTREME.
GUNNAR DIDN'T COME OUT OF MY
BODY, SO I BELIEVE THAT'S MORE
INTENSE RATHER THAN MY
INTENTION.
YOU HEARD WHETHER BLAC CHYNA AND
ROBERT KARDASHIAN WHETHER THEIR
CHILD CAN GO ON A REALITY SHOW.
SOMETIMES IT DOESN'T END WELL.
>> WHAT WAS THE CONVERSATION
BEFORE YOU MADE THE DECISION?
>> ALL DUE RESPECT TO ROB AND
BLAC CHYNA BUT WE'VE BEEN
TOGETHER 12 YEARS.
SO OUR RELATIONSHIP IS A LITTLE
STRONGER THAN THOSE TWO, WHICH,
YOU KNOW B -- YOU KNOW, --
CHARLES: THAT'S NOT SHADE.
THOSE ARE FACTS.
IF GUNNAR HAD NOT ENJOYED THE
PROCESS AND DIDN'T LIKE PEOPLE,
YOU KNOW, WE WOULDN'T HAVE DONE
IT.
BUT HE WOULD CRY WHEN THEY WOULD
LEAVE.
IT WAS LIKE FUN.
ALMOST LIKE AN ADVENTURE FOR
HIM.
YOU KNOW, HE'S MORE LIKE AN
ASSAD.
THEY WERE BORN FOR IT.
>> WE'RE GOING TO PLAY A GAME,
THIS IS TOTAL FANTASY LAND.
PRETEND I'M 19 YEARS OLD.
AND I'M THINKING, WAIT A MINUTE.
THESE FOLKS ARE MARRIED NOW.
THEY'VE GOT A KID.
I WANT TO SEE PEOPLE PARTYING
AND DOING WHATNOT WHAT THEY DID
IN THE O.G.
SO TELL ME --
>> OOH!
I GOT YOU MR. 19-YEAR-OLD HARVEY
LEVIN.
LET ME TELL YOU ABOUT BRANDON
THOMAS LEE, THE SON OF TOMMY
LEE, THE SON OF PAMELA ANDERSON.
SHE JUST TURNED 22.
HE HAS MORE DATES THAN ANYBODY
I'VE SEEN IN MY LIFE HE'S
BREAKING HEARTS.
SUPERER MODEL.
HE'S COOLER THAN ANY OF US EVER
WERE.
HE'S THE NEXT LEVEL.
HE'S BRINGING THAT 19-YEAR-OLD
INTEREST.
AND IF YOU'RE ONE OF THESE OLDER
PEOPLE LIKE US --
>> MORE SEASONED.
MORE SEASONED.
>> YEAH, MORE BETTER.
BUT I WILL SAY, THAT YOU KNOW,
ONE THING ABOUT BEING A PARENT
IS WHEN YOU DO GET TO GO OUT
LIKE I WAS ALLOWED OUT TWO
NIGHTS A WEEK, ANY 21 COULD EVER
PARTY BECAUSE I'M LIKE -- I'M
OUT OF THE HOUSE!
AH!
SO I WOULD SAY, I DRANK AND
PARTY HARDER THAN EVER BEFORE ON
THIS SEASON.
I WAS ACTUALLY LIKE MY GOAL WAS
TO OUTPARTY ANY OF THESE OTHER
REALITY SHOWS.
AND I THINK I DID IT.
I WAS GOING TO EVERY SCENE WITH
TWO BOTTLES OF DON JULIO.
HARVEY: EXCELLENT ANSWER,
SPNSER.
EXCELLENT ANSWER.
19-YEAR-OLD HARVEY IS IN.
THERE WAS ONCE A 19 YEAR-OLD.
>> BRANDON IS A SUPERSTAR.
HE COULD HAVE HAD HIS OWN SHOW
ON MF MTV CALLED -- MTV CALLED
BRANDON.
HARVEY: CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU GUYS ENDURED.
THE SHOW ENDURED.
IT'S AMAZING.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'M IN A TIME
MACHINE.
>> LIKE OLD TIMES.
>> SPENCER, CONGRATS AND SEND
THE SAME REGARDS TO HEIDI AND
GUNNAR.
AND GUNNAR.
>> THANK YOU TO ALL THE "TMZ"
LIVE COMMONORS.
HARVEY: GOD, IT'S BEAUTIFUL
THERE.
HOLY SMOKES.
OK.
TAKING A BREAK.
♪ ♪ ♪
Start the car! Start the car!
The IKEA Summer Sale.
Wooooooo!
Save up to 50% off select
items in store only
June 26th to July 7th.
IKEA.
Can you actually love
wearing powerful sunscreen?
Yes!
Neutrogena® Ultra Sheer®.
No other sunscreen
works better
or feels so good.
Clinically proven Helioplex®
provides unbeatable
UVA/UVB protection
to help prevent early skin
aging and skin cancer
all with a clean light feel.
For unbeatable
protection.
It's the one.
The best
for your skin.
Ultra Sheer®.
Neutrogena®.
See what's possible.
Brushing only reaches
25% of your mouth.
LISTERINE® cleans
virtually 100%.
Helping to prevent gum
disease and bad breath.
Never settle for 25%.
Always go for 100.
Bring Out the Bold™
CHARLES: WELCOME BACK TO "TMZ"
LIVE.
IT MAY HAVE BEEN THE --
ACTUALLY, I AM GOING TO SAY THE
MOST MENACING NEWS.
O.J. SIMPSON SAYING HE WAS GOING
TO GET EVEN WITH SOME PEOPLE.
HE NOW HAS A TWITTER ACCOUNT.
AND THE FIRST -- I DON'T KNOW IF
THIS IS SOMEONE HE FEELS HE
NEEDS TO GET EVEN WITH.
BUT THE FIRST THING HE CHOSE TO
ADDRESS WAS WHO IS KHLOE
KARDASHIAN'S FATHER?
THIS HAS BEEN A LONG-HELD RUMOR
THAT O.J. --
HARVEY: UNSUBSTANTIATED.
THAT O.J. WANTED TO GIVE HIS TWO
CENTS ON IT.
HERE'S WHAT HE SAID.
HARVEY: THE WAY HE SAYS IT.
HARVEY: IT'S ABOUT WHAT HE'S
SAYING ABOUT CHRIS.
>> BOB KARDASHIAN IS LIKE A
BROTHER TO ME.
HE'S A GREAT GUY.
HE MET AND MARRIED KRIS.
THEY REALLY HAD A TERRIFIC TIME
TOGETHER WHEN THEY WERE
TOGETHER.
UNFORTUNATELY, THAT ENDED.
IN ANY WAY SHAPE OR FORM HAVE I
HAD INTEREST IN KRIS
ROMANTICALLY.
SO ALL OF THESE STORIES ARE JUST
BOGUS, BAD, YOU KNOW, TASTELESS.
KHLOE, LIKE ALL THE GIRLS I'M
VERY PROUD OF SCLUST JUST LIKE
-- JUST LIKE I KNOW BOB WOULD
BE.
BUT THE SIMPLE FACT OF THE
MATTER SHE'S NOT MINE.
THERE ARE GUY IS SO PATHETIC.
HE'S DOING THIS BECAUSE THE
ATTENTION IS RUNNING LOW AND WE
-- HE LENDS HIS VOICE TO IT.
>> THE THING ABOUT KRIS WHERE HE
SAYS, I HAVE NO INTEREST IN HER
WHATSOEVER.
>> THAT'S KIND OF INCIDENTAL.
THE BEGINNING IS.
I HAVE NO INTEREST IN HER.
VAN: I AGREE THAT IT'S INCIDENT
E -- INCIDENTAL.
I WASN'T INTO HER.
AND AS FAR -- AND SHE NEVER TOLD
ME SHE WAS INTO ME.
SO --
CHARLES: IT SEEMS HONEST FROM
O.J.
>> WHY NOT JUST SAY, HEY, IT
JUST DIDN'T HAPPEN?
VAN: NOT ONLY DID IT NOT HAPPEN
-- BUT HE'S SAYING NOT ONLY DID
IT NOT HAPPEN -- THERE WAS
NOTHING BETWEEN US LIKE THAT.
IT'S NOT TO DEAL WITH SOME KIND
OF FLING THAT WE DIDN'T ACT ON.
THAT'S JUST WEIRD.
>> THE REASON I FEELS WEIRD
BECAUSE HONESTLY IT'S O.J. JUST
BEING HONEST.
>> WHY ARE YOU ON TWITTER?
HARVEY: YOU KNOW WHAT THE END
GAME HAS TO BE SOMEHOW, RIGHT?
HE THINKS IT'S MONEY.
SOMEHOW IT'S GOING TO GET A
CERTAIN NUMBER OF FOLLOWERS AND
HE'S GOING TO BE ABLE TO
TRANSLATE INTO MONEY.
>> ANYBODY SHOULD BE WILLING TO
CUT THEIR LOSSES AN GO AHEAD AND
LIVE OUT THE REST OF THEIR LIFE
WHICH IS VIRTUAL OBSCURITY.
HARVEY: YOU CAN MAKE THAT
ARGUMENT AFTER THE MURDER TRIAL.
BUT HE REFUSED TO.
AND, YOU KNOW, WHERE IT GOT HIM
>> MY NAME IS ERICA CHASTAIN.
I'M FROM GEORGIA.
WHEN THESE O.J. TWEETS STARTED
POPING UP ON MY TIME LINE.
HE DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO THINK.
HE SAID THAT THE KHLOE RUMORS,
ARE BAD, BOGUS AND TASTELESS.
YOU CAN TAKE IT SERIOUS WHEN IT
SAYS THAT.
IF YOU PUT A PICTURE OF KHLOE
KARDASHIAN PREOP IT'S
UNDENIABLE.
IT'S LIKE THEY'RE TWINS.
>> ERICA, YOU'RE JUST GAVE ON --
YOU'RE GOING TO CLEATLY START
THIS UP AGAIN?
EVERYBODY INVOLVED SHOT IT DOWN.
HARVEY: PEOPLE LOOK LIKE OTHER
PEOPLE.
AN ALSO SIDNEY SIMPSON, THAT
WOULD BE A DIFFERENT MOTHER.
>> HOW MANY TIMES ARE YOU GOING
TO SAY PREOP?
THAT'S SHADE, DOC.
HARVEY: WE'RE GOING TO MOVE ON.
CHARLES: MAFIA RULES DO NOT
APPLY FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP.
BECAUSE GEORGE IS GOING AFTER
THE FIRST FAMILY SPECIFICALLY ON
THE IMMIGRATION POLICIES OF THE
ADMINISTRATION AND SAYS THAT HE
HAS NO ISSUES DRAGGING CHILDREN
INTO IT.
I GET THAT THE PRESIDENT HAS
OLDER DIFFICULT CHILDREN.
THIS IS THE POST THAT GEORGE
LOPEZ PUT UP.
AND MADE THE POINT OF INCLUDING
BARRON WHO IS 13 YEARS OLD.
AND MAKING A POINT THAT THEY
CAME FROM AN IMMIGRANT MOTHER.
TIFFANY IS NOT INCLUDED THERE.
SO I CALL THEM ANCHOR BABIES.
SO WE GOT GEORGE OUT BECAUSE A
LOT OF PEOPLE FELT LOOK,
OBVIOUSLY PEOPLE ARE VERY
CRITICAL ABOUT THE IMMIGRATION
POLICY.
BUT WHEN YOU START BRINGING, YOU
KNOW, MINOR CHILDREN INTO IT.
DOES IT CROSS THE LINE?
>> WE GOT IT NOW.
DO YOU THINK I SHOULD PUT HIM IN
THE POST?
>> WHY?
THEY'RE KIDS.
LET'S GO, ANCESTRY.COM AT IF AND
B.
>> EVERYONE'S SWAPPING THE
INSEED OF THEIR MOUTH.
YOU KNOW WE CAN ALL AGREE ON.
IMMIGRATION IS HERE.
IT WILL CONTINUE TO BE A
PROBLEM.
BUT ONLY TARGETING LATINOS IS
NOT GOOD.
HARVEY: SO YOU KNOW WHO WOULD
DISAGREE WITH HIM?
THE OBAMAS.
THEY MADE IT VERY CLEAR DURING
THE PRESIDENCY THAT UNLESS, YOU
KNOW, SASCHA AND MALEAH WERE
PART OF AN EVENT WHERE, YOU
KNOW, THEY WERE THERE, THEY
REALLY WERE AGAINST THEM EVEN
BEING FRAFFED.
I THEY THEY WOULD DISAGREE WITH
THAT.
>> I THINK THE: TOS DISAGREED
BECAUSE THEY FOUGHT FOR PRIVACY
BECAUSE SHE WAS IN THE LIMELIGHT
AS WELL.
AND FACED A LOT OF, YOU KNOW,
UNDUE ATTENTION AND A LOT OF
CRITICISM, MEANNESS AND THIS IS
BEFORE THE ERA OF SOCIAL MEDIA.
WHAT GEORGE IS REFERRING TO BY
TARGETING DONALD TRUMP'S
CHILDREN IS AGAIN SORT OF THE
ACTION TAKEN AGAINST THE
ADMINISTRATION PUTTING THEM IN
CAGES.
I THINK THE POINT THAT HE'S
TRYING TO MAKE, YOU KNOW, MIGHT
BE A VALID ONE.
BUT IT'S USING -- IT'S USING
PEOPLE THAT YOU KNOW, IT'S
UNFAIR.
>> HE COULD MAKE THE POINT JUST
WITH DONALD JR. AND ERIC AND
IVANKA.
>> YOU WOULDN'T -- THAT'S WHERE
-- IT'S A LITTLE PROBLEMATIC.
>> HEY, GUYS HOW ARE YOU DOING?
MY NAME IS DOMINICK.
THIS ISSUE IS A LITTLE PRESSING.
I WOULD SAY INSTEAD OF
TARGETTING BARRON TRUMP, HE
INCLUDES HIM.
BUT TO COMPARE THE OBAMA'S AND
THE CLINTONS TO THE TRUMPS IS
LITERALLY COMPARING APPLES AND
ORANGES.
HARVEY: I DON'T THIS IT IS.
>> COULD YOU ERASE POLITICS.
-- YOU ERASE POLITICS?
WHATEVER EVER YOU ALLOW ON THIS
SIDE, THIS SIDE IS GOING TO DO.
IF THE POLICY THEY'RE FAIR GAME.
IF THEY'RE FAIR GAME ON ONE SIDE
THEY'RE GOING TO BE FAIR GAME ON
THE OTHER SIDE.
RIGHT.
>> OK, TAKING A BREAK.
The best way
to hit the beach?
With Neutrogena®
Beach Defense® sunscreen.
Helioplex® powered,
UVA, UVB strong.
Beach strength protection
for the whole family.
For the best day in the sun.
Neutrogena®.
We have to be able to
repair the enamel
on a daily basis.
With the new
Pronamel
Repair toothpaste
we can help actively repair
enamel in its weakened state.
It's innovative.
My go-to toothpaste
is going to be Pronamel Repair.
CHARLES: WELCOME BACK TO "TMZ"
LIVE.
HARVEY AND VAN HERE.
I'M REAL EXCITED ABOUT THIS SHOW
TODAY.
I MEAN, THIS IS GREAT.
I LOVE JOHN RATSEN BURGER.
I JUST LOVE JOHN RATZENBURGER.
VAN: YOU LIKE PEOPLE WHO ARE
TALENTED.
BUT YOU ALSO LOVE PEOPLE WHO
HAVE TWO DISTINCT ACTS.
HE WAS ON "CHEERS."
BIGGEST SHOW ON TELEVISION.
HE HAS A FANTASTIC SECOND CAREER
DOING THAT.
HARVEY: I LOVE THAT SPEAKING OF
"TOY STORY 4" SOUNDS AMAZE.
THE CAST IS AMAZING -- SOUNDS
AMAZE.
AND THERE'S A POSTURE
MISCHARACTER ON THIS.
JOHN, WELCOME TO "TMZ" LIVE?
>> THANK YOU, THANK YOU FOR THAT
NICE INTRO.
WELL DESERVED.
SO I A LOT OF PEOPLE WERE
SHOCKED BECAUSE THEY THOUGHT TOY
STORY 3 WAS THE HUGE.
>> I WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED IF
THEY LEFT THEM THE FIFTH ONE.
SOMEWHERE DOWN THE LINE.
>> HOW LONG DID IT TAKE TO DO?
>>
>> I THINK THINK IT TOOK THEM
THROUGH TO FOUR YEARS.
IT IS A BIG INVESTMENT.
I LOVE THE CAST.
IN ADDITION TO YOU YOU'VE GOT
TOM HANKS, TIMOTHY ALLEN.
HE WAS SO AMAZING ON VIPE.
I THINK IT'S THE FUNNIEST
CHARACTER IN THE MOVIE, THE
CHARACTER HE PLAYS IS
HYSTERICAL.
>> I SAW TOY STORY 3.
AND OF COURSE, IT WAS A
PHENOMENAL MOVIE.
ATTEND IT WASN'T SAD.
IT WAS A VERY, VERY SAD TOUGH
WATCH WITH PEOPLE DRYING AND
STUFF LIKE THAT.
PARENTS ARE CONCERNED ABOUT
BRINGING THEIR KID TO THE MOVIE
IS THIS ONE GOING TO HAVE THE
SAME TENOR OR DIFFERENT?
>> THE KIDS DON'T HAVE TO WAIT
UNTIL THEIR GRANDFATHER DIES.
[LAUGHTER]
>> YOU HAVE A CHANCE TO WORK
THROUGH THE SADNESS AT AN EARLY
AGE.
[LAUGHTER]
IT'S NOT THAT SAD.
IT'S SAD.
HARVEY: IT'S HILARIOUS.
IT'S NOT THAT SAD.
DON RICKLES, YOU KNOW, HE PLAYED
HARVEY: IT'S HILARIOUS.
MR. POTATO HEAD, HE PASSED IN
DON RICKLES, YOU KNOW, HE PLAYED
2017.
MR. POTATO HEAD, HE PASSED IN
YOU GUYS, BROUGHT HIM BACK.
2017.
>> YEAH, THE DIRECTOR SEARCHED
YOU GUYS, BROUGHT HIM BACK.
FOR HOURS AND HOURS OVER AN OLD
>> YEAH, THE DIRECTOR SEARCHED
TAPE THAT THEY HAD FOR DON IN
FOR HOURS AND HOURS OVER AN OLD
THE OTHER OLD STORIES AN OF SOME
TAPE THAT THEY HAD FOR DON IN
PROMOS HE DID.
THE OTHER OLD STORIES AN OF SOME
>> THAT IS ACTUALLY AMAZE.
PROMOS HE DID.
HARVEY: IT IS ACTUALLY AMAZING.
>> THAT IS ACTUALLY AMAZE.
I'VE GOT TO ASK YOU, YOU'VE JUST
HARVEY: IT IS ACTUALLY AMAZING.
HAD THE MOST INCREDIBLE CAREER.
I'VE GOT TO ASK YOU, YOU'VE JUST
I'M JUST CURIOUS ABOUT WHEN YOU
HAD THE MOST INCREDIBLE CAREER.
FINISH WITH CHEERS BECAUSE THERE
I'M JUST CURIOUS ABOUT WHEN YOU
ARE SO MANY PEOPLE WHO THINK IT
FINISH WITH CHEERS BECAUSE THERE
WILL NEVER GET BIGGER.
ARE SO MANY PEOPLE WHO THINK IT
JUST PERSONALLY, DID YOU THINK
WILL NEVER GET BIGGER.
THAT -- WAS IT SHOCKING TO YOU?
JUST PERSONALLY, DID YOU THINK
DID YOU EXPECT IT ALL ALONG.
THAT -- WAS IT SHOCKING TO YOU?
I'M DYING TO KNOW WHAT WAS IN
DID YOU EXPECT IT ALL ALONG.
YOUR HEAD AT THE END O THAT RUN.
I'M DYING TO KNOW WHAT WAS IN
>> YOU, NO EVERY DAY WAS A GIFT
YOUR HEAD AT THE END O THAT RUN.
FROM GOD.
>> YOU, NO EVERY DAY WAS A GIFT
YOU HAD TO PINCH YOURSELF
FROM GOD.
BECAUSE YOUR JOB DESCRIPTION YOU
YOU HAD TO PINCH YOURSELF
IS IT AT A BAR AND CRACK JOKES
BECAUSE YOUR JOB DESCRIPTION YOU
AND GET PAID FOR IT.
IS IT AT A BAR AND CRACK JOKES
I MEAN, TALK ABOUT THE LUCKIEST
AND GET PAID FOR IT.
PEOPLE ON EARTH.
I MEAN, TALK ABOUT THE LUCKIEST
THEN I GET A CALL FROM JOHN
PEOPLE ON EARTH.
LASITER.
THEN I GET A CALL FROM JOHN
YOU WANT TO PLAY A PIG IN A
LASITER.
CARTOON MOVIE?
YOU WANT TO PLAY A PIG IN A
25 YEARS NOW, I'VE BEEN WORKING
CARTOON MOVIE?
WITH PICKS AR.
25 YEARS NOW, I'VE BEEN WORKING
>> PICKS AR IS THE MOST
WITH PICKS AR.
SUCCESSFUL OF ALL TIME.
>> PICKS AR IS THE MOST
YOU ARE IN EVERY PICKS AR AND
SUCCESSFUL OF ALL TIME.
MOVIE.
YOU ARE IN EVERY PICKS AR AND
ARE YOU THE MOST SUCCESSFUL
MOVIE.
ACTOR OF ALL TIME?
ARE YOU THE MOST SUCCESSFUL
[LAUGHTER]
ACTOR OF ALL TIME?
>> WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING?
[LAUGHTER]
SERIOUSLY.
>> WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING?
>> I THINK IMAGES OF SPENCER
SERIOUSLY.
TRAZEY AND JOHN MALCOVICH POPPED
>> I THINK IMAGES OF SPENCER
UP IN MY HEAD.
TRAZEY AND JOHN MALCOVICH POPPED
-- SPENCER TRACY AND JOHN
UP IN MY HEAD.
MALCOVICH POPPED UP IN MY HEAD.
-- SPENCER TRACY AND JOHN
>> I THINK I'M NUMBER THREE
MALCOVICH POPPED UP IN MY HEAD.
THOUGH.
>> I THINK I'M NUMBER THREE
>> REALLY?
THOUGH.
>> SAMUEL L. JACKSON.
>> REALLY?
WOW.
>> SAMUEL L. JACKSON.
WE'VE GOT A TOP FIVE STAR OF ALL
WOW.
TIME!
WE'VE GOT A TOP FIVE STAR OF ALL
-- ON OUR SHOW, MAN!
TIME!
>> I'M SO EXCITED.
-- ON OUR SHOW, MAN!
>> WE'RE THRILLED FOR YOU.
>> I'M SO EXCITED.
IT REALLY IS AN HONOR TO HAVE
>> WE'RE THRILLED FOR YOU.
YOU ON.
IT REALLY IS AN HONOR TO HAVE
AND CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU ON.
IT'S ENORMOUS.
AND CONGRATULATIONS.
JUST CONGRATULATIONS ON ALL YOUR
IT'S ENORMOUS.
SUCCESS OVER MANY, MANY YEARS.
JUST CONGRATULATIONS ON ALL YOUR
>> THANK YOU.
SUCCESS OVER MANY, MANY YEARS.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> YOU'RE A AMAZING.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
HARVEY: THANK YOU, JOHN.
>> YOU'RE A AMAZING.
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE A BREAK.
You've tried so many
moisturizers...
but one blows them all
out of the water.
Hydro Boost with hyaluronic acid
to plump skin cells
so it bounces back...
Neutrogena®
And try our hydrating makeup.
Buy One Take One is back,
starting at just $12.99,
at Olive Garden.
Join us for a NEW
favorite today.
Then bring one home
for tomorrow--on us.
Buy One Take One
For a limited time.
Only at Olive Garden.
CHARLES: WELCOME BACK TO "TMZ"
LIVE.
IF YOU SHOWED UP FOR SOMETHING
CALLED SCANK FEST, IT'S A CAM DI
FESTIVAL.
CAM DI MAYHEM.
IT'S A CAM DI FESTIVAL IN
BROOKLYN, YOU GOT A BIG SURPRISE
BECAUSE YOU GO A PERFORMER THAT
NO ONE KNEW HE WAS GOING TO BE
THERE.
THE ONLY PERSON WHO PULLED THIS
OFF WAS THE OWNER AND ANNOUNCED
THAT SURPRISE, LOUIE C.K. IS
HERE.
HARVEY: WHAT KIND OF REACTION DO
YOU THINK HE GOT?
I WOULD HAVE REACTED A STRONG
REACTION BECAUSE HE'S ALWAYS
RECEIVED THAT.
>> THIS IS A FESTIVAL ABOUT
COMEDIANS FOR THREE DAYS.
IF YOU'RE THERE, YOU'RE A DIE
HARD COMIC.
>> THERE ARE ISSUES THAT CAME UP
WITH HIM --
BRAD: BUT HE MADE A SURPRISE
APPEARANCE.
LOUIE MASTURBATING IN FRONT OF
PEOPLE.
AND YOU KNOW, HE LOST A LOT OF
GIGS.
HE LOST A MOVIE.
HE'S BEEN DOING THESE APARENTSES
EVERY NOW -- APPEARANCES EVERY
NOW AND THEN.
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENED.
>> RIGHT?
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
CRAZY THINGS HAPPEN.
HERE'S ONE OF THOSE CRAZY
THINGS.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, LOUIE C.K.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
[CROWD CHANTING "LOUIE"]
HARVEY: THIS WENT ON FOR A LONG
TIME.
>> LONG OVATION.
YOU CAN'T SAY THAT'S MIXED.
HARVEY: IT WAS NOT MIXED.
BRAD: THAT IS A FULL-THROATED
OVATION HE'S GOING TO GET.
>> IT'S A PRETTY SHOCKING
RESPONSE.
IT ALMOST FEELS LIKE THE
AUDIENCE FAVORITE TEAM WON A
GAME.
>> A LOT OF THEM -- LOUIE BEFORE
EVERYTHING HAPPENED, REMEMBER,
WAS ON TOP OF THE COMEDY WORLD.
SO THIS WAS, YOU KNOW, FOR DIE
HARD COMEDY FANS WHO PROBABLY
BEEN JONESING TO SEE LOUIE C.K.
AGAIN, I THINK THAT'S HE GOT
THAT REACTION.
I DON'T KNOW IF THIS WILL HELP
HIM BUT HE ACTUALLY -- WAS OPEN
WITH A JOKE --
>> HE OPENED THE JOKE SAYING IF
YOU MASTURBATE IN FRONT OF
SOMEONE FIRST, AND IF THEY SAY
YES, DON'T DO IT.
>> ROSEANNE IS PERFORMING IN
ATLANTIC CITY AND THE SAME
THING, THAT YOU KNOW, THIS IS
AGAIN WHAT WE TALKED ABOUT WITH
SNAPSHOTS AND THINGS LIKE THAT.
ANDREW DICE CLAY.
THAT'S AN INTERESTING DOUBLE
BUILDER.
CALLER: I THINK HE'S DOING WHAT
HE DOES BEST.
HE MAY HAVE MADE A MISTAKE AND
DONE SOME THINGS SOME PEOPLE
DON'T LIKE, BUT GETTING RIGHT
BACK INTO, YOU KNOW, THE
BUSINESS, WHAT HE LOVES TO DO.
AND WHAT HE'S GOOD AT.
AND HE'S GOOD AT MAKING PEOPLE
LAUGH.
SO I MEAN, I THINK HE SHOULD
HAVE GOTTEN RIGHT BACK --
>> AND THE AUDIENCE RECEIVED
WELL.
HARVEY: WE'RE GOING TO TAK
♪ ♪ ♪
Start the car! Start the car!
The IKEA Summer Sale.
Wooooooo!
Save up to 50% off select
items in store only
June 26th to July 7th.
IKEA.
CHARLES: WELCOME BACK TO "TMZ"
LIVE.
MARC ANTHONY PASSIONATELY
SINGING "I WILL ALWAYS LOVE YOU"
TO JENNIFER LOPEZ.
HE WAS PASSIONATELY SINGING BUT
THIS WAS AN EVENT FOR MARC AND
JENNIFER'S KIDS.
AND ALEX IS THERE, OF COURSE,
NOW, AND POSTED A VIDEO THAT
SHOWS EVERYBODY IS GETTING ALONE
JUST FINE.
-- ALONG JUST FINE.
♪ ALWAYS LOVE YOU
ALWAYS LOVE YOU ♪
CHARLES: THIS WAS ONE OF THEIR
-- I DON'T KNOW WHICH ONE OF
THEIR KISS WAS HAVING A CHOIR
CONCERT.
>> YOU HAVE TO COMMEND THEM FOR
GETTING ALONG AS GOOD AS THEY
DO.
IN ORDER TO BRING ANOTHER PERSON
IN THAT RELATIONSHIP IT COULD
MESS EVERYTHING UP.
BY A-ROD IS A GREAT DUDE.
LIKES LIKE THEY ARE BROS.
>> IT WORKS FOR THEM.
>> WE WILL SEE YOU NEXT TIME.
[CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY THE
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE,
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTION CONTENT AND
ACCURACY.VISIT NCICAP.ORG]
>> I'M A LAWYER.
We are sisters.
And we just moved in together.
Why Alissa and Aleah chose Fios.
We stream sooo much.
A lot of times Alissa is
watching TV on her laptop,
using her phone, also using her
tablet.
I am really good at multitasking
Cause I'm awesome.
A little.
The best internet is even better
at our best price.
Switch now and get our fastest
speeds available.
Plus, a free Samsung Chromebook
on us.
That's Fios.