[CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
WARNER BROS. DOMESTIC TELEVISION
DISTRIBUTION]
ANNOUNCER: TODAY ON "TMZ."
HARVEY: THIS IS CLEARLY THE
ROLL-UP TO THE GRAMMYS AND
BEYONCE IS SKATING THERE.
>> JANELLE MONAE HAD A ROLLER
SKATING PARTY AND HER GUEST OF
HONOR WAS BEYONCE.
HARVEY: I'M JUST THINKING,
PEOPLE GO OUT DURING THE WEEK
DAY?
RAQUEL: CELEBRITIES DON'T GO OUT
IN THE WEEKEND.
THEY GO OUT DURING THE WEEK.
>> IF YOU DON'T HAVE A REAL JOB.
IT'S BETTER TO PARTY ON THOSE
DAYS.
RAQUEL: I CAN'T GO ON A TUESDAY
AND MONDAY NIGHT LIKE EVERYBODY
ELSE.
I HAVE TO BE AT WORK EVERY DAY.
>> YOU ALSO HAVE CHILDREN AT
HOME!
>> ARIANA GRANDE IS CALLING THE
PRODUCER OF THE GRAMMYS A LIAR.
THE PRODUCER SAID ARIANA PULLED
OUT BECAUSE SHE WAS TOO FRAZZLED
AND COULDN'T GET A DECENT
PERFORMANCE TOGETHER IN TIME.
ARIANA IS PISSED.
SHE TWEETED, I CAN PULL TOGETHER
A PERFORMANCE OVERNIGHT AND YOU
KNOW THAT, KEN.
>> WHEN YOU SAY THE NAME, KEN,
YOU'RE REALLY MAD.
>> DAMN IT, KEN!
YOU KNOW THAT!
>> WE HAVE MATT GAETZ,
HE IS A REPUBLICAN
REPRESENTATIVE FROM FLORIDA.
WE SAY PEOPLE ARE CALLING YOU
THE CONSERVATIVE OF ALEXANDRIA
OCASIO CORTEZ.
>> COULD YOU BE A POWER COUPLE?
>> THAT MIGHT BE A LITTLE
PRESUMPTUOUS OF ME BUT I WOULD
SWIPE RIGHT ON THE OPPORTUNITY.
HARVEY: HE REPRESENTS PENSACOLA,
FLORIDA.
VERY CONSERVATIVE.
RAQUEL: FUN FACT, PENSACOLA,
FLORIDA, HAS THE WHITEST BEACHES
IN THE UNITED STATES.
>> PENSACOLA, EVEN THE BEACHES
ARE WHITE.
>> JEN SELTER HIT UP THE BEACHES
OF CABO IN THIS REALLY CUTE
BIKINI.
SHE LOOKS INCREDIBLE.
RAQUEL: SHE'S BEING A LITTLE BIT
THIRSTY BECAUSE TODAY THE
WEATHER IS 22 DEGREES.
>> THAT'S CELSIUS.
[LAUGHTER]
RAQUEL: OH.
ANNOUNCER: "TMZ" KIDS, "TMZ"
KIDS.
LET'S HAVE FUN WITH -- "TMZ"
DADDIES, OH, YA!
GOO GOO, GAGA, CONOR MCGREGOR.
>> CONOR MCGREGOR JUST LOOKS SO
GOOD.
>> HE'S GOT A GREAT BODY AND HIS
SWAGGER.
ANNOUNCER: HE'S GOT SO MUCH
SWAGGER, EVEN THE WAVES WASN'T
KNOCK HIM DOWN.
WHO'S THE PARTY POOPER?
RAQUEL: THE SWIM DIAPER KEEPS
ALL THE BOO BOO INSIDE.
ANNOUNCER: GOOD TO KNOW.
WHO'S THE KID?
>> HE'S WITH CONOR JR., HIS
FIRST BORN SON.
IT WAS A WARM WINTER DAY IN
MIAMI.
ANNOUNCER: CONOR SPENT AN
IDYLLIC DAY BY THE SEA WITH HIS
1-YEAR-OLD SON.
A LITTLE TOO IDYLLIC.
IF YOU ASK THIS GUY --
HARVEY: IS THIS ORCHESTRATED?
>> CONOR TAKES HIS SON
EVERYWHERE.
HE TOOK HIS SON TO THE SUPER
BOWL.
ANNOUNCER: YEAH, HE LIKES BEING
SEEN WITH HIS ADORABLE CHILD.
WAIT A MINUTE!
HARVEY: IT'S INTERESTING BECAUSE
IT IS A WAY TO SOFTEN HIS IMAGE
AFTER THE DOLLY.
ANNOUNCER: AS IN THE DOLLY CONOR
HURLED AT A BUS CAUSING INJURIES
TO A FELLOW FIGHTER'S FACE?
SPEAKING OF FACES, IT'S LIKE
CONOR'S LOOKING INTO A MIRROR.
OH!
RAQUEL: RIGHT NOW IT'S VERY
CHILLY OUT HERE.
IF YOU CAN AFFORD IT, WHY NOT GO
TO MIAMI WHERE IT'S IN THE HIGH
70'S.
HARVEY: HE'S FROM IRELAND.
RAQUEL: THAT'S EVEN WORSE THAN
L.A.
THAT'S NEGATIVE PROBABLY WHO
KNOWS.
>> I WANT TO OPEN MY PHONE AND
IT SAYS IT'S NEGATIVE WHO KNOWS.
HARVEY: OH, MY GOD, I NEED A
JACKET, IT'S NEGATIVE PROBABLY
WHO KNOWS.
CHARLIE: AND YOU OPEN IT UP, IT
SAYS HOT AS FISH GREASE.
ANNOUNCER: HAPPY DADDY'ING.
DADDY.
>> KIM KARDASHIAN WAS ON JIMMY
FALLON'S SHOW.
AND TALKING ALL ABOUT HER FOURTH
KID BUT YOU COULDN'T CONCENTRATE
BECAUSE SHE WAS SO FRICKING
GORGEOUS IN THIS SKIN-TIGHT,
SNAKESKIN DRESS.
I KNOW WE SAY THIS ALL THE TIME
BUT IT'S THE BEST SHE'S EVER
LOOKED.
>> SHE LOOKS AMAZING EVERY DAY.
IT'S RIDICULOUS.
HARVEY: HOW LONG DOES IT TAKE
KIM KARDASHIAN TO GET READY?
>> HOURS.
HOURS.
HARVEY: OH, GOD.
TO SIT THERE --
>> WHY DO YOU CARE ABOUT SITTING
THERE?
SOMEONE'S PAYING FOR IT.
YOU'RE DRINKING.
WHO CARES?
HARVEY: THE WORST!
IT WOULD DRIVE ME CRAZY.
>> HOW LONG DOES IT TAKE YOU TO
GET READY?
HARVEY: 11 MINUTES.
CHARLIE: HAVE YOU TIMED
YOURSELF?
HARVEY: UH-HUH, BECAUSE I
HAVE TO TIME MYSELF IN THE
MORNING.
CHARLIE: WHAT DO YOU DO ON THE
11TH MINUTE?
COURTNEY: DO YOU WINK AT
YOURSELF?
>> YOU GOT THIS, LEVIN.
ANNOUNCER: IT'S ONE OF THE
BIGGEST FUSED IN HOLLYWOOD.
ARIANA GRANDE VERSUS THIS GUY!
WHO THE HELL IS THAT, RICHARD
DRYFESS?
>> ARIANA GRANDE IS CALLING THE
PRODUCER OF THE GRAMMYS A LIAR.
ANNOUNCER: KEN ERLICH WHO DID AN
INTERVIEW SAYING ARIANA GRANDE
WON'T BE PERFORMING AFTER ALL
BECAUSE HE SAID IT WAS TOO LATE
FOR HER TO PULL SOMETHING
TOGETHER.
NOW ARIANA IS CLAPPING BACK
PELOSI-STYLE CALLING EHRLICH A
LIAR, LIAR, MCLIARSON.
>> SHE SAID I CAN PULL TOGETHER
A PERFORMANCE OVERNIGHT AND YOU
KNOW THAT, KEN.
ANNOUNCER: ACCORDING TO ARIANA,
SHE WANTED TO SING HER HIT SONG
"JAPANESE BARBECUE" BUT KEN
DIDN'T THINK THE AUDIENCE WOULD
RELATE.
TO WHICH ARIANA SAID, THANK YOU,
NEXT.
WHO DO WE BELIEVE?
HARVEY: I AM 100% TEAM ARIANA.
THEY ARE PUTTING HER EVERYWHERE
-- HER FACE EVERYWHERE.
BECAUSE THEY WANT HER AUDIENCE
TO COME TO THE GRAMMYS.
>> "7 RINGS" IS THE NUMBER ONE
SONG IN THE COUNTRY.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE TO
ME.
>> WHO DO WE KNOW THIS FROM?
CHARLES: KEN SAYS SHE WAS TOO
FRAZZLED TO PULL IT TOGETHER.
HARVEY: IT'S NOT TRUE.
DID YOU SEE THE STATEMENT?
>> FROM WHO?
HARVEY: KEN!
ANNOUNCER: BOYS, BOYS, CALM
DOWN.
PERHAPS WE NEED SOME ESTROGEN TO
CLEAR THIS UP.
>> THEY ONLY LET YOU PERFORM
SONGS THAT ARE NOMINATED.
THAT SONG IS NOT NOMINATED.
ANNOUNCER: YOU TELL HIM, GIRL!
EXCEPT FOR ONE THING.
CHARLES: LAST YEAR AT THE
GRAMMYS, CHILDISH GAMBINO
PERFORMED A SONG THAT WAS NOT
NOMINATED AND SO DID SAM SMITH.
ANNOUNCER: WOMEN, RIGHT.
HEY, AT LEAST THEY TRY.
WE'LL MISS YOU AT THE GRAMMYS
THIS YEAR, ARIANA.
MAYBE KEN WON'T.
BUT YOU KNOW, EVERYONE ELSE
WILL.
>> I LOVE YOU, DUDE.
>> JULIAN EDELMAN'S PLAYOFF
BEARD IS SO MORE.
HARVEY: HE SHAVED IT OFF.
>> BECAUSE OF ELLEN DEGENERES.
SO JULIAN HAD AN EPIC BEARD AND
HE'S BEEN GROWING IT NINE
MONTHS.
IT'S AROUND TRAINING CAMP TIME.
HE GOT ON ELLEN DEGENERES AND
SHE SAID I'LL DONATE $10,000 TO
THE BOYS AND GIRLS CLUB.
>> BUT YOU NEED TO LET ME SHAVE
THAT BEARD FIRST.
>> LET'S DO IT!
HARVEY: HOW DOES HE LOOK AFTER?
>> HE'S A VERY BEAUTIFUL MAN.
>> HE'S SO HOT.
OH, MY GOSH.
HE'S SO HOT.
>> HOTTER WITH THE BEARD OR
WITHOUT?
>> WITHOUT, SO HOT.
HARVEY: HE'S GREAT LOOKING.
CHARLIE: EVERYBODY'S HOTTER WITH
A BEARD.
>> I AGREE.
>> NOT TRUE.
CHARLIE: EVERYBODY'S BETTER WITH
A BEARD.
>> NO.
>> GIRLS LOVE A GEORGE MICHAEL
OVERGROWTH.
COURTNEY: STOP SAYING WHAT WE
LIKE!
HARVEY: JULIAN EDELMAN LOOKS A
MILLION TIMES BETTER WITHOUT THE
BEARD.
CHARLIE: NOT AT ALL.
BEARDS, MAN.
COURTNEY: NO, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
CHARLIE: BELIEVE ME, MAN.
GIRLS LIKE BEARDS.
>> THAT'S NOT TRUE.
>> GIRLS LIKE BEARDS BECAUSE --
>> STOP TELLING US WHAT WE LIKE.
CHARLIE: GIRLS LIKE BEARDS.
>> HOW YOU DOING, MAN?
ANNOUNCER: FELLOW AMERICANS, SAY
HELLO TO REPUBLICAN CONGRESSMAN,
MATT GAETZ, FROM THE GREAT STATE
OF FLORIDA.
HARVEY: SUPER CONSERVATIVE, I
BELIEVE.
>> VERY MUCH ABOUT THE WALL.
ANNOUNCER: MANY ARE CALLING HIM
THE CONSERVATIVE ALEXANDRIA
OCASIO CORTEZ.
>> THAT IS TOTALLY UNFAIR.
A.O.C. IS WAY MORE INTERESTING
AND ATTRACTIVE AND CAPABLE THAN
I AM.
HARVEY: HE SAID CAPABLE?
DID HE SANDWICH THAT ATTRACTIVE
IN?
>> LITERALLY IN BETWEEN THE TWO.
ANNOUNCER: OH, WELL.
MAYBE YOU CAN GET RASHEDA TO
PASS HER A NOTE DURING SESSION
BUT YOU TWO ARE SO DIFFERENT!
FOR INSTANCE, SHE'S LIKESSING
DANCING AND YOU TRY TO GET
PARENTS OF PARKLAND VICTIMS
KICKED OUT OF A CONGRESSIONAL
HEARING.
>> THE BIGGEST DIFFERENCE IN
THIS TOWN ISN'T WHETHER PEOPLE
ARE REPUBLICANS OR DEMOCRATS OR
WHETHER THEY WANT TO SHAKE THE
PLACE UP OR NOT.
IF SHE DOES, I ADMIRE HER FOR
IT.
HARVEY: I DON'T REMEMBER ANY
CONGRESS PERSON REFERRING TO
ANOTHER CONGRESS PERSON THAT
WAY.
>> REPUBLICANS, USUALLY THEIR
LINE IS SHE'S YOUNG AND STUPID.
>> SOMETIMES HATERS GOT TO HATE.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I'M ABOUT.
ANNOUNCER: WHAT IS MATT GAETZ
ABOUT?
HE'S EXTREMELY PRO-GUN BUT ALSO
PRO-MARIJUANA WHICH MEANS YOU
CAN BE PREPARED FOR THE ZOMBIE
APOCALYPSE BUT WON'T CARE WHEN
IT HAPPENS.
SAY, YOU KNOW WHO ELSE IS PRO
MARIJUANA?
A.O.C.
>> I WOULD SWIPE RIGHT ON THE
OPPORTUNITY TO INVITE A
CANDIDATEOVER FOR DINNER.
ANNOUNCER: DUDE.
>> OH, NO!
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
CHARLIE: WOULD IT HELP AMERICA
IF THOSE GUYS STARTED DATING?
THEY SEEM LIKE ROMEO AND JULIET.
ANNOUNCER: AND THAT TURNED OUT
GREAT.
HARVEY: HE DOES TAKE A CHANCE ON
PISSING OFF HIS ELECTORATE.
HE REPRESENTS PENSACOLA,
FLORIDA, VERY CONSERVATIVE.
RAQUEL: WAIT, PENSACOLA,
FLORIDA, HAS THE MOST WHITEST
SANDEST BEACHES IN THE UNITED
STATES.
>> PENSACOLA, EVEN THE BEACHES
ARE WHITE.
>> THANKS, CONGRESSMAN.
ANNOUNCER: POLITICS!
>> JEN SELTER, SUPER POPULAR
INSTAGRAM MODEL, HIT UP THE
BEACHES OF CABO IN THIS REALLY
CUTE BIKINI.
SHE LOOKS INCREDIBLE.
>> SHE WAS LIKE THE O.G. BUTT
GIRL.
NOW I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE HELL
HAPPENED TO HER.
>> STILL BIG.
>> I DISAGREE.
>> WE HAVEN'T HEARD FROM HER IN
A WHILE.
>> SHE HAS 13 MILLION INSTAGRAM
FOLLOWERS AND LAUNCHED A
FITNESS, DIET PLAN.
SHE'S DOING GREAT.
>> IF YOU HAVE 13 MILLION
INSTAGRAM FOLLOWERS, YOU CAN
MAKE HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS OF
DOLLARS ADVERTISING PRODUCTS ON
INSTAGRAM.
SHE'S DOING REALLY, REALLY WELL.
RAQUEL: YOU KNOW WHAT, SHE'S
BEEN A LITTLE BIT THIRSTY
BECAUSE TODAY THE WEATHER IS 22
DEGREES.
>> THAT'S CELSIUS.
[LAUGHTER]
RAQUEL: OH.
HA-HA-HA-HA!
ANNOUNCER: COMING UP --
>> JANELLE MONAE THREW THE BEST
PRE-GRAMMY PARTY.
SHE DID A RETRO ROLLER SKATING
PARTY.
HER GUEST OF HONOR WAS BEYONCE
SO WE HAVE VIDEO OF BEYONCE
ROLLER SKATING.
>> YOU'RE LIKE OUT OF BREATH.
>> I'M SO EXCITED.
ANNOUNCER: PLUS --
>> PATRICK WHITESELL, SUPER
AGENT.
WE GOT HIM OUT LAST NIGHT AT
NICE GUY AND HE WAS WITH HOT
MODEL.
>> THAT'S A SUBTLE MESSAGE, AT
NICE GUY.
>> HOW IS THAT A SUBTLE MESSAGE?
>> HE IS THE NICE GUY.
>> YOU ARE AN IDIOT
>> DANIELLE BREGOLI HAD HER OWN
SHOW COME OUT ON SNAPCHAT.
HARVEY: IF I HAD TO PUT MY MON
When I walked through a
snowstorm for a cigarette,
that's when I knew
I had to quit.
For real this time.
That's why I'm using Nicorette.
Only Nicorette Gum has patented
dual-coated technology
for great taste.
Plus intense
craving relief.
Every great why,
needs a great how.
NEW Theraflu PowerPods.
The cold and flu fighting
machine.
You put in your machine.
Press the button to brew up
powerful relief.
To defeat your toughest
cold and flu symptoms fast.
NEW Theraflu PowerPods.
Press. Sip. Relief.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON, JANELLE?
ANNOUNCER: THAT'S SINGER
SONGWRITER JANELLE MONAE.
ATTENDING A PRE-GRAMMY AWARDS
PARTY IN L.A., REPPING HER
POTENTIAL ALBUM OF THE YEAR.
>> 30 COMPUTER.
ANNOUNCER: RIGHT.
IT WAS JANELLE'S PRE-GRAMMY
PARTY OF THE SAME NAME THAT
REALLY HAD PEOPLE SPINNING.
>> SHE DID A RETRO ROLLER
SKATING PARTY AND HER GUEST OF
HONOR WAS BEYONCE.
ANNOUNCER: OH, YEAH!
THERE'S QUEEN BEY GETTING HER
SWERVES ON ALL OVER THE RINK.
>> BEYONCE.
WE HAVE VIDEO OF BEYONCE ROLLER
SKATING.
>> YOU'RE OUT OF BREATH.
>> I'M SO EXCITED.
JANELLE MONAE AND BEYONCE ROLLER
SKATING, IT'S SO COOL.
ANNOUNCER: BEYONCE'S ROCKING
LUCKY NUMBER SEVEN AND JANELLE'S
ROCKING YOU'RE GOING TO GET
LUCKY SKIN-TIGHT PANTS.
MODEL SEAN ROSS.
TRANSPARENT ACTRESS, TRACY
LASET.
HARVEY: WE HAVE VIDEO OF HER
ROLLER SKATING?
>> WE KIND OF JUST SHOWED IT.
CHARLIE: THOUGHT IT WAS AN
AVERAGE THURSDAY NIGHT, HAPPENS
TO BE JANELLE MONAE'S PARTY?
RAQUEL: CELEBRITIES DON'T GO OUT
ON THE WEEKEND.
THEY GO OUT DURING THE WEEK.
THAT'S WHY I'M WHACKED NOW.
I CAN'T GO OUT ON A TUESDAY AND
MONDAY NIGHT, ACE OF DIAMONDS,
THINGS LIKE THAT.
I HAVE TO BE AT WORK EVERY DAY.
>> YOU ALSO HAVE TWO YOUNG
CHILDREN AT HOME.
HARVEY: YOU HAVE CHILDREN,
RAQUEL!
ANNOUNCER: OH, THAT'S HANDLED.
ALEXA, WATCH CHILDREN.
GOTTA ROLL.
>> I WENT FROM SLEEPING ON THE
FLOOR IN A TRAILER TO HAVING A
GOLD RECORD IN SIX MONTHS.
>> DANIELLE BREGOLI IS BREAKING
RECORDS.
SHE HAD HER OWN SHOW COME OUT ON
SNAPCHAT THIS WEEK AND IT'S
CALLED BRINGING UP BABY.
THIS THING KILLED IT.
ON THE VERY FIRST DAY, IT GOT
OVER 10 MILLION VIEWS.
SNAPCHAT EVEN SAID IF YOU
COMPARE THIS TO "KEEPING UP WITH
THE KARDASHIANS," "KEEPING UP
WITH THE KARDASHIANS" GETS ABOUT
1.5 MILLION VIEWS.
HARVEY: SHE'S A HIT.
>> SHE'S SUPPOSED TO MAKE $10
MILLION THIS YEAR.
HARVEY: IF I HAVE TO PUT MY
MONEY ON A 15-YEAR-OLD BECOMING
RICH AND FAMOUS, SHE'S GOING TO
BE IN THE TOP FIVE.
>> SHE'S ALREADY RICH AND
FAMOUS.
THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD BET.
YOU REALLY WENT ON A LIMB.
RAQUEL: YOU ALSO HELPED HER OUT
A LOT.
WE PITCH HER EVERY OTHER DAY.
EVERY TIME WE TALK ABOUT A LOT
OF PEOPLE OF NOBODY, WE HELP
THEM OUT SO MUCH, IT'S INSANE.
HARVEY: GUESS WHAT THEY DO AFTER
THEY GET FAMOUS?
RAQUEL: DON'T TALK TO US.
HARVEY: EXACTLY.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
THEY STOP BEING FAMOUS, THOUGH,
WE STOP TALKING TO THEM.
HARVEY: THAT'S THE PARTY LINE.
ANNOUNCER: AND NOW, AS THE BEZOS
TURNS.
MONEY, WIENER PICS, AMAZON,
DATING, BEZOS.
YES, IT'S BEEN A CRAZY WEEK FOR
THE RICHEST MAN IN THE WORLD BUT
NOW, NEW DRAMA!
HIS NEW GIRLFRIEND'S ESTRANGED
HUSBAND IS DATING THIS CHICK.
WAIT.
WE'VE GOT A BETTER PHOTO.
ALL RIGHT!
>> PATRICK WHITESELL, SUPER
AGENT FROM WILLIAM MORRIS.
HARVEY: ALSO LAUREN SANCHEZ'S
ESTRANGED HUSBAND.
ANNOUNCER: RIGHT BECAUSE SHE WAS
MARRIED TO HER AND FRIENDS WITH
HIM AND INTRODUCED HER TO HIM
AND NOW THEY'RE TOGETHER.
CHARLES: PATRICK IS OK BECAUSE
HE WAS OUT LAST NIGHT WITH A
MODEL NAMED KEIRA ALEXA.
THEY DID THE THING WHERE THEY
WALK OUT SEPARATELY.
HARVEY: AND GET IN THE SAME CAR
IN THE BACK SEAT.
ANNOUNCER: SLICK MOVE, GUYS.
TELL US ABOUT THIS HOT LADY.
CHARLES: KEIRA ALEXA, SHE'S A
MODEL.
THAT'S ALL I KNOW ABOUT HER.
ANNOUNCER: THANKS FOR THAT
DETAILED REPORT.
WE'LL TAKE IT FROM HERE.
SHE LOVES TO SELL COOKIES AND
WEAR BRAS AND ALSO NOT WEAR BRAS
AND LOOKS A LOT LIKE PATRICK'S
EX, LAUREN.
CHARLES: SHE'S ROUGHLY 25 YEARS
YOUNGER THAN LAUREN.
ANNOUNCER: THAT EXPLAINS THE
COOKIES.
>> LAUREN IS WITH JEFF BEZOS.
ANNOUNCER: SPEAKING OF, HE'S GOT
HIS DRAMA OF HIS OWN WITH HIS
WHOLE.
>> SEMI ERECT MANHOOD PRESSING
AGAINST YOUR ZIPPER.
ANNOUNCER: WE WERE GOING TO SAY
EXTORTION CLAIMS BUT THANKS FOR
GETHD SPECIFIC.
HARVEY: AMERICAN MEDIA IS
SAYING, AUTOPSIES, WE'RE GOING
TO INVESTIGATE OURSELVES IN THIS
THING.
JEFF BEZOS SAYS THEY TRIED
BLACKMAILING HIM.
>> THE EMAILS WERE CRAZY.
RAQUEL: WHY WOULD "NATIONAL
ENQUIRER" GO AGAINST THE RICHEST
MAN?
THAT'S DUMB.
ANNOUNCER: LET'S BREAK IT DOWN
IN DETAIL.
HARVEY: THERE'S A BUNCH OF
STUFF.
ANNOUNCER: RIGHT, SO GOOD LUCK,
JEFF.
AND PATRICK, YOU ALREADY GOT
LUCKY.
EVAN: GOOD NEWS, EVERYBODY.
MY NEW MOVIE CAME OUT TODAY.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU KNOW THIS.
I'M STARRING IN A NEW MOVIE.
HARVEY: WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
EVAN: IT'S CALLED "HIGH FLYING
BIRD" DIRECTED BY STEVEN
SODERBERGH.
ZAZI BEACH IS MY CO-STAR.
ALONG WITH ZACHARY PINTO.
IT'S ABOUT THE BASKETBALL
LOCKOUT AND DURING THE BEST
SCENE OF THE MOVIE --
>> OH, MAN, THIS IS GETTING
CRAZY.
JAMIL AND ERIC SCOTT GOING AT IT
IN PUBLIC CALLING EACH OTHER OUT
ON TWITTER.
>> YOU NEVER WANT TO MAKE THESE
THINGS PUBLIC BUT THESE GUYS
HAVE --
>> DID YOU MAKE IT?
>> I'M CANCELING MY NETFLIX.
>> YOU MEAN YOU'RE GOING TO
DELETE YOUR MOM'S PASSWORD?
>> I DON'T KNOW ANYONE WHO USES
THEIR OWN ACCOUNT.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> I USE MY MOM'S.
IT'S NETFLIX!
RAQUEL: HOW DO WE GET THAT CODE?
>> I GOT YOU.
>> IF YOUR PARENTS SEE, WHAT YOU
MIGHT ALSO LIKE, AND RAQUEL'S
GOT --
ANNOUNCER: COMING UP --
>> BILLY MCFARLAND SUED FOR $3
MILLION AND LOST.
HOW DO YOU GET IT FROM BILLY IF
HE'S IN PRISON?
HARVEY: THEY CAN STILL HAVE
MONEY.
>> YOU KNOW THEY DON'T TAKE YOUR
MONEY TO PRISON WITH YOU, RIGHT?
>> I'M WELL AWARE.
>> CHRIS PRATT IS GETTING RID OF
HIS DAD BOD WITH FASTING AND
SPIRITUALITY.
>> RELIGIOUS AND FASTING?
When Girl Scout ingenuity
meets Dunkin' coffee,
you get a cup of can-do.
Girl Scout Cookie
inspired flavors
are back at Dunkin'.
Try Thin Mints, Coconut Caramel
or Trefoils shortbread flavors.
And get your $2 medium latte
or cappuccino from 2-6 PM.
America runs on Dunkin'.
ANNOUNCER: "TMZ" ONLINE AND ON
YOUR PHONE 24/7.
ANNOUNCER: AND NOW, "TMZ" PIRACY
PRESENTS, X MARKS THE SPOT.
TO WHERE DISGRACED FYRE FESTIVAL
FOUNDER BILLY MCFARLAND
HOPEFULLY HAS SOMETHING VALUABLE
BURIED BECAUSE HE'S ON THE HOOK
FOR A CRAP LOAD OF CASH.
ARGHHH!
>> BILLY MCFARLAND WAS SUED FOR
$3 MILLION AND LOST.
THIS INVESTMENT COMPANY FUNDED
HIM $3 MILLION THREE WEEKS
BEFORE THE FYRE FESTIVAL AND
THEY WERE NEVER PAID BACK.
SO THEY SUED HIM FOR THE $3
MILLION BUT INTEREST PLUS LEGAL
FEES AND WON.
ANNOUNCER: FESTIVAL CO-FOUNDER
JA RULE WAS MENTIONED IN THE
SUIT BUT ISN'T ON THE HOOK FOR
THE THREE MILL WHICH MEANS THEY
GOT TO GET IT ALL FROM BILLY.
>> HOW DO YOU GET IT FROM BILLY
IF HE'S STILL IN PRISON?
HARVEY: HE CAN STILL HAVE MONEY.
>> THEY DON'T TAKE YOUR MONEY TO
PRISON WITH YOU.
ANNOUNCER: HOPEFULLY BILLY'S
MONEY IS PROTECTED VIA THE
METHOD ANY SOLID FINANCIAL
PLANNER WOULD RECOMMEND --
RAQUEL: DIG A HOLE IN HIS
BACKYARD AND PUT IT IN A BAG.
>> PRETTY GOOD IDEA.
HARVEY: TERRIBLE IDEA.
CHARLIE: WHAT ABOUT UNDER THE
SEA, LOBSTER TRAP.
THEN YOU BRING IT UP WHEN YOU'RE
OUT OF PRISON.
ANNOUNCER: UNLESS SOME LOBSTER
SWIPES IT AND IS LIVING LARGE ON
YOUR CHEDDAR.
BUT HERE'S A BETTER IDEA FOR
BILLY'S MONEY.
CHARLIE: PUT IT IN THE
COMMISSARY.
HARVEY: BERNIE MADOFF, I'VE GOT
$14 BILLION IN COMMISSARY.
CHARLIE: THAT'S A LOT OF INSTANT
NOODLES.
ANNOUNCER: THE POINT IS,
HOPEFULLY'S BILLY'S GOT THAT
-- SOME PLACE.
RAQUEL: I KNOW A LOT OF PEOPLE
WHO HAVE MONEY BURIED.
HARVEY: YOU'VE SEEN PEOPLE BURY
MONEY?
RAQUEL: 1,000 PERCENT.
ANNOUNCER: WOW, THAT'S A LOT OF
PERCENT.
SHE MUST BE TELLING THE TRUTH.
LYING CON MAN, GOODBYE,
EVERYBODY.
COMING UP --
CHARLIE: SHEILA E SENDS A LITTLE
MESSAGE TO HER NUMBER ONE FAN.
HARVEY: WHO?
CHARLIE: ERIC.
ERIC: I LOVE HER.
-Ah, the old crew!
Remember when we all used to go
to the cafeteria
and just chow down midday?
-You mean, like, lunch?
-Come on. Voted
"Most Likely to Help People
Save $668 When They Switch."
-At this school?
-Didn't you get caught
in the laminating machine?
-Ha. [ Sighs ]
-"Box, have a great summer.
Danielle."
Ooh.
Danielle, control yourself.
I'd like to slow it down here
with a special discount
for a special girl.
Danielle, this one's for you.
Here's your Buick sir.
with a special discount
for a special girl.
Actually, that's my Buick.
Your Buick doesn't have a
roof rack!
This is my Buick.
How are we gonna fit in your
mom's Buick?
Easy.
I like that new Buick.
Me too.
I was actually talking about
that Buick.
I knew that.
Did you?
Buick's fresh new lineup is full
of surprises.
Get great deals on our
expectation-shattering lineup.
Pay no interest for 72 months
on most Buick models.
[ music playing ]
♪ Here Comes the Sun ♪
You, all of you.
How you live. What you love.
[ laughter ]
That's what inspired us
to create America's
most advanced Internet.
Internet that
puts you in charge.
[ chattering ]
That protects what's important.
That handles everything
[ group cheering ]
and reaches everywhere.
This is beyond WiFi.
This is xFi.
Simple. Easy. Awesome.
Xfinity.
The future of awesome.
ANNOUNCER: THE "TMZ" CELEBRITY
TOUR HAS A NEW HOME DIRECTLY
ACROSS FROM THE HOLLYWOOD AND
HIGHLAND CENTER IN THE HEART OF
TINSELTOWN.
ON BOARD, YOU NEVER KNOW WHO YOU
MIGHT SEE.
KIM KARDASHIAN, BEN AFFLECK, THE
ROCK, MARIAH CAREY, JUSTIN
BIEBER, KEVIN HART.
GET YOUR FIX ONLINE OR AT THE
FABULOUS TOUR CENTER IN
HOLLYWOOD.
"TMZ" CELEBRITY TOUR!
CHARLIE: IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU,
SHEILA.
SHEILA E, L.A.X.
HARVEY: WOW, LOVE SHEILA E.
CHARLIE: THURSDAY SHE SAID
PRINCE'S SUPER BOWL HALFTIME
SHOW, BEST EVER.
>> IT WAS THE BEST.
YOU COULDN'T BEAT THAT.
COULDN'T PLAN IT ANY BETTER.
IT RAINED WHEN HE PLAYED PURPLE
RAIN, THE BEST SUPER BOWL EVER.
CHARLIE: SHE SENT A LITTLE
MESSAGE TO HER NUMBER ONE FAN.
HARVEY: WHO?
CHARLIE: ERIC.
>> HI, ERIC AT WORK.
SHEILA E HERE.
I HEARD YOU'RE A PRINCE FAN.
ARE YOU A SHEILA E FAN?
CHARLIE: HE OWNS ALL YOUR
RECORDS?
ERIC: I DO.
>> NEXT TIME I SEE YOU, YOU GET
A BIG HUG.
ERIC: I LOVE HER.
HARVEY: OH, MY GOD.
CHARLIE: I SAY, ERIC'S NOT HERE
RIGHT NOW.
WE DON'T KNOW IF THIS WILL
HAPPEN.
I'LL TAKE ON HIS BEHALF RIGHT
NOW.
OH, YES!
>> DON'T BE JEALOUS.
CHARLIE: I CAN TRANSFER THIS
HUG!
HOW DID IT FEEL?
ERIC: CHARLIE IS REALLY GOOD AT
TRANSMITTING THINGS FROM ONE
PERSON TO ANOTHER.
CHARLIE: THANK YOU, SHEILA.
BYE.
[CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY THE
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE,
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTION CONTENT AND ACCURACY.
VISIT NCICAP.ORG.]
>> I'M A LAWYER!