>>> WELCOME BACK TO WAKE UP
WASHINGTON, THE RECORD-BREAKING
FILM BLACK PANTHER IS THE FIRST
SUPERHERO MOVIE EVER TO BE
NOMINATED FOR BEST PICTURE.
IT FEATURES A PREDOMINANTLY
BLACK CAST AND GIVES A BLACK
BOYS AND GIRLS A CHANCE TO
IMAGINE THEMSELVES AS
SUPERHEROES.
BLACK PANTHER IS ALL ALSO AN
EXAMPLE OF AFRO FUTURISM.
WE EXPLAIN THE HISTORY AND
REVIVAL AS WE CELEBRATE BLACK
HISTORY MONTH.
>> I SEE THESE POSTS AT TIMES
WHERE PEOPLE SAY I JUST WANT TO
SEE BLACK MERMAIDS AND BLACK
PEOPLE IN SPACE, WE DECEIVE
BLACK STORIES THAT AREN'T ABOUT
BLACK PAIN BECAUSE THE
CONFERENCE , CONSTANT.
THIS WRITER IS AMONG THE
ARTISTS AT THE FOREFRONT OF THE
RESURGENCE OF AFRO FUTURISM.
>> IT IS JUST KIND OF A UTOPIA
TO IMAGINE WHAT IS.
WHAT THE STORY WASN'T A STORY
OF HAVING EVERYTHING TAKEN AWAY
AND HAVING SO MUCH LIKE
OPPRESSION AND BRUTALITY AND
SENSELESS MURDER AND SLAVERY?
WHAT IF IT COULD BE SOMETHING
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT?
>> THAT IS THE FOUNDATION OF
THE BESTSELLER CHILDREN OF
BLOOD AND BONE, A WEST AFRICAN
FANTASY NOVELS FEATURING A YOUNG
BLACK FEMALE PROTAGONIST.
>> WHEN DID IT OCCUR TO YOU
THAT WOMEN OF COLOR OR MEN OF
COLOR IN CHILDREN OF COLOR CAN
BE FANTASY CHARACTERS?
>> I DIDN'T REALIZE UNTIL MY
SENIOR YEAR OF HIGH SCHOOL THAT
NO CHARACTERS LOOKED LIKE ME,
SO ALL OF MY PROTAGONIST WORK
WHITE OR BIRACIAL.
THEN I REALIZED IT'S NOT JUST
ME WHO NEEDS THIS, IT'S OTHER
PEOPLE WHO LOOK LIKE ME, IT'S
ALSO PEOPLE WHO DON'T LOOK LIKE
ME, BECAUSE THE REASON I DIDN'T
THINK I COULD BE IN THE STORE
WAS BECAUSE I DIDN'T SEE IT.
>> THROUGH HER WRITING, SHE
DIRECTLY TACKLES RACISM AND
INEQUALITY.
>> I WANTED TO WRITE A STORY
THAT COMMENTED ON THE BLACK
EXPERIENCE.
IN SOME WAYS, AFRO FUTURISM IS
A REVOLUTIONARY ACT, DO YOU
THINK OF YOURSELF AS A
REVOLUTIONARY?
>> AT THIS POINT I CAN THINK OF
MYSELF AS A PART OF THE
REVOLUTION, AND SO DOES JENELLE
MONET.
ON HER NEW ALBUM, DIRTY
COMPUTER, SHE EXPLORES AFRO
FUTURISM THROUGH MUSIC.
>> AFRO FUTURISM IS ABOUT BLACK
PEOPLE, US SEEING OURSELVES IN
THE FUTURE AND KNOWING THAT WE
ARE NOT THE STEREOTYPE THAT HAS
BEEN PERPETUATED ON US.
>>
>> SHE BELIEVES THIS IS A TIME
FOR AFROCENTRIC, AFROCENTRIC
ART.
>> IT'S A WAY FOR BLACK WOMEN
LIKE MYSELF TO TELL OUR STORIES
THROUGH OUR OWN LENS, BECAUSE I
THINK IT IS IMPORTANT THAT WE
ARE TELLING OUR STORY.
IF WE ALLOW OTHER PEOPLE WHO
ARE NOT US TO TELL OUR STORY,
THEY MAY NOT BE TOLD PROPERLY.
>> ENTER BLACK PANTHER, WITH A
BLACK SUPERHERO AND A NEARLY
ALL BLACK CAST SET IN AN
AFRICAN INSPIRED UTOPIA
SOMETIME IN THE FUTURE, PANTHER
POPULARIZED THE IDEA OF AFRO
FUTURISM, BUT THE TRUTHS RUN
DEEP.
>> ALL OF THE EARLY
ABOLITIONISTS THAT WE
CELEBRATE, FREDERICK DOUGLASS,
THEY WERE ALL AFRO FUTURISTS,
GEORGE CLINTON.
>> CULTURAL RIDDICK GREG TATE
IS CONSIDERED ONE OF THE
LEADING SCHOLARS OF THIS
MOVEMENT.
>> ANYBODY WHO HAD A VISION OF
BLACK PEOPLE'S STORIES AND
PRESENCE AND IMAGING CAN BE
TOLD AND ELEVATED.
>> ON ONE HAND WE HAVE A MOVIE
LIKE BLACK PANTHER WHICH IS THE
ENTRY POINT FOR A LOT OF
PEOPLE, BUT THEN YOU HAVE BLACK
LIVES MATTER MOVEMENTS.
DO YOU SEE A CONNECTION BETWEEN
THOSE TWO THINGS?
>> DEFINITELY.
I DON'T THINK THAT BLACK
PANTHER WOULD'VE HAPPENED
WITHOUT THE PRECEDENT OF BLACK
LIVES MATTER, BECAUSE I THINK
AT ANY TIME, THERE'S OUTRAGE
AND PROTEST IN THE STREET, THE
CULTURAL ELITE IN AMERICA TEND
TO OPEN UP RESOURCES AND
ACTUALLY IN SPACE, FOR BLACK
CREATORS.
>> AND RESPONSE SUGGEST
AUDIENCES WILL START TO SEE
EVEN MORE AFRO FUTURIST ART
BLACK PANTHER SNAGGED THE TOP
FRIES AT SAG AWARDS AND WAS
NOMINATED FOR SEVEN OSCARS.
AND A SEQUEL IS UNDERWAY.
THE BOOK IS BEING MADE INTO A
MAJOR MOTION PICTURE WITH TWO
MORE BOOKS IN THE WORKS.
>> YOU THINK ARTS AND
ENTERTAINMENT ARE CHANGING?
>> I DEFINITELY THINK THEY ARE
CHANGING.
WE ARE FINALLY GETTING TO SEE
PEOPLE WHO WANT TO SHARE WITH
PEOPLE AND PEOPLE WHO DON'T
THINK THAT OH, PEOPLE ARE GOING
TO RELATE TO THIS BECAUSE IT IS
BLACK OR THEY WON'T RELATE TO
THIS BECAUSE IT'S AFRICAN, IT'S
TWO DIFFERENT, NO, THIS IS A
GREAT STORY, GREAT CHARACTER,
LET'S MAKE IT VISIBLE, AND WHEN
PEOPLE FIND IT, THEY WILL FALL
IN LOVE WITH IT.
>> AM PRETTY HAPPY TO SEE THE
DIRECTION THAT ARTS AND
ENTERTAINMENT IS HEADING IN
NOW, IT SEEMS MORE INCLUSIVE,
AND FILMS LIKE THAT, YOU LITTLE
BOYS AND LITTLE GIRLS WHO SAY
HEY, I SEE MYSELF THERE,
>> AND I CAN BE ANYTHING I
WANT, I COULD BE A SUPERHERO I
CAN CONQUER WHATEVER I WANT.
I'M EXCITED TO SEE HOW BLACK
PANTHER DOES AT THE OSCARS.
>> I KNOW IT'S BEEN SWEEPING UP
A LOT OF AWARDS.
>> IT WILL BE THE TALK OF THE
TOWN TOMORROW MORNING.
>> FOR SURE.
>> THE TALK AND THEN RUN HERE
IS THE FORECAST.
>> WE HAVE A BUMPY RIDE, WE
HAVE SHOWERS MOVING OUT AND
TURNING WARMER TODAY, BUT IT IS
WINDY, SO THE GUSTY WINDS COULD
BRING DOWN TREES AND POWER
LINES BETWEEN TODAY AND TONIGHT
AND TOMORROW MORNING, THAT'S
WHEN WE SEE WINDS GUSTING IN
THE METRO AS HIGH AS 50 MILES
PER HOUR AND HIGHER THAN THAT
OUT IN THE MOUNTAIN.
WE WILL SEE A PRETTY QUIET WEEK
OVERALL, MORE SHOWERS AT THE
END OF THE WEEK AND TODAY IS
ALL ABOUT THE WIND AND WARMTH.
>> TAKE IT EASY OUT THERE AND
ENJOY YOUR SUNDAY.
>> CBS SUNDAY MORNING IS COMING
UP NEXT.
HAVE A
Here's your Buick sir.
Actually, that's my Buick.
Your Buick doesn't have a
roof rack!
This is my Buick.
How are we gonna fit in your
mom's Buick?
Easy.
I like that new Buick.
Me too.
I was actually talking about
that Buick.
I knew that.
Did you?
Buick's fresh new lineup is full
of surprises.
Get great deals on our
expectation-shattering lineup.
Pay no interest for 72 months
on most Buick models.