TODAY AND TOMORROW.
>> VIRGINIA GOVERNOR RALPH
NORTHAM CONTINUES TO DEFY CALLS
TO RESIGN AND NOW FORMER
CLASSMATES ARE STANDING BY HIM
AFTER A RACIST PHOTO WAS
UNCOVERED IN HIS OLD YEARBOOK.
>> BAD NEWS FOR WIZARDS FANS,
WHY YOU WON'T SEE JOHN WALL IN
A WIZARDS UNIFORM FOR AT LEAST
ANOTHER YEAR.
>>> AND COOLER TEMPERATURES
TODAY WITH A WET COMMUTE
TONIGHT, MIRI MARSHALL IS
TRACKING THE RAIN AND SHOWERS
FOR YOU.
>> GOOD MORNING EVERYONE.
WE HAVE A YELLOW WEATHER ALERT
BECAUSE OF THOSE SHOWERS THAT
MAY IMPACT YOUR EVENING COMMUTE
TODAY, BUT WHETHER WHIPLASH,
THAT IS THE PHRASE OF THE DAY,
BECAUSE WE HAVE TEMPERS THAT
WILL BE MUCH COOLER THAN WHAT
WE EXPERIENCED YESTERDAY, RIGHT
AT 47 DEGREES IN DC METRO RIGHT
NOW.
TEMPERATURES TODAY 48 TO 53
DEGREES, WE TOPPED OUT AT 74
DEGREES IN DC YESTERDAY FOR A
RECORD HIGH TEMPERATURES
YESTERDAY, BUT TODAY, MUCH
COOLER AIR IS IN PLACE ALONG
WITH SHOWERS AND CLOUDY SKIES.
THE BEST TIME FOR SHOWERS IN
METRO IS AROUND THE 5:00 HOUR
AND HERE IS WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE
ON THE FUTURECAST.
WE CAN SEE SHOWERS ACROSS
MARTINSBURG AND HAGERSTOWN AND
EVEN THROUGH FREDERICK AND
LEESBURG.
BY 5:00 IN THE AFTERNOON, WE
SEE SHOWERS PUSHING INTO THE DC
METRO AREA, SO LIGHT RAIN ALL
THE WAY HOME COULD SLOW YOU
DOWN AND EVEN AT 8:00 TONIGHT,
STILL SOME RAIN LINGERING AND
MODERATE SHOWERS ALONG THE
FREDERICKSBURG AREA.
THESE ARE SOME OF THE REASONS
WE'VE ISSUED THE YELLOW WEATHER
ALERT.
THURSDAY MORNING AT 8 AM,
LIKELY SOME SHOWERS IN THE
MORNING AS YOU ARE HEADING TO
WORK, BUT THURSDAY AFTERNOON,
WE BEGIN TO SEE THIS
TEMPERATURES REMAIN IN THE 50s
AND 60s, AND WE BEGIN TO SEE
THE RAIN CHANCES SORT OF
DISSIPATE A BIT UNTIL FRIDAY
WHEN THE FINAL FEATURE COMES
IN, THE COLD FRONT HEADING OUR
WAY WHICH WILL REALLY BEGIN TO
CHANGE OUR WEATHER PATTERN
ALTOGETHER.
LET'S LOOK AT WHAT WE WILL SEE
OVER THE NEXT 12 HOURS, 47 BY
NOON AND RIGHT AROUND 49 BY
4:00 AND BY 6 PM, RIGHT ON THE
50 DEGREE MARK.
SO YOU CAN SEE THE TEMPERATURE
SLOWLY RISING.
THE NEXT FIVE DAYS LOOK LIKE
THIS, TEMPERATURES IN THE 60s
TODAY AND TOMORROW AND 50s
TODAY, THURSDAY AND FRIDAY, 60s
AGAIN AND LOOK AT THE SHARP
DROP FROM FRIDAY COME 60s THE
39 DEGREES ON SATURDAY, 41
DEGREES BY SUNDAY.
MUCH COLDER AIR IS ON THE WAY.
WE HAVE TO PRESS REWIND ON
YESTERDAY FOR JUST A BIT.
IT IS ALMOST LIKE WE WENT FROM
POLAR VORTEX TO SOLAR VORTEX
WHICH IS NOT A REAL
METEOROLOGICAL TERM, JUST THE
FANCY WAVES AND WE HAD WARM AIR
AROUND HERE.
CHECK THIS OUT, JANUARY 31, 10
DEGREES WAS THE LOW
TEMPERATURE, YESTERDAY, WE
TOPPED OUT AT 74 DEGREES FOR
RECORD WARMTH AND THAT'S A 64
DEGREE DIFFERENCE IN JUST A FEW
DAYS.
>> WHAT A DIFFERENCE A JET
STREAM MAKES.
>> I WILL TAKE THE DAY ON THE
RIGHT.
>> PLEASE, NO MORE POLAR VORTEX
IS.
WE'RE LOOKING AT A CRASH ON
SUSAN PARKWAY.
OUR PHOTOGRAPHER IS ON FORREST
MILL ROAD TRYING TO GET FROM
FOREST HILL TO SUITLAND AND
THAT'S SHUTDOWN RIGHT NOW,
TRYING TO HEAD INBOUND ON SUSAN
PARKWAY HAS BEEN SHUT DOWN AS
WELL, WE'VE HAD A SERIOUS CRASH
DUE TO ACCIDENT RECONSTRUCTION.
OUT ON SUSAN PARKWAY, YOU'LL BE
OKAY THIS IS RIGHT HERE BY
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE AND ROUTE 4
WITH SLIGHT DELAYS JUST BEFORE
YOU GET TO THE BELTWAY.
AND REPORTS OF A NEW CRASH ON I-
66, THE ONLY ONE OUT THERE
BESIDES THE SUITLAND HEADING
EASTBOUND AS YOU GO THROUGH
GAINESVILLE BY ROUTE 29.
>> RAKING FROM OVERNIGHT, FIRE
FORCES FOR PEOPLE OUT OF THEIR
HOMES IN SOUTHEAST DC.
FIREFIGHTERS HAD TO WORK
QUICKLY WHEN THEY ARRIVED IN
THE 1300 BLOCK OF E STREET,
BECAUSE FLAMES WERE COMING OUT
OF THE SECOND STORY WINDOW.
>> THAT WAS THE ONLY ROOM THAT
BURNED.
INVESTIGATORS HAVE BEEN AT THE
SCENE OVERNIGHT TO TRY TO
DETERMINE HOW THE FIRE STARTED
PEOPLE ARE TOLD THE FOUR PEOPLE
DISPLACED ALL FOUND OTHER
PLACES TO SPEND THE NIGHT.
>> IN THE COUNTRY IN THE
MEANTIME IS REACTING TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S SECOND STATE
OF THE UNION ADDRESS THIS
MORNING.
LAST NIGHT, HE CALLED FOR AN
END TO THE POLITICAL STALEMATE
BETWEEN DEMOCRATS AND
REPUBLICANS.
>> MET GREGORY IS LIVE ON
CAPITOL HILL WITH MORE ON THE
STATE OF THE UNION ADDRESS AND
THE DEMOCRATIC RESPONSE.
GOOD MORNING.
>> LAST NIGHT, THE PRESIDENT'S
STATE OF THE UNION ADDRESS WAS
VOLVO CALL FOR UNITY AS WELL AS
A RALLYING CRY FOR HIS
ACCOMPANIMENTS AND GOALS THAT
HE IS SET OUT AND THE DEMOCRATS
HIT BACK RIGHT AFTER WITH A
RESPONSE THAT SAID THAT ALL THE
POLITICAL DISCOURSE COMES FROM
THE PRESIDENT.
>>> HERE ARE THREE THINGS THAT
ARE FROM THE STATE OF THE UNION
AND THE DEMOCRATIC RESPONSE,
NUMBER ONE, PRESIDENT TRUMP
CALLED FOR CONGRESS TO PASS
TIGHTER BORDER SECURITY
MEASURES INCLUDING A CONTINUED
CALL FOR A BORDER WALL BETWEEN
THE U.S. AND MEXICO, NUMBER
TWO, THE PRESIDENT REVEALED HE
WILL HAVE ANOTHER MEETING WITH
NORTH KOREAN PRESIDENT KIM JONG-
UN.
IT WILL TAKE EVERY 27th AND 28
IN VIETNAM AND THE GOAL IS TO
GET AN AGREEMENT FOR
DENUCLEARIZATION.
AND GEORGIA DEMOCRAT AND A
FORMER CANDIDATE FOR GOVERNOR
STACEY ABRAMS DELIVERED THE
REBUTTAL BLAMING THE PRESIDENT
FOR THE DIVISIVENESS OF THE
COUNTRY.
SHE POINTED TO THE 35 DAY
PARTIAL GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN AS
AN EXAMPLE OF HIS REFUSAL TO
COMPROMISE AND HOW THAT HURT
THE COUNTRY.
>> I SHOULD POINT OUT THAT THE
PARTIAL GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN
ENDED WITH A TEMPORARY FUNDING
BILL, AND THAT WILL RUN OUT ON
FEBRUARY 15, THAT MEANS IF AN
AGREEMENT BETWEEN DEMOCRATS AND
THE PRESIDENT ISN'T REACHED BY
THE 15th, WE WILL GO BACK TO
ANOTHER GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN.
>>> ONE OF THE PEOPLE IN THE
HOUSE CHAMBER WAS A WOMAN WE
FIRST MET DURING THE GOVERNMENT
SHUTDOWN.
FAYE SMITH IS A FEDERAL
CONTRACTOR FURLOUGHED DURING
THE SHUTDOWN AND SHE ALONG WITH
THOUSANDS OF OTHERS NEVER GOT
BACK PAY AND YOU STEPPED UP TO
HELP FLOODING A GOFUNDME
ACCOUNT WITH DONATIONS.
SHE ATTENDED AS A GUEST OF
ELEANOR HOLMES NORTON.
>> MR. TRUMP, PLEASE, THIS
POINT, JUST GO AHEAD AND BUILD
YOUR WELCOME YOU SAY YOU WAS
GOING TO BUILD IT, YOU WERE
GOING TO PAY FOR IT, PAY FOR
IT.
MS. NANCY IS NOT GOING TO PAY
FOR THE WALL, STOP HOLDING US
HOSTAGE EVERY TIME YOU GET A
NOTE.
>> WANT TO HEAR FROM YOU, DO
YOU THINK THE STATE OF THE
UNION ADDRESS WILL HELP UNITE
BOTH PARTIES?
YOU CAN VOTE ON OUR WEBSITE,
WUSA9.COM/VOTE OR THE  WUSA9
APP . YOU CAN SAY YES OR NO OR
NEVER HAD A CHANCE.
YOU CAN CHECK ON THE RESULTS TO
THE REST OF THE MORNING AND
MARCELLA ROBERTSON IS LIVE ON
CAPITOL HILL TO VERIFY SOME OF
THE CLAIMS THE PRESIDENT MADE.
>> GOOD MORNING.
DURING THE 82 MINUTE SPEECH
LAST NIGHT, HE TOUCHED ON A LOT
OF THINGS FROM JOBS IN THE
ECONOMY TO NORTH KOREA, AND WE
HAVE RESEARCHERS FACT CHECKING
THE SPEECH LIVE, SO THIS
MORNING I WANT TO TAKE A LOOK
AT THREE SEPARATE CLAIMS AND
WHETHER THEY ARE TRUE OR FALSE.
>> JUST OVER 2 YEARS SINCE THE
ELECTION, WE'VE CREATED 5.3
MILLION NEW JOBS.
>> STARTING WITH JOBS TO GET
ANSWERS, WENT TO THE BUREAU OF
LABOR STATISTICS AND ACCORDING
TO THE BUREAU, ONCE THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION STARTED AFTER
THE JANUARY TO 2017 ELECTION,
THEY ADDED 4.9 MILLION NEW
JOBS, NOT 5.3 MILLION, SO WE
CAN VERIFY THAT CLAIM IS FALSE.
>> IN THE LAST 2 YEARS, THE
BRAVE ICE OFFICERS MADE 266,000
ARRESTS OF CRIMINAL ALIENS
INCLUDING THOSE CHARGED OR
CONVICTED OF NEARLY 100,000
ASSAULTS, 30,000 SEX CRIMES AND
4000 KILLINGS.
>> THIS ONE IS VERIFIED.
>> DATA KEPT BY ICE PACKS UP
THESE NUMBERS.
THE NUMBER OF ARRESTS IS
CORRECT, BUT THERE IS ALSO
IMPORTANT CONTEXT.
THOSE 266,000 ARRESTS, ABOUT
HALF OF THEM WERE FOR ASSAULT
AND SEX CRIMES AND MURDER AND
THE OTHER HALF WERE FOR
NONVIOLENT CRIMES INCLUDING
ILLEGAL ENTRY.
>> OUR HOSTAGES HAVE COME HOME.
NUCLEAR TESTING HAS STOPPED,
AND THERE HAS NOT BEEN A
MISSILE LAUNCH IN MORE THAN 15
MONTHS.
>> THAT IS ALSO VERIFIED.
>> WE HAVEN'T TESTED ANY
BALLISTIC MISSILE SINCE
NOVEMBER 29 OF 2017.
>> AND WE HAVE THE FULL FACT
CHECKING ON WUSA9.COM.
AND WE ALSO HAVE STATEMENTS
THAT WERE FACT CHECKED FROM THE
DEMOCRATIC RESPONSE TO THE
SPEECH LAST NIGHT.
THAT IS THE LATEST OUTSIDE
CAPITOL HILL.
I WILL SEND IT BACK TO YOU.
>> LET'S SEE HOW YOU ARE VOTING
SO FAR IN THE POLL.
WE ASKED IF THE STATE OF THE
UNION WOULD HELP UNITE PARTIES,
SO FAR, 54% OF THE PEOPLE SAID
THEY NEVER HAD A CHANCE AND
CONTINUE TO VOTE AND WEIGH IN
AND WE WILL CHECK ON THE
RESULTS THROUGHOUT THE MORNING,
LET'S GO TO MIRI NOW , I'M
STILL HANGING ONTO YESTERDAY.
>> IT WAS SUCH A GLORIOUS DAY,
RECORD WARMTH YESTERDAY WITH
TEMPERATURES AROUND 74 AND WE
KISS THAT GOODBYE TODAY.?
OH BACK TO COOLER TREND.
HERE ARE THE TOP THREE THINGS
YOU NEED TO KNOW ABOUT THE
WEATHER.
SHOWERS, THAT'S THE KEY WORD
TODAY, WE ARE LOOKING AT RAIN
AFTER 2:00 TODAY AS WE HAVE A
FRONT STALLING ACROSS THE AREA,
AND ALSO THURSDAY AND FRIDAY,
MORE RAIN WILL BE IN THE
FORECAST, COLDER THIS WEEKEND,
THAT'S THE TREND AND NEXT
WEEK'S TREND CALLS FOR COLDER
WEATHER AND RAIN AND SNOW
CHANCES.
WINTER IS GOING TO SHOW UP,
FINALLY.
47 AS YOU STEP OUT IN DC TODAY,
38 AROUND THE MANASSAS AREA AND
HIGH TEMPERATURES TODAY, 40 TO
53 WITH SHOWERS AND CLOUDY
SKIES, WE WILL BE IN THE UPPER
40s TO MID-50s, DC SOUTH AND
AREAS WILL LIKELY GET LOCKED
INTO THE 40s TODAY, FOR THE
NEXT FEW HOURS, THIS IS WHAT IT
LOOKS LIKE IN TERMS OF THE
HOURLY PLANNER, TEMPTRESS OF
THE 46 BY 9 AM AND 46 BY 11 AM,
WE HOLD TIGHT IN THE 40s FOR
THE FIRST HALF OF THE DAY AND
WRITE ABOUT 40 DEGREES BY 1:00
THIS AFTERNOON AND AT THAT
POINT, YOU COULD SEE LIGHT
SHOWERS ESPECIALLY NORTH AND
WEST OF THE DC METRO AREA.
2:30 TODAY, SHOWERS ARE IN
MARTINSBURG AND WINCHESTER IN
HAGERSTOWN AND WE ADVANCE THE
CLOCK TO 6:00 AND THIS IS PRIME
TIME TO HEAD HOME INTO RUSH
HOUR AND WE HAVE LIGHT RAIN
FALLING.
IT'S ONE OF THE REASONS WE
ISSUED THE YELLOW WEATHER ALERT
BECAUSE THERE WILL BE THE LIGHT
RAIN AND THE TIMING OF IT
DURING THE EVENING RUSH.
EVEN TO THE DINNER HOUR AT 8
PM, WE LOOK AT SOME RAIN AND
MODERATE SHOWERS RATHER SPUR
GARY.
TOMORROW MORNING WILL BE THE
BETTER TIME TO SEE SHOWERS OVER
THERE.
WE LOOK AT DIFFERENT
TEMPERATURES IN THE 50s AND 40s
AT 8 AM AND THAT COMMUTE WILL
BE A WET ONE FOR YOU AS WELL.
AND THURSDAY AFTERNOON HAS A
SLIGHT BREAK FROM THE RAIN
BEFORE WE GET THE MAIN COLD
FRONT MAKING ITS WAY IN ON
FRIDAY WHICH WILL KNOCK OUT ALL
OF THIS ABOVE AVERAGE
TEMPERATURES.
SO THE NEXT FIVE DAYS LOOK LIKE
THIS AND WE SEE 50s TODAY RIGHT
ON 65 TOMORROW AND 60s ON
FRIDAY, BUT TEMPERATURE BEGAN
TO DROP AS THE COLD FRONT COMES
IN.
LOOK AT THIS SHARP CHANGE IN
TEMPERATURES FROM 60s FRIDAY
DOWN TO A HIGH OF ONLY 39
DEGREES ON SATURDAY AND SUNDAY
HAS A HIGH OF 41 DEGREES.
WE HAVE SOME WINTER WEATHER IN
THE FORECAST AND IT LOOKS LIKE
MONDAY HAS A CHANCE FOR RAIN
AND SNOW IN THE MORNING.
ALL RAIN IN THE AFTERNOON.
WE WILL SEE WHAT THIS LOOKS
LIKE COMING UP IN THE NEXT
UPDATE.
>> I DISAGREE, THE REAL WINTER
CAN SIT BACK DOWN AND THE FAKE
SPRING CAN STAND BACK UP.
>>> WE HAVE A COUPLE ACCIDENTS
ALREADY, WE HAVE A LIVE SHOT
RIGHT NOW ON SUITLAND PARKWAY
AT FOREST HILL ROAD, THIS WHITE
TRUCK HAS BEEN PUT UP ON THE
TOW TRUCK AND THEY ARE STILL
TRYING TO PUSH THAT BACK A
LITTLE BIT HERE TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT WHAT'S GOING ON IN
THE ACCIDENT AND HOW MANY, IT
SOUNDS LIKE TO BE CLOSE, HOW
MANY BLOOD ENTRIES BECAUSE THEY
ARE DOING ACCIDENT
RECONSTRUCTION WHICH MEANS IT
HAS BEEN A SERIOUS CRASH.
ALL LANES TRYING TO GO INBOUND
ON SUITLAND PARKWAY HAVE BEEN
CLOSED.
OUTBOUND LANES ARE STILL OPEN
AND THE AREA FROM FORTH THE
ROAD TO TRY TO GET ONTO SUSAN
PARKWAY HAS BEEN CLOSED AS WELL
AND DELAYS ON PENNSYLVANIA
AVENUE OR ROUTE 4 BEFORE YOU
GET TO THE BELTWAY WHERE ALL OF
THIS IS GOING ON AND WE HAVE AN
ACCIDENT ON I-66, NO DELAYS,
BUT THIS ONE IS OUT IN
GAINESVILLE.
>>> A LOCAL MAN TALKS ABOUT HIS
FIGHT TO SURVIVE A HEART
ATTACK.
>>> HELLO PROGRAM IN THE DMV
HELPED THEM PAY THE MEDICAL
BILLS TOTALING ALMOST $90,000.
This is not a bed.
>> AND A 2-YEAR-OLD BOY
It's a revolution in sleep.
The Sleep Number 360
smart bed is on sale now,
from $899, during the
Ultimate Sleep Number Event.
It senses your movement,
and automatically adjusts
to keep you both comfortable.
It even helps with this.
So you wake up ready to
hit the ground running.
Only at a Sleep Number store.
Save 50% on the Sleep Number 360
Limited Edition smart bed.
Plus, 24-month financing
on all smart beds.
Only for a limited time.
Sleep Number.
Proven, quality sleep.
♪
It hasn't always
been easy, has it?
♪
There have been days
when you doubted yourself.
♪
And days when you
were ready to quit.
♪
But you didn't.
Because you had the courage to
venture into something powerful.
Education.
If I leave you with just
three words of advice:
never...stop...growing.
[cheering]
>>> GOOD MORNING AND WELCOME
BACK TO WAKE UP WASHINGTON,
IT'S FIVE DECK 14 ON YOUR
WEDNESDAY, LET'S GET THE THREE
THINGS YOU MAY WANT TO KNOW
BEFORE YOU GO OUT THE DOOR, AND
THERE'S AN ARIZONA CHART WITH
SEXUALLY ASSAULTING AN
INCAPACITATED WOMAN HAS PLED
NOT GUILTY.
NATHAN SUTHERLAND IS CHARGED
WITH RAPING A WOMAN  IN THE
FACILITY.
HE WAS ARRESTED AFTER HIS DNA
MATCHED A BLOOD SAMPLE FROM THE
SUN.
HE REMAINS IN JAIL ON HALF $1
MILLION BOND.
>>> JURY DELIBERATIONS CONTINUE
FOR JOAQUIN EL CHAPO GUZMAN,
THEY SAY HE IS RESPONSIBLE FOR
AT LEAST 200 TONS OF COCAINE IN
THE U.S. HE PLED NOT GUILTY TO
17 CATS WHICH INCLUDED DRUG
TRAFFICKING AND MONEY
LAUNDERING CHARGES.
IF CONVICTED, HE FACES THE
POSSIBILITY OF LIFE IN PRISON.
>>> AND POPE FRANCIS WRAPPED UP
HIS TRIP TO THE MIDDLE EAST.
1 MILLION PEOPLE CAME OUT TO
SEE THE FIRST MASS IN THE
UNITED ARAB EMIRATES.
HE TALKED ABOUT PEAS AND
REJECTING WAR AND HE MADE
HEADLINES ACKNOWLEDGING A
SCANDAL OF PRIESTS AND BISHOPS
ABUSING NUNS.
HE SAID THEY NEED TO DO MORE TO
COMBAT THE PROBLEM.
>>> FIVE DECK 15, PUTTING YOUR
HEALTH FIRST AS PART OF THE
MONTH-LONG HEALTH MATTERS
SERIES THAT RAISES AWARENESS
ABOUT THE IMPORTANCE OF KNOWING
YOUR BODY.
FEBRUARY IS AMERICAN HEART
MONTH, McKEE AND TURNER SAT
DOWN WITH A PERSON WHO IS
THANKFUL TO BE ALIVE.
>> YOU HAVE THIS EXPERIENCE A
MONTH BEFORE YOUR BIRTHDAY AND
IT IS A REAL WAKE-UP CALL.
>> Reporter: CHRISTOPHER ROBIN
WAS JUST A FEW WEEKS SHY OF HIS
51st BIRTHDAY.
>> RIGHT AROUND MIDNIGHT,
STARTED AT THIS INCREDIBLE
SENSATION IN MY ARMS AND IN MY
CHEST AS IF SOMEONE WERE TAKING
THEIR NAILS AND JUST RAKING
THROUGH MY ARM, INSIDE, AND
THERE WAS NOTHING I COULD DO
ABOUT IT.
>> Reporter: HE FELT A SIMILAR
FEELING BEFORE, BUT THIS TIME
WAS DIFFERENT, THIS WAS SCARY,
HE KNEW SOMETHING WAS WRONG.
>> IT WAS WORKING ITS WAY DOWN
BOTH BICEPS AND INTO MY
FOREARMS AND THAT'S WHEN I KNEW
I WAS PRETTY MUCH IN TROUBLE.
I CAN ONLY DESCRIBE IT AS WHAT
I CALL THE REAPER'S EMBRACE.
IT WAS PRETTY TERRIFYING.
AND I SAID, GOD, I'M NOT READY
TO CHECK OUT, BUT I CAN'T CHECK
IN BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE
HEALTHCARE.
>> BETWEEN JOBS AND WORRIED
ABOUT EXPENSES, HE WAS TRYING
TO SURVIVE.
HE WAS RUSHED TO RESTON MEDICAL
CENTER WHERE HE LEARNED ABOUT
BLOCKAGES IN AN ARTERY AND
STENTS WERE INSERTED TO HELP
BLOOD FLOW.
>> IF YOU HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY
TO GET ROUTINE CHECKUPS AND
IT'S COVERED, GO EVERY SIX
MONTHS, ESPECIALLY AFTER THE
AGE OF 40, BECAUSE THE
LIKELIHOOD OF YOU HAVING A
SITUATION LIKE I HAD IS GOING
TO BE, IT'S GOING TO BE GREATER
AND GREATER.
>> THAT WAS AN UNBELIEVABLE
STORY.
WHEN HE HAD HEALTHCARE, HE GOT
RID OF IT AND HE DIDN'T GET
CHECKUPS, NOW HE IS FIGHTING
FOR IT AFTER LOSING A BUSINESS
HE OWNED FOR 30 YEARS.
>> HIS MEDICAL BILLS TOTALED
ALMOST $90,000, BUT A CHARITY
PROGRAM AT RESTON HOSPITAL
CENTER WAIVED SOME OF THE
BILLS.
AND THAT IS WHY THIS THURSDAY
IS SO IMPORTANT.
>> THAT IS TOMORROW.
WE HIGHLIGHT THE IMPORTANCE OF
REGULAR CHECKUPS.
KEEP THIS IN MIND, WE DO THAT
BY HOLDING A FREE HEALTH EXPO
AT THE YMCA IN RESTON, WE CALL
IT IMPACT HEALTH MATTERS, WE
OFFER BLOOD PRESSURE AND BMI
AND DIABETES EDUCATION AND CPR
AND ALL OF THE SCREENINGS ARE
FREE.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS SIGN UP
FOR THEM AND THERE WILL BE TWO
SESSIONS, 70 AND THROUGH NOON
AND 2 PM THROUGH 7:00.
THAT'S THE SECOND ONE, JUST GO
TO OUR WEBSITE,
WUSA9.COM/HEALTH MATTERS  FOR
MORE.
>>> THE TIME IS 5:18 ON THIS
WEDNESDAY, WHAT ARE WE LOOKING
AT?
>> WE HAVE A WARM AND COLD
FRONT STALLING AROUND THE AREA.
THIS RED LINE REPRESENTS THE
WARM FRONT AND THE BLUE ONE IS
THE COLD FRONT, THAT IS
STRADDLED ACROSS BASICALLY THE
MARYLAND AND PENNSYLVANIA
BORDER.
WE HAVE THE STALLED FRONT WITH
SHOWERS AND COOLER TEMPERATURES
ESPECIALLY WITH A LITTLE BIT
MORE CLOUD COVER TODAY.
OUTSIDE THE DOOR, 47 IN DC AND
46 IN THE FREDERICKSBURG AREA.
NOTICEABLY COOLER TODAY BUT
STILL ABOVE AVERAGE, 43 DEGREES
IS THE TEMPERATURE RANGE,
SHOWERS OUT THERE UNDER CLOUDY
SKIES AND THE BEST TIME FOR
SHOWERS WILL BE AFTER 3:00
TODAY IN THE DC METRO AREA IN
AREAS NORTH AND WEST OF DC AND
ANYTIME AFTER 20 CLOCK IS FAIR
GAME.
46 BY 10 AM AND 48 BY 2:00 THIS
AFTERNOON AND RIGHT AROUND 50
BY 6 PM WITH RAIN FALLING OUT
THERE.
WE SEE THE BETTER CHANCE FOR
RAIN THIS AFTERNOON, THAT'S ONE
OF THE REASONS WHY TOPPER SHUTT
ISSUED THE YELLOW WEATHER
ALERT.
HE KNOWS WHEN YOU GET THE
RAINDROPS MIXING IN WITH
EVENING RUSH, IT SLOWS THINGS
DOWN . HERE ARE THREE THINGS TO
KNOW, MOST AREAS WILL SEE
SHOWERS AFTER 2:00 TODAY AND WE
HAVE SHOWERS THURSDAY AND
FRIDAY AS WELL.
SHOWERS, THIS WEEKEND GETS
COLDER, TEMPERATURES FALLING
BACK TO 30s AND 40s FOR DAYTIME
HIGHS AND NEXT WEEK HAS WINTER
COMING BACK.
AND WE HAVEN'T SEEN WINTER IN A
WHILE AFTER RECORD WARM
TEMPERATURES YESTERDAY TOPPING
OUT AT 74.
IT WAS SO GREAT.
NONE OF THAT TODAY.
WE WILL BE MUCH COOLER OUT
THERE.
MAYBE A JACKET AND UMBRELLA
KEEPS THE COMPANY.
WINCHESTER AND HAGERSTOWN AND
WINCHESTER TODAY AROUND 2:00
HAS RAIN FALLING AND AT 6:00,
WE SEE RAIN AROUND THE DC METRO
AREA WITH TEMPERATURES HOLDING
OFF IN THE 50s AT THIS POINT
AND EVEN IN THE DINNER HOUR, WE
ARE LOOKING AT RAIN.
LET'S LOOK AT THE BEST TIME TO
SEE IT, IN THE MORNING
SOMEWHERE AROUND 7:00 OR 8:00
AND WE HAVE LIGHT RAN ACROSS DC
METRO AND THROUGHOUT THE DAY IN
THE AFTERNOON, A LITTLE BIT OF
A BREAK IN THE RAIN BEFORE WE
GET THE MAIN FRONT MAKING ITS
WAY IN BY FRIDAY.
FRIDAY STARTS OFF WITH
TEMPERATURES IN THE 60s AND
TEMPERATURES DROP IN THE
AFTERNOON WITH A COLD FRONT
COMING IN.
AHEAD OF THE FRONT,
TEMPERATURES IN THE 60s BEHIND
THAT WITH 20s AND TEENS FOR THE
DAYTIME HIGHS AS WE LOOK AT THE
MIDWEST.
LOOK AT TEMPERATURES IN THE
UPPER 30s ON SATURDAY BEHIND
THE FRONT.
A PRETTY STRONG COLD FRONT
COMING IN, 41 DEGREES ON SUNDAY
BEHIND THE COLD FRONT WITH
WINTER WEATHER MAKING ITS WAY
BACK AS I ELUDED TO NEXT WEEK.
COLDER AIR IN PLACE AND
DISTURBANCES PASSING BY.
THAT WILL BE THE SETUP.
MONDAY MORNING STARTS WITH A
RAIN AND SNOW MIX POSSIBLE AND
THEN IT CHANGES OVER TO ALL
RAIN BY LATE MONDAY MORNING
INTO MONDAY AFTERNOON.
LET ME SAY THIS ABOUT THE
TRENDS WITH THE MODELS.
LOOK AT THE GFS FIRST AND IT
HAS BEEN SHIFTING TO RAIN AND
SNOW A LITTLE BIT FURTHER
NORTH, THAT'S THE TREND I'VE
SEEN CHANGE WITHIN THE LAST DAY
OR TWO.
WE WILL STILL GET SOME RAIN AND
SNOW AROUND 5 AM MONDAY, BUT IT
LOOKS LIKE A LOT OF AREAS
ESPECIALLY AROUND
FREDERICKSBURG AND CULPEPER AND
MANASSAS STAYS IN AN ALL RAIN
SITUATION.
AND THEN TUESDAY INTO WEDNESDAY
HAS ANOTHER CHANCE FOR RAIN AND
SNOW AND PERHAPS BY WEDNESDAY,
ALL SNOW, BUT THEN WE ARE STILL
SEVERAL DAYS OUT, THIS IS NOT A
LOCK AND LOAD SITUATION, THERE
WILL BE STILL SOME TIME TO FINE-
TUNE IT, BUT JUST KEEP IN MIND,
NEXT WEEK, IT WILL GET MESSY
AGAIN WITH THE RAIN AND SNOW
MAKING ITS WAY BACK INTO THE
FORECAST.
HERE IS THE 70, 53 TODAY, 65
DEGREES THURSDAY AND SICK
BEFORE WITH FALLING
TEMPERATURES AND 41 SUNDAY AND
SUNDAY NIGHT, AS EARLY AS
SUNDAY NIGHT, YOU SEE THE
SHOWERS AND EVEN SOME SNOW
MIXING IN FOR THE NORTHERN
SUBURBS, BUT REALLY BY MONDAY
AND TUESDAY, YOU SEE THE MIX
ONCE AGAIN.
>> AT LEAST WE HAD THIS BRIEF
BREAK.
WE'VE BEEN ENJOYING IT.
>> WE HAVE A CLOSURE ON SUSAN
PARKWAY AS HE TRIED TO HEAD
INBOUND.
OUTBOUND IS OKAY, BUT THE LAST
TIME I SHOWED YOU THIS LIVE
SHOT FROM OUR PHOTOGRAPHER ON
THE SCENE, WE SAW A WHITE TOE
TRUCK, A WHITE PICKUP TRUCK
BEING TOWED AWAY.
HE SAYS HE'S SEEN ANOTHER CAR
SOMEWHERE IN THE DISTANCE ALSO
BEING PUT UP ON A TOW TRUCK.
IT SEEMS LIKE THERE WERE TWO
VEHICLES INVOLVED, PRETTY
SERIOUS INJURIES AND WE ARE
STILL DOING ACCIDENT
RECONSTRUCTION AND YOU CAN SEE
IT WITH A HEAVY POLICE PRESENCE
AND THERE'S THE WHITE TOE TRUCK
RIGHT THERE, IT HASN'T LEFT THE
SCENE YET, BUT ALL INBOUND
LANES ON SUSAN PARKWAY, AT
FORCEFUL ROAD
I'm off to college.
I'm worried about my parents'
retirement.
Don't worry.
Voya helps them to and through
retirement...
dealing with today's
expenses...
while helping plan, invest and
protect for the future.
So they'll be okay?
I think they'll be fine.
Voya. Helping you to and
through retirement.
>>> WELCOME BACK AND, ANIMAL
LOVERS IN PENNSYLVANIA HAVE
CREATED AN APP THAT THEY ARE
CALLING TENDER FOR DOGS.
IT IS CALLED PET FEATURES
PROFILES OF DOGS AVAILABLE FOR
ADOPTION IN LOCAL SHELTERS.
USERS CAN SCROLL THROUGH WITH
MORE INFORMATION ABOUT THE DOG
AND SWIPE RIGHT IF THEY ARE
INTERESTED.
>> SO IF YOU SWIPE LEFT, THE
NEXT DOG APPEARS, THE PLAN IS
TO EVENTUALLY INCLUDE CATS AND
OTHER ANIMALS AS WELL.
>> I LIKE THE IDEA, BECAUSE YOU
CAN FIND COMPANIONSHIP BY
READING UP ON THE DOGS, LITTLE
MORE INTIMATE EXPERIENCE, BUT I
FEEL LIKE IT'S A LITTLE BIT ONE-
SIDED, WHAT IF THE DOG DOESN'T
LIKE YOU?
>> AT LEAST AT THE SHELTER,
THEY CAN SMITE, THEY CAN READ
THEIR BODY LANGUAGE AND DOGS
ARE REALLY SMART, SO THEY CAN
BARK OR GRAVEL AT YOU.
>> THE BRANDING AS TENDER FOR
DOGS, IT'S PROBABLY NOT THE BEST
, BECAUSE WE KNOW WHAT TENDER
IS ACTUALLY FOR.
>> I THINK THAT'S MORE OF A
SOCIAL UNDERSTANDING.
>> NEXT UP, CHILD IN ALABAMA
WENT TO GREAT LENGTHS TO TRY TO
GET A TOY TO A 2-YEAR-OLD AND
IT GOT A LITTLE TOO SERIOUS IN
A RESTAURANT AND GOT STUCK
INSIDE ONE OF THOSE CLAW
MACHINES WE TRY TO GRAB A
PRIZE.
>> I WILL NEVER UNDERSTAND HOW
THIS HAPPENS.
FORTUNATELY, THE CHILD WAS NOT
HURT.
THAT'S GOOD NEWS, BUT GETTING
HIM OUT CERTAINLY WAS NOT EASY.
NO ONE AT THE RESTAURANT EVEN
HAD A KEY TO OPEN THE MACHINE,
SO FIREFIGHTERS HAD TO STEP IN
AND TAKE IT APART AND RESCUE
HIM.
THE LITTLE GUY CLIMBED UP IN
THERE.
>> THE PROPENSITY FOR THIS TO
HAPPEN IS HIGHER IF YOU HAVE
MORE KIDS, BECAUSE YOU ARE MORE
LIKELY, LIKE HE HAS BROTHERS
AND SISTERS, SO IT'S EASIER TO
LOSE ONE IN THE SHUFFLE IF YOU
ARE PARENTING 2 TO 3 TO 4 KIDS
OR SO AS OPPOSED TO JUST NO
ONE.
IF YOU JUST HAVE THE ONE, THEN
YOU HAVE LITTLE TO NO EXCUSE
LET THAT HAPPEN.
>> BUT HE IS FINE.
>> I'M SO GLAD HE IS OKAY.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS THE
STATE OF THE UNION IS STRONG WE
WILL HAVE MORE ON HIS SPEECH
INCLUDING NEW PLANS TO MEET
WITH KIM JONG UN.
>> AND WE WILL
When was the last time
you felt...
Free.
It's time to uncover
that feeling again.
With the compassion and
strength of a name...
Most accepted by top doctors
and specialists.
And the power of a card...
that opens doors in
all fifty states.
Giving you the freedom to love
to dream to dance
Like no one is watching.
CareFirst
Blue Cross Blue Shield.
Live fearless.
>>> [ MUSIC ] 5:30, WELCOME
BACK TO WAKE UP WASHINGTON.
THE BIG WEATHER STORY TODAY,
BIG SWING AT TEMPERATURES AND
WE HAVE SOME SHOWERS MARCHING
IN THIS AFTERNOON.
IT IS 47 AS YOU STEP OUT IN DC
METRO AND WE TOPPED OUT AROUND
THE 53 DEGREE MARK TODAY AND WE
HAD A HIGH OF 74 IN DC, SO LET
THESE COOLER TEMPERATURES SINK
IN FOR A MOMENT BEFORE YOU STEP
OUTSIDE.
LOOKING AT SHOWERS AND THE BEST
TIME TO SEE THE SHOWERS IN
METRO DC WILL BE RIGHT AROUND
THE 5:00 OUR AND WE START TO
SEE THEM IN THE NORTH AND
WESTERN SUBURBS ANYTIME AFTER 2
PM.
THIS IS WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE BY
THE HOUR, 46 BY 10 AM, 48 BY
2:00 AND WRITER 50 BY 6 PM WITH
SHOWERS FALLING ACROSS THE
AREA.
ON FUTURECAST HIM HE COULD SEE
BY 2:00, 2:30, THE
FREDERICKSBURG AND LEESBURG
AREA AND 6:00 HAS LIGHTNING.
THAT'S ONE OF THE REASONS
TOPPER ISSUED A YELLOW WEATHER
LIVE BECAUSE OF THE TIMING OF
ALL THIS.
8:00 IS THE DINNER HOURS, WE
STILL HAVE LIGHT TO MODERATE
SHOWERS TO THE FREDERICKSBURG
AREA FALLING ACROSS DC METRO.
DURING THE MORNING COMMUTE, THE
EVENING COMMUTE TOMORROW LOOKS
DRIER.
THERE WILL BE A LAG.
CAN WE GET A BREAK TOMORROW
AFTERNOON BUT TEMPERATURES GET
BACK TO THE 60s ONCE AGAIN.
THIS IS A ROLLER COASTER RIDE
WHEN IT COMES TO TEMPERATURES.
JUST BUCKLE UP AND GET READY.
THE NEXT FEW DAYS LOOK LIKE
THIS, 50s TODAY AND MID-
SIXTIES, RIGHT AROUND 65 ON
THURSDAY AND 64 ON FRIDAY AND A
SHARP DROP IN TEMPERATURES.
A STRONG COLD FRONT COMES IN
TAKING US FROM 64 ON FRIDAY
DOWN TO A HIGH OF JUST 39
DEGREES BY SATURDAY AND SUNDAY
HAS A HIGH OF 41 DEGREES.
AND DO NOT SCRATCH OUT WINTER
JUST YET, WINTER WEATHER IS
RETURNING, ESPECIALLY COMING UP
NEXT WEEK AND WE LOOK AT A
CHANCE FOR RAIN AND SNOW FOR
BRIEF MOMENT MONDAY MORNING,
AND THEN ALL RAIN BY MONDAY
AFTERNOON.
COMING UP IN THE NEXT UPDATE,
WE SHOW YOU WHAT THIS LOOKS
LIKE BY THE HOUR.
>>> GOOD NEWS, JUST BEFORE THE
BIG RUSH HOUR KICKS IN, THE
PARKWAY OPENS BACKUP.
A LIVE SHOT HERE FROM THE EXACT
SAME AREA AS LAST TIME, THE
WHITE PICKUP TRUCK IS GONE AND
THE TOW TRUCKS ARE GONE AND THE
INBOUND LANES ARE OPENING UP.
WE'VE HAD A CLOSURE SO FAR
INBOUND AND WE SHOULD GET
BETTER.
THERE ARE SLIGHT DELAYS ON
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE JUST BEFORE
THE BELTWAY.
TOP SIDE OF THE BELTWAY, OUTER
LOOP LOOKS LIKE AN ACCIDENT AND
WE HAVE TWO PROBLEMS ON 266.
EASTBOUND THROUGH GAINESVILLE
BY 129, THE OTHER ACCIDENT IS
WESTBOUND A I-66 GOING AWAY
FROM DC, AND IT'S OUT OF THE
LANES AS WELL.
>> IT PROBABLY WON'T HAVE A BIG
IMPACT FOR MOST COMMUTERS.
>> IT HAS BEEN FIVE DAYS SINCE
WE LEARNED ABOUT THE SHOCKING
AND RACIST PHOTO IN THE 1984
YEARBOOK OF RALPH NORTHAM, AND
ALTHOUGH HE HASN'T BEEN IN
PUBLIC FOR DAYS, HE SAYS HE
WILL NOT RESIGN.
>> HE GOT THE SUPPORT FROM HIS
OLD CLASSMATES.
>> IT'S DEFINITELY BEEN A VERY
CHAOTIC WEEK.
BUT NOW HE'S GETTING SUPPORT
FROM NINE STUDENTS, ALL THAT
HAVE COME FORWARD DEFENDING
GOVERNOR NORTHAM.
THEY WERE CLASSMATES OF HIS AT
THE EASTERN VIRGINIA MEDICAL
SCHOOL.
SO LET'S START RIGHT THERE AND
TAKE A LOOK AT EXACTLY WHAT
THEY WROTE.
>>> THE STATEMENT WAS WE FULLY
BELIEVE GOVERNOR RALPH NORTHAM
IS NEITHER OF THE PEOPLE IN THE
REPUBLIC COSTUMES.
WE ATTENDED CLASSES AND
SOCIALIZED WITH HIM AND KNEW
HIM VERY WELL, BUT THINGS
REMAINED PRETTY ROCKY FOR THE
EMBATTLED GOVERNOR.
HE HAS BEEN HELD UP IN THE
EXECUTIVE MANSION AND CALENDAR
NOT UPDATED FOR DAYS AND MANY
PUBLIC EVENTS HAVE BEEN
CANCELED, BUT BEHIND CLOSED
DOORS, HE IS TRYING TO GOVERNOR
AND HE SIGNED OFF ON GIVING
MILLIONS AND HE SIGNED OFF ON
CONDOLENCES FOR A STATE TROOPER
KILLED IN THE LINE OF DUTY AND
THE NEW YORK TIMES SAYS HE
PLANS TO HIRE A PRIVATE
INVESTIGATOR TO LOOK INTO THE
PICTURE AND FIND OUT HOW IT GOT
IN THE YEARBOOK.
MANY LAWMAKERS FROM DIFFERENT
PARTIES EVEN TRADITIONAL ALLIES
ARE CALLING FOR HIS
RESIGNATION.
>> I CAN'T TELL YOU WHY HE
RESIGNED, BUT DOES
>> WE'VE CALLED FOR THE
RESIGNATION.
>> ADDING TO THE CRISIS, SEXUAL
ASSAULT ALLEGATIONS DATING BACK
TO 2004 AGAINST HIS LIEUTENANT
GOVERNOR, JUSTIN FAIRFAX WHO
WOULD TAKE OVER IN A NORTHAM
RESIGNATION OFFERED A STRONG
DENIAL.
>> THE ALLEGATION VAPORIZED FOR
A YEAR AND RESURFACED ON THE
EVE OF MY POTENTIAL ELEVATION
GIVEN THE CURRENT SITUATION,
IT'S COMPLETELY POLITICAL AND
IS A SMEAR.
>> WE ARE LEARNING THAT THE
ACCUSER OF JUSTIN FAIRFAX HAS
HIRED A LAWYER AND
INTERESTINGLY ENOUGH, IT'S THE
SAME LEGAL TEAM THAT
REPRESENTED CHRISTINE BLASEY
FORD.
WHETHER RALPH NORTHAM WILL
RESIGN IS ANYONE'S GUESS.
>>> REACTION IS POURING IN
FOLLOWING THE SECOND STATE OF
THE UNION ADDRESS.
WE ASK, DO YOU THINK THE STATE
OF THE UNION ADDRESS WILL HELP
UNITE BOTH PARTIES?
YOU CAN VOTE ON OUR WEBSITE OR
THE WUSA9 APP.
ONE OF THE BIGGEST TAKEAWAYS
WAS THE PLAN TO MEET WITH KIM
JONG-UN.
>> MUCH WORK REMAINS TO BE
DONE, BUT MY RELATIONSHIP WITH
KIM JONG-UN IS A GOOD ONE.
CHAIRMAN KIM AND I WILL MEET
AGAIN ON FEBRUARY 27 AND 28th
IN VIETNAM.
>> THE PRESIDENT TALKED ABOUT
THE NEED FOR A WALL ALONG THE
SOUTHERN BORDER.
>> IN THE PAST, MOST OF THE
PEOPLE IN THIS ROOM VOTED FOR
AWOL.
BUT THE PROPER WALL NEVER GOT
BUILT.
I WILL GET IT BUILT.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP TO DECLARE
NATIONAL EMERGENCY TO BUILD THE
WALL, LAWMAKERS HAVE JUST NINE
DAYS TO REACH A DEAL ON BORDER
SECURITY BEFORE ANOTHER PARTIAL
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN GOES INTO
EFFECT.
>>> STACEY ABRAMS WHO LOST THE
RACE FOR GEORGIA GOVERNOR LAST
YEAR GAVE THE OFFICIAL
DEMOCRATIC RESPONSE LAST NIGHT
AND BLAME THE GOVERNMENT
SHUTDOWN ON THE GOVERNMENT.
COME UP ON THE PRESIDENT.
>> IT WAS A STUNT ENGINEERED BY
THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES, ONE THAT DEFIED EVERY
TENET OF FAIRNESS AND ABANDON
NOT JUST OUR PEOPLE, BUT OUR
VALUES.
>> SHE WENT ON TO SAY ALTHOUGH
SHE DISAGREES WITH THE
PRESIDENT, SHE DOESN'T WANT TO
SEE HIM FAIL.
>> WE ARE SEEING HOW YOU ARE
VOTING, DO YOU THINK THE STATE
OF THE UNION WILL HELP UNITE
BOTH PARTIES.
>> YOU HAVE 69% OF USING IT
NEVER HAD A CHANCE.
CONTINUE TO VOTE AND WEIGH IN
AND WE CHECK ON THE RESULTS
THROUGHOUT THE MORNING.
>>> THINGS GO FROM BAD TO MUCH
WORSE WHEN IT COMES TO THE
WIZARDS AND JOHN WALL.
>> WILL TELL YOU WHY YOU WON'T
SEE THE STAR POINT GUARD IN A
WIZARDS UNIF
Ways to lose
stubborn belly fat:
Metal Vibration Therapy.
( ♪♪ )
(Glass breaking)
(Gasp)
Not cool.
Freezing away fat cells
with CoolSculpting?
Now that's cool!
CoolSculpting safely
freezes and removes fat cells
with little or no downtime
and no surgery.
Results and patient
experience may vary.
Some common side
effects include
temporary numbness,
discomfort, and swelling.
Ask your doctor
if CoolSculpting
is right for you and visit
CoolSculpting.com today
for your chance
to win a free treatment.
(Music blaring)
People aren't talking
about how much
for your chance
to win a free treatment.
money they saved
buying Giant Brand Chicken.
They're not talking
about how our
pre-chopped veggies are
perfect time-savers.
They're also not talking
about our unique assortment
of over 1,300 Nature's
Promise Items.
Or our fresh grab and
go salads and sandwiches.
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Oh hello, that
looks so good.
At Giant, it's the little
things that make
meal time easy,
so you have more time with
the people you love.
>>> 5:40 NOW, A YELLOW WEATHER
ALERT, BECAUSE WE HAVE COOLER
AIR AND WE ALSO HAVE SOME
SHOWERS IN THE FORECAST THIS
AFTERNOON.
47 DEGREES IN DC AND FOR KIDS
WAITING AT THE BUS STOP, YOU
MAY FIND TEMPERATURES IN THE
30s AND 40s THROUGHOUT THE
MORNING.
YOU WILL SEE 46 DEGREES BY 6 AM
AND 46 BY 9:00 AND 47 AT NOON
AND AS KIDS GO HOME, LOOK FOR
SHOWERS AND TEMPERATURES IN THE
UPPER 40s ESPECIALLY IN UPPER
SUBURBS AND DC APPROACHES THE
50 DEGREE MARK LATER THIS
AFTERNOON.
WE HAVE A BIG DIFFERENCE FROM
YESTERDAY WITH 70s, 48 TO MID-
50s TODAY.
SHOWERS AND CLOUDY AND THE BEST
TIME FOR SHOWERS IS AROUND 5:00.
NORTHERN AND WESTERN SUBURBS
SEE THEM EARLIER, AT 230 TODAY,
49 IN MARTINSBURG AND FREDERICK
AROUND 50 AT 2:30 AND YOU SEE
LIGHT SHOWERS FALLING.
6:00 THIS EVENING HAS REIGNED
OVER DC METRO AND ONE OF THE
REASONS WE HAVE THE YELLOW
WEATHER ALERT IS BECAUSE OF THE
TIMING OF THIS RAIN.
8:00 TONIGHT, DINNERTIME STILL
HAS SHOWERS OUT THERE AND IT'S
NOT UNTIL LATER TONIGHT THAT WE
HAVE A BRIEF BREAK IN THE RAIN
IN TOMORROW MORNING, THE
COMMUTE WILL LIKELY BE WET AS
WELL.
AS LONG AS WE HAVE THE FRONT
STALLING ACROSS THE AREA, THAT
WILL GIVE US THE RAIN CHANCE
AND WE HAVE THE WINDSHIELD
WIPERS AT 8:00 IN THE MORNING
AND A LITTLE BREAK IN THE
AFTERNOON AS WE GET READY FOR
THE MAIN COLD FRONT TO COME
THROUGH FRIDAY WITH THE FINAL
PUSH OF RAIN.
THIS IS A ROLLER COASTER RIDE
OF WEATHER.
70s YESTERDAY, 50s TODAY, 65 ON
THURSDAY WITH SHOWERS AND 64 ON
FRIDAY AND WATCH TEMPERATURES
DROPPED AT 39 FOR THE HIGH ON
SATURDAY.
THIS IS A BIG TEMPERATURE
DIFFERENCE.
MELISSA PUT SOLAR VORTEX VERSUS
A POLAR VORTEX.
[ LAUGHTER ] THERE IS NO SUCH
THING AS A SOLAR VORTEX.
BUT 10 DEGREES WAS A LOW
TEMPERATURE ON JANUARY 31.
YESTERDAY, WE SOARED UP TO 34.
64 DEGREE DIFFERENCE IN THE
SPAN OF JUST A FEW DAYS.
SO AGAIN, MONDAY, WE LOOK AT
THE CHANCE FOR RAIN AND SNOW
AND EARLY MONDAY MORNING AT 5
AM, WE CAN SEE THE RAIN MAKING
ITS WAY INTO THE AREA AND
MONDAY AFTERNOON, WE BEGIN THE
TRANSITION TO ALL RAIN ACROSS
METRO DC AND THERE IS SLIGHTLY
WARMER AIR AND TUESDAY HAS A
CHANCE FOR RAIN AND SNOW.
>>> THE MONDAY MORNING DRIVE
MAY NOT BE GREAT, SNOW AND
RAIN, WE WILL BE TRACKING IT
FOR YOU AND LETTING YOU KNOW
ABOUT DELAYS.
WE ARE OPEN ON SUITLAND PARKWAY
GOING INBOUND.
THERE WAS A SERIOUS CRASH
OVERNIGHT AND RECONSTRUCTION,
BUT THEY'VE OPENED THE LANES.
SOUTHBOUND HAS A PROBLEM BY
ROUTE 7 AND ON THE OUTER LOOP
OF THE BELTWAY, WE HAVE AN
ACCIDENT REPORTED BY NEW
HAMPSHIRE AVENUE AND ISSUES ON
I-66, EASTBOUND IN GAINESVILLE
IS THE GREATER CONCERN.
THE OTHER ONE IS I-66 W. BOUND
SO THIS SHOULD HAVE AN IMPACT.
>>> HAVE YOU EVER SENT A
MESSAGE
>>> WELCOME BACK IN EVERYBODY,
IT IS 5:46.
PEOPLE CONCERNED ABOUT NATURAL
GAS LEAKS IN DC ARE INVITED TO
SHARE EXPERIENCES WITH THE
PUBLIC SERVICE COMMISSION.
THEY ARE HOLDING THE REGULAR
MEETING AT 2 PM TODAY, BUT
COMMUNITY MEMBERS ARE INVITED
TO ASK OFFICIALS QUESTIONS
ABOUT SAFETY PRACTICES AND
PROCEDURES AMONGST OTHER
THINGS.
THEY ARE ACCEPTING WRITTEN
COMMENTS FOR NEXT WEEK.
EXTREMITY AN AGREEMENT HAS BEEN
REACHED TO SAVE THE FORT DuPONT
ICE ARENA.
IT WAS IN JEOPARDY AFTER THEY
WERE CONSIDERING REALLOCATING
MILLIONS OF DOLLARS OF FUNDING
COMMITTED TO THE FACILITY.
BUT NOW THE FRIENDS OF FORT
DuPONT SAY IT HAS BEEN SAVED.
DC CHAIRMAN PHIL MENDELSON
SCHEDULED A MEETING TO NAIL DOWN
THE CURRENT STABILITY.
FENNEL, PHIL MENDELSON WILL
HAVE A MEETING TO RENOVATE THE
FACILITY AND BREAK GROUND ON A
SECOND ICE RINK.
>>> MORE BAD NEWS FOR WIZARDS
FANS, WE KNEW JOHN WALL WOULD
MISS THE SEASON, BUT NOW NEXT
SEASON IS IN JEOPARDY.
HE WILL MISS MOST IF NOT ALL OF
NEXT SEASON BECAUSE HE NEEDS
SURGERY ON HIS LEFT ACHILLES
TENDON WHICH HE TORE ON A FALL
AT HOME.
THEY DISCOVERED THE INJURY
DURING A PROCEDURE ON MONDAY.
HE IS ASSIGNED TO THE 2023
SEASON AND SET TO MAKE ALMOST
$40 MILLION NEXT SEASON.
>>> LET'S GET ANOTHER CHECK ON
THE FORECAST.
>>> GOOD MORNING EVERYONE.
HERE IS WHAT WE ARE LOOKING AT
ACROSS THE AREA.
TEMPERATURES, THE GRAPHIC IS
STUCK, BUT IT IS LOADING.
THIS IS WHAT WE LOOK AT ACROSS
THE AREA.
TEMPERATURES GETTING UP TO THE
50s TODAY, SO A BIG CHANGE AND
I THINK THIS IS STOCK.
LET'S TRY THIS AGAIN, MY
COMPUTER NEEDS A LITTLE COFFEE
THIS MORNING.
THERE WE GO.
WE CAN SEE THE TEMPERATURES IN
THE NEXT SEVEN DAYS WILL BE
MODIFYING QUITE A BIT.
I WANT TO START WITH WHAT'S
HAPPENING RIGHT HERE AND WHAT
WE ARE SEEING THIS MORNING.
WE HAVE SOME CLOUDS AND SHOWERS
OUT TO THE WEST OF US AND THAT
IS BECAUSE OF THE FRONT THAT IS
STALLED ACROSS THE AREA, SO
LOOK TO THE NORTH AROUND
MARYLAND AND PENNSYLVANIA
BORDER, WE HAVE A WARM FRONT
RIGHT THERE AND A COLD FRONT
STRADDLING.
THAT'S LINGERING ACROSS THE
AREA AND AS LONG AS WE HAVE
THESE FEATURES IN PLACE, WE
WILL SEE THESE SHOWERS MEETING
TODAY AND TOMORROW AND EVEN
FRIDAY, WE LOOK AT RAIN AND
COOLER TEMPERATURES, WE TOP OUT
AT 74 YESTERDAY IN DC FOR
RECORD TEMPERATURES AND THAT
WILL NOT BE THE CASE TODAY.
40 TO 55 DEGREES IS THE RANGE,
SHOWERS OUT THERE AND CLOUDY
WITH WINDS OUT OF THE SOUTHEAST
AT AROUND FIVE MILES PER HOUR
AND I WANT TO TALK ABOUT WHAT
THIS LOOKS LIKE BY THE HOUR,
BECAUSE THE RAIN IS GOING TO BE
MOVING IN THIS AFTERNOON.
2:00 FROM NORTHERN AND WESTERN
SUBURBS AND RIGHT ON 5:00 IS
BEST TIME TO SEE THE RAIN
ACROSS METRO DC.
THIS IS AT 2:30 PM, WE CAN SEE
THE RAIN AROUND FREDERICK AND
MARTINSBURG AND WINCHESTER AND
EVEN THROUGH LEESBURG AND BY
6:00 THIS EVENING, WE LOOK AT
LIGHT TO MODERATE RAIN AT 6:00
IN THE DC METRO AREA.
WE HAVE THE YELLOW WEATHER
ALERT FOR THE DRIVE HOME,
THAT'S ONE OF THE REASONS WHY
WE ISSUED THIS BECAUSE OF THE
TIMING OF IT.
WE GET THE RAIN ON THE ROADS
AND THAT COULD CAUSE SOME
PROBLEMS FOR US.
ADVANCING TO 8:00 THIS EVENING
AT DURING THE DINNER HOURS, YOU
ARE STILL LOOKING AT RAIN OUT
THERE.
TOMORROW MORNING, ALSO LOOKING
AT A WET COMMUTE IN THE
MORNING, BUT IN THE EVENING, WE
GET A BREAK FROM THE SHOWERS.
WE WAKE UP THURSDAY MORNING
WITH TEMPERATURES IN THE 50s
AND 40s AND LIGHT RAIN AS YOU
GET ABOUT YOUR DAY, BUT IN THE
AFTERNOON, WE HAVE A LITTLE
BREAK IN THE RAIN BEFORE IT
RETURNS AGAIN ON FRIDAY.
LET'S TALK ABOUT WHERE ELSE WE
SEE THIS ON FRIDAY, STRONG COLD
FRONT COMES TO THE AREA, THIS
IS THE FORECAST THAT I INVITED,
YOU CAN SEE WE ARE IN THE 60s
AHEAD OF THE FRONT IN DC, BUT
ONCE THE STRONGER AIR COMES IN,
TEMPERATURES ARE GOING TO DROP
THROUGHOUT THE DAY ON FRIDAY
SUMMER, SO 60 START AND BY
FRIDAY AFTERNOON, WE HAVE THE
JACKET AND TEMPERATURES
GRADUALLY BEGIN TO FALL TO THE
50s AND 40s, SO BEHIND THAT
COLD FRONT ON FRIDAY, 39
DEGREES ON SATURDAY AND
SATURDAY HAS 41 BY SUNDAY AND
THIS IS GOING TO START THE
COMEBACK OF THE WINTER.
WINTER WEATHER WILL BE MAKING
ITS WAY BACK INTO THE FORECAST
AND ON MONDAY MORNING, WE LOOK
AT A CHANCE FOR RAIN AND SNOW.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT THE TREND
I'VE SEEN WITH THE MODELS OVER
THE PAST FEW DAYS BECAUSE THERE
HAS NOT BEEN COMPLETE
AGREEMENT.
IN THE GFS MODEL, I'VE SEEN
RAIN AND SNOW LINE SHIFTING A
LITTLE FURTHER NORTH, AND THAT
WOULD PUT US IN A MOSTLY RAIN
EVENT ACROSS DC AND RAIN AND
SNOW AS YOU HEAD TOWARDS
NORTHERN MONTGOMERY COUNTY AND
ALONG THE MARYLAND AND
PENNSYLVANIA BORDER.
WE WILL KEEP THE CHANCE FOR
RAIN AND SNOW MIXED IN DC FOR 5
AM MONDAY AND BY MONDAY
AFTERNOON, WE SEE ALL RAIN
ACROSS THE AREA AS WE GET TO
WARMER AIR WITH WHEN COMING IN
FROM THE SOUTH.
TUESDAY AND WEDNESDAY, WE HAVE
ANOTHER SHOT OF SEEING SOME
WINTER-LIKE WEATHER AROUND
HERE.
RAIN AND SNOW MIXED POSSIBLE
TUESDAY I'M, TUESDAY BY
MIDMORNING, WE HAVE THE
CHANGEOVER TO ALL SNOW BY
WEDNESDAY AT SOME POINT.
THERE IS STILL TIME TO FIND TO
THE FORECAST, BUT THIS IS WHAT
WE ARE LOOKING AT.
WE GOT SPOILED YESTERDAY WITH
TEMPERATURES IN THE 70s AND NOW
IT LOOKS LIKE WE WILL SEE
WINTER REARING ITS HEAD ONCE
AGAIN ACROSS THE AREA.
AT 8 PM, WE SEE ARENA STOMACHS
AROUND THE AREA, ESPECIALLY OFF
TO THE WEST.
THE SEVEN-DAY FORECAST LOOKS
LIKE THIS, 53 DEGREES TODAY AND
65 TOMORROW AND STILL SOME
SHOWERS OUT THERE, 64 DEGREES
AND FALLING TEMPERATURES ON
FRIDAY, AND THEN WHEN THEY
FALL, THEY COME CRASHING DOWN
THE TEMPERATURES AROUND 39
DEGREES BY SATURDAY.
MICK WE HAVE SEEN A NUMBER OF
ACCIDENTS PICKING UP OUT THERE.
WE'VE ALREADY HAD A FEW
CLOSURES THIS MORNING.
SUSAN PARKWAY IS BACK OPEN AND
WE LOOK AT FOUR VEHICLES
INVOLVED IN A CRASH ON DC 295
SOUTHBOUND BY EAST CAPITOL
STREET.
THE EXPECTATION IS THAT THEY
ARE ON THE SHOULDER AND DELAYS
ARE GROWING BACK TO ROUTE 50.
IF YOU ARE IN ST. MARY'S THIS
MORNING, ROUTE 5 IS CLOSED
SOUTHBOUND AND THERE ARE
PICTURES OF THE SCENE, YOU CAN
SEE THE DELAYS.
THE ACCIDENT IS BETWEEN
MECHANICSVILLE ROAD AND THREE
NOTCH ROAD, IT LOOKS LIKE A
COMMUTER BUS THAT MAY HAVE
Val, Vern... I'm off to college
and I'm not gonna be around...
I'm worried about my parents'
retirement.
Oh, don't worry.
Voya helps them to and through
retirement...
...dealing with today's
expenses...
...like college...
...while helping plan, invest
and protect for the future.
So they'll be okay... without
me?
Um...
And when we knock out this
wall...
imagine the closet space.
Yes! Oh hey, son.
Yeah, I think they'll be fine.
Voya. Helping you to and
through retirement.
>>> THE TOUR IS EXPECTED TO
MAKE TOURS IN NEW ZEALAND AND
AUSTRALIA AND SRI LANKA.
>>> FACEBOOK IS ROLLING OUT THE
UNSEND A MESSAGE FOR IOS AND
ANDROID.
TO DELETE A MESSAGE FROM A
SINGLE OR GROUP CHAT, ALL YOU
HAVE TO DO IS TAP ON THE
MESSAGE YOU WANT TO DELETE AND
THEN CHOOSE THE OPTION LABELED
DELETE FOR EVERYONE.
SO THE QUESTION IS, IS THIS A
GOOD OR BAD IDEA.
THIS IS SIMILAR TO TWITTER
CONSIDERING THE DELETE OR EDIT
TWEET BUTTON, THERE IS A
CONCERN OVER WHETHER OR NOT YOU
SHOULD BE ABLE TO DELETE OR
EDIT IT.
>> I THINK IT'S NOTHING BUT A
GOOD IDEA, WHO HASN'T SENT A
MESSAGE THAT THEY REGRET?
IT GIVES YOU 10 MINUTES TO SEND
WHATEVER MESSAGE YOU WANT TO
SEND AND THEN YOU'RE LIKE OH,
MY BAD, JUST PULL IT BACK.
>> 10 MINUTES IS YOUR WINDOW.
>> ISN'T THAT WHAT YOU GET?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF IT IS 10
MINUTES COMING UP WITH GMAIL,
YOU COULD DO THAT WITH 30
SECONDS TO RETRACT YOUR
MESSAGE.
BUT THIS IS FACEBOOK, DO YOU
EVEN TRUST IT?
>> 30 SECONDS IS NOT LONG
ENOUGH.
>> YOU HAVE TO LET IT FULLY
MARINADE.
>> AM I GOING TO GET FIRED FOR
THIS?
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP DELIVERED
THE STATE OF THE UNION AND I
WILL WEIGH IN ON MY FINAL
THOUGHTS.
>>> AND IF YOU SMOKE
CIGARETTES, HAWAII IS NOT THE
STATE YOU WANT TO LIVE IN, AND
IS BILLIONAIRE A BAD
At Children's National,
stronger is caring for
a baby's heart
in the first 12 weeks
of pregnancy.
And a future when
prenatal pediatrics
leads to healthier children.
It's being the
number one newborn
intensive care unit
in the country.
And giving parents
peace of mind.
It's less recovering
in our bed,
and more jumping on yours.
Stronger is standing out
and standing proud.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>>> THE PRESIDENT GIVES HIS
SECOND STATE OF THE UNION
ADDRESS WHICH IS A CALL FOR
UNITY, BUT DEMOCRATS HIT BACK
SAYING THE PROBLEM WITH UNITY
IS HIS FAULT.
>>> WAS THE PRESIDENT RIGHT
WHEN HE SAID ICE MADE HUNDREDS
OF ARRESTS?
>> FROM RECORD HEAT YESTERDAY
TO NEEDING A JA A