>> THE '80S, A TIME OF DIFFERING
MEMORIES.
>> THE 80's WERE THE TIME OF MY
LIFE.
>> JUST SURVIVIN' IN--
IN THIS STATE,
LIKE COMPLETE NOTHINGNESS.
>> DIVERGENT MUSIC.
>> WE JUST DID ANYTHING
AND EVERYTHING.
WE WERE JUST CRAZY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> IF YOU CAN'T MOVE TO GO-GO,
YOU WASN'T MEANT TO MOVE.
>> COME ON!
>> DEVELOPMENT.
>> WASHINGTON WAS
EMERGING AS THE
GREAT COSMOPOLITAN WORLD
CAPITAL.
>> DEFENDING CHAMPIONSHIPS.
>> GOOD HOLE!
>> I WENT FROM BEING PRETTY
SMART TO THE NEXT DAY I'M A
BUFFOON.
>> AND DEATH.
>> WE'D HAVE SHOOTINGS, BUT YOU
HAD OVERDOSE DEATHS.
>> I PERSONALLY HAD A HUGE
NUMBER OF FRIENDS
THAT I LOST.
>> AND A MAYOR WHO
DEFINED THE CITY.
>> THAT LITTLE WHITE POWDER IS
SO POWERFUL.
>> HE WAS THE SUN AROUND WHICH
WE ALL ORBITED.
>> JOIN US AS WE TRAVEL BACK IN
TIME TO WASHINGTON IN THE '80s.
>> [HIP-HOP PLAYING]
>> ♪ THE WAY SHE SHOOK HER
BOOTY, SURE LOOK GOOD TO ME ♪
>> WASHINGTON, AT THE BEGINNING
OF THE '80s,
STILL REBUILDING AFTER THE
'68 RIOTS.
>> I THINK THE RESIDENTS
WERE FEELING HOPEFUL.
WE HAD A NEW MAYOR.
AND SO I THINK IT WAS A
GOOD FEELING.
>> WE WERE ALL JUST
COMIN' OFF OF THE CIVIL RIGHTS
ERA, AND SO THE COMMUNITY WAS
BUILDING AND COEXISTING.
>> WE'D JUST HAD HOME RULE
FOR A FEW YEARS, AND IT JUST
SOUNDED LIKE EVERYTHING WAS
GOING TO BE GREAT. OF COURSE,
IT WASN'T.
>> WASHINGTON, D.C., WAS STILL A
CITY DIVIDED.
>> ONE BLACK CITY AND ONE
WHITE CITY.
ONE CITY IN POVERTY AND ONE CITY
DOING WELL.
>> MIDDLE-CLASS WHITE FLIGHT
MEANT THE 172,000 WHITE
RESIDENTS WHO REMAINED TENDED TO
BE ABOVE AVERAGE INCOME, AND
LIVE IN THE CITY'S LEAFIER,
NORTHWEST SUBURBS.
>> THERE WERE THE WHITE WARDS
THAT WERE, QUOTE, UNQUOTE,
RECEIVED ANYTHING THEY WANT.
AND THERE WAS THE OTHER WARDS,
THE FORGOTTEN WARDS, THAT WERE
SORT OF OUT THERE HANGING OUT.
>> AFRICAN AMERICANS, WHO MADE
UP 70% OF THE CITY'S RESIDENTS,
TENDED TO LIVE AND WORK IN THE
POORER EASTERN QUADRANTS OF THE
CITY AND CLOSE TO DOWNTOWN.
>> ♪ AH, IT'S BECOMING
LIKE A GHOST TOWN ♪
>> WHEN YOU DROVE DOWNTOWN WITH
YOUR PARENTS, WHO MADE SURE THE
DOORS WERE LOCKED, YOU KNOW,
EVERYTHING WAS BOARDED UP.
DOWNTOWN WAS A LOT OF CRIME.
IT WAS A SCARY PLACE.
>> THERE WAS SOME HOPE
THAT THAT WOULD CHANGE, BUT
THERE WAS NOTHING YET THAT GAVE
AN INDICATION THAT CHANGE WAS
REALLY COMING.
>> THE FEDERAL CITY'S MOST
PROMINENT RESIDENT FOUND HIMSELF
IN A SIMILAR STATE OF
STAGNATION.
>> IT IS A CRISIS OF CONFIDENCE.
>> OUR HOSTAGES HAD BEEN TAKEN
IN IRAN, WE HAD 21% INTEREST
RATES, 13% INFLATION.
>> WASHINGTON WAS, AS IT IS
NOW, A PREDOMINANTLY DEMOCRATIC
TOWN.
SO WASHINGTON WANTED THIS
PRESIDENT TO SUCCEED.
>> THE REST OF AMERICA DID NOT
FEEL THE SAME.
>> NBC NEWS NOW MAKES ITS
PROJECTION.
REAGAN IS OUR PROJECTED WINNER.
>> ♪ ANOTHER ONE
BITES THE DUST ♪
[CHEERING]
>> ♪ ANOTHER ONE
BITES THE DUST
AND ANOTHER ONE GONE... ♪
>> I RONALD REAGAN DO SOLEMNLY
SWEAR...
>> THAT I WILL FAITHFULLY
EXECUTE THE OFFICE OF...
>> TWO MONTHS LATER, JUST AS
REPUBLICAN RONALD REAGAN TOOK
THE OATH OF OFFICE, AYATOLLAH
KHOMEINI OF IRAN RELEASED ALL
52 HOSTAGES.
>> I AM CONVINCED THEY
SUSPECTED THAT RONALD REAGAN
WOULD GIVE THEM 48 HOURS, AND IF
THE HOSTAGES WEREN'T ON THEIR
WAY HOME, THERE WOULD BE
MILITARY ACTION.
[CHEERING]
>> THOUGH WASHINGTONIANS WERE
EXCITED TO WELCOME THE HOSTAGES,
MOST DIDN'T FEEL THE SAME ABOUT
THE NEW PRESIDENT.
>> DEPRESSED WOULD BE A GOOD
WAY OF DESCRIBING THE FACT
THAT RONALD REAGAN WAS
BRINGING WITH HIM A WHOLE NEW
POLITICAL CULTURE.
>> THERE WERE FUR COATS
ALL OVER THE PLACE. THERE WAS A
PERCEPTION THAT THE CALIFORNIA
CONSERVATIVES THAT CAME WERE A
PRETTY RICH CROWD AND NOT VERY
MUCH IN TOUCH WITH THE AVERAGE
FOLKS.
>> I THINK THE GAY COMMUNITY
AT THAT TIME HAD AN
UNDERSTANDABLE AMOUNT OF
TREPIDATION, YOU KNOW, WHAT
WAS THIS PRESIDENT GOING TO BE
LIKE.
>> I GAVE REAGAN ALL THE
ATTENTION HE DESERVED. HE WAS
NOT A FRIEND OF THE CITY.
>> OTHERS WERE MORE WELCOMING.
>> THE PRESIDENT ELECT SAID
THERE'S A ONE WORD DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN PRESIDENT AND RESIDENT.
AND HE WANTED TO BRIDGE THE GAP
BETWEEN RESIDENT AND PRESIDENT.
AND I BELIEVE THAT, AND I
APPRECIATE THAT BECAUSE I'M
THE MAYOR OF THE CITY,
AND HE'S GONNA BE ONE OF MY
CONSTITUENTS.
>> I THINK HE KNEW MORE
ABOUT HOW WASHINGTON FUNCTIONED
THAN A LOT OF OTHER PRESIDENTS.
HE WAS THE ONLY PRESIDENT
THAT I'VE KNOWN WHO ACTUALLY
INVITED THE LOCAL MEDIA TO
MEET WITH HIM.
>> WHEN REAGAN CAME TO TOWN,
THAT ARTS BEAT AND ENTERTAINMENT
BEAT JUST EXPLODED BECAUSE
REAGAN BROUGHT ALL OF HIS
SHOWBIZ CONNECTIONS TO TOWN.
WHEN THEY HAD HIS FIRST
INAUGURATION, THEY HAD THIS
HUGE EVENT.
>> [RAY CHARLES SINGING
INDISTINCTLY]
>> AND REAGAN SET THE TONE
FOR MOVIES AND SHOW BUSINESS IN
WASHINGTON.
>> WASHINGTON WAS EMERGING AS
THE GREAT COSMOPOLITAN WORLD
CAPITAL IT IS TODAY.
IT WAS A GREAT TIME IN
AMERICA AND IT WAS A GREAT FOR
THE REAGANAUTS.
>> UNTIL MARCH 30, 1981.
[GUNSHOTS]
AS REAGAN WAS LEAVING THE
WASHINGTON HILTON, JOHN HINCKLEY
JR. FIRED 6 TIMES.
>> GET HIM OUT!
>> ONE SHOT HIT PRESS SECRETARY,
JAMES BRADY, CRITICALLY WOUNDING
HIM.
ANOTHER RICOCHETED OFF THE
PRESIDENTIAL LIMOUSINE, LODGING
IN REAGAN'S LUNG.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
WHEN YOU GET HOME?
>> SIT DOWN.
[CHEERING]
>> WITHIN A MONTH REAGAN WAS
BACK AT WORK.
AND THE WASHINGTON HILTON HAD A
NICKNAME.
>> MEET ME OVER THERE.
OVER THERE BY THE HILTON, THE
HINCKLEY HILTON.
>> THE HINCKLEY HILTON.
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER DRIVEN
BY THAT HOTEL WITHOUT THINKING
ABOUT IT.
>> BACK AT HIS DESK, THE
PRESIDENT WORKED WITH
HIS ADMINISTRATION
TO FULFILL HIS CAMPAIGN PROMISE
TO CUT SPENDING.
GROWING DISCONTENT WITH EXISTING
TREATMENTS PROMPTED CUTS IN
MENTAL HEALTH SERVICES.
>> YOU BEGAN TO SEE LARGE
NUMBERS OF PANHANDLERS APPEARING
ON THE STREETS OF WASHINGTON.
>> TO BE IN D.C. WHERE THE
PRESIDENTS RESIDES,
YOU WOULD THINKING WE
SHOULDN'T HAVE SOME PLACES LIKE
THIS.
>> I WALK THE STREET AND I
SLEEP ON THE ...DAMN STREET.
>> MANY DISTRICT HOMELESS WERE
VETERANS DAMAGED BY THEIR
EXPERIENCES IN VIETNAM FIGHTING
AN UNPOPULAR WAR.
>> ♪ I WANT TO GO WHERE LOVE IS
I WANT YOU SHOW ME ♪
>> I DIDN'T EVEN HAVE TO GO.
I WANTED TO GO. EVERYTHING
I PUT MY HEART INTO YOU COME
BACK AND YOU GOT DUMPED ON.
>> ♪ I WANT YOU TO SHOW ME ♪
>> IN 1980, CONGRESS AUTHORIZED
CONSTRUCTION OF A VIETNAM
MEMORIAL ON THE MALL.
FOLLOWING A NATIONWIDE
COMPETITION, A DESIGN FOR A
SUNKEN, REFLECTIVE, BLACK
GRANITE WALL BY MAYA LIN,
A 21-YEAR-OLD COLLEGE STUDENT,
WAS SELECTED.
>> IT WAS SO SIMPLE AND SO
DIRECT THAT IT WAS INCREDIBLE.
>> BUT NOT EVERYONE WAS HAPPY
WITH THE DESIGN.
>> I SAID, YOU KNOW THIS DOESN'T
LOOK LIKE SOMETHING HONORING
THESE PEOPLE'S SERVICE, AND
THERE WAS A TREMENDOUS CULTURAL,
ARTISTIC DEBATE THAT WENT ON IN
THIS TOWN, AND A LOT OF PEOPLE
FELT, ARE THEY DISHONORING THE
VETS BY DOING THIS?
>> EVENTUALLY THE DESIGN FOR THE
MEMORIAL WAS AMENDED, AND 3
SOLDIERS WERE ADDED.
BUT ON ITS OPENING IN 1982, THE
STRENGTH OF THE ORIGINAL DESIGN
BECAME EVIDENT.
>> I'M HERE TO PAY EULOGY
AND HOMAGE TO ALL MY COMRADES
WHO DIDN'T MAKE IT BACK WITH ME.
>> I THINK THEY WANTED SOMETHING
MORE HEROIC.
BUT I THINK THEY GOT
SOMETHING THAT WAS EVEN MORE
PROFOUND.
>> I THINK WHAT TURNED IT
AROUND WAS NOT THE BLACK WALLS,
IT'S THE NAMES ON THE WALLS.
AND I WILL SAY THAT IT TURNED
OUT FROM THE WAY THAT THING'S
BEEN RECEIVED THAT I WAS WRONG
ON THAT ONE.
WRONG BIG TIME.
>> AND I LOVE THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE FOR BEING HERE.
AND JUST SAYING "THANK YOU,"
BECAUSE THAT'S ALL WE WANTED,
IS TO HEAR THAT.
>> FOR MORE THAN A CENTURY, THE
CITY HAD SUPPORTED TWO
NATIONALLY RECOGNIZED DAILY
NEWSPAPERS--
THE MORE PROGRESSIVE "WASHINGTON
POST" AND MORE CONSERVATIVE
"WASHINGTON STAR."
["FREEZE FRAME" PLAYING]
BUT THE RECESSION AND SHRINKING
DEMAND FOR EVENING DAILIES
FORCED THE "STAR" INTO
BANKRUPTCY IN 1981.
>> TV KILLED THEM.
PEOPLE WATCH THE TV NEWS, GO
HOME AND THEY DON'T SIT THERE
AND READ THEIR PAPER.
CLICK.
>> FOR ABOUT A YEAR AND A
HALF WE WERE A ONE-PAPER TOWN.
AND THAT WAS, I FELT, A LITTLE
DANGEROUS.
>> BUT IN A SIGN OF THE GROWING
CLOUT OF CONSERVATIVE VOICES, AN
UPSTART DAILY WITH AN UNWAVERING
POINT OF VIEW HIT THE NEWSSTANDS
IN 1982.
>> IT'S CALLED THE "WASHINGTON
TIMES" AND IT'S OWNED BY THE
PUBLISHING ARM OF THE REVEREND
MOON'S UNIFICATION CHURCH.
>> I WASN'T EXCITED TO SEE
THE MOONEY PAPER COME AROUND,
NO.
WELL, REVEREND MOON WAS A--
A GREAT CHRISTIAN EVANGELIST
FROM KOREA.
HE OBVIOUSLY FELT THAT IT WOULD
BE NICE TO HAVE A
GOOD MOUTHPIECE IN WASHINGTON.
>> MY COLUMN USED TO APPEAR
IN THE "WASHINGTON TIMES"
ON A REGULAR, YOU KNOW, TWICE A
WEEK, AND EVERY CONSERVATIVE
READ IT.
I MEAN IT WAS SOMETHING WE
HAD THAT WE HAD NEVER HAD
BEFORE.
>> NO ONE WHO WORKED THE NEWS
ROOMS OF WASHINGTON
IN THE '80s CAN FORGET
JANUARY 13, 1982.
>> I HAD JUST COME ACROSS
THE BRIDGE IN A BLINDING
SNOWSTORM, AND WHEN I GOT,
LIKE, 10 FEET OFF THE BRIDGE,
WE HEARD A CRUNCH.
>> AT 4:01 P.M.,
AIR FLORIDA FLIGHT 90 CRASHED
INTO THE 14th STREET BRIDGE.
>> AND WE GET DOWN THERE AND WE
DON'T REALLY HAVE A METHOD FOR
DEALING WITH THAT KIND OF MASS
CAUSALITY. THE RADIO
SYSTEMS DIDN'T FUNCTION LIKE
THEY SHOULD.
WE DIDN'T HAVE ANYPLACE
TO DEAL WITH THE BODIES.
>> PASSER-BY LENNY SKUTNIK DOVE
INTO THE WATER TO HELP SAVE A
DROWNING WOMAN.
>> WE HAVE JUST LEARNED THAT
THAT WOMAN FIGHTING TO SURVIVE
IN THE ICY POTOMAC
WAS ONE OF THE STEWARDESSES ON
BOARD THE PLANE,
HER NAME KELLY DUNCAN.
>> HE REALLY SYMBOLIZED, I
THINK, FOR A LOT OF PEOPLE HERE,
THAT PEOPLE WANTED TO HELP AND
WERE WILLING TO HELP EACH OTHER.
>> 74 PEOPLE ON THE PLANE AND
4 ON THE BRIDGE WERE KILLED.
>> ONE OF MY DEAREST FRIENDS
WAS ON THAT PLANE. SHE WAS THE
MOTHER OF 3 YOUNG CHILDREN.
AND I MISS HER TO THIS DAY.
>> AS WORD OF THE CRASH SPREAD,
AND THE WASHINGTON PRESS CORP
DESCENDED ON THE SCENE, IT
BECAME CLEAR THAT ANOTHER
TRAGEDY HAD STRUCK THE REGION.
>> REPORTERS COULDN'T GET
THERE BECAUSE THE METRO TRAIN
ALSO HAD DERAILED.
>> 30 MINUTES AFTER THE PLANE
CRASH, AN ORANGE LINE TRAIN
JUMPED THE TRACKS IN A TUNNEL
NEAR FEDERAL TRIANGLE.
>> TWO WOMEN AND A MAN WHOSE
NAMES HAVE NOT BEEN RELEASED
WERE BEEN KILLED.
>> THAT FORCED THE REGION TO
THINK, OH, MY GOODNESS, WHAT DO
WE DO IF...
>> BY 1982, BARRY'S FIRST TERM
AS MAYOR WAS COMING TO A CLOSE.
FOR THE FIRST TIME SINCE HIS
ELECTION IN 1978, VOTERS WERE
GIVEN THE CHANCE TO JUDGE HIS
RECORD.
>> HE WAS ELECTED BY WHITES
BECAUSE HE WON
ESSENTIALLY WITH THE VOTES OF
PEOPLE IN WARDS ONE, TWO, 3,
AND 6.
>> THIS IS JUST THE BEGINNING
OF WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO HERE.
>> BUT ONCE IN POWER, BARRY KNEW
THAT TYING HIS POLITICAL FUTURE
TO THE CITY'S WHITE RESIDENTS
WAS UNSUSTAINABLE.
>> HE MADE AN INCREDIBLY
PRUDENT POLITICAL DECISION TO
SWITCH HIS BASE TO BLACK,
THROUGH THE MINORITY CONTRACTING
PROGRAMS, AND BRINGING BLACK
FOLKS INTO KEY POSITIONS IN THE
GOVERNMENT.
>> I CAN REMEMBER HIM SAYING,
"LISTEN, YOU'RE GOING TO BE ABLE
TO ADVANCE, YOU GOT TO GET
PREPARED FOR LEADERSHIP,"
AND FOR SOMEBODY LIKE ME, I
GOT TO BE CHIEF BECAUSE OF
BARRY.
>> BARRY USED THE POWER OF HIS
POSITION TO ENCOURAGE THE
CREATION AND DEVELOPMENT OF
AFRICAN-AMERICAN OWNED
BUSINESSES.
>> AND IF YOU WERE GOING TO DO
BUSINESS IN D.C.,
ONE OF THE FIRST QUESTIONS
THEY'D ASK YOU, "DO YOU HAVE
MINORITY PARTICIPATION IN THIS
DEAL?"
WHAT CAME ABOUT WAS
SORT OF A PHILOSOPHY THAT
WHITE BUSINESSES SHOULD
PARTNER UP WITH QUALIFIED
AFRICAN-AMERICAN BUSINESS
PEOPLE, AND ONCE YOU GET A
BLACK CITY COUNCIL, ALL OF A
SUDDEN, THE WHITE LAW FIRMS
STARTS SAYING, "WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE BLACK PARTNERS."
AND SOME OF THE WHITE BUSINESSES
STARTED SAYING, "WE HAVE TO HAVE
BLACK LOBBYISTS."
>> THE INCREASED FLOW OF MONEY
MOVING THROUGH THE CITY'S
ECONOMY SWELLED THE DISTRICT'S
COFFERS, GIVING BARRY THE INCOME
TO SPEND ON PROJECTS THAT
BENEFITED THE CITY'S POORER
YOUTH AND BUILD A BASE FOR THE
REST OF HIS POLITICAL CAREER.
>> MY MOST MEMORABLE PROGRAM IS
THE SUMMER JOB PROGRAM.
OVER 100,000 YOUNG PEOPLE WENT
THROUGH OUR SUMMER JOB PROGRAM.
>> I WAS JUST AT SOME EVENT
AND THE GUY WHO WAS IN CHARGE OF
THE PEOPLE PARKING THE CARS CAME
UP TO ME, HE SAYS, "I GOT MY
FIRST JOB IN THE MARION BARRY
SUMMER JOBS PROGRAM." AND HE
SAID, "NOW I HELP RUN THIS
COMPANY."
>> THAT WAS THE BOMB.
YOU GO DOWN 500 C STREET, AND
THERE'S A LONG LINE OF KIDS
WAITING IN LINE TO GET THEIR
CHECKS, YOU KNOW, SO, YOU WOULD
SEE THEM ALL DOWNTOWN AT
THE GO-GO AT NIGHT, YOU KNOW.
SO THAT WAS AWESOME, YES,
INDEED.
>> RECOGNIZING THE DISTRICTS'
AGING WERE UNDER-SERVED,
BARRY ALSO INVESTED HEAVILY IN
SERVICES FOR THE ELDERLY.
>> AND THE FLIPSIDE OF THAT FOR
BARRY WAS AND IN ADDITION TO
THAT BEING A GOOD THING WAS THAT
HE WOULD TAKE BUSES,
RECREATION BUSES,
AND TAKE THEM ALL DOWN TO VOTE.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
>> IN 1982, BARRY WAS ELECTED TO
A SECOND TERM AS MAYOR WITH
81% OF THE VOTE
>> I WANT TO THANK ALL OF YOU
FOR REAFFIRMING YOUR FAITH IN
ME.
[CHEERING]
>> SO IT WAS CLEAR THAT
HIS SUCCESS IN THE ELECTION HAD
BEEN LARGELY THROUGH BLACK FOLKS
AND NOT FROM THE WHITE
COMMUNITY. HE SAID, "GET OVER
IT."
>> DURING HIS FIRST TERM, BARRY
HAD HONORED PROMISES MADE TO THE
GAY COMMUNITY, A CORE
CONSTITUENCY THAT HELPED TO
ELECT HIM.
>> HE UNDERSTOOD THAT WE
WERE A POLITICAL POWER.
>> JUST HIS WILLINGNESS TO SAY,
"I WILL HAVE OPENLY GAY PEOPLE
IN MY ADMINISTRATION."
NOBODY DID THAT AT THAT TIME.
SO THAT WAS HUGE.
>> BARRY'S ACTIONS HELPED TO
ESTABLISH D.C. AS ONE OF THE
COUNTRY'S MOST GAY FRIENDLY
CITIES.
>> IT AFFECTED MOST GAY
PEOPLE'S SOCIAL LIVES, IN THAT
THEY BECAME MORE OPEN.
>> IT GAVE THE COMMUNITY THIS
ENORMOUS NUMBER OF
HEALTHY, HAPPY WAYS OF MEETING
PEOPLE.
AND SO IT MADE IT A LOT EASIER
FOR PEOPLE TO COME OUT.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
>> BY 1984, EXPANSION OF D.C.'s
ANNUAL GAY PRIDE DAY TO A
WEEKLONG FESTIVAL WAS COMPLETE,
CEMENTING WASHINGTON'S STATUS AS
HOME TO ONE THE COUNTRY'S
LARGEST AND MOST VIBRANT
GAY COMMUNITIES.
IMPROVEMENT IN THE CITY'S
FORTUNES ALSO SPREAD TO THE
FOOTBALL FIELD.
[CHEERING]
IN 1981,
TEAM OWNER JACK KENT COOKE
FIRED COACH JACK PARDEE AND
REPLACED HIM WITH SAN DIEGO
OFFENSIVE COORDINATOR JOE
GIBBS.
>> AT FIRST I SAID IF I'M NOT
SUCCESSFUL, HEY, THAT'S PART OF
LIFE.
BUT WHEN I GOT THERE, WHAT I
REALIZED WAS HOW MANY PEOPLE
DEPEND ON YOU.
>> THE TEAM BEGAN THE SEASON
0 AND 5.
>> I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO BE
THE FIRST GUY TO EVER COACH IN
THE NFL AND NEVER WIN A GAME.
I TOLD PAT, PLEASE SELL THE DOG,
I'D HATE TO COME HOME AND SEE
THAT FELLOW DRAPED OVER THE
STEPS.
>> BUT A THIRD OF A WAY THROUGH
THE '81 SEASON, WINS REPLACED
LOSSES AND THE TEAM FINISHED
8-8.
>> THEY HAD A REALLY
UNIQUE SQUAD.
THEISMANN WAS JUST REALLY SLICK.
>> JOE T. WAS PROBABLY ONE OF
THE MOST PASSIONATE FOOTBALL
PLAYERS. I MEAN THAT GUY WANTED
TO BE SUCCESSFUL.
>> RIGGINS WAS A BULL.
AND THEN YOU HAD A JOE
WASHINGTON,
WHO WAS JUST THIS SMALL, SPEEDY
GUY.
ART MONK, ANYTHING YOU THREW
UP, HE CAUGHT.
>> THE HOGS WERE BIG AND FAT.
AND THEY--THEY PUT UP
A LOT OF MEAT AGAINST
THAT LINE.
[CROWD CHANTING
"WE WANT DALLAS"]
>> AFTER GOING 8-1 AND FIRST IN
THE NFC EAST IN THE STRIKE-
SHORTENED 1982 SEASON, THEY
HOSTED THE NFC CHAMPIONSHIP GAME
AGAINST THEIR FIERCEST RIVAL.
>> THE EXCITEMENT OF RFK YOU
HEARD OUTSIDE THE STADIUM, JUST
UP IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
YOU JUST CAN HEAR THAT ROARING
CROWD.
>> THE HOME TEAM WAS LEADING
24-17 WITH LESS THAN 7 MINUTES
REMAINING.
>> PLAY ACTION FAKED TO DORSET.
SCREEN PASS BATTED IN THE AIR
BY MANLEY.
DARRYL GRANT'S THERE, PICKED
IT OFF.
TOUCHDOWN WASHINGTON REDSKINS!
UNBELIEVABLE!
>> THE STADIUM WOULD ROCK.
IT WAS THUNDEROUS.
>> I DO NOT BELIEVE IT.
>> WITH THAT WIN, THE TEAM
HEADED TO PASADENA TO PLAY THE
MIAMI DOLPHINS IN SUPER BOWL
XVII.
THE GAME WAS CLOSE THROUGHOUT.
>> IT CAME DOWN TO THE FOURTH
QUARTER. I THINK WE WERE ON THE
PLUS 41 YARD LINE,
AND IT WAS FOURTH AND
ONE, AND I MADE THE CALL TO GO
FOR IT .
>> HERE GOES THE DIESEL.
THERE'S THE SNAP TO THEISMANN,
HAND TO RIGGINS.
HE'S GOT A GOOD HOLE. HE'S GOT
THE FIRST DOWN AT THE 40.
HE'S GONE!
THE 35, THE 30, THE 20!
TOUCHDOWN, WASHINGTON REDSKINS!
HE'S GONE!
HOLY COW, WAS THAT A PLAY OR
TOUCHDOWN, WASHINGTON REDSKINS!
WHAT?
HOLY COW, WAS THAT A PLAY OR
>> THE FINAL SCORE 27-17,
WHAT?
WASHINGTON.
>> THE FINAL SCORE 27-17,
>> WOO! REDSKINS ARE NUMBER ONE!
WASHINGTON.
>> EVERYBODY POURED INTO THE
>> WOO! REDSKINS ARE NUMBER ONE!
STREETS OF M STREET IN
>> EVERYBODY POURED INTO THE
GEORGETOWN.
STREETS OF M STREET IN
IT WAS EUPHORIC. THE
GEORGETOWN.
CITY'S TEAM FINALLY BROUGHT
IT WAS EUPHORIC. THE
HOME THE BACON.
CITY'S TEAM FINALLY BROUGHT
>> WOO!
HOME THE BACON.
[GO-GO MUSIC PLAYING]
>> WOO!
>> FOOTBALL WASN'T THE ONLY
[GO-GO MUSIC PLAYING]
THING MAKING FANS AT RFK CHEER.
>> FOOTBALL WASN'T THE ONLY
>> THE BACK-TO-SCHOOL BOOGIE,
THING MAKING FANS AT RFK CHEER.
THE BATTLE OF THE BANDS.
>> THE BACK-TO-SCHOOL BOOGIE,
YOU GET AN OPPORTUNITY TO SEE
THE BATTLE OF THE BANDS.
ALL THESE GO-GO BANDS PERFORM
YOU GET AN OPPORTUNITY TO SEE
INSIDE OF A HUGE STADIUM.
ALL THESE GO-GO BANDS PERFORM
>> I'M OUT HERE WITH FAMILY!
INSIDE OF A HUGE STADIUM.
>> I USED TO ALWAYS SAY IF YOU
>> I'M OUT HERE WITH FAMILY!
CAN'T MOVE TO GO-GO,
>> I USED TO ALWAYS SAY IF YOU
YOU WASN'T MEANT TO MOVE.
CAN'T MOVE TO GO-GO,
I REMEMBER THE FIRST TIME
YOU WASN'T MEANT TO MOVE.
HEARING TROUBLE FUNK.
I REMEMBER THE FIRST TIME
THERE'S A SONG TO PUMP ME UP.
HEARING TROUBLE FUNK.
>> ♪PUMP, PUMP, PUMP
THERE'S A SONG TO PUMP ME UP.
PUMP ME UP ♪
>> ♪PUMP, PUMP, PUMP
>> AND HENRY ROLLINS, WHO WAS MY
PUMP ME UP ♪
BEST FRIEND,
>> AND HENRY ROLLINS, WHO WAS MY
WE HEARD IT ON THE RADIO, AND WE
BEST FRIEND,
JUST PULLED THE CAR OVER
WE HEARD IT ON THE RADIO, AND WE
TO LISTEN TO THE SONG.
JUST PULLED THE CAR OVER
>> IN ADDITION TO CHUCK BROWN
TO LISTEN TO THE SONG.
AND TROUBLE FUNK, BANDS SUCH AS
>> IN ADDITION TO CHUCK BROWN
RARE ESSENCE AND EU CREATED A
AND TROUBLE FUNK, BANDS SUCH AS
MUSIC AND CULTURE PROUD OF ITS
RARE ESSENCE AND EU CREATED A
D.C. ROOTS.
MUSIC AND CULTURE PROUD OF ITS
>> ...ALL RIGHT.
D.C. ROOTS.
>> GO-GO WAS A PRODUCT OF A TIME
>> ...ALL RIGHT.
WHEN D.C. PUBLIC SCHOOLS HAD
>> GO-GO WAS A PRODUCT OF A TIME
MORE MUSIC PROGRAMS.
WHEN D.C. PUBLIC SCHOOLS HAD
>> KIDS COULDN'T AFFORD TO
MORE MUSIC PROGRAMS.
BUY INSTRUMENTS.
>> KIDS COULDN'T AFFORD TO
AND SO, THE KIDS
BUY INSTRUMENTS.
WOULD CHECK OUT THEIR
AND SO, THE KIDS
INSTRUMENTS, AND THEY'D GO HOME
WOULD CHECK OUT THEIR
TO PRACTICE, ALL RIGHT,
INSTRUMENTS, AND THEY'D GO HOME
BUT WITH THE LOCAL GO-GO BAND.
TO PRACTICE, ALL RIGHT,
>> LIVE RECORDINGS,
BUT WITH THE LOCAL GO-GO BAND.
BETTER KNOWN AS "P.A. TAPES,"
>> LIVE RECORDINGS,
BECAME A FORM OF CURRENCY FOR
BETTER KNOWN AS "P.A. TAPES,"
GO-GO FANS.
BECAME A FORM OF CURRENCY FOR
>> WE USED TO GO TO THE GO-GOS
GO-GO FANS.
WITH OUR BIG BOOM BOXES, AND--
>> WE USED TO GO TO THE GO-GOS
AND STAND IN FRONT OF THE
WITH OUR BIG BOOM BOXES, AND--
SPEAKERS.
AND STAND IN FRONT OF THE
>> IT WAS AND IT STILL IS A BIG
SPEAKERS.
THING TO GET YOUR NAME CALLED
>> IT WAS AND IT STILL IS A BIG
OUT, ESPECIALLY IF YOUR NAME IS
THING TO GET YOUR NAME CALLED
ALWAYS HEARD ON THE P.A. TAPES.
OUT, ESPECIALLY IF YOUR NAME IS
YOU KNOW.
ALWAYS HEARD ON THE P.A. TAPES.
>> WHOO, THAT WAS A BIG FEELING.
YOU KNOW.
AND SO, YOU WANTED THAT P.A.
>> WHOO, THAT WAS A BIG FEELING.
TAPE FROM THIS DAY.
>> THE CITY'S INSATIABLE
APPETITE FOR LIVE GO-GO
LED TO PERFORMANCES SPRINGING UP
ALL OVER TOWN.
>> EVERYBODY REPRESENTED WHERE
THEY CAME FROM. YOU KNOW,
JUNK YARD FROM BARRY FARMS.
PETWORTH NAMED ITSELF AFTER THE
AREA.
>> MY FIRST-EVER
EXPERIENCE PLAYIN'
LIVE WITH A GO-GO BAND WAS IN MY
FRIEND'S BACKYARD, AND PEOPLE
WOULD CROWD AROUND
AND LISTEN TO US.
A COMPULSION TO PLAY LIVE
MUSIC THAT LED TO AN UNLIKELY
SHARING OF STAGES.
>> A LOT OF THE REGULAR
CLUBS, LIKE AT THE BAYOU AND,
YOU KNOW, DESPERADOES ONLY
BOOKED, YOU KNOW, BIG ROCK BANDS
OR BIG NAME PEOPLE, SO WE
WOULD PLAY ANYWHERE.
AND IT ENDED UP THAT WE WOULD
PLAY TOGETHER.
[CLASH'S "SHOULD I STAY OR
SHOULD I GO" PLAYING]
>> ONE OF THESE CROSSOVER VENUES
WAS AT 930 F STREET NORTHWEST.
>> THEIR SLOGAN WAS A PLACE AND
A TIME.
>> WHEN ORIGINAL OWNERS DODY
DiSANTO AND JON BOWERS OPENED
THE 9:30 CLUB IN 1980, THEIR
CHOICE OF LOCATION,
IN THE HEART OF DOWNTOWN,
WAS UNCONVENTIONAL.
>> WHEN THE 9:30 WAS THERE,
THERE WERE PEEP SHOWS AND, YOU
KNOW, LIQUOR STORES AND STRIP
JOINTS.
PEOPLE COULDN'T AFFORD TO BUY
EXPENSIVE REAL ESTATE, SO
THEY HAD TO DO IT IN THE
BAD PARTS OF TOWN.
>> THE TINY, ODD-SHAPED SPACE
WAS AN ACQUIRED TASTE.
>> THERE WAS REALLY NOT MUCH
ROOM FOR THE AUDIENCE.
IT WAS LIKE YOU WERE IN A
LOBBY. WE WOULD HAVE BANDS
SHOW UP WHO WERE APPALLED, AND
ASK..."SO, WHERE'S THE CLUB?"
AND SOME BANDS WALKED OUT.
DJ JAZZY JEFF AND THE FRESH
PRINCE, WILL SMITH, WALKED OUT.
TWO SOLD-OUT SHOWS.
>> OF COURSE, WHEN THE BAND
DID GO ON, YOU WERE RIGHT
IN FRONT OF THEM.
THERE WAS NO CLOSER
EXPERIENCE TO SEE A SHOW THAN
THE OLD 9:30 CLUB.
>> A UNIQUE VENUE THAT BECAME A
FAVORITE OF THE LOCAL HARD-CORE
PUNK SCENE,
DEFINED BY ITS INCLUSION OF
ANYONE WHO DIDN'T FEEL THEY
BELONGED.
>> IF YOU GREW UP IN THIS TOWN I
THINK YOU FEEL REALLY
MARGINALIZED FOR ONE REASON OR
ANOTHER.
>> D.C. PUNK GAVE BIRTH TO BANDS
LIKE GOVERNMENT ISSUE, STATE OF
ALERT, AND MINOR THREAT, WITH
IAN MACKAYE ON LEAD VOCALS.
>> [SINGING INDISTINCTLY]
> WE IDENTIFIED AS WASHINGTON,
D.C.
AND IT WAS A CHIP ON OUR
SHOULDER.
>> THE REGION ALSO PRODUCED THE
GROUND-BREAKING BAD BRAINS.
>> [SINGING INDISTINCTLY]
>> THE BAD BRAINS WERE 4 GUYS
FROM ANACOSTIA AND PG COUNTY
AND THEY WERE JUST AN
INCREDIBLE BAND.
>> ♪ THEY'RE PLAYING
BASKETBALL ♪
>> THE EARLY '80s SAW AN
EXPLOSION IN THE POPULARITY OF
GEORGETOWN UNIVERSITY
BASKETBALL.
>> ♪ ...BASKETBALL ♪
>> I CAN REMEMBER WHEN
GEORGETOWN WAS JUST A TYPE OF
IVY LEAGUE,
JESUIT SCHOOL, BUT THEN JOHN
THOMPSON CAME AND TURNED IT
AROUND AND EVERYONE WAS HOYAS,
HOYAS, HOYAS.
>> THE TEAM'S TOUGH
DEFENSE-MINDED
STYLE HELPED TO ATTRACT A STRONG
LOCAL FOLLOWING.
>> A PREDOMINANTLY BLACK
BASKETBALL TEAM AT--
AT A REALLY GOOD UNIVERSITY,
THAT INSPIRED A LOT OF US.
WE HUNG OUT IN GEORGETOWN.
WE WORE GEORGETOWN UNIVERSITY
SWEATSHIRTS.
>> IT WAS LIKE A PARTY TO ME.
IT WAS THE PLACE TO BE. THE
ENERGY WAS ALL OVER THE PLACE.
>> IN MARCH OF 1982,
THE HOYAS LED BY
CENTER PATRICK EWING ADVANCED TO
THE NCAA CHAMPIONSHIP GAME.
WITH LESS THAN 10 SECONDS LEFT,
THEY HAD A CHANCE TO TAKE THE
WINNING SHOT.
>> FRED BROWN WITH THE BALL.
OH, HE THROWS IT TO THE WRONG
GUY.
>> I HAD TO TURN THE TV OFF.
I COULDN'T STAND TO WATCH
ANYMORE.
>> TWO SEASONS LATER, THE TEAM
WENT 34-3,
WINNING THE BIG EAST
CHAMPIONSHIP.
>> ♪ THEY'RE PLAYING
BASKETBALL ♪
>> THEY ADVANCED THROUGH THE
NCAA REGIONAL, THE FINAL FOUR TO
THE CHAMPIONSHIP GAME AGAINST
HOUSTON.
>> MICHAEL GRAHAM JUST
GOES UP AND TOMAHAWK DUNKS IT,
AND HE LOOKS AT PAT,
AND HE JUST POINTS AT HIM,
JUST TO LET HIM KNOW,
OK, WE--WE GOT THIS.
>> WOO!
>> GEORGETOWN WINS THE TITLE,
AND FRED BROWN GETS THE HUG.
>> THE HOYAS WERE WELCOMED BACK
WASHINGTON AS CHAMPIONS
AND COACH THOMPSON AS A HERO.
>> AND I THINK ALL OF US FEEL
A GREAT PRIDE IN WHAT YOU'VE
ACCOMPLISHED.
>> AS PRESIDENT REAGAN
CAMPAIGNED FOR RE-ELECTION
IN 1984, MITCH SNYDER,
THE LEADER OF HOMELESS ADVOCACY
GROUP "COMMUNITY FOR CREATIVE
NON-VIOLENCE," OR CCNV,
STAGED A HUNGER STRIKE TO DEMAND
THE ADMINISTRATION RENOVATE A
SHELTER IN AN ABANDONED FEDERAL
BUILDING.
>> THE ADMINISTRATION'S SAYING,
AND EVERYBODY'S NAME,
INCLUDING OURS, IT HAS NO
RESPONSIBILITY TO PEOPLE WHO
ARE THE POOREST OF THE POOR.
>> MY SISTER-IN-LAW
FOR A VERY BRIEF TIME WAS, UH,
IN HUD DEALING WITH THE
HOMELESS.
AND SHE WANTED TO GO AND
INTERVIEW MITCH SNYDER.
AND ESSENTIALLY THE
ADMINISTRATION SAID,
"DON'T DO IT."
AND "DON'T DO ANYTHING."
>> ♪ AND I NEED TO BE LOVED
JUST LIKE EVERYBODY ELSE DOES ♪
>> 51 DAYS INTO HIS PROTEST,
SNYDER GOT HIS WISH.
>> I THINK WE CAPITULATED TO
SOME DEGREE. TRUTH BE TOLD,
REAGAN WAS A SENSITIVE--I MEAN,
SOMETHING LIKE THAT WOULD AFFECT
HIM.
>> TWO DAYS LATER, PRESIDENT
RONALD REAGAN WAS RE-ELECTED.
>> YOU AIN'T SEEN NOTHING YET.
>> I HAD SEVERAL FRIENDS
THAT SEEMED TO HAVE THIS
CONTINUAL FLU BUG.
AND THEN IT BECAME PNEUMONIA,
AND THEN THEY JUST DIED.
>> AS REAGAN BEGAN HIS SECOND
TERM, A LACK OF ACTION TOWARDS
THOSE SUFFERING AND DYING FROM
HIV INFECTION PERSISTED.
>> WHITE HOUSE OFFICIALS
CONFIRMED THAT THE PRESIDENT HAS
NEVER TALKED TO HIS SURGEON
GENERAL ABOUT AIDS.
>> THOSE IN THE DISTRICT TURNED
TO THE "WASHINGTON BLADE" FOR
INFORMATION.
>> THE COMMUNITY DESPERATELY
NEEDED INFORMATION ABOUT THE
DISEASE.
>> ON APRIL 4, 1983, THE
WHITMAN-WALKER CLINIC HELD
D.C.'s FIRST PUBLIC
FORUM ON THE EPIDEMIC.
>> WHITMAN WALKER WAS ONE OF
THE FOUNDING FATHERS OF AIDS
INFORMATION, BUT THEY ALSO
HELPED HOUSE PEOPLE.
THEY HELPED TO FEED PEOPLE.
THEY HAD TO ACTUALLY STEP
IN AND BECOME INVOLVED IN THE
LINK BETWEEN THE DOCTORS AND THE
HOSPITALS AND THE PATIENTS.
BECAUSE A LOT OF PEOPLE WERE
BEING TURNED AWAY FROM
HOSPITALS.
>> ♪ THERE'S JUST NO CAUSE
THERE'S JUST NO CAUSE... ♪
>> BUT THE DEATHS OF TWO
PUBLIC FIGURES WITH TIES TO
WASHINGTON FORCED THE COUNTRY,
AND THE PRESIDENT, TO ACT.
>> ROCK HUDSON WAS
FAMILIAR WITH THE PRESIDENT
HIMSELF AND AN INDIVIDUAL WHO
HAD ONE PARTICULAR VERY
INFLUENTIAL FRIEND IN
WASHINGTON--ELIZABETH TAYLOR.
NOT ONLY WAS SHE AN ICON OF THE
MOVIES, SHE WAS ALSO MARRIED
TO A U.S. SENATOR FROM VIRGINIA,
JOHN WARNER.
AND SO MINDS WERE CHANGED
AND THE PERCEPTION BEGAN TO
SHIFT.
>> ...THAT SCIENCE WILL CONTINUE
TO FIND THE CRITICAL ANSWERS.
>> JERRY SMITH, MY FAVORITE
TIGHT END FOR THE WASHINGTON
REDSKINS,
WHEN HE WAS STRICKEN WITH
AIDS, IT BECAME APPARENT THAT
THIS HE-MAN WAS GAY.
>> RONALD REAGAN'S OPINION
DEFINITELY CHANGED BECAUSE
THESE WERE YOUR FRIENDS DYING.
SAME THING HAPPENED TO ME.
>> GAY RIGHTS! NOW!
GAY RIGHTS! NOW!
>> A YEAR AFTER JERRY SMITH'S
PASSING, AN ESTIMATED HALF A
MILLION PEOPLE DESCENDED ON
WASHINGTON FOR THE SECOND MARCH
FOR GAY AND LESBIAN RIGHTS.
>> ♪ EVERY ONE YOU MEET
EVERY STEP YOU TAKE... ♪
>> THE HIGHLIGHT, A MASSIVE
MEMORIAL QUILT COVERING THE MALL
WITH THE NAMES OF THE THOUSANDS
OF AMERICANS WHO HAD DIED OF
AIDS.
>> ♪ I'LL BE WATCHING YOU ♪
>> AMERICA IS A QUILT, MADE UP
OF MANY PATCHES, MANY PIECES,
MANY TEXTURES. BUT EVERYBODY
FITS!
>> EVERY ONE OF US WHO WERE
THERE JUST LOOKED AT EACH OTHER
AND EITHER CRIED OR SMILED OR A
COMBINATION OF THE TWO.
>> ♪ I'LL BE WATCHING YOU
EVERY STEP YOU TAKE
EVERY SMILE YOU... ♪
>> ♪ YEAH ♪
>> BY 1987, THE DECADE'S EARLY
PROMISE WAS BEGINNING TO FADE.
>> ♪ WE'RE ON THE ROAD
TO NOWHERE
COME ON INSIDE ♪
>> ATTEMPTS TO GIVE THE DISTRICT
CONGRESSIONAL REPRESENTATION AND
STATEHOOD HAD GONE NOWHERE.
MANY STARTED TO ASK IF BARRY'S
MANAGEMENT OF THE CITY WAS PART
OF THE PROBLEM.
>> MARION BARRY WAS
ALREADY STARTING TO HAVE SOME
BUDGET PROBLEMS, RUNNING SOME
DEFICITS.
BUT HE DIDN'T CUT HIS CRONY
CONTRACTS, HE DIDN'T CUT WASTE,
FRAUD, AND ABUSE.
WHAT HE CUT WAS
1,500 POLICE OFFICERS.
>> MAYOR BARRY'S LIFESTYLE ALSO
RAISED QUESTIONS.
>> KAREN JOHNSON JUST TOLD
AUTHORITIES THAT SHE SOLD
THE MAYOR COCAINE 20-30 TIMES
FROM LATE 1980 TO 1982.
>> HE WAS NOTORIOUS FOR
STAYING OUT LATE WITH WOMEN WHO
WERE NOT HIS WIFE.
THIS IS WHEN HE WOULD USE
THE SECURITY DETAIL TO
PROCURE A WOMAN FOR HIM.
>> MAYOR MARION BARRY TONIGHT
ANGRILY DENIED THAT HE HAS
BEEN HOSPITALIZED AFTER
OVERDOSING ON COCAINE.
>> MARION BARRY BECAME TOO
COMFORTABLE WITH POWER. AFTER
HE WON OVER THE OVERWHELMING
MAJORITY OF THE AFRICAN-AMERICAN
POPULATION, HE FELT HE
COULD NO LONGER BE REMOVED.
>> HE WAS POWERFUL. HE COULD
MAKE A LOT OF THINGS HAPPEN IN
YOUR WARD.
HEY, DO YOU WANT THAT NEW FIRE
STATION?
DO YOU WANT THE LIBRARY?
>> GROWING DISCONTENT THAT LED
BARRY TO HAVE REAL COMPETITION
IN THE '86 MAYORAL ELECTION.
>> IN WASHINGTON, D.C.,
WHERE THE VOTER REGISTRATION WAS
10:1 DEMOCRATS TO REPUBLICANS, I
GOT A THIRD OF THE VOTE.
>> THOUGH SCHWARTZ'S TALLY
EXCEEDED EVERYONE'S
EXPECTATIONS, BARRY'S BASE
DELIVERED HIM A THIRD TERM WITH
61% OF THE VOTE.
>> THE "WASHINGTON POST"
ENDORSED HIM 3 STRAIGHT TIMES,
I THINK WITH GROWING
RELUCTANCE OR SOMETHING LIKE
THAT THE THIRD TIME.
>> BUT THE ELECTORATE AND
OPINION PAGES' COOLING ON BARRY
DID NOTHING TO SLOW HIS LARGER-
THAN-LIFE PERSONA.
>> WHEN PEOPLE ELECTED ME,
THEY DIDN'T ELECT ME POPE.
THEY ELECTED ME MAYOR. IF I GO
OUT AT NIGHT AT 9:00 OR 10:00,
WHAT'S THAT GOT TO DO WITH
ANYTHING?
>> BECAUSE OF HIS SHORT
ATTENTION SPAN, HE COULD
COMPARTMENTALIZE, HE COULD--
I MEAN, HE WOULD GO OUT
AT NIGHT WITH THE
FAMOUS "I'M A NIGHT OWL."
AS IF THAT WOULDASH THINGS
AWAY.
>> THE "CITY PAPER" DUBBED HIM
"MAYOR FOR LIFE."
>> WHEN YOU FOR THE PEOPLE,
THE PEOPLE KNOW IT. HE'S THE
ONLY ONE I SEEN THAT STOOD THERE
FOR US.
>> IF HE HADN'T BEEN MAYOR,
BARRY'S NIGHTLIFE WOULD NOT HAVE
BEEN SURPRISING AS D.C.'s BAR
AND CLUB SCENE REACHED A PEAK
IN THE MID '80s.
>> THERE WAS THIS CLUB CALLED
THE FOX TRAPPE, AND IT WAS
THE PLACE TO GO FOR THE BUPPIES.
>> THAT WAS THE
QUINTESSENTIAL PLACE WHERE
HIGH-INCOME,
SOPHISTICATED PEOPLE GO.
>>OU'D DRESS UP TO GO
THERE; YOU DRESSED UP YOUR
BEHAVIOR, TOO, AND YOUR MANNERS
IN MOST CASES.
>> BECAUSE THE FOXTRAPPE WASN'T
JUST A NIGHTCLUB, IT WAS A D.C.
INSTITUTION WHERE MEMBERS OF THE
BLACK CONGRESSIONAL CAUCUS
RUBBED SHOULDERS WITH AFRICAN-
AMERICAN BUSINESS LEADERS
AND CELEBRITIES.
>> [MUSIC PLAYING]
>> THERE WAS ALWAYS AN
INTERESTING EVENT GOING ON, A
LOT OF THEM WERE FUNDRAISERS.
A LOT OF THEM WERE WHAT WE WOULD
CALL JUST NETWORKING EVENTS.
IT WAS VERY IMPORTANT
FOR YOUNG BLACK PROFESSIONALS
TO FEEL A SENSE OF
SOLIDARITY AND TO SHARE THEIR
EXPERIENCES.
AND IT WAS A GREAT WAY TO
SOCIALIZE AND ALSO TO MEET NEW
PEOPLE.
>> IT WAS NICE, BUT YOU
KNOW, IT WAS AN IMPORTANT
STEP IN THE PROCESS.
>> D.C.'s SUPER-DISCOS
WERE ALSO EXPERIENCING
UNPARALLELED POPULARITY.
>> THE PIER, THE LOST AND
FOUND, THE OTHER SIDE, IT WAS A
BLAST.
IT WAS A FRICKIN' HOOT!
INSANE.
REDSKINS CAME IN THEIR
REDSKINS JERSEYS.
YOU COULD RUN INTO EXTREMELY
FAMOUS PEOPLE, AND THEY ALL
MERGED TOGETHER.
>> A VIBRANT PARTY SCENE THAT
BECAME SYNONYMOUS WITH THE '80s
RECREATIONAL DRUG OF CHOICE.
>> EVERYONE DID COCAINE.
IT WAS EVERYWHERE.
AND IT WAS CONSIDERED TO BE LIKE
A COCKTAIL.
YOU HAD A GLASS OF GIN, YOU HAD
A LINE OF COKE.
>> BUT AS PARTICIPATION WAS
RELIANT ON A CERTAIN LIFESTYLE,
IT WAS SOMETHING MANY AVERAGE
AMERICANS NEVER EXPERIENCED.
>> IT WAS A SUBCULTURE THAT I
KNEW ABSOLUTELY NOTHING ABOUT
AND IT WAS BROUGHT TO THE
FOREFRONT.
>> IN 1984, SOPHOMORE LEN BIAS
FROM PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY LED
THE UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND TO
THE ATLANTIC COAST CONFERENCE
TITLE, BRINGING NATIONAL
ATTENTION TO THE TEAM.
LEN BIAS' SENIOR SEASON WAS
HIGHLIGHTED BY A WIN OVER THE
TOP RANKED TAR-HEELS.
>> MARYLAND HAS KNOCKED
OFF NORTH CAROLINA IN ONE OF THE
BIGGEST UPSETS THIS YEAR, AND
THERE IS ONE HAPPY LEN BIAS.
>> YOU COULDN'T STOP HIM.
HE--
HE HAD THE ATHLETICISM.
HE HAD THE DEFENSE.
HE CAN REBOUND.
>> SKILLS THAT MADE HIM THE
SECOND OVERALL PICK IN THE 1986
NBA DRAFT.
>> WE WERE JUST SO HAPPY AND IT
WAS JUST A WONDERFUL, WONDERFUL
TIME.
HE COMES BACK TO MARYLAND, AND
I AM NOT AT HOME.
AND I NEVER SEE HIM AGAIN.
>> ♪ PAINT YOUR TOE
SELL YOUR SOUL ♪
>> INVESTIGATORS THIS MORNING
ARE TRYING TO DETERMINE EXACTLY
WHAT CAUSED THE DEATH THURSDAY
OF FORMER UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND
BASKETBALL STAR LEN BIAS.
>> THE AUTOPSY SHOWED THAT BIAS
HAD DIED FROM A COCAINE
OVERDOSE.
>> LIKE I SAID, THERE WAS A
SUBCULTURE THAT I KNEW NOTHING
ABOUT UNTIL MY SON DIED AND THEN
BOOM, YOU FIND OUT THIS IS REAL
LIFE.
>> I LOVED YOU, LEONARD, AND
I'LL MISS YOU. I'LL SEE YOU
IN HEAVEN ONE DAY.
>> AS COCAINE USE WAS PEAKING
IN THE WASHINGTON REGION, A
NEW, MORE POTENT, SMOKABLE FORM
OF THE DRUG BEGAN TO APPEAR.
>> THE FIRST TIME THAT WE
MADE A SEIZURE OF CRACK WAS UP
IN NORTHWEST, AND FROM THEN ON
IT WAS ON.
>> ♪ OH, YEAH ♪
>> IT SEEMED LIKE SUDDENLY
ONE DAY WE WOKE UP, AND WE
WERE IN THE MIDDLE OF A CRACK
COCAINE EPIDEMIC.
AND THIS TIME IT WAS THE
CREWS OF KIDS WHO HAD GROWN
UP WITH MY OWN KIDS WHO
WERE ON THE CORNER SELLING CRACK
COCAINE, BATTLING OVER TURF.
>> ONE MINUTE IT FELT LIKE WE
WERE PUTTIN' QUARTERS INTO THE
SPACE INVADERS MACHINES TO, YOU
KNOW, BEIN' A DRUG DEALER.
YOU HAD TO SURVIVE, SO YOU
JOINED A GANG JUST TO AVOID
BEING SUPPRESSED BY A GANG.
>> WHILE YOUNG AFRICAN-AMERICAN
MEN BOTH PROFITED AND DIED
DURING THE CRACK EPIDEMIC,
SOME OF ITS MOST TRAGIC VICTIMS
WERE YOUNG WOMEN.
>> WHEN I WAS MUCH YOUNGER,
I FANCIED MYSELF A PHOTOGRAPHER,
AND I HAD TAKEN PHOTOS OF YOUNG
WOMEN IN MY NEIGHBORHOOD WHEN
THEY WERE 7, 8 YEARS
OLD, THE LIGHT IN THEIR EYES,
THE SMILES ON THEIR FACES.
AND TO SEE THOSE SAME YOUNG
WOMEN PROSTITUTING HERSELF ON A
CORNER IN HER OWN NEIGHBORHOOD
WHERE EVERYBODY KNEW HER TO
BUY CRACK COCAINE...
>> THROUGH IT ALL, THE CITY AND
POLICE DEPARTMENT SEEMED
POWERLESS.
>> THE CLEAN SWEEP OPERATION
WAS DESIGNED TO ATTACK THE
CROWDS THAT WERE GATHERING TO
BUY AND SELL DRUGS.
AND WE JUST ARRESTED
PEOPLE IN THE HUNDREDS.
>> ♪ ...ROCKET SHIP EXPLODES
AND EVERYBODY SPILLS BLOOD ♪
>> I WAS ONE OF THE ONES
THAT THEY GRABBED AND THREW
DOWN, AND THEY DIDN'T TAKE ME
STRAIGHT TO THE PRECINCT.
THEY HAD TO TAKE ME TO D.C.
GENERAL HOSPITAL FIRST BECAUSE I
WAS BEATEN UP PRETTY BADLY.
>> THERE WASN'T ANY STUDY TO
SAY, DOES THIS MAKE SENSE?
IS THERE ANY LONG-TERM IMPACT?
THE COURTS WOULD SAY WE
CAN'T PROCESS 700 PEOPLE. WE'D
COME IN MAKE THE ARREST, IN
TWO WEEKS, THEY'RE BACK, AND
THEY'RE DOING THE SAME THING.
>> WHILE THE HEADLINES WERE
DOMINATED BY BAD NEWS, THE
POPULARITY AND PROFITABILITY OF
LOCAL TV AND RADIO MADE IT AN
EXCITING TIME FOR THE BUSINESS.
>> IT WAS THE GRAND AGE OF
COMPETITION BETWEEN LOCAL
TELEVISION STATIONS AND LOCAL
RADIO STATIONS.
YOU COULD EXPERIMENT,
PEOPLE WERE A LITTLE LESS SAFE.
>> EARLIER IN THE DECADE ICONIC
RADIO STATION DC101 PUSHED THE
EXPERIMENTAL ENVELOPE TO ITS
LIMITS,
HIRING A YOUNG DJ NAMED HOWARD
STERN TO HOST ITS MORNING SHOW.
>> EVERYBODY WOULD COME IN THAT
DAY AND SAY,
DID YOU HEAR WHAT HOWARD STERN
DID OR SAID THIS MORNING?
ONE TIME WHEN HIS WIFE HAD
A MISCARRIAGE, HE DID AN ENTIRE
SHOW ON IT.
>> IF SOMEBODY DOESN'T WANT
TO LISTEN TO MY RADIO PROGRAM,
THEY SHOULD TURN THE DIAL AND
LISTEN TO SOME OTHER JERK.
>> WHILE HOWARD STERN WAS THE
MOST SHOCKING DJ IN TOWN, DONNY
SIMPSON WAS UNDISPUTED FAVORITE.
>> EVERY RADIO STATION WANTED
TO FIGURE OUT A WAY TO ATTRACT
YOUNG WHITES AND YOUNG BLACKS,
AND DONNIE STARTED MIXING THOSE
TWO KINDS OF MUSIC, AND
DONNIE WOULD SAY, "I'M PLAYING A
FUDGE RIPPLE."
HA HA!
>> ♪ WE ALL KNOW
THAT PEOPLE ARE THE SAME
WHEREVER YOU GO ♪
>> DONNIE HAD THIS SMILE.
HE HAD THE LAUGH.
HE HAD THE BUBBLY EYES.
>> GOOD LOOKS AND A PERSONALITY
MADE FOR A NEW NATIONAL TV
NETWORK.
>> WHEN WE PUT DONNIE ON
B.E.T. AS THE HOST OF VIDEO
SOUL...
>> I'M DONNIE SIMPSON.
JOIN ME TONIGHT FOR
"VIDEO SOUL."
THAT'S TONIGHT, "VIDEO SOUL,"
9 P.M. EASTERN TIME RIGHT HERE
ON B.E.T.
>> HE BECAME INSTANTLY
OVERNIGHT A CELEBRITY,
AND B.E.T.
BEGAN TO BE DEFINED BY DONNIE
SIMPSON AND "VIDEO SOUL."
>> WE'LL BE BACK. WE GOT A...
>> IT WAS NATIONAL, AND
SO IT ALLOWED US TO BROADEN
OUR SCOPE
ON WHO WE WERE AS A CULTURE.
>> WHILE CABLE TV WAS IN ITS
INFANCY, WASHINGTON'S LOCAL
AFFILIATES WERE AT THEIR HEIGHT.
>> HEY, YOU WANT DEPTH?
WATCH CHANNEL 26. THIS IS
CHANNEL 4. WE HAVE FUN HERE.
>> ♪ SO GOOD TO TURN TO ♪
>> CHANNEL 5, WASHINGTON'S
MOST-WATCHED STATION.
>> FROM WJLA-TV...
>> AS RATINGS FOR LOCAL NEWS
CREATED ADVERTISING DOLLARS, THE
BATTLE BETWEEN SPORTS
DEPARTMENTS BECAME PARTICULARLY
FIERCE.
>> IT TURNED INTO A GOLDEN
TIME OF COMPETITION BETWEEN
CHANNEL 9 AND CHANNEL 4.
GEORGE MICHAEL HAD AN OPEN
CHECKBOOK.
GEORGE COULD COVER ANYTHING HE
WANTED.
GLENN BRENNER, ON THE OTHER
HAND, WAS PROBABLY THE MOST
TALENTED, CREATIVE, HILARIOUS
CHARACTER WHO EVER WORKED IN
TELEVISION NEWS.
>> I MEAN, WHAT'S THE,
WHAT'S THE CHARGE?
>> YOU GOT AN OVER LARGE...
>> WEENIE?
>> WEENIE ON THE STREET, SIR.
>> MY WEENIE'S TOO BIG?
>> GEORGE AND GLENN HATED
EACH OTHER.
THEY WOULD GO TO THE SUPER
BOWL, GET THE ROOM NUMBER THAT
THE OTHER GUY WAS IN, AND THEN
WALK INTO THE BAR AND SAY,
"HEY, DRINKS ON THE HOUSE."
>> MOST RESIDENTS ALSO REMEMBER
A FAVORITE NEWS STATION.
>> MY FAVORITE WAS CHANNEL 4.
JIM VANCE WAS JUST COOL. HE'S
JUST A SMOOTH CAT.
HE HAD A WAY OF TELLING HIS
STORIES WITHOUT GIVING UP THE
COOL.
>> CHANNEL 9 WAS HELD IN HIGH
REGARD AS THE
NUMBER ONE NEWS STATION TO A LOT
OF PEOPLE BECAUSE THEY
COVERED THE NEWS STORIES WITHOUT
OPINIONS RAISED IN THEM.
>> STARTING WITH HIS THIRD TERM
THERE SEEMED TO BE A
DETERIORATION IN THE ATTENTION
THAT MARION BARRY PAID TO THE
CITY.
>> IN JANUARY 1987,
THE CITY WAS SHUT
DOWN BY A MASSIVE SNOW STORM.
>> EVERYTHING STOPPED.
I HAD ACTUALLY HOSTED A LARGE
PARTY THE NIGHT BEFORE, AND
WE CAME STUMBLING OUT THE DOOR
INTO 6 FEET OF SNOW.
>> THE DAY BEFORE BARRY LEFT
TOWN TO ATTEND THE SUPER BOWL IN
CALIFORNIA.
>> HE'S NO GOOD BECAUSE HE DON'T
CLEAN THE STREET!
>> WHILE THE MAYOR WAS IN
CALIFORNIA, THE REGION WAS HIT
WITH A BIGGER BLIZZARD, BUT
BARRY STUCK TO HIS PLANS,
REPORTEDLY PARTYING SO HARD HE
WAS TAKEN TO THE HOSPITAL.
BARRY RETURNED TO D.C. THE
NEXT DAY.
>> IT'S UNFORTUNATE THAT SO MUCH
SNOW FELL,
WHICH WE CERTAINLY AREN'T
RESPONSIBLE FOR.
>> BARRY'S LACK OF ATTENTION WAS
ESPECIALLY PROBLEMATIC AS CRACK-
RELATED VIOLENCE THREATENED TO
OVERRUN THE CITY.
>> THE STRANGE THING ABOUT HIM,
HE NEVER WOULD TELL YOU TO
DO ANYTHING EXCEPT LOCK UP THE
DRUG DEALERS.
>> OUTSIDE OF THE
KILLINGS, ONE OF THE LOWEST
CRIME RATES IN THE COUNTRY.
>> AT THE SAME TIME THE
DISTRICT'S YOUTH WERE DRAGGED
INTO THE EPIDEMIC, THE CITY CUT
FUNDING FOR RECREATIONAL
SERVICES, LEAVING GO-GOS
ONE OF THE FEW PLACES TO MEET
AND GATHER.
>> ONE ELEMENT OF GO-GO
IS CALL AND RESPONSE.
IT'S VERY EASY FOR A LEAD
TALKER TO ASK A CROWD, "IS
SOUTHEAST BETTER THAN
NORTHEAST?"
AND SO THERE'S THIS AUTOMATIC
TRIBALISM. A FEW GO-GO
BANDS WOULD SORT OF ADVERTISE
P.C.P., YOU KNOW.
"TELL ME NOW.
WHAT Y'ALL SMOKE?"
AND THE PEOPLE WOULD RESPOND,
"LOVE BOAT."
>> AND YOU GET A WHOLE BUNCH
OF KIDS TOGETHER JUST TO DANCE
AND ALL THAT, AND SOMEBODY PULLS
OUT A GUN.
>> GO-GO'S RISE TO NATIONAL
PROMINENCE STALLED AS THE MUSIC
BECAME IDENTIFIED WITH VIOLENCE.
>> IT WAS PART OF SOCIETY.
UNFORTUNATELY KNUCKLE HEADS LIKE
MUSIC, TOO.
>> ♪ I'M FEELING LIKE A... ♪
>> UNDER THE NAME THE "GO-GO
POSSE," A NUMBER OF LOCAL BANDS
RECORDED A SINGLE PROMOTING AN
END TO THE VIOLENCE CALLED,
"D.C. DON'T STAND FOR
DODGE CITY."
>> ♪ LIKE THE WILD, WILD WEST
AND ITS CALAMITY
BUT D.C. DON'T MEAN DODGE CITY
D.C. DON'T MEAN DODGE CITY
YEAH ♪
>> IT DIDN'T CHANGE MY LIFE
BECAUSE GO-GO MUSIC OFTENTIMES,
IT WOULD GLORIFY ALL OF THE
THINGS THAT THIS PARTICULAR SONG
WAS SPEAKING AGAINST.
>> AS THE DEATH TOLL MOUNTED,
THE CITY GAINED A DUBIOUS TITLE.
>> WASHINGTON IS NOW CALLED THE
MURDER CAPITAL OF THE USA.
>> MY KIDS WERE IN HIGH
SCHOOL AT THE TIME, AND THEY HAD
ON THEIR WALL A LIST OF THE
PEOPLE WHO THEY KNEW EITHER FROM
THEIR NEIGHBORHOOD OR THEIR
SCHOOL WHO HAD DIED.
BEFORE THEY GRADUATED FROM
DUNBAR HIGH SCHOOL THAT LIST HAD
GROWN TO 25 PEOPLE.
>> WHILE CRACK CREATED SQUALOR
IN PREVIOUSLY VIBRANT
RESIDENTIAL NEIGHBORHOODS,
THE CITY'S COMMERCIAL AREAS WERE
ENJOYING A RELATIVE BOOM.
>> DOWNTOWN WAS DEAD.
AND BARRY SAID WE'VE GOT TO
DO SOMETHING ABOUT THIS.
THE DEVELOPERS WENT TO HIM,
SAID, "WE WANT THIS, WE WANT
THAT," AND GAVE THEM THE
LAND VIRTUALLY FREE, AND THESE
PROJECTS WERE BUILT.
>> AND WE PERSUADED THE BANKS
AND OTHERS TO LEND MONEY TO
THESE DEVELOPERS.
>> AFTER SOME POLITICKING, THE
GEORGETOWN WATERFRONT WAS ONE OF
THE FIRST VISTAS TO SEE RESULTS.
>> MARION BARRY RECOGNIZED
THAT WASHINGTON HARBOR COULD BE
AN ENORMOUS BOON TO THE CITY.
AND SO HE WAS
VERY INSTRUMENTAL.
>> THE SUCCESS OF PROJECTS IN
GEORGETOWN AND DOWNTOWN GAVE
BARRY THE CONFIDENCE TO TRY TO
RE-DEVELOP LESS LIKELY
LOCATIONS, INCLUDING GROUND-ZERO
OF THE '68 RIOTS.
>> IF YOU TOLD SOMEONE YOU WERE
GOING TO 14 AND U, YOU WERE
GOING TO BUY DRUGS, PERIOD.
>> THE FRANK D. REEVES MUNICIPAL
CENTER, NAMED AFTER THE LAWYER
AND LOCAL CIVIL RIGHTS LEADER,
OPENED IN 1986.
>> THE PEOPLE WHO WERE GOING
TO WORK IN THOSE OFFICES EVERY
DAY WOULD NEED SERVICES.
AND EVEN THOUGH AT THE TIME IT
SEEMED FAIRLY FARFETCHED, THERE
WAS A CERTAIN SENSE THAT IT
WOULD RESTORE AN ELEMENT OF
VALIDITY TO A ONCE FLOURISHING
NEIGHBORHOOD.
>> SEVERAL LONG-CLOSED
ICONS OF THE PAST WERE ALSO
RESURRECTED.
THE OLD POST OFFICE,
A ROMANESQUE REVIVAL STRUCTURE
DATING TO 1899,
HAD BEEN ON THE VERGE OF THE
WRECKING BALL FOR YEARS.
>> SIR DAVID WILLS, WHO WAS
HEIR TO THE TOBACCO FORTUNE IN
ENGLAND, CAST A REPLICA OF THE
WESTMINSTER BELLS AS A
BI-CENTENNIAL GIFT TO THE UNITED
STATES.
HE HAD THIS IDEA THAT THEY
SHOULD HANG IN THE DOME OF THE
CAPITOL.
>> BUT THE CAPITOL WASN'T BUILT
FOR THAT PURPOSE.
>> ONE BONG OF THESE GREAT
BELLS AND THE CAPITOL DOME WOULD
BE SITTING DOWN ON THE MALL.
THE CONGRESS WAS SO CONCERNED
ABOUT THAT THEY
APPROPRIATED A NEW AMOUNT OF
MONEY, AND THAT WAS WHAT FINALLY
SAVED THE ENTIRE BUILDING.
>> ALL THIS WAS DONE WITH
PARTNERSHIPS.
AND I THINK THE RESULTS HAVE
BEEN AMAZING.
>> SAVING UNION STATION, A
NEGLECTED BEAUX ARTS MASTERPIECE
THAT HAD BECOME THE CITY'S
UNOFFICIAL HOMELESS SHELTER,
BECAME THE RESPONSIBILITY OF A
PUBLIC/PRIVATE PARTNERSHIP.
>> I THOUGHT IT WAS
VERY SUCCESSFUL.
THEY WERE VERY CAREFUL IN
PRESERVING GREAT SPACES.
>> D.C.'s DOWNTOWN AREAS
RECEIVED AN
ADDITIONAL BOOST AS A SLEW OF
LOCAL THEATERS OPENED THEIR
DOORS.
>> THESE LITTLE COMPANIES
STARTED SPRINGING UP BECAUSE
DOWNTOWN WAS SO EMPTY THAT THEY
COULD GET SPACE CHEAP.
THE WOOLY MAMMOTH AND THE STUDIO
THEATERS OPENING ON 14th STREET.
14th STREET SORT OF BECAME THE
CENTER OF ALTERNATIVE THEATER.
>> BUT AT FIRST RESIDENTS
WEREN'T CONVINCED.
>> I WOULD GO OVER THERE TO
WATCH SOME OF THEIR SHOWS.
YOU KNOW, 10, 15, 20
PEOPLE IN THE
AUDIENCE, PLUS THE ACTORS.
>> BUT IN TIME, PEOPLES'
RELUCTANCE TO COME DOWNTOWN
EASED, AND WASHINGTON BEGAN ITS
RISE TO AMERICA'S SECOND CITY OF
THEATER.
>> WASHINGTON WAS LIKE THAT.
I MEAN, IT HAD CERTAIN KINDS OF
CULTURAL NICHES, IF YOU WILL.
>> I'M A WASHINGTONIAN, AND
THE FIRST THEATER I EVER SAW
WAS FROM THE TOP BALCONY
OF THE NATIONAL.
>> AS WASHINGTON'S THEATER SCENE
GAINED COUNTRYWIDE ATTENTION, IT
ESTABLISHED AN AWARD
NAMED IN HONOR OF ONE OF THE
CITY'S MOST ACCLAIMED DAUGHTERS
TO RECOGNIZE LOCAL THEATRICAL
EXCELLENCE.
>> THE GREAT "WASHINGTON POST"
CRITIC RICHARD COE CALLED ON
HIS FRIENDSHIP WITH HELEN HAYES
AND TOGETHER THEY CREATED THE
HELEN HAYES AWARDS,
AND ONCE THE HELEN HAYES
AWARDS STARTED, MORE COMPANIES
STARTED POPPING UP.
BY THE END OF THE DECADE,
WASHINGTON WAS ON THE SAME
PLAYING FIELD AS CHICAGO.
>> THE REGION'S GROWING INTEREST
IN THE ARTS WAS EXPLOITED BY
WASHINGTON'S TV AFFILIATES,
STILL HUNGRY FOR NOVEL
PROGRAMMING.
>> THE KING OF THE CRITICS
IN WASHINGTON, D.C.,
WAS DAVEY MARLIN JONES.
DAVEY WAS ONE OF THE MOST
INTERESTING PEOPLE I HAD EVER
MET.
>> THERE MAY BE SOMETHING THERE.
>> DAVEY WORE HATS.
HE ALSO PUSHED THE ENVELOPE
WITH HIS CLOTHES, HE PUSHED HIS
ENVELOPE IN EVERY WAY.
>> TIGHT, TAUT, TENSE.
>> DAVEY OWNED THIS TOWN.
>> ...INSIDE THE THEATER
CALLED LIFE.
>> A POPULAR FORMAT THAT
ENCOURAGED IMITATION.
>> EVERY STATION IN TOWN
HAD A CRITIC, AND IT WAS BECAUSE
WE WERE ALL TRYING TO COMPETE
WITH DAVEY. IT WAS ONE OF THE
GREAT GAGS OF LOCAL TELEVISION.
WHEN HE FINISHED HIS REPORT, YOU
DIDN'T KNOW IF HE LIKED THE
MOVIE OR NOT.
>> HOPE YOU'LL FIND ONE
CINEMATIC SPARKLER AMONG THEM.
DAVEY MARLIN JONES.
>> I TRIED TO MAKE MYSELF
DIFFERENT FROM DAVEY, SO I USED
A RATING SYSTEM.
ON MY SCALE OF 1-4 STARS,
"RAIDERS OF THE LOST ARK"
GETS A 5.
SO AT LEAST WHEN I WAS
FINISHED, YOU WOULD KNOW WHAT I
THOUGHT OF THE MOVIE OR NOT.
>> IN 1986, WASHINGTON'S
FOOTBALL TEAM
PICKED UP JOURNEYMAN QUARTERBACK
DOUG WILLIAMS TO BACK UP ITS
YOUNG PHENOM, JAY SCHROEDER.
DURING THE FOLLOWING SEASON,
WILLIAMS SHARED QUARTERBACK
DUTIES WITH THE OFT-INJURED
SCHROEDER.
BUT ONCE THE TEAM MADE IT TO THE
PLAY-OFFS,
WILLIAMS' PERFORMANCE PUT AN END
TO ANY CONTROVERSY.
>> WE HAD TO GO TO CHICAGO,
PLAY IN 13 BELOW TEMPERATURE.
WE WON.
THE CHAMPIONSHIP GAME AGAINST
THE MINNESOTA VIKINGS, I
CAME OFF THE BENCH AND WE WON
THE GAME, AND AT THE COACHES
PRESS CONFERENCE HE MENTIONED
THAT I WAS GOING TO BE THE
STARTING QUARTERBACK.
BEING THE FIRST AFRICAN-AMERICAN
TO PLAY IN THE SUPER BOWL,
I REALLY CHERISHED THAT TIME AND
FOR TWO WEEKS LEADING UP TO THAT
GAME IT WAS PRETTY MUCH CRAZY.
>> THE GAME STARTED OUT BADLY.
>> TOUCHDOWN DENVER, 56...
>> THE SCORE WAS 10-0
AGAINST THE REDSKINS IN
THE FIRST QUARTER.
>> AND THEN IT GOT WORSE.
>> I HYPER-EXTENDED MY KNEE.
DIDN'T KNOW AT THAT
PARTICULAR TIME WHETHER OR NOT I
WAS GOING TO BE ABLE TO FINISH
THE FOOTBALL GAME.
>> I WAS GOING TO SUBSTITUTE FOR
HIM, HE SAID, "HEY, GET BACK
OUT. THIS IS MY TEAM."
>> IN AN HISTORIC REVERSAL OF
FORTUNE, THE TEAM SCORED 5
TOUCHDOWNS IN THE SECOND
QUARTER.
>> TOUCHDOWN!
WASHINGTON TAKES THE LEAD!
>> EVERYTHING WE CALLED WORKED.
>> HE'S GOT SANDERS IN THE
CLEAR. AT THE 10, TOUCHDOWN!
TOUCHDOWN WASHINGTON REDSKINS!
AND A NEW SUPER BOWL RECORD!
>> I REMEMBER HIM HOLDING THAT
HELMET WHEN HE SCORED 35 POINTS
IN THE SECOND QUARTER.
IT WAS PROBABLY
THE GREATEST QUARTER OF A GAME
IN SUPER BOWL HISTORY.
>> DOUG WILLIAMS, THE MVP
OF SUPER BOWL XXII.
>> WILLIAMS WAS THE FIRST
BLACK QUARTERBACK TO START, OR
WIN, A SUPER BOWL,
AND WAS CROWNED THE
GAMES MOST VALUABLE PLAYER.
>> IT WAS ONE OF THOSE
TIMES THAT I RAISED MY HAT AND
THINKING TO MYSELF, YOU KNOW,
I'D REALLY LIKE TO TELL SOME
PEOPLE WHERE TO GO, BUT IT
WASN'T IN MY NATURE TO DO IT.
[CHEERING]
>> AS THE '80s DREW TO A CLOSE,
BARRY'S LIFESTYLE CONTINUED TO
MAKE HEADLINES.
>> AT NO TIME DID I SEE
ANY DRUGS, USE ANY DRUGS,
OR HAVE ANY KNOWLEDGE OF
ANY DRUGS.
>> THAT LITTLE WHITE POWDER IS
SO POWERFUL.
IT CAUSES YOU TO DO THINGS THAT
YOU THOUGHT YOU NEVER WOULD DO.
>> THE FBI UNCOVERED MORE
ALLEGATIONS OF DRUG USE AND
RAMPANT CORRUPTION AMONG BARRY'S
STAFF, THAT INCLUDED DEPUTY
MAYOR IVANHOE DONALDSON.
>> I HAVE BEEN TRIED,
CONVICTED, SENTENCED, AND DOIN'
TIME BY SOME MEMBERS OF THE
MEDIA.
>> I THINK MARION WAS VERY GOOD
ABOUT PLAYING THE VICTIM.
SOMEBODY SET HIM UP, SOMEBODY
WAS PICKING ON HIM.
>> HE DIDN'T HAVE THE DISCIPLINE
TO STICK TO VIRTUALLY ANYTHING.
I'VE HEARD MORE FROM BARRY
ABOUT HOW HE'S GOING TO
"BEHAVE BETTER THAN I HAVE FOR
MY OWN SON."
>> DESPITE IT ALL BARRY RETAINED
A GRIP ON POWER,
KEPT AFLOAT BY HIS POPULIST
APPEAL.
>> I THINK THAT SOME BLACK
FOLKS IN THE CITY REALLY THOUGHT
THAT PEOPLE WERE GOING AFTER
MARION BECAUSE HE WAS BLACK, AND
I DON'T THINK THAT WAS
NECESSARILY THE CASE.
>> I'M A VERY CONTROVERSIAL
PERSON BECAUSE I SPEAK OUT, BUT
ON THE OTHER HAND, I'M LOVED BY
A LOT OF PEOPLE.
IN FACT, PEOPLE SAY, "MARION
BARRY, YOU'RE THE BEST MAYOR WE
EVER HAD!"
THEY TELL THE TRUTH, TOO.
HA HA!
>> MARION BARRY DOMINATED
WASHINGTON IN THE '80s.
>> HE WAS THE SUN AROUND WHICH
WE ALL ORBITED.
>> THE GOOD THINGS, THE BAD
THINGS.
>> BUT EVEN THOUGH THE CITY AND
THE MAYOR'S EARLY PROMISE WERE
NOW LOST AMONGST DYSFUNCTI AND
DECAY, RESIDENTS DEPARTED THE
'80s WITH GOOD MEMORIES
AND OPTIMISM FOR THE FUTURE.
>> YOU COULD DO 60 MILES AN HOUR
UP MASS AVENUE AND NOBODY WOULD
BLINK AN EYELASH.
>> MY KIDS, WHO GREW UP IN
THE MIDDLE OF THAT, LOOK BACK
FONDLY ON THEIR YOUNGER DAYS.
I'LL NEVER FORGET WHEN THEY
GRADUATED, THEY SAID, "WE KNOW
THE BEST PART OF OUR LIVES ARE
PROBABLY BEHIND US RIGHT NOW."
>> DANGER IS EXCITING.
THERE WAS LOTS OF OPPORTUNITY
FOR ART TO SPRING UP
LIKE LITTLE FLOWERS IN THE
GARDEN.
AND IT WAS A WONDERFUL
COMBINATION.
>> ♪ KEEP ON MOVING
DON'T STOP
LIKE THE HANDS OF TIME
CLICK CLOCK
FIND YOUR OWN WAY TO STAY
THE TIME WILL COME ONE DAY
WHY DO PEOPLE CHOOSE TO LIVE
THEIR LIVES...
THIS WAY?
YEAH
KEEP ON MOVING, DON'T STOP, NO
KEEP ON MOVING
OH, HO, WHOA... ♪
>> DISCOVER MORE ABOUT
WASHINGTON IN THE '80s AT
WETA.ORG.
♪♪