LIVINGSTON COUNTY SHERIFF TOM
DOUGHERTY SAYS IT'S UP TO HIS
DEPUTIES' <Sheriff Tom
Dougherty, Livingston County
Sheriff: (56:59) And ultimately
if their license is removed and
they don't have that privilege
anymore they're extremely upset.
They have to rely on friends and
neighbors and families for
rides. (08) But I would say as
sheriff, my number one priority
is keeping the roads safe. (12)
>
I WANTED TO KNOW HOW MANY
REPORTS ARE FILED EVERY YEAR?
HOW MANY DRIVERS LOSE THEIR
LICENSE?
AND WHY DOES ONE PERSON GET A
ROAD TEST LIKE ROSALIE AND
ANOTHER DRIVER DOESN'T?
THE STATE DMV WOULDN'T ANSWER
THOSE SPECIFIC QUESTIONS.
BUT WROTE IN AN EMAIL... "The
thorough review process allows a
driver to demonstrate their
fitness to drive and helps the
DMV ensure safety on New York's
roadways for all who use them,
which is our top priority."
<Brean: (45:39) How has this
impacted your life? >
<Brean:
Rosalie Zito, license revoked
after road test: (39:55) I need
to be independent. And I've
always been independent. What
can I say? (40:05) >
BB, NEWS10NBC.
MORE PLANS WERE ANNOUNCED
TODAY FOR SKYVIEW ON THE RIDGE,
THE RE-DEVELOPMENT OF THE FORMER
IRONDEQUOIT MALL.
ST. ANN'S COMMUNITY WILL
EXPAND THEIR ADULT DAY HEALTH
CARE SERVICE THERE IN 20-20.
THEY PROVIDE CARE FOR OLDER
ADULTS AND PEOPLE WITH
DISABILITIES.
ST. ANN'S SAYS THERE'S A
GROWING NEED FOR ADULT DAY
HEALTH CARE SERVICES IN OUR
COMMUNITY, AND THE NEW LOCATION
WILL DOUBLE THE NUMBER OF PEOPLE
THAT CAN BE SERVED.
IT OVERALL WAS A NICE DAY HERE
IN DOWNTOWN ROCHESTER. I WAS
TRACKING A FEW SPOTTY SHOWERS
EARLIER ON TODAY SOUTH OF THE
CITY BUT EVEN THOSE HAVE TAPERED
OFF AND NOW THINGS ARE BECOMING
MOSTLY SUNNY NORTH OF THE LAKE
BREEZE AND PARTLY CLOUDY SOUTH
OF IT. THINGS TONIGHT WILL ALSO
STAY ON THE CLEAR SIDE WITH A
LOW OF SIXTY AND SOME AREAS IN
THE HIGHER ELEVATIONS
APPROACHING THE HIGH 50S.
TOMORROW IS ANOTHER MILD DAY
WITH ISOLATED SHOWERS IN THE
AFTERNOON BUT THINGS OVERALL
SHOULD STAY ON THE CALM SIDE
WITH A HIGH OF 81 DEGREES. THE
REST OF THE WEEK WILL TURN OUT
NICE AS WELL AS HIGH PRESSURE
DOMINATES BUT A SOUTHERLY WIND
WILL MOVE IN BY THE WEEKEND
CREATING WARM AND MUGGY
CONDITIONS. THE NEXT CHANCE OF
RAIN DOES NOT RETURN UNTIL
SUNDAY NIGHT IN TO MONDAY. THIS
ALL THANKS TO A FRONT THAT WILL
SETUP JUST NORTH OF WESTERN NEW
YORK. THIS WILL BE A SLOW MOVER
MEANING THAT WE COULD GET A FEW
DAYS OF ON AND OFF SHOWERS
THROUGH THE EARLY PART OF NEXT
WEEK. ALONG WITH THE ADDITIONAL
CLOUD COVER WE WILL SEE HIGH
TEMPERATURES REDUCED A LITTLE
BIT BACK IN TO THE LOW 80S TO
HIGH 70S. LOWS WILL REMAIN IN TO
THE 60S DUE TO THE OVERNIGHT
CLOUD COVER REDUCING THE DIURNAL
TEMPERATURE SWINGS AS SHOWN ON
OUR NEWS TEN TEN DAY FORECAST IN
TO NEXT WEEK.
IT'S A SIGN THAT WEEK.
FORECAST IN TO NEXT NEWS TEN TEN
DAY AS SHOWN ON OUR TEMPERATURE
SWINGS DIURNAL COVER REDUCING
THE OVERNIGHT CLOUD 60S DUE TO
THE WILL REMAIN IN TO THE 80S TO
HIGH 70S. LOWS BACK IN TO THE
LOW REDUCED A LITTLE BIT
TEMPERATURES SEE HIGH CLOUD
COVER WE WILL WITH THE
ADDITIONAL NEXT WEEK. ALONG THE
EARLY PART OF SHOWERS THROUGH
THE EARLY PART OF NEXT WEEK.
ALONG WITH THE ADDITIONAL CLOUD
COVER WE WILL SEE HIGH
TEMPERATURES REDUCED A LITTLE
BIT BACK IN TO THE LOW 80S TO
HIGH 70S. LOWS WILL REMAIN IN TO
THE 60S DUE TO THE OVERNIGHT
CLOUD COVER REDUCING THE DIURNAL
TEMPERATURE SWINGS AS SHOWN ON
OUR NEWS TEN TEN DAY FORECAST IN
TO NEXT WEEK.
IT'S A SIGN THAT FOOTBALL
SEASON IS ALMOST HERE!
WHAT YOU NEED TO KNOW ABOUT
BUFFALO BILLS TRAINING CAMP IF
YOU PLAN ON GOING.
PLUS,
WHICH LOCAL COUNTY IS
OPTING OUT - OF MAKING YOU PAY A
TAX FOR PAPER BAGS AT THE
GROCERY STORE.
BUT FIRST -
HERE'S WHAT WE'RE WORKING
ON FOR NEWS10NBC AT 11.
THE ROCHESTER AREA IS
EXPERIENCING A CRAFT BEER BOOM.
SO WHERE DO OUR BREWERS GET
THEIR INGREDIENTS?
IT TURNS OUT A LOCAL HOP
FARM IS A MAJOR SUPPLIER.
IN OUR SMALL BUSINESS
SPOTLIGHT -- WE TAKE YOU TO
COBBLESTONE HOP YARD.
THAT'S TONIGHT AT 11.