>>> ARE YOU READY?
WE ARE HOURS AWAY FROM SNOW AND
ICE.
OUR MID UROLOGIST ARE WATCHING
YOU WALKING YOU THROUGH, HOUR
BY HOUR.
>>> AND HIS BACK, BERNIE
SANDERS IS OFFICIALLY RUNNING
FOR PRESIDENT, AGAIN.
>>> PLUS, SPEAKING OUT, ONE OF
THE WOMEN ACCUSING JUSTIN FOR
EFFECTS OF SEXUAL MISCONDUCT
SAID SHE'S WILLING TO TESTIFY.
AND WE'VE LEARNED OF SECRET
GUIDELINES #
>>> SLOP OF SNOW AND ICE WILL
LEAVE MUCH OF THE METRO
TEMPORARILY PARALYZED.
LET'S GET TO WHAT YOU NEED TO
KNOW ABOUT THE APPROACHING AND
IMPENDING STORM.
WE COULD SEE UP TO SIX INCHES
IN THE METRO.
POWER OUTAGES ARE POSSIBLE AS
WELL.
THE IMPACT WILL BE SUBSTANTIAL
TO THE ROADS AS WELL AS ON AIR.
OUR TEAM IS ON TOP OF THIS
STORM, MICHAEL HAS A LOOK AT
SNOW PREPARATIONS NDC AND ALSO
TELL US HOW OFFICIALS IN
MARYLAND AND VIRGINIA ARE
GETTING READY FOR THE STORM AS
WELL.
WHAT TO LOOK OUT FOR AND IN
YOUR NEIGHBORHOOD, LET'S GET
THIS UPDATED FORECAST RIGHT NOW.
MELISSA, WE'VE GOT SOME SERIOUS
UPDATES ALREADY IN THE
NEWSROOM?
>> I JUST GOT OFF THE PHONE
WITH BOTH METEOROLOGISTS, WE
THINK THERE'S GOING TO BE A LOT
MORE SLEEP THAT'S HAPPENING
TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
WE HAVE UPDATED THE SNOW TOTALS.
HERE'S THE LATEST AS OF RIGHT
NOW, WE WILL START OFF WITH THE
HIGHEST TOTAL, THESE WILL
INCLUDE LOUDOUN COUNTY, UPPER
MONTGOMERY COUNTY AND POINTS
NORTH AND WEST OF THAT AND SET
OF 6-8 INCHES, WE ARE GOING 4-6
INCHES BECAUSE WE THINK IT'S
MORE SLEEP THAT'S GOING TO BE
HAPPENING TOMORROW AFTERNOON
WHICH WOULD MEAN A LITTLE LESS
SNOW.
LET'S GO INTO THE D.C. AREA,
THE BELTWAY, PRINCE GEORGES
COUNTY, THE NORTHERN HALF OF
THIS, TO-FOUR INCHES OF SNOW
AND SLEET COMBINED, THEN WE
HAVE FAR SOUTHERN MARYLAND,
THAT IS AN ADJUSTMENT FROM WHAT
WE SHOWED YOU YESTERDAY EVENING
ON THE NEWS AT 5 PM.
AND, WE ARE GOING TO BE LOOKING
OVER MORE INFORMATION THIS
AFTERNOON.
WE'VE GOT ANOTHER SET OF MODELS
COMING IN, THERE WILL LIKELY BE
ADDITIONAL ADJUSTMENTS TO THAT
BUT THE IMPACTS ARE LOCKED IN
AT THIS POINT.
WE KNOW THERE'S GOING TO BE
SNOW TOMORROW MORNING, IT'S
GOING TO TRANSITION OVER TO
SLEET AND FREEZING RAIN, AND
THAT IS GOING TO CAUSE MORE
IMPACTS FOR TRAVEL, AND THE
FREEZING RAIN WILL BE MORE
SIGNIFICANT ALONG I 81, WHERE
DO YOU THINK WE CAN SEE POWER
OUTAGES.
FOR THE METRO, THE PRIMARY
IMPACT IS GOING TO BE TRAVEL,
WHEN IT BECOMES DIFFICULT,
IT'LL BECOME DANGEROUS AS THE
MORNING UNFOLDS. HERE'S THE
TIMING ON FUTURECAST, WE WILL
START OFF ON MIDNIGHT TONIGHT,
ENJOY THAT LITTLE BIT OF
SUNSHINE OUT THERE, CLOUDS ARE
BUILDING BY MIDNIGHT, WE ARE
STILL DRY BUT THE SNOW IS
ARRIVING TOMORROW MORNING,
ARRIVING IN BC SOMETIME BETWEEN
FIVE-6 AM, WE WILL SEE THAT
SNOW LINE SHIFTING NORTHEAST,
AND AFTER 7 AM, THE SNOW RATE
WILL START TO PICK UP, EVEN IF
YOU ARE TRYING TO DRIVE INTO
WORK TOMORROW MORNING AND IT'S
FAIRLY SNOWING, IT GETS WORSE
AS IT GOES THROUGHOUT THE
MORNING.
LET'S GO TO NOON, SOUTHWEST
SIDE OF THE METRO, IT WILL
TRANSITION FROM SNOW INTO SLEET
AND FREEZING RAIN, WE'VE GOT
THE TRANSITION NDC HAPPENING AT
2 PM, NOW WE'VE GOT THIS HUGE
AREA IN PINK OF SNOW, SLEET AND
PHRASING RAIN FREEZING RAIN,
GUYS, WE'VE GOT FREEZING RAIN
AND SLEET. FOR D.C., HERE'S
YOUR TIMING, 6 AM, SNOW, ONCE
WE GET TO NOON WE'VE GOT THIS
MAKES STARTING TO HAPPEN, AND
IT'S NOT UNTIL THE VERY END OF
THE DAY, 5 PM ONWARD, DO YOU
SEE TRANSITIONS INTO RAIN, I'LL
TALK MORE ABOUT IMPACT, ZONE BY
ZONE, COMING UP IN JUST A FEW
MINUTES.
>>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
ANY TIME THERE'S A THREAT OF
SEVERE WINTER WEATHER IN THE
DISTRICT, THE DEPARTMENT OF
WORKS AND THE DEPARTMENT OF
TRANSPORTATION JOIN FORCES TO
CREATE WHAT'S KNOWN AS THE SNOW
TEAM.
MICHAEL HAS MORE.
>> D.C. SNOW TEAM USES THE
NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE TO
MONITOR WEATHER REPORTS.
ONCE A WEATHER THREAT IS
FORECASTED THE SNOW TEAM
DECIDES ON AN ACTION PLAN BUT
IT'S NEVER ONE SIZE FITS ALL.
>> WE HAVE TO TAKE THE VERACITY
OF THE REPORTING THAT'S COMING
IN, HOW CONFIDENT THE WEATHER
FOLKS ARE ON THEIR FORECAST,
THEN WE HAVE TO ADD IN THE
FACTOR IF WE WANT TO MAKE SURE
WE ARE AHEAD OF THINGS.
>> THE NUMBER OF WORKERS,
EQUIPMENT AND SUPPLIES DEPENDS
ON THE PREDICTION OF THE STORM.
>> WE GET UP THERE, WHEN WE HAVE
BIG STORMS, OR IF WE GET INTO A
BIG ICE SITUATION.
IT'S A LARGE OPERATION.
>> WHEN THE THREAT IS MOST
SEVERE, THE SNOW TEAM WILL
DEPLOY MORE THAN 800 PEOPLE AND
MORE THAN 500 PLOWS, ALL
WORKING 12 HOUR SHIFTS UNTIL
THE STORM IS OVER.>> THE ADDED
ICE WE ARE EXPECTED TOMORROW
WILL CAUSE PROBLEMS AS WELL, A
COATING OF ICE CAN INCREASE THE
WEIGHT OF TREE BRANCHES AND
POWERLINES, PREPARED TO KEEP
THE CHILDREN AWAY FROM TREES
FROM THE STORM.
FAMILIES MAY ALSO WANT TO
PREPARE FOR THE POSSIBLE LOSS
OF POWER.
PLEASE MAKE SURE YOU FOLLOW THE
DIRECTIONS FROM THE
MANUFACTURER.
>> OUR WEATHER TEAM IS UPDATING
THE FORECAST EVERY HOUR AND ARE
REPORTERS ARE GATHERING MORE
INFORMATION ABOUT DELAYS AND
CLOSURES.
STAY CONNECTED WITH US.
>>> THREE PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
ARRESTED AND CHARGED IN THE
MURDER OF A 27-YEAR-OLD GIRL
AND FATHER.
CHRISTOPHER TURNER WENT MISSING
ON JANUARY 20, HIS CAR WAS
DISCOVERED DAYS LATER IN
HAGERSTOWN.
HIS BODY WAS FOUND LAST MONTH
IN WEST VIRGINIA.
TODAY WE LEARNED THREE PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN ARRESTED, FOR HIS
MURDER, THEY ARE FACING MURDER,
ASSAULT AND ROBBERY CHARGES.
HE HAD TWO YOUNG CHILDREN AND A
THIRD ON THE WAY.
>>> MARYLAND AND VIRGINIA HAVE
JOINED IN THE FIGHT TO STOP A
SOUTHERN BORDER WALL FROM BEING
BUILT.
LAST NIGHT, BOTH STATES JOINS
THE 16 STATE LAWSUIT AGAINST
THE TRAP ADMINISTRATION FUNDING
FOR THE BORDER WALL.
>> BOTH STATES, MARYLAND AND
VIRGINIA, STAND TO LOSE
SUBSTANTIAL AMOUNT OF FUNDING
FOR MILITARY CONSTRUCTION
PROJECTS, IF THE NATIONAL
EMERGENCY DECLARATION HOLD UP
IN COURT.
THE NATIONAL EMERGENCY
DECLARATION GIVES THE PRESIDENT
POWERS TO MOVE FUNDS AROUND
WITHOUT CONGRESSIONAL APPROVAL.
IN THIS CASE, THAT'S TO PAY FOR
THE BORDER WALL PROJECT.
$6 BILLION WILL COME FROM THE
MILITARY BUDGET, SO IN
VIRGINIA, THAT'S RIGHT $131
MILLION IN MILITARY
CONSTRUCTION PROJECTS.
MONEY MEANT FOR SIX BASES IN
VIRGINIA INCLUDING THE
PENTAGON.
THE STATE OF MARYLAND CAN LOSE
AS MUCH AS $513 MILLION IN
PROJECTS.
FUNDING FOR PROJECTS SUPPORTS
MEET AND JOINT BASE ANSWERS,
THAT'S WHAT MONDAY NIGHT, BOTH
STATES SIGNED ON TO BE PART OF
THE 16 STATE LAWSUIT AGAINST
PRESIDENT TRUMP NATIONAL
EMERGENCY.
>> BOTH MARYLAND AND VIRGINIA
AS ATTORNEY GENERALS SAID THE
SITUATION AT THE BORDER DOES NOT
CONSTITUTE A NATIONAL
EMERGENCY.
THAT'S GOING TO BE AT THE HEART
OF THE LAWSUIT, WHETHER OR NOT
WHAT THE PRESIDENT BELIEVES IS
HAPPENING AT THE BORDER IS A
NATIONAL EMERGENCY AND WHETHER
OR NOT THERE IS INFORMATION TO
SUPPORT THE REASONING.
>>> ONE MAN IS DEAD, THREE
OTHERS HURT AFTER A THREE CAR
ACCIDENT IN PRINCE GEORGE
COUNTY, IT HAPPENED AROUND 10
PM LAST NIGHT ON INDIAN HEAD
HIGHWAY. POLICE SAY IT INVOLVES
TWO SUVS AND A THIRD CAR.
POLICE ARE STILL INVESTIGATING
EXACTLY WHAT CAUSED THE
ACCIDENT.
>>> ONE WOMAN ACCUSING JUSTIN
FAIRFAX OF SEXUAL ASSAULT SAID
SHE WANTS TO TESTIFY IN PUBLIC.
MEREDITH WATSON BLASTED THE
GENERAL ASSEMBLY TO FOR THEIR
FAILURE TO HOLD PUBLIC HEARINGS
IN AN OP-ED PUBLISHED IN THE
WASHINGTON POST.
SHE CLAIMS FAIRFAX ASSAULTED
HER WHEN THE TWO WERE COLLEGE
STUDENTS.
>>> BERNIE STANDARDS SANDERS
OFFICIALLY ANNOUNCED HIS
CAMPAIGN FOR PRESIDENCY.
>>> I AM GOING TO RUN FOR
PRESIDENT.
THAT'S CORRECT.
>> WAS GOING TO BE DIFFERENT
THIS TIME?
>> WE ARE GOING TO WIN.
WE ARE GOING TO ALSO LAUNCH
WHAT I THINK IS UNPRECEDENTED
IN MODERN AMERICAN HISTORY,
THAT IS A GRASSROOTS MOVEMENT,
JOHN, TO LAY THE GROUNDWORK FOR
TRANSFORMING THE ECONOMIC AND
POLITICAL LIFE OF THE COUNTRY.
THAT'S WHAT'S DIFFERENT.
>> THE 77-YEAR-OLD DEMOCRATIC
SOCIALIST CHALLENGED HILLARY
CLINTON IN THE DEMOCRATIC
RESIDENTIAL PRIMARY IN 2016,
SANDERS HAS RESHIPPED HIM
ACCREDIT POLITICS AND EARN A
LOYAL FOLLOWING WITH HIS WITH
HIS PASSIONATE DEFIANCE.
>>> LARRY HOGAN SAT DOWN WITH
BRUCE TO TALK ABOUT A POSSIBLE
RUN IN 2020, HOGAN HAS HIGH
APPROVAL RATINGS AS REPUBLICAN
GOVERNOR IN A VERY BLUE STATE
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN HE IS A
LOT OF SUPPORT RUNNING FOR
PRESIDENT.>> CAN I CALL YOU A
MODERATE REPUBLICAN?
>> YOU COULDN'T SURVIVE THE
PRIMARY.
>> SO YEAH, LOOK, I'M NOT
THINKING ABOUT THAT.
OUR SYSTEM IS SUCH THAT THE
MOST LIBERAL DEMOCRATS USUALLY
WINS THE DEMOCRATIC MANY, THE
MOST CONSERVATIVE REPUBLICAN
WINS THE REPUBLICAN NOMINATION.
>> A NEW POLL SHOWS THAT 55% OF
MARYLAND RESIDENTS DON'T WANT
THE GOVERNOR TO RUN FOR
PRESIDENT.
85% OF THOSE INTERVIEWED SAID
THE GOVERNOR IS LIKABLE, 80%
APPLY WHAT HE'S DOING WITH THE
STATE GOVERNMENT.
SOME REPUBLICANS FEEL HE WOULD
MAKE A GOOD CHALLENGER TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>>> STILL TO COME, A NEW REPORT
REVEALS THE CATHOLIC CHURCH HAS
SECRET GUIDELINES FOR WHAT TO
DO WHEN PRIE
>>>
A SHOCKING REPORT FROM THE NEW
YORK TIMES SAYS THE CATHOLIC
CHURCH HAS BEEN AWARE OF PRIESTS
FATHERING CHILDREN FOR DECADES.
IT ALSO REVERED REVEALED THEIR
SECRET RULES ON HOW TO HANDLE
THE SITUATION.
>> THE VATICAN REVEALED IT HAS
SECRET GUIDELINES FOR PRIESTS
WHO FATHER CHILDREN DESPITE
THEIR VOWS OF CELIBACY.
THIS IS ALL ACCORDING TO A
REPORT BY THE NEW YORK TIMES.
IT COMES AT A TIME WHERE THE
CATHOLIC CHURCH IS DEALING WITH
A SLEW OF SCANDALS INVOLVING
SEXUAL ABUSE OF CHILDREN.
THE REPORT TELLS A STORY OF ONE
MAN, WHOSE FATHER WAS A
CATHOLIC PRIEST.
WHEN ASKED BY THE NEWSPAPER IF
THESE SECRET RULES EXIST, THE
VATICAN CONFIRMED IT.
UNDER THOSE RULES, A PRIEST WHO
FATHERS A CHILD IS REQUESTED TO
LEAVE THE CHURCH AND DEVOTE
HIMSELF TO THAT CHILD HOWEVER,
A SPOKESPERSON FOR THE CHURCH
SAYS IT'S REALLY MORE A
FORMALITY THAN AN ORDER.
NOW PRIEST, THEY ARE REQUIRED
TO MAINTAIN A LIFE OF CELIBACY,
WE SEE WITH THE GROWING NUMBER
OF SEXUAL ABUSE SCANDALS, THAT
THESE VALVES ARE OFTEN BROKEN.
IT WAS JUST A FEW WEEKS AGO
THAT POPE FRANCIS KNOWLEDGE FOR
THE FIRST TIME, THAT THERE'S
ALSO BEEN SEXUAL ABUSE OF NUNS
BY PRIESTS AND BISHOPS INSIDE
THE CATHOLIC CHURCH.
THIS COMES AS CATHOLIC BISHOPS
FROM ALL OVER THE WORLD WILL
MEET THIS WEEK FOR A SUMMIT ON
THE ISSUE OF CLERICAL SEXUAL
ABUSE.
DURING THAT RETREAT, CHILDREN
OF PRIESTS WILL ALSO BE THERE,
MEET WITH MEMBERS OF THE
CATHOLIC CHURCH.
>>> THE VATICAN SAYS THE
GUIDELINES WERE DESIGNED TO
PROTECT THE CHILD, RECENTLY THE
CATHOLIC CHURCH IMPOSED A TIES
PUNISHMENT BY DEFROCKING FOR
THE FORMER CARDINAL PETER
McCARRICK, HE'S THE MOST SENIOR
FIGURE TO BE DEFROCKED IN
MODERN TIMES.
>>> A WELL-KNOWN DESIGNER, CARL
LAGERFELD PASSED AWAY TODAY, HE
WAS KNOWN FOR HIS ICONIC DESIGN
AS WELL AS HIS WHITE PONYTAIL
AND DARK GLASSES.
WORKING FOR DESIGNERS LIKE
SANDY AND CHANELLE, HIS AGE HAS
BEEN A MYSTERY FOR DECADES,
THERE ARE REPORTS THAT HE HAD
TWO BIRTH CERTIFICATES, ONE
DATED 1933, AND ANOTHER, 1938,
HE WAS AROUND 85 YEARS OLD.
>>> SOUTHWEST AIRLINES IS BEING
INVESTIGATED BY THE FAA OVER
BAGGAGE WEIGHT DISCREPANCIES.
AIR SAFETY REGULATORS ARE
INVESTIGATING WHETHER THE
CARRIER HAD WIDESPREAD
MISCALCULATIONS OF COMBINED
WEIGHT FOR CHECKED BAGS, LOADED
ONTO PLANES, SPARKING SAFETY
CONCERNS.
THE COMPANY SAID IT WILL BEGIN
A NEW BAGGAGE COUNTING
PROCEDURE BY THE END OF THE
YEAR.
>>> THE NEWS COMES AFTER A
WEEKEND WHERE SOUTHWEST SAW
MORE CANCELLATIONS AND DELAYS
THAN ANY OTHER USAir LINE,
ABOUT 100 FLIGHTS WERE CANCELED
OVER PRESIDENTS' DAY WEEKEND.
MORE THAN 40 PLANES HAD TO BE
TAKEN OUT OF SERVICE, THAT'S
MORE THAN DOUBLE THEIR USUAL
AVERAGE.
IT WAS ALL OVER MAINTENANCE
ISSUES AND AN INTERNAL MAN ML,
MANAGERS CALLED IT IN
OPERATIONAL STATE OF EMERGENCY.
>>> WE CAN TALK ABOUT
EMERGENCIES AS WE GET READY TO
FACE THIS STORM.
YOU TALKED ABOUT THE CHANGING
FORECAST, AND I DON'T THINK WE
CAN BRUSH AWAY THE FACT THAT
ICE AND SLEET IS STILL
DANGEROUS?
>> NO, IN FACT IT'S MORE
DANGEROUS THAN DRIVING ON THE
SNOW.
IN SNOW, YOU CAN GET A LITTLE
BIT OF TRACTION, WITH ICE, YOU
CAN'T.
WE'VE GOT MULTIPLE FACETS OF
THIS STORM IT'S GOING TO BE A
SLOPPY MESS.
NOW, LET'S TALK ABOUT THE SLEET
AND SNOW FALL POTENTIAL,
THROUGH ABOUT 4 PM TOMORROW,
OUR BULL'S-EYES ? THE NORTHWEST
OF BC, 4-6 INCHES, LOCALLY IT
COULD BE HIGHER IN SOME OF THE
HIGHER ELEVATIONS.
2-4 INCHES FOR D.C. I THINK
YOUR CHANGEOVER IS GOING TO
HAPPEN EARLIER, SO YOU DON'T
END UP WITH AS MUCH.
LET'S LOOK AT WHAT'S HAPPENING,
WHY ARE WE NOT GETTING ALL
SNOW?
IT ALL HAS TO DO WITH WHAT THE
TEMPERATURES IN THE ATMOSPHERE
LOOK AT.
I'VE PULLED UP HERE, A DIAGRAM,
IF IT'S ALL COLD FROM THE
CLOUDS TO WHERE IT SNOWS ON THE
GROUND, IT IS SNOW, BUT
SOMETIMES THESE SITUATIONS LIKE
WHAT WE ARE GETTING, WE HAVE A
LITTLE NOSE OF WARM AIR MIXING
AND, THAT WE GET FREEZING RAIN
AND SLEET AND FREEZING RAIN IS
THE MOST DIFFICULT FOR DRIVING,
THIS IS WHAT'S HAPPENING.
IT'S FALLING AS LIQUID, AND
THEN IT FREEZES ON CONTACT,
THAT'S WHERE IT MAKES BRIDGES
AND OVERPASSES VERY DIFFICULT
FOR TRAVELING ON, AND THAT'S
WHAT I'M CONCERNED ABOUT FOR
TOMORROW, AND SOME OF OUR 81
COMMUNITIES.
THIS IS ICE POTENTIAL, THIS IS
SHOWING WE COULD BE DEALING
WITH A QUARTER INCH OF ICE.
WE COULD BE LOOKING AT POWER
OUTAGES OUT IN THAT DIRECTION,
I DON'T THINK WE HAVE ENOUGH
FOR POWER OUTAGES INSIDE THE
METRO AREA BUT A GLAZING OF
ICE, IT'LL MAKE ENOUGH TO CAUSE
REALLY DIFFICULT TRAVEL AND
SLICK CONDITIONS.
SO, THE IMPACT TOMORROW,
MORNING COMMUTE, AFTERNOON
COMMUTE, YEAH, YOUR IMPACT IS
THAT TRAVEL BECOMES DIFFICULT.
WE'RE ALSO DEALING WITH COLD
OUT TOMORROW.
IT STARTS TOMORROW BEFORE 5 AM
TOUR SOUTHWESTERN COUNTIES,
D.C. METRO, IN BLUE, 5-7 HIM IS
WHEN THE SNOW IS WRITING, AFTER
6 AM FOR BALTIMORE AND THE
EAST.
HERE COMES THE BEGINNING EDGE
OF THE SNOW ARRIVING AT THAT
MORNING COMMUTE. YOU ARE
HEADING INTO WORK, IT STARTS TO
SNOW, QUICKLY THE ROADS ARE
BECOMING SLICK AND SNOW-COVERED
IF THEY HAVEN'T BEEN TREATED,
AND 10 AM, THE SNOW IS PICKING
UP IN INTENSITY.
SO TOMORROW MORNING, THAT SNOW
IS NOT JUST LIGHT, IT IS
BECOMING LOCALLY MODERATE TO
HEAVY AT TIMES.
12 PM, THERE IS STILL SNOW IN
D.C. BUT WE ARE MIXING WITH
SLEET AND FREEZING RAIN, AND
D.C. TRANSITIONS TO THAT WINTRY
MIX AS WE GET CLOSER TO 2 PM TO
4 PM.
FINALLY, BY THE EVENING
COMMUTE, D.C. IS ABOVE
FREEZING, WE WILL BE DEALING
WITH RAIN, BUT IT'S GOING TO
TAKE UNTIL 7 PM, IF NOT LATER,
FOR SOME OF THOSE NORTHERN
COUNTIES TO FINALLY TRANSITION
OUT OF THE FREEZING RAIN, TO
RAIN, JUST RECAPPING, SNOW FOR
THE MORNING COMMUTE, ROADS ARE
SLICK, LUNCH TIME, SNOW TO THE
NORTH, MIXED TO THE SOUTH,
ROADS ARE STILL SLICK AND ROADS
ARE SLICK NORTH OF TOWN WITH A
MIXED CONTINUING, THEN SOUTH OF
TOWN, WE ARE TRANSITIONING TO
RAIN. SEVEN DAY FORECAST, WE
GET PAST TOMORROW AND YEAH, WE
DO TURN WILDER FOR MILDER FOR
YOUR THURSDAY MORNING.
LARRY?
>>> YOUR HEALTH MATTERS HERE AT
WUSA9, WE ARE HOLDING FREE
HEALTH SCREENINGS  THIS THURSDAY
. OUR INITIATIVE IS CALLED
IMPACT HEALTH MATTERS, THE
SCREENINGS WILL START AT NOON
AND GO UNTIL 7 PM.
WE ARE PARTNERING WITH CAPITAL
REGION HEALTH AND THE PRINCE
GEORGES COUNTY HEALTH
DEPARTMENT, TO PROVIDE A WIDE
RANGE OF SCREENING AND DEMOS
FOR YOU.
THERE WILL BE 20 IN TOTAL, SOME
OF THEM INCLUDE CHOLESTEROL,
GLUCOSE EVEN DENTAL SCREENING.
THERE WILL BE DOCTORS ON AND.
EVERYTHING IS FREE BUT YOU DO
NEED TO REGIST
Stronger is rebuilding
a newborn's heart...
and restoring a
father's faith.
It's standing tall
after one surgery...
not six.
Stronger is being
a typical kid...
despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding
it earlier ...
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is
seeking answers...
And not giving up,
until you find them.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
Patients that I see that
complain about dry mouth,
they feel like they have
to drink a lot of water.
Medications seem to be the
number one cause for dry mouth.
Dry mouth can cause
increased cavities,
bad breath, oral irritation.
I like to recommend Biotene.
Biotene has a full array
of products that replenishes
the moisture in your mouth.
Biotene definitely works.
It makes patients
so much happier.
I'm a concrete mason.
I had severe fatigue, went to
a doctor.
Became diagnosed with
Hodgkin's lymphoma.
I had to put my trust in
somebody.
We recommended chemotherapy,
and then a stem cell transplant.
When his disease progressed,
I thought that he would be a
good candidate
for immunotherapy
to unleash his immune system
against the cancer.
I'm back to working hard.
I've honestly have never felt
this great.
The evolution of cancer care
is here.
Learn more at cancercenter.com
appointments available now.
>>> WE ARE BRACING FOR A MAJOR
DOSE OF WEATHER, THE WASHINGTON
NATIONALS ARE LIVING IT UP IN
FLORIDA AND ARIZONA AND THINGS
ARE GOING TO GET SUNNIER.
DARREN HAYNES HAS LOOK AT THE
POSSIBILITY THAT HARPER COULD
BECOME A $400 MILLION MAN.>>
HOW MUCH DO YOU WANT HIM ON THE
TEAM?
>> BRYSON I HAVE A SPECIAL
RELATIONSHIP.
EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT.
WHO WOULDN'T WANT BRYCE HARPER
ON THEIR TEAM?
IT'S ONE OF THE BEST YOUNG
PLAYERS IN THE GAME.
FOR ME, IT'S ALL ABOUT WHAT HE
WANTS, FOR HIS FAMILY AND HIS
CAREER.
IT REALLY IS.
HE'S GOT BIG DECISIONS TO MAKE.
BUT I'D BE WRONG TO SAY, YOU
KNOW, OF COURSE, ANYBODY WOULD
WANT HIM ON THEIR TEAM.
HE CAN MAKE A BIG DIFFERENCE.
>> IF BRYCE DECIDED, YOU KNOW
WHAT, I'M COMING BACK TO THE
NATIONALS, WHAT WOULD BE YOUR
REACTION WHEN HE WALKS THROUGH
THE DOOR?
>> I BE LIKE HEY, WELCOME BACK.
TIME TO WORK.
>> TO THINK BRYCE HARPER IS
COMING BACK?
>> A PART OF ME SAYS NO AND A
PART OF ME SAYS YES.
YOU KNOW, YOU JUST, THE WAY
THIS GAME IS, YOU REALLY DON'T
KNOW.
>> WHICH WAY ARE YOU LEAVING
LEANING?
>> LIKE I SAID, I CAN'T LEAN
EITHER WAY.
IT'S SO WEIRD BECAUSE, YOU
KNOW, LIKE I SAY, I TRIED TO
SAY HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT? THIS IS
WHAT I'VE GOT TO DO TODAY.
YOU KNOW, I'VE GOT TO LEAD 59
GUYS, TOMORROW MORNING, GET UP
AT 6 AM, GET TO THE BALLPARK
AND GET THE DAY GOING.
I FOCUS IS ON THE DAY AT HAND,
AND THE HERE AND NOW, AND
THAT'S WHAT I WORRY ABOUT.
>> EAT YOUR FOOD, MAN.
>>> IT'S GOING TO BE A LONG DAY
TOMORROW.
WE'VE GOT SNOW IN THE MORNING,
MAKES IN THE AFTERNOON, RAIN BY
EVENING. YOU WILL NOTICE THE
SNOW TOTALS ARE DIFFERENT THAN
WHAT WE SHOWED YESTERDAY, WE
ARE GOING TO UPDATE THEM AGAIN
TODAY AT 5 PM WITH NEW DATA.