>> THIS WAS A PROLONGED AND
BRUTAL CRIME.
>> BLAKE WAS CONCERNED THAT HIS
BROTHER HAD PLACED THE FAMILY IN
DANGER.
>> WAS IT REVENGE OR WAS HIS
GRAPHIC NOVEL A SCRIPT FOR
MURDER?
>> IT'S JUST MORE LIKE A HORROR
MOVIE.
>> CBS NEWS, ORIGINAL REPORTING.
WENT KNOCKING DOWN TREES AND
KNOCKING OUT POWER.
THE STORMS WERE INTENSE.
WE WILL FIND OUT IF WE ARE IN
THE CLEAR.
OUR METEOROLOGIST IS WITH US
NOW, ALYSSA I HAVE THE FEELING
THE ANSWER IS NO.
>> YOU ARE GUESSING RIGHT, THE
STORM GAME IS GOING STRONG, AT
11:00 TONIGHT YOU CAN SEE THE
PROGRESSION OF THE STORMS OVER
THE LAST FIVE HOURS AND IN THE
LAST HOUR, WE ARE TRACKING
ANOTHER INTENSE THUNDERSTORM,
OVER SOUTHERN MARYLAND, GOING
TO CHARLES COUNTY AND NO MOVING
INTO ST. MARY'S COUNTY.
MECHANICSVILLE HAD A LOT OF
HEAVY RAIN AND ABOUT 20 THINK
STRIKES IN THE LAST TEN MINUTES
ALONE, THIS IS ONE LAST STORM
OF THE NIGHT, MOVING TOWARD
LEXINGTON PARK AT 11:36.
IT WILL HOLD TOGETHER, OVER
MARYLAND, IT WILL REACH AT
ABOUT MIDNIGHT TONIGHT.
TOMORROW WE HAVE ANOTHER ROUND
OF STORMS.
TOMORROW I THINK THE GREATER
OVERALL THREAT IS GOING TO END
UP BEING SOME VERY HEAVY RAIN
FALLING ON SATURATED GROUND,
THAT COULD LEAD TO ISSUES, WITH
AN ISOLATED STORM THAT COULD
BECOME STRONG OR SEVERE.
NOT AS MANY IS WHAT WE SAW
TODAY, BUT STORMS TOMORROW WILL
STILL BE INTENSE.
WE START WITH PATCHY FOG.
WE WILL TAKE THE FUTURE CAST
OUT TILL NOON.
WE ARE MOSTLY DRY ON THE FUTURE
CASS, BUT STARTING IN THE
AFTERNOON, THE NEXT ROUND OF
STORMS STARTS FIRING UP.
WHEN IT STARTS GOING, IT WILL
ONLY GET MORE INTENSE FROM
THERE.
WE WILL TAKE YOU THROUGH THE
REST OF THE FUTURE CAST.
WE WILL BE LOOKING AHEAD UNTIL
THE NEXT STREAK OF DRY DAYS,
NEXT.
>> THANK YOU, MELISSA.
AND THIS SHOULD COME AS NO
SURPRISE, STORMS LEFT BEHIND
DAMAGE IN THE AREA TONIGHT.
CHECK OUT THIS HUGE TREE THAT
BRUSHED AGAINST THIS HOUSE ON
RESERVOIR ROAD, RIGHT BEFORE
FALLING OVER.
THERE IS NO WORD OF ANY
INJURIES TONIGHT.
>>> IN GLOVER PARK, THIS TREE
SNAPPED AND FELL RIGHT ONTO
THAT PARKED SUV, SOME OF THE
OTHER CARS NEARBY MAY HAVE BEEN
DAMAGED AS WELL.
AND CHECK THIS OUT.
ALSO IN THE DISTRICT, ANOTHER
TREE CRASHES ONTO A CAR, YOU
CAN'T REALLY SEE THE CAR
BECAUSE THAT TREE IS SO BIG.
THIS HAPPENED ON NEW HAMPSHIRE
AVENUE.
AND HERE IS A LOOK AT MORE
WEATHER PICTURES COMING IN
TONIGHT FROM THROUGHOUT THE
REGION, THESE WERE JUST
SPECTACULAR.
LOOK AT THIS.
BECAUSE OF THE INTENSITY OF
THIS STORM, WHAT YOU CAN GAUGE
FROM THESE IMAGES ALONE, MANY
ARE WITHOUT POWER TONIGHT
ESPECIALLY IN PRINCE GEORGE
COUNTY.
IF YOU HAVE PICTURES OR VIDEO
THAT YOU WOULD LIKE TO SEND OUR
WAY, TAG US ON FACEBOOK OR ON
TWITTER, OR SHARE THEM HERE.
>>> POLICE RESPONDED TO A
DEADLY MOTORCYCLE CRASH ON
MONTGOMERY COUNTY.
THIS HAPPENED OFF TO 70 AND THE
INTERSECTION OF 370 AND ROUTE
200.
A 45-YEAR-OLD MAN CRASHED.
>>> IT HAS BEEN A TENSE DAY AND
NIGHT IN WASHINGTON.
RIGHT
AND LEFT-WING PROTESTERS, THEY
FACED OFF NEAR THE WHITE HOUSE
TODAY, ONCE I DEMANDING FREE
SPEECH.
THE OTHER, FREE - - SPEECH FREE
OF STATE.
HERE IS CHRIS ARNOLD WITH MORE
INFORMATION.
>> Reporter: RIGHT RING RALLY
HERE IS AN PROTESTERS WERE IN
DC, SATURDAY.
AIKO - - TRUMP IS TRYING TO
DIVIDE US.
>> Reporter: THE NEOFASCIST
GROUP PROUD BOYS, THE RIGHT
RALLY TO DEFEND FREE SPEECH,
AFTER FIGHTS OVER TWITTER AND
FACEBOOK WERE CENSORED.
>> WE HAVE THE RIGHT TO SHARE
TWEETS AND PHOTOS, AND
DIFFERENT STATES OF MIND.
WE CAN DO RALLIES LIKE THIS.
>> Reporter: GROUP LIKE BLACK
LIVES MATTER, SANCTUARY AND
OTHER ACTIVISTS CAME TO PROTEST
HATE IN PERSHING PARK.
>> EVEN IN THE FACE OF WHITE
SUPREMACY AND HATE, WE ARE
WORKING TOWARD LIBERATION.
>> Reporter: SOME QUESTIONS
WERE INEVITABLE.
>> THESE BIG TECH COMPANIES,
THEY LIE.
THEY CALL US NAZIS.
THEY CALL US TERRIBLE PEOPLE.
THEY CALL US RACIST.
AND THE PEOPLE OVER THERE HAVE
THE COMPLETE A WRONG IDEA.
THEY ARE AGAINST OUR VOICES.
>> THOSE FOR AND AGAINST THE
PRESIDENT HAD NO PROBLEM
RAISING VOICES ON SATURDAY.
>> THE BLACK COMMUNITY IS
ALIVE.
>> I'M ASHAMED OVER THE THINGS
THAT ARE GOING ON IN THE
COUNTRY.
>>> THEY FINALLY REMOVE THAT
READ MINIVAN, THERE WAS A
SINKHOLE OVER NORTHERN
VIRGINIA.
THANKFULLY THE VAN WAS JUST
PARKED.
THE VIRGINIA DEPARTMENT OF
TRANSPORTATION IS BLAMING A
STORM WATER PIPE THAT BURST.
IT COULD STILL TAKE WEEKS TO
REPAIR, SO IT WILL REMAIN
CLOSED.
>>> NEW DETAILS ON A SINGLE CAR
CRASH THAT SHUT DOWN PARTS OF
INTERSTATE  95 YESTERDAY, SOME
OF YOU MAY HAVE BEEN CAUGHT UP
IN IT, DURING THE WORKDAY.
THE FORD EXPLORER WAS TRAVELING
NORTH ON INTERSTATE  95 WHEN A
DRIVER RAN OFF THE RIGHT
SHOULDER AND OVERTURNED SEVERAL
TIMES BEFORE COMING TO REST IN
THE LEFT SHOULDER.
THE DRIVER WAS FROM WEST
VIRGINIA.
HE WAS TAKEN TO A NEARBY
HOSPITAL, HE HAD LEFT RANGE - -
HE HATH RIGHT - - HE HAD LIFE-
THREATENING INJURIES.
THE PASSENGER WAS EJECTED AND
DIED AT THE SCENE.
THOMAS WAS NOT WEARING A
SEATBELT.
ANOTHER PASSENGER, ROBERT
ROUGHER THIRD WAS ALSO KILLED.
THERE WERE OTHER PASSENGERS - -
ROBERT ROUGHER THIRD - - ROBERT
RUTHERFORD WAS IN THE CAR WITH
HIM.
BOTH OF THOSE PASSENGERS WERE
WEARING SEATBELTS.
>>> A GAS EXPLOSION REDUCE
PARTS OF A SHOPPING MALL TO
RUBBLE.
THE BLAST WAS MASSIVE, 21
PEOPLE WERE HURT.
THIS
HAPPENED WEST OF FORT
LAUDERDALE.
HERE IS PETER KING.
>> Reporter: THE LAST
ORIGINATED INSIDE A VACANT
PIECE OF PIZZA RISE - - A PIZZA
RESTAURANT, FALLING DEBRIS
CRUSHED SEVERAL CARS IN THE
PARKING LOT.
>> I HEARD A LOUD BOOM.
I THOUGHT IT WAS FIREWORKS.
>> Reporter: THE FORCE OF THE
BLAST SHATTERED WINDOWS AND
DAMAGED BUSINESSES IN THE SAME
SECTION OF THE PLAZA, INCLUDING
AN LA FITNESS CENTER THE ENTIRE
COLLAPSED, PATRONS WERE SENT TO
GET OUT.
>> I THOUGHT IT WAS AN
EARTHQUAKE.
OBVIOUSLY NOT.
I WAS TERRIFIED, HONESTLY.
>> Reporter: THE EXPLOSION WAS
POWERFUL ENOUGH TO BE FELT FOR
MILES AROUND.
>> WE FOUND PEOPLE SCATTERED
ALL ABOUT THE DEBRIS AREA.
>> Reporter: FIRST RESPONDERS
SET UP TRIAGE.
FIREFIGHTERS WITH SPECIALLY
TRAINED DOGS SEARCHED THE AREA
TO MAKE SURE NO ONE WAS TRAPPED
OR KILLED.
FIRE OFFICIALS SAY EVERYONE HAS
BEEN ACCOUNTED FOR.
WE ARE VERY RELIEVED THAT
CONSIDERING HOW WHERE WE FOUND
THEM, THESE INJURIES ARE NOT AS
SEVERE AS WE WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
THEM TO BE.
>> Reporter: PETER KING
REPORTING WITH CBS NEWS IN
ORLANDO.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP DOUBLING
DOWN ON HIS FIGHT OVER A
CONTROVERSIAL QUESTION ABOUT
CITIZENSHIP ADDED TO THE
CENSUS.
NICOLE IS IN BROOKLYN HEIGHTS,
NEW JERSEY.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT TRUMP
FLEW TO NEW JERSEY FOR HIS
FIRST SUMMER VISIT TO A COUNTRY
CLUB.
WELL BACK IN WASHINGTON, IT'S
SCRAMBLED TO GET A CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION INCLUDED IN THE CENSUS
DESPITE PUSHBACK FROM THE
SUPREME COURT.
>> WE HAVE FIVE WAYS TO DO IT.
WE ARE WORKING ON A LOT OF
THINGS INCLUDING THAT EXECUTIVE
ORDER.
>> Reporter: A SOURCE TELLS US
ATTORNEYS ARE REVIEWING ALL OF
THE OPTIONS, THEY ARE TRYING TO
RESOLVE LEGAL ISSUES AS QUICKLY
AS POSSIBLE.
CRITICS CHARGE THAT THE
CITIZENSHIP WAS DISCRIMINATING
AGAINST IMMIGRANTS AND
COMMUNITIES OF COLOR.
>> WE WILL LOSE A LOT OF
SUPPORT FOR OUR COMMUNITIES, IN
THOSE REGIONS.
>> Reporter: EXPERTS SAY THE
PRESIDENT CANNOT OVERRIDE THE
SUPREME COURT DECISION TO BLOCK
THAT QUESTION, BUT HE CAN COME
UP WITH A NEW RATIONALE FOR WHY
IT IS WARRANTED.
>> SOME QUESTIONS CAN BE ADDED
IF THERE ARE VALID REASONS TO
DO SO.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT ALSO
WANTS ACTION ON IMMIGRATION
AFTER PROPOSED DEPORTATION
ROUNDUPS, HE SAYS THAT THEY ARE
GOING TO START SOON.
>> I SAID THEY CAME IN
ILLEGALLY AND WE ARE LEGALLY
MOVING THEM.
>> Reporter: THE ADMINISTRATION
CONTINUES TO COME UNDER FIRE
FOR POOR CONDITION THAT MIGRANT
DETENTION CENTERS ALONG THE
SOUTHERN BORDER.
PRESIDENT TRUMP CLAIMS THE
FACILITIES ARE CLEAN AND RUN
BEAUTIFULLY.
A WATCHDOG REPORT CAUSED THE
CRISIS A SEE A TICKING TIME
BOMB, DEMOCRATS PLAN A HEARING
NEXT WEEK.
NICOLE KILLIAN, REPORTING FROM
OAKLAND HEIGHTS, NEW JERSEY.
>>> IF YOU LIKE BURGERS, YOU
WILL LIKE TO HEAR ABOUT THE
JUICIEST BURGERS IN THE NATION,
FIND OUT WHY THEY ARE BEING
COOKED UP FOR A GOOD CAUSE.
>> Reporter: THOUSANDS OF
EARTHQUAKES HAVE HIT SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA, ONE OF THEM BEING A
7.1 MAGNITUDE.
I'M
REPORTING
[ MUSIC ]
>>> THIS IS WHAT PEOPLE ARE
DEALING WITH OUT WEST, A STRONG
EARTHQUAKE JOLTED LOS ANGELES
LAST NIGHT ONE DAY AFTER A
SLIGHTLY WEAKER ONE RATTLED
CALIFORNIA.
THE EARTHQUAKE EPICENTER IS
NEAR RIDGECREST.
AND A ROCKSLIDE SHUT DOWN A
ROAD.
IT ALSO TRIGGERED FIRES.
JOY HAS MORE INFORMATION FROM
PASADENA.
>> Reporter: THE MAGNITUDE 7.1
EARTHQUAKE CAME ONE DAY AFTER
THURSDAY'S SIX-POINT FOUR
JOLTS.
>> THERE WERE STRUCTURE FIRES,
GAS LEAKS, ROAD DAMAGE AND
ROCKSLIDE'S.
>> Reporter: THIS WAS THE SCENE
IN RIDGECREST, NEAR THE
EPICENTER OF THE PLANE, FOOD
AND OTHER ITEMS FELL OFF THE
SHELVES.
150 MILES SOUTHWEST, COLLEAGUES
IN LOS ANGELES SAW THAT
EARTHQUAKE AS THEY WERE
BROADCASTING AT THE DOCTORS
HOME GAME.
>> SOMETHING STARTED SHAKING
AND WE WERE LOOKING AROUND.
>> Reporter: THE BASEBALL GAME
CONTINUED, THE EARTHQUAKE EVEN
RATTLED LAS VEGAS WITH ENOUGH
FORCE TO STOP THE NBA GAME.
DOESN'T - - THOUSANDS OF
EARTHQUAKES HAVE STRUCK
CALIFORNIA, SCIENTISTS ARE
CRUNCHING THE NUMBERS TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT THE PROBABILITY OF
MORE.
>> WE ARE CONCERNED ABOUT
>> Reporter: THE LIKELIHOOD OF
ANOTHER MAGNITUDE SIX QUAKE IS
MORE THAN 25%.
JOIN BENEDICT, CBS NEWS,
PASADENA, CALIFORNIA.
>>> GAVIN NEWSOM DECLARED A
STATE OF EMERGENCY, FOR
SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA, THERE WAS
SIGNIFICANT DAMAGE AFTER FRIDAY
NIGHTS EARTHQUAKE.
AND MELISSA IS WITH US TONIGHT,
IT HAS BEEN A BUSY NIGHT, AND
IT IS STILL NOT OVER.
ONE STORM IS LEFT OUT THERE, WE
GET TO DO IT ALL AGAIN
TOMORROW, AS IF YOU ARE NOT
DONE WITH IT ALREADY.
LOOK AT THE TOWER CAMERA, NICE
AND DRY OVER THESE RIGHT NOW.
AND WINDY GUST REAGAN NATIONAL,
AS THE STORMS ARE COMING
THROUGH, IT WAS JUST ABOUT 40
MILES PER HOUR.
AT THE CAPITAL, IT WAS 66,
THERE ARE DOZENS, I'M NOT
KIDDING, 66 AT THE US CAPITOL.
IT CAN HAPPEN.
WE WILL LEAVE IT THERE.
THERE WERE DOZENS OF TREES DOWN
ALL OVER DC.
WE HAD 5000 PEOPLE WITHOUT
POWER, 4000 PEOPLE IN PRINCE
GEORGES COUNTY, AND LET ME SHOW
YOU THE LAST REMAINING STORM,
WITH STILL A LOT OF LIGHTNING,
AND I PUT A LIGHTNING TRACKER
ON THIS.
THIS STORM IS HOLDING TOGETHER
WELL, WITH HEAVY RAIN MOVING
INTO LEONARD WITH 45 STRIKES,
IN THE LAST TEN MINUTES ALONE.
HERE IS THE SET UP, THIS FRONT
IS TRYING TO MOVE THROUGH, IT
IS GOING TO STALL OUT OVER THE
AREA, TOMORROW.
THAT FRONT IS THE DIVIDING LINE
BE DUE BETWEEN THIS DISGUSTING
HUMID AIR MASS THAT WE HAVE
BEEN IN, AND NOT EXACTLY
CANADIAN PLEASANTRY, BUT IT
WILL BE A LITTLE UNMANAGEABLE
OUTSIDE BY TUESDAY.
WE ARE IN THE TRANSITION FOR
SUNDAY AND MONDAY, WITH STILL
SOME STORM CHANCES.
I PULLED UP THE WEATHER MODEL,
OVER THE NEXT 48 HOURS ALONE,
LOOK AT THIS.
WE HAVE THE IN-HOUSE RPM MODEL
SHOWING ANOTHER THREE AND A
HALF INCHES AND SOME ISOLATED
SPOTS.
THIS IS SHOWING A HEAVY
RAINFALL THREAT, SETTING UP FOR
TOMORROW.
AND TOMORROW'S STORMS COULD
BRING LOCALLY HEAVY RAIN, THAT
IS MY BIGGEST CONCERN OF ALL OF
THE STORM THREATS.
WE COULD HAVE ISOLATED STRONG
TO SEVERE STORMS LIKE WE SAW
TODAY, NOT AS MANY, WITH SOME
DAMAGING WIND.
I
THINK THE OVERALL THREAT WILL
BE SOME DOWNPOURS FALLING ON
SATURATED GROUND, THAT COULD
LEAD TO FLOODING.
WE WILL ALSO SEE SOME
LIGHTNING.
IF YOU ARE BOATING OR HIKING
OUTSIDE, OR ENJOYING LUNCH,
HEADS UP FOR THE STORMS, YOU
DON'T WANT TO BE CAUGHT OUTSIDE
WITH THEM.
HOURLY, AFTER TODAY'S STORMS I
THINK WE WILL SEE SOME FOG
FORMING OVERNIGHT.
SOME OF THAT FOG COULD BE
LOCALLY DANCE.
WE WILL START WITH CLOUD COVER,
PATCHY FOG, TEMPERATURES IN THE
70s.
BY LUNCHTIME THERE IS STILL A
LITTLE BIT OF CLOUD COVER, IT
WILL BREAK UP A LITTLE BIT.
TEMPERATURES ARE IN THE 80s, WE
GO UNTIL THREE A CLOCK IN THE
AFTERNOON, THIS IS HOW WE START
TO SEE SOME SCATTERED STORMS
DEVELOPING.
I THINK THE STORM TIMEFRAME
TOMORROW IS LATER THAN IT WAS
TODAY.
STORMS WILL START AROUND MIDDLE
AFTERNOON, REALLY RAMPING UP
PAST DINNERTIME AND EVENING.
A LOT OF COMPUTER MODELS ARE
GOING TO KEEP STORMS IN THE
FORECAST THROUGHOUT SUNDAY
NIGHT AND EVEN INTO MONDAY
MORNING.
WITH A LOT OF HEAVY STORMS THAT
KEEP RINGING ROUNDS OF HEAVY
RAIN INTO THE AREA.
I THINK TOMORROW IS GOING TO BE
A BIGGER FLOODING THREAT
LOCALLY, ESPECIALLY CREEK AND
STREAM FLOODING, RISING.
WE START WITH A MOSTLY DRY
START TO THE DAY AND LATER IN
THE DAY WE START TO BRING THE
STORM CHANCES IN, THE HIGH
TEMPERATURES ARE IN THE MIDDLE
80s.
THE FORECAST FOR TOMORROW,
KANSAS CITY ROYALS, 1:35 FOR
THE FIRST PITCH, WE ARE GETTING
LUCKY AT THE BEGINNING OF
THINGS, BY THE END OF THE GAME,
WE WILL BE TRACKING SOME WIDELY
SCATTERED STORMS.
BY THE FINISH, IT IS POSSIBLE
THERE COULD BE A RAIN DELAY.
CROSS YOUR FINGERS, 1:35 LOOKS
LIKE A BETTER START TIME RATHER
THAN MIDDLE OF THE AFTERNOON.
TOMORROW, HERE ARE THE SHOWERS
AND THE THUNDERSTORMS.
GOING INTO MONDAY, THAT FRONT
IS STILL CLOSE ENOUGH TO US, IT
WILL LEAVE US WITH SOME STORM
CHANCES.
TUESDAY, WEDNESDAY, THAT HIGH-
PRESSURE WILL COMPLETELY DRY
ICE OUT, BRING US US TO A
SLIGHTLY LOW HUMIDITY.
IT WILL
COMPLETELY DRY US OUT.
STORM CHANCES CONTINUE TUESDAY
AND WEDNESDAY.
BACK IN THE TROPICS THERE IS A
20% CHANCE OF A SYSTEM DEVELOP
MEANT, ACTUALLY AN UPPER-LEVEL
TROUGH OVER WESTERN TENNESSEE,
IT WILL MOVE OUT TO THE GULF.
THIS IS THE AREA THAT WE ARE
GOING TO BE WATCHING FOR HEAVY
RAINFALL TO SET UP SHOP TO THIS
WEEK.
IF YOU ARE TAKING A VACATION
TOWARD PANAMA CITY - - PANAMA
CITY BEACH, THIS IS WHAT I AM
TRACKING WITH THE TROPICS THIS
WEEK.
THE LOW IN THE HIGH
TEMPERATURES ARE AT 88.
CLOUD COVER AND FOG WILL LIMIT
HOW HOT WE GET, IS HUMID WITH
THUNDERSTORMS LATE IN THE DAY
AND INTO TOMORROW NIGHT.
THERE WILL BE MORE STORMS ON
MONDAY, IT WILL BE DRY ON
TUESDAY AND WEDNESDAY.
WE WILL BE BRINGING BACK STORM
CHANCES ON THURSDAY WITH MORE
HUMIDITY THAT WILL RETURN ON
FRIDAY.
>> MELISSA, THANK YOU.
>>> IF YOU HAVE AN APPETITE FOR
BURGERS, THE PLACE TO BE IS
WISCONSIN.
YOU ARE NOT GOING TO LIKE ME
AFTER THIS, GOING TO BED,
THINKING ABOUT FOOD, WE WILL
SHOW YOU THIS JUICINESS.
CHEFS ARE OFFERING UP THE
TASTIEST BURGERS EVERYWHERE,
THE BURGER BASH IS THE FOURTH
ANNUAL AND FOR TEN DOLLARS YOU
CAN SAMPLE BURGERS FROM
COMPETING CHEFS.
THERE FROM WISCONSIN,
MINNESOTA, IOWA, AND THERE WILL
BE A $300 REWARD.
LOCAL ORGANIZATIONS AND CHEFS
MADE OF A PANEL OF JUDGES THAT
DECIDE THE BEST BURGERS.
>>> THIS IS DEFINITELY A
PETITION, THE CHEF AND THE
JUDGE TAKES THIS SERIOUSLY.
EACH CHEF REALLY LIKES TO KNOW
WHAT PEOPLE THINK OF THE
RECIPES.
>> THE PEOPLE BEHIND HER LOOK
SO HAPPY.
PROCEEDS GO TO THE BIKE BRIGADE
FUNDRAISER TO PAY DOWN SCHOOL
LUNCH THAT FOR KIDS.
>>> THE NBA FINALS MVP IS
MOVING ON, WHAT IS NEXT FOR
KAWHI LEONARD, NEXT.
>> PLUS THE OBSTACLE COURSE
FEATURING CO
We are sisters.
And we just moved in together.
Why Alissa and Aleah chose Fios.
We stream sooo much.
A lot of times Alissa is
watching TV on her laptop,
using her phone, also using her
tablet.
I am really good at multitasking
Cause I'm awesome.
A little.
The best internet is even better
at our best price.
Switch now and get our fastest
speeds available.
Plus, a free Samsung Chromebook
on us.
That's Fios.
This is not a bed.
It's a revolution in sleep.
The Sleep Number 360
smart bed is on sale now
during our Lowest
Prices of the Season.
It senses your movement,
and automatically adjusts
to keep you both comfortable.
It even helps with this.
So you wake up ready to
hit the ground running.
Don't miss our 4th of
July Special with the
queen Sleep Number 360
c4 smart bed now $1299.
Plus, free premium delivery
when you add a base.
Ends Sunday.
Sleep Number.
Proven, quality sleep.
>>> TODAY, THE POWDER BLUE
JERSEY, THEY WEREN'T DURING THE
INAUGURAL SEASON 50 YEARS AGO.
THE FIRST TIME THEY WERE THOSE
UNIFORMS, AND AS FOR THE GAME?
[ CHEERING & APPLAUSE ]  [
CROWD NOISE ]
>> KURT SUZUKI SINCE IT DID TO
THE LEFT, SEE YOU LATER!
IT GOES ABOVE THE BULLPEN!
- - KURT SUZUKI SENDS IT TO THE
LEFT.
>> SEE YOU LATER!
MELISSA WAS SUPPOSED TO JOIN ME
BUT LEFT ME HANGING.
THERE WAS ENOUGH SUPPORT FOR
MAX SCHERZER.
HE PICKED UP HIS NINTH VICTORY
OF THE SEASON, THE NATS SHOT
OUT INTO CITY 6-0.  AND ANTHONY
RENDON WILL NOT PLAY THE ALL-
STAR GAME.
HE HAS BEEN DEALING WITH MINOR
AILMENTS AND NEED SOME TIME TO
REST AND HEAL.
>>> THE ORIOLES WERE IN CANADA
IT - - THE ORIOLES WERE IN
CANADA TO WRAP UP THE FIRST
SEASON.
>> IT IS GONE!
GOODBYE HOME RUN!
IT STAYS.
NUNEZ WILL CRANK ONE, A COUPLE
RBIS AND A 10-0 LEAD FOR THE
ORIOLES.
>> THAT WAS PART OF A FIVE-
MONTH A FIVE-RUN FOURTH, THE
BIRDS WINNING THREE KEEP GOING.
THE WASHINGTON WIZARDS HAVE
ACQUIRED DAVID, FROM SAN
ANTONIO, IN A THREE TEAM DEAL,
THE WIZARD SENT AARON WHITE TO
BROOKLYN.
>>> CHANGES TO THE LANDSCAPE
ARE COMING FOR THE NBA, THE
CLIFF MADE A COUPLE BIG MOVES,
SIGNING FREE AGENT KAWHI
LEONARD TO A FOUR YEAR, $142
MILLION CONTRACT.
WHILE COMPLETING A TRADE WITH
THE OKLAHOMA CITY LETTER, FOR
PAUL GEORGE.
LEONARD BECOMES THE FIRST
PLAYER EVER TO SWITCH TEAMS
AFTER WINNING THE FINALS THE
MVP.
>>> MAYBE THEY JUST NEEDED TIME
TO DOUBLES MATCH AND WENT OFF,
BLASTING THOSE PLAYERS WHO WERE
SITTING ON THE BENCH DURING THE
CHANGEOVER.
NOT FUN AT ALL, RIGHT?
AND THEY ARE OFF, IN THIS CASE,
A TRADITION OF FIREWORKS, IN
THE FAMED RUNNING OF THE BULLS,
OPENING NINE DAYS OF
UNINTERRUPTED PARTIES.
AND THEY LAUNCHED THE ROCKET TO
MARK 100 YEARS SINCE THE LOCAL
ENSEMBLES FOUNDATION.
THEY WERE DRESSING IN WHITE
ATTIRE, WEARING ADDITIONAL RED
SCARVES, AND SPRING EACH OTHER
WITH WINE.
ERNEST HEMINGWAY IMMORTALIZED
THE FIESTA.
THEY HAVE AROUND 1 MILLION
VISITORS, SUNDAY, VENDOR LEVELS
ALONG THE YARD SEVERE AND HIS
WIFE HAVE THE TITLE, IT'S GOING
- - THEY BEAT DOZENS OF OTHER
COUPLES FOR A SECOND YEAR
RUNNING, THEY WENT OVER A
GRUELING 278-YARD OBSTACLE
COURSE IN ONE MINUTE AND 6.72
SECONDS, A TENTH OF A SECOND
BEHIND THE WORLD CHAMPION AND
HIS PARTNER.
DOZENS OF COUPLES TAKE PART IN
THIS ANNUAL RACE FROM FINLAND
AND PRICES ARE ISSUED TO THE
FIRST THREE, THE MOST
ENTERTAINING, THE BEST COSTUME,
AND THE STARKEST CARRIER.
CAN YOU GET OVER THIS VIDEO?
WILD STUFF RIGHT HERE.
DESPITE THE NAME, THE COUPLES
DO NOT HAVE TO BE MARRIED.
>>> RELATIONSHIP WILLING
EXERCISES.
STILL AHEAD, WE HAVE
Honey, this
Gig-speed Internet
is ridiculously fast.
We are seriously keeping
up with the Joneses.
Keeping up
with the Ford's.
Keeping up with
the Garcia's.
The Romeros.
Patels.
the wahh-the-wahh
Wolanske's. Right.
No one is going to
have Internet like this.
Xfinity makes keeping
up with the Joneses
Simple. Easy. Awesome.
Want Gig-speed Internet?
We've got you covered.
Or check out our other amazing
speed options at new low price.
Get started now for as
low as $29.99 a month.
Call, click or visit
a store today.
>>> STILL WAITING AROUND FOR
THAT COLD SUMMER DAY, NO RAIN,
NO STORMS.
YOU WANT SUMMER.
>> THIS IS THE FOURTH OF JULY,
IN TYPICAL FASHION FOR US IN
DC.
WE HAVE ANOTHER ROUND OF
SCATTERED SHOWERS AND STORMS,
LATE TOMORROW, SOME VERY HEAVY
RAINFALL, ISOLATED STRONG TO
SEVERE STORMS AND THEY WILL
CONTINUE INTO SUNDAY NIGHT WITH
ANOTHER ROUND OF STORMS
POSSIBLE ON MONDAY.
I THINK YOUR PICK OF THE WEEK
IS GOING TO BE TUESDAY.
LOW HUMIDITY, IT IS DRY AND
SUNNY, MORE STORMS COME ON
THURSDAY.
WE CAN GO THROUGH IT WEEK BY
WEEK.
I KNOW IT SUCKS FOR FANS, WHEN
THERE ARE RAIN DELAYS.
NEXT FRIDAY'S GAME ACTUALLY
LOOKS REALLY GOOD.
>> OKAY, OKAY, I WAS AT A GAME
WHERE WE GOT RAINED OUT
RECENTLY.
I WAS LIKE OF COURSE.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
WE WILL BE BACK AGAIN TOMORROW
NIGHT AT 9:00.
HAVE A