10:00 IN THE MORNING.
THE LATER YOU GO TO WORK ON
FRIDAY, THE BETTER.
WE DON'T SEE ANY HUGE PROBLEMS
IN TERMS OF ACCUMULATION AND
MOST WILL BE ON GRASSY
SURFACES.
WE GET GOING INTO FRIDAY NIGHT
AND WE HAVE CLOUDS LEFT OVER,
HERE IS THE SNOWFALL, 7/10 OF
AN INCH AND ONLY 3/10 FOR THE
AMERICAN MODEL AND ZERO FOR THE
EUROPEAN.
WE WILL COME BACK AND TALK
ABOUT A BETTER CHANCE OF SNOW
SUNDAY INTO MONDAY.
>>> FOUR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENTS
ARE UNDER INVESTIGATION FOR
CHILD PORNOGRAPHY.
THEY ARE UNDER INVESTIGATION
FOR ALLEGEDLY SHARING PICTURES
OF STUDENTS ON SNAPCHAT.
AS MANY AS FIVE HIGH SCHOOLS
COULD BE INVOLVED.
>> WE KNOW THE INVESTIGATION
BEGAN AT ROBINSON SCHOOL WHERE
THE STUDENTS TOLD THE POLICE
THERE WAS ANOTHER STUDENT WITH
THE SNAPCHAT ACCOUNT THAT WAS
SHARING FULLY NAKED UNDERAGED
GIRLS.
THE SUSPECT ALSO ASKED FOR
OTHER PICTURES OF NAKED GIRLS
FROM OTHER HIGH SCHOOLS, LAKE
BRADDOCK, WOODSON, WEST
SPRINGFIELD AND SOUTH COUNTY.
WE ARE NOT SURE IF ANY PICTURES
CAME FROM THOSE SCHOOLS, BUT
THE POLICE OFFICER WRITES IN
THE SEARCH WARRANT THAT ALL
FOUR SUSPECTS HAD ACCESS TO THE
COUNT AND THE OFFICER SAYS THAT
ALL FOUR OF THE STUDENTS
CONFESSED TO POSSESSING AND
DISTRIBUTING THOSE PICTURES.
THE OFFICER STATES THAT HE SAW
THESE PICTURES AND CONCLUDES
THEY ARE CHILD PORNOGRAPHY.
THE CLINICAL PSYCHOLOGIST IS
NOT SURPRISED.
>> I THINK THIS WAS HAPPENING
MUCH MORE THAN WE ARE AWARE OF,
THE JOURNAL OF THE AMERICAN
MEDICAL ASSOCIATION CAME OUT
WITH A STUDY VERY RECENTLY THAT
SAID ONE OUT OF FOUR STUDENTS
ARE RECEIVING SEXUAL IMAGES,
THAT IS BETWEEN THE AGE OF 11
AND 17.
13%
>> I'M GUESSING THAT THE
SUSPECT PROBABLY HAVE NO IDEA
THAT THESE PICTURES COULD BE
CONSIDERED CHILD PORNOGRAPHY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I DON'T THINK THE PERSON AT
THAT AGE AND STAGE,
DEVELOPMENTALLY UNDERSTANDS
WHAT CHILD PORNOGRAPHY IS, BUT
I ALSO DON'T THINK THAT THEY
ASSUME THAT THERE IS ANYTHING
WRONG WITH IT.
IF SOMEONE IS SENDING THIS TO
ME AND THEY WANT ME TO HAVE IT.
>> SHE SAYS PARENTS NEED TO
HAVE CONVERSATIONS WITH THEIR
CHILDREN ABOUT SEXUAL TEXTING
AS SOON AS THEY GIVE THEM A
CELL PHONE.
>> WE NEED TO START WITH BEING
THOUGHTFUL ABOUT WHAT WE POST,
THINK BEFORE YOU POST, HOW
WOULD I FEEL IF THIS WAS SHARED
WITH OTHERS?
COULD THIS BE USED TO HURT ME?
>> FAIRFAX COUNTY POLICE WILL
NOT TALK PUBLICLY ABOUT THIS
INVESTIGATION BECAUSE IT IS
ONGOING.
NO CHARGES HAVE BEEN FILED YET.
>>> FAIRFAX COUNTY LOOK SCHOOLS
RELEASED A STATEMENT SAYING THE
DISTRICT IS AWARE OF THE POLICE
INVESTIGATION, AND SINCE IT
REMAINS AN ACTIVE
INVESTIGATION, THERE WILL BE NO
ADDITIONAL COMMENTS AT THE
TIME.
>>> CAUGHT ON CAMERA, A MAN WHO
SHOT TWO PEOPLE IN BROAD
DAYLIGHT OVER THE WEEKEND, DC
POLICE WANT YOU TO TAKE A GOOD
LOOK AT THIS SURVEILLANCE
VIDEO.
IT HAPPENED ON THE 3300 BLOCK.
SOMEONE IN THE SUV STARTED
FIRING AT A MAN AND WOMAN WERE
STRUCK.
IF YOU RECOGNIZE THE SHOOTER OR
VEHICLE OR HAVE ANY
INFORMATION, DC POLICE WANT TO
HEAR FROM YOU.
>>> THE SEARCH IS ON FOR A HIT-
AND-RUN DRIVER THAT KILLED A
WOMAN WALKING IN TYSON'S
CORNER.
SHE WAS STRUCK AROUND 6:30 THIS
MORNING ON THE OUTER LOOP OF
THE BELTWAY.
SHE WAS FOUND NEAR A CROSSWALK
AND THE DRIVER LEFT THE SCENE
AND PLEASE DON'T HAVE A
DESCRIPTION.
THEY ARE ASKING FOR ANY WITNESS
TO COME FORWARD.
>> BREAKING NEWS IN THE SHOP,
SHOCKING CASE OF THE BODY FOUND
IN BETHESDA.
THE MEDICAL EXAMINER HAS JUST
ROLLED IN THE LAST HOUR THAT
THIS WAS INDEED HOMICIDE.
POLICE BELIEVE THE VICTIM WAS
KILLED SOMEWHERE ELSE AND
DUMPED ALONG BUSY OLD
GEORGETOWN ROAD NEAR DEMOCRACY
BOULEVARD.
NEIGHBORS ARE HORRIFIED.
>> IT IS PRETTY SHOCKING.
IT'S A SAFE NEIGHBORHOOD.
>> FOR HIM, A CHILLING SCENE,
HERE IN A PROSPEROUS
NEIGHBORHOOD OF HOMES OUTSIDE
THE BELTWAY, BODY FOUND JUST UP
FROM A BUS STOP NEXT TO BUSY
OLD GEORGETOWN ROAD AT ROANOKE
DRIVE.
>> I HOPED IT WOULD BE A
HOMICIDE.
>> THAT WOULD BE SCARY.
>> Reporter: A PASSERBY NOTICED
THE PLASTIC BAG ON THE SIDE OF
THE ROAD MONDAY EVENING AND
LOOKED INSIDE.
THEY MUST'VE BEEN SHOCKED TO
FIND THE BODY.
WITH HIGH WINDS, DETECTIVES
ARRIVED AND SWEPT UP THE BAG
AND BODY AND EVERYTHING ELSE
THEY COULD FIND.
THEY WERE WORRIED EVIDENCE
MIGHT BLOW AWAY AND THEY RUSHED
THE PACKAGE TO THE MEDICAL
EXAMINER'S OFFICE IN BOLTON.
>> NOW A BIG DEVELOPMENT, THE
MEDICAL EXAMINER HAS RULED THE
DEATH WAS A HOMICIDE.
THE MAN WRAPPED UP HIS BODY
DUMPED AT THE BUS STOP.
POLICE BELIEVE HE WAS MURDERED
ELSEWHERE, AND IT COULD'VE BEEN
ALMOST ANYWHERE.
OLD GEORGETOWN IS A POSSIBLE
CONNECTOR FROM I-TO 70 TO THE
BELTWAY.
INVESTIGATORS WILL BE CASTING A
WIDE NET TO TRY TO FIGURE OUT
WHO KILLED HIM.
>> IN CASE YOU ARE WONDERING,
THAT IS A BUSY SIDEWALK.
SCHOOLS AND CHURCHES IN THE
WILDWOOD SHOPPING CENTER ARE
NOT FAR FROM MONTGOMERY MALL.
POLICE WILL BE CHECKING METRO
BUS SURVEILLANCE CAMERAS TO SEE
IF THAT LEADS THEM.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP IS IN
VIETNAM FOR A SECOND SUMMIT
WITH THE NORTH KOREAN DICTATOR
JOHN KUHN.
THEY WILL TALK ABOUT NORTH
KOREA ENDING THE NUCLEAR
WEAPONS PROGRAM IN EXCHANGE FOR
THE EVENING OF ECONOMIC
SANCTIONS, PRESIDENT TRUMP AND
KIM JONG-UN WILL DINE TOGETHER
BEFORE THEY BEGIN OFFICIAL
TALKS ON THURSDAY.
LAWMAKERS IN WASHINGTON ARE
SKEPTICAL THAT NORTH KOREA WILL
EVER GIVE UP THE NUKES.
>> ARE YOU OPTIMISTIC?
>> NO.
I'M NOT.
I DON'T THINK KIM JONG-UN IS
EVER GOING TO GET RID OF
NUCLEAR WEAPONS.
HE MAKES PROMISES AFTER
PROMISES, AND HE DOESN'T KEEP
HIS PROMISES, AND IT IS NOW
TIME FOR HIM TO SHOW SOME GOOD
FAITH.
>> SECURITY IS TIGHT AT THE
HANOI HILTON HOTEL WHERE THEY
HAVE THE NORMALLY RECLUSIVE
DICTATOR.
NORTH KOREA BROUGHT ALL OF HIS
FOOD AND COOKING SUPPLIES AND
EVEN UTENSILS HE WILL USE TO
EAT.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP'S PERSONAL
LAWYER TESTIFIES BEHIND CLOSED
DOORS ON CAPITOL HILL, BUT
PEOPLE ARE TALKING ABOUT WHAT
WE MAY HEAR HIM SAY TOMORROW.
>>> WE ARE HEARING FROM
PASSENGERS WHO ARE FINALLY
MOVING AGAIN AFTER BEING
STRANDED ON AN AMTRAK TRAIN
SINCE SUNDAY.
>>> UP NEXT,
♪ We buy any car ♪
♪ Any make, any model,
any age, any price ♪
♪ From 50 bucks to 100 grand ♪
♪ We buy any car ♪
♪ Any, any, any, any ♪
At webuyanycar.com,
the gimmicks stop with our ads.
Trading in our selling
your car is hassle-free
with just three easy steps.
One, get your free
online valuation.
Two, drive to your local
car buying centre.
And three,
walk out with your check
in as little as 30 minutes.
So don't wait.
Get your free online
valuation now.
♪ Find out how much
your car's worth ♪
♪ At webuyanycar.com ♪
>>> THE HOUSE IS SET TO PASS A
RESOLUTION AIMED AT PREVENTING
THE EMERGENCY DECLARATION TO
BUILD A BORDER WALL.
IT COULD COME IN THE NEXT
COUPLE HOURS AND DEMOCRATS
CLAIM IF THE EMERGENCY VIOLATION
VIOLATES THE BALANCE OF POWER.
ONLY ONE REPUBLICAN CONGRESSMAN
IS SUPPORTING THE RESOLUTION.
SENATE WILL VOTE NEXT WEEK.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS HE WILL
VETO THE RESOLUTION IF IT HAS
SUCCESS.
>>> A SHERIFF SAYS HIS OFFICE
WILL NOT COMPLY WITH
LEGISLATION THAT WOULD REGULATE
OWNERSHIP OF RIFLES AND
SHOTGUNS IF IT PASSES THE
GENERAL ASSEMBLY.
THE CHEF WAS ONE OF DOZENS OF
PEOPLE TESTIFYING BEFORE THE
MARYLAND HOUSE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE CONSIDERING SEVERAL
GUN RELATED BILLS.
AND THAT INCLUDES ONE REQUIRING
BACKGROUND CHECKS AND PERMITS
TO PURCHASE SHOTGUNS AND OTHER
LONG GUNS.
>> IT COSTS THE AVERAGE
RESIDENT ABOUT $300 IN FEES TO
MARYLAND STATE AND GETTING
FINGERPRINTS DONE.
>> PEOPLE WITH TERMINAL
BACKGROUND, CONVICTED FELONS,
DOMESTIC ABUSERS, PEOPLE WITH
MENTAL HEALTH ISSUES THAT MAKE
THEM DANGEROUS CAN PURCHASE
LONG GUNS ONLINE OR IN PRIVATE
SALE.
>> WE FEEL THAT IT WON'T DO
ANYTHING TO FIGHT CRIME.
IT'S JUST A WAY TO TAKE GUNS
AWAY FROM THE CITIZENS.
>> OTHER BILLS BEING CONSIDERED
INCLUDE OUTLAWING 3-D PRINTED
GUNS AND IMPOSING CERTAIN
MANDATORY STORAGE REQUIREMENTS
FOR GUN OWNERS.
>> A BEAUTIFUL DAY OUT THERE
TODAY.
OF COURSE WE HAVE SOMETHING
ELSE AROUND THE CORNER, A
WINTRY MIX ON THE WAY LATER
THIS WEEK.
WE WILL HAVE, TOPPER SHUTT WILL
BE BACK WITH ALL THE DETAILS.
>>> IN THE SOCIAL MEDIA POST OF
A SMALL CAMERA ON  AN AIRPLANE
ENTERTAINMENT.
IT HAS A LOT OF YOU WONDERING
IF THE AIRLINES ARE WATCHING
YOU.
I WOULD VERIFY TEAM IS ON THIS
ONE.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP FORMER
FIXER, MICHAEL COHEN BEGINS
THREE DAYS OF TESTIMONY.
I'M NATALIE BRAND ON CAPITOL
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.
What would she do without me?
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP FORMER
PERSONAL LAWYER MICHAEL COHEN
BEGINS THREE DAYS OF TESTIMONY
ON CAPITOL HILL.
THE SENATE SESSION WAS CLOSED
TO THE PUBLIC.
>> THE SOURCE CONFIRMS THAT IN
THE OPEN SESSION ON THE HOUSE
SIDE, COCOA AND PLANS TO
PUBLICLY ACCUSE THE PRESIDENT
OF CRIMINAL CONDUCT.
MICHAEL COHEN ARRIVED ON
CAPITOL HILL TUESDAY TO TESTIFY
BEFORE THE SENATE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE IN A CLOSED-DOOR
SESSION.
THE COMMITTEE WANTS TO GIVE HIM
THE CHANCE TO CORRECT THE
RECORD AFTER LYING TO CONGRESS
IN 2017 ABOUT PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
PLANS TO BUILD A MOSCOW TOWER
IN 2016.
THEY WANT TO KNOW IF SOMEONE
TOLD HIM TO LIE AND HOW MANY
OTHER RUSSIA DEALS DID HE
PURSUE AND WHO WEAR THE RISKY
BUSINESS PARTNERS.
>> WHAT I INTEND TO KEEP
FOCUSED ON IS UNTANGLING THE
VERY COMPLICATED FINANCIAL
ARRANGEMENTS BETWEEN DONALD
TRUMP AND RUSSIA.
>> HE IS SET TO REPORT TO
PRISON INMATE FOR CAMPAIGN-
FINANCE VIOLATIONS AND LYING TO
CONGRESS THE LAST TIME HE
TESTIFIED.
TODAY IS JUST THE START,
POTENTIALLY EXPLOSIVE TESTIMONY
COULD COME WEDNESDAY DURING AN
OPEN SESSION BEFORE THE HOUSE
OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE.
A SOURCE CONFIRMS TO CBS NEWS
THAT COHEN PLANS TO ACCUSE THE
PRESENT OF CRIMINAL CONDUCT IN
CONNECTION WITH HUSH MONEY PAID
TO TWO WOMEN WHO CLAIM THEY HAD
AFFAIRS WITH MR. TRUMP.
HE REPORTEDLY WILL ALSO REVEAL
FINANCIAL STATEMENTS HE SHOWED
THE STATEMENT COULD HAVE
ENGAGED IN TAX FRAUD.
WHITE HOUSE PRESS SECRETARY
SARAH SANDER SAID IN A
STATEMENT IT IS LAUGHABLE THAT
ANYONE WOULD TAKE A CONVICTED
LAYER LIKE MICHAEL COHEN AT HIS
WORDS AND THAT IT TO SEE HIM
GIVEN YET ANOTHER OPPORTUNITY
TO SPREAD HIS LIES.
HE WILL WRAP UP HIS TESTIMONY
ON THURSDAY WITH A CLOSED-DOOR
SESSION BEFORE THE HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE.
>> NEARLY 200 AMTRAK PASSENGERS
ARE FINALLY OFF OF THE TRAIN IN
OREGON AFTER BEING STRANDED FOR
MORE THAN 36 HOURS.
THE TRAIN WAS GOING FROM
SEATTLE TO LA WHEN IT HIT A
TREE THAT HAD FALLEN ON TRACKS,
THAT WAS SUNDAY EVENING WITH
MORE THAN A FOOT OF SNOW ON THE
GROUND, PASSENGERS HAD TO SIT
TIGHT WHILE CREWS CLEARED THE
TRACKS.
>> WE PLAYED HEARTS AND TOOK
NAPS, AND WE LOOKED OUTSIDE AT
THE SNOW PILING UP.
>> IT WAS SO PROFESSIONAL AND
KIND, AND WE REALLY WANTED FOR
NOTHING EXCEPT MAYBE SOMEPLACE
COMFORTABLE TO LIE DOWN IN A
SHOWER.
>> I WAS VERY DISAPPOINTED WITH
THE LACK OF COMMUNICATION.
>> AMTRAK SAYS PASSAGES WERE
PROVIDED FOOD AND HEAT AND
ELECTRICITY AND TOILETS AND
THAT IT WILL PROVIDE REFUNDS
AND OTHER COMPENSATION TO ITS
CUSTOMERS.
IT ALL SEEMS, THEY ALL SEEM
PRETTY CALM.
36 HOURS, I WOULD BE FREAKING
OUT.
>> I GUESS THAT IS THE BEST
THING TO DO IN THAT SITUATION.
>> IT WAS A WEATHER RELATED
ISSUE.
I CAN IMAGINE WE WOULD ALL BE
FRUSTRATED.
BUT IT SOUNDS LIKE THEY DID THE
BEST THEY COULD.
>> YOU ARE NOT JUST TAKING OFF
INTO THE WILDERNESS.
>> CAN WE BAN THE WORD WINTRY
MIX?
>> WE WILL NOT BAN SNOW AND
SLEET.
>> I DIDN'T ASK FOR THOSE,
ASKED FOR TWO WORDS, WINTRY
MIX.
>> WE CANNOT DO THAT.
BUT WHAT WE CAN DO IS TALK
ABOUT SOME SNOW STATS FOR LATE
IN THE YEAR AND ALSO FOR MARCH.
LET'S GO THROUGH SOME OF THESE,
THESE ARE NOT TOO SURPRISING.
THE AVERAGE MARCH SNOW IS 1.3
INCHES AND THAT'S DOWNTOWN DC.
THE AVERAGE LAST SNOW IS MARCH
8, AND THE LAST SNOW ON THE
RECORD IS APRIL 7 AND THE
LATEST SNOW BACK IN 2018 WAS
MARCH 21.
WE HAD FOUR INCHES.
MARCH CANNOT, MARCH CAN BE AN
ACTIVE MONTH AND WE HAVE SOME
CHANCES COMING UP.
WE WILL JUMP AHEAD TO SUNDAY
AND THIS IS SUNDAY AFTERNOON.
THIS IS THE AMERICAN MODEL,
CLOUDS ARE IN PLACE BY SUNDAY
NIGHT AND SNOW OFF TO THE SOUTH
AND WEST AND WE ADVANCE THIS
AND BY MONDAY MORNING, THIS
COULD AFFECT THE MONDAY MORNING
COMMUTE I THINK THIS IS A MORE
SERIOUS THREAT THAN THE FRIDAY
MORNING THREAT.
PRETTY GOOD SNOW DOWN TO
NORFOLK, THAT HAS COLDER AIR TO
IT.
IT MAY TURN BRIEFLY INTO A MIX
BY 2:30 ON MONDAY, BUT THAT
WOULD MEAN A PRETTY NASTY
COMMUTE MONDAY MORNING FOR
EVERYONE.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE EUROPEAN
MODEL, THE SAME SORT OF DEAL,
BUT WITH THE PRECIPITATION MUCH
SOONER.
THIS IS AS EARLY AS SUNDAY
AFTERNOON AND SUNDAY NIGHT IS
NOT AS COLD, SO WE HAVE RAIN IN
SOUTHERN MARYLAND AND SNOW IN
DC NORTH AND WE GET INTO MONDAY
MORNING AT 6:00 AND THERE IS
SOME SNOW.
IT WILL STILL BE A NASTY
COMMUTE AND RAIN IN SOUTHERN
CHARLES COUNTY INTO CALVERT AND
ST. MARY'S AND THAT GETS BACK
IN THIS AFTERNOON AND BEGINS TO
CLEAR BY THE EVENING.
WHAT DOES THIS ADD UP TO?
THESE SNOW MAPS ARE ESSENTIALLY
TAKING INTO ACCOUNT THE SUNDAY
AND MONDAY STORM AND VERY
LITTLE IS BEING ADDED TO THE
FRIDAY STORM ON THE EUROPEAN.
THIS IS GOING HOGWILD AGAIN,
SEVERAL INCHES NORTH AND WEST,
THE AMERICAN MODEL SAYS SOME
SNOW SUNDAY MONDAY AND MAYBE
MORE LIKE AN INCH OR TWO IN THE
METRO AREA AND THAT'S A BETTER
CHANCE THAN WE HAD.
46 TOMORROW, KIND OF COLD AND
52 ON THURSDAY, 50 ON FRIDAY
WHICH IS ABOUT AVERAGE AND 49
ON SATURDAY AND COLD ON SUNDAY
AS ARCTIC AIR MOVES IN.
ONLY 35.5 FOR A HIGH.
LOTS OF CLOUDS TOMORROW AND WE
CALL IT COLD.
PLEASANT ON THURSDAY AND THEN
THE EARLY MIX, VERY EARLY STILL
POSSIBLE ON FRIDAY.
TWO THINGS I WANT TO EMPHASIZE,
EARLY AND POSSIBLE.
THOSE ARE THE TWO MOST
IMPORTANT THINGS TO TALK ABOUT
ON FRIDAY.
10:00 TONIGHT, 32 IN
GAITHERSBURG AND 39 DOWNTOWN
AND BY 6 AM, WE ARE 26 AND 29
IN BOWIE AND BY MIDMORNING, MID
30s AND LOW 40s AFTER
LUNCHTIME.
46 TOMORROW AND 52 ON THURSDAY,
A YELLOW WEATHER ALERT FOR NOW
ON FRIDAY WITH A MORNING MIX
POSSIBLE AND VERY LIGHT AND
EARLY AND REBOUNDING BACK TO
50.
SATURDAY IS NOT AS UGLY AS LAST
SATURDAY, BUT STILL SHOWERS AND
RAIN AND 49 IN THE THURSDAY
AFTERNOON MIX ON SUNDAY AND
BLUSTERY ON TUESDAY.
WE SEE SOME FLURRIES WITH HIGHS
ONLY IN THE 30s.
>>> SOMETIMES IT'S THE LITTLE
THINGS THAT HAVE THE BIGGEST
IMPACT AND WE BELIEVE A SMALL
MOMENT OF KINDNESS CAN CHANGE
EVERYTHING AND WE SET OUT TO
PROVE IT WE GRANTED FIVE LITTLE
WISHES WITH THE HELP OF THE
COMMUNITY.
LET'S START IN MARYLAND WITH
THE STORY OF A SON WHO WAS
DETERMINED TO HELP HIS MOTHER
WHO WAS RECOVERING FROM BREAST
CANCER.
SOMETIMES IT'S THE LITTLE
THINGS THAT HAVE THE BIGGEST
IMPACT, SO WE PUT JARS AROUND
TOWN AND ASKED PEOPLE ONLINE
WHAT IS YOUR LITTLE WISH?
AND WE ASKED NEIGHBORS TO HELP
NEIGHBORS AND MAKE IT ALL COME
TRUE.
THIS IS A LITTLE WISHES.
>> Reporter: I CAN'T REALLY,
HI, HOW ARE YOU, JARED?
YOU WROTE TO US WITH THE LITTLE
WISH ABOUT YOUR MOM?
>> YES.
>> Reporter: YOU TOLD US ABOUT
THE DOOR.
>> I THINK SOMEBODY MAY HAVE
TRIED TO BREAK IN ONE TIME AND
EVER SINCE THEN, IT WAS OFF THE
TRACKS.
YOU CAN FEEL THE AIR SWEEPING
THROUGH UNDERNEATH.
I THOUGHT SOMETHING LIKE THAT
WOULD REALLY MAKE HER HAPPY.
COME ON IN.
>> Reporter: HELLO.
GOOD MORNING.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> I WAS DIAGNOSED IN 2015, SO
I CAN TELL YOU THAT THROUGH MY
JOURNEY I'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT
OF THINGS AND I WAS A WIDOW AT
A YOUNG AGE.
AND WE'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT.
BUT THIS YOUNG MAN HAS STOOD BY
ME.
HE TAKES GREAT CARE OF ME.
>> CAN I BRING YOU UP HERE?
>> SURE.
GOOD MORNING.
YOU HAVE SOME FRIENDS FROM
LOWE'S, THIS IS JORDAN.
AND THIS IS TY, AND THESE ARE
PEOPLE FROM TOP DOG, THIS IS
LUKE AND CARLOS, WHAT WILL YOU
DO FOR HER TODAY?
>> WE WILL PUT SOME DOORS IN
THE BACK.
>> YES.
>> EVERY TIME I GO TO THE
DOCTOR, I CAN'T GET BACK IN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> WE ARE ALWAYS LOOKING FOR
OPPORTUNITIES TO HELP OTHER
PEOPLE OUT, HER STORY
DEFINITELY HIT CLOSE TO HOME
FOR ME BECAUSE IT WAS MY FAMILY
MEMBER THAT WAS IN A SITUATION
LIKE SHE WAS IN, I WOULD WANT
SOMEONE TO HELP OUT.
>> WE WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT
OUR CUSTOMERS KNOW THAT WE ARE
HERE TO SUPPORT AND SIMPLE
GESTURES LIKE THIS COULD MEAN A
WORLD OF DIFFERENCE TO ANYBODY.
>> THE FRONT DOOR SAYS SO MUCH
ABOUT A HOME.
THAT IS YOUR FIRST KIND OF YOUR
EYE IS DRAWN TO THE DOOR AND
THAT'S WHERE YOU COME IN AND BE
WELCOME, INSTEAD OF COMING HOME
EVERY DAY AND BEING WELCOMED BY
A MISSING HANDLE, AND HAVING TO
STRUGGLE WITH INJURIES WHERE
YOU CAN'T EVEN ACCESS YOUR OWN
HOME, I JUST CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE
HOW DIFFICULT THAT WOULD BE.
>> YOUR SON WROTE US WITH A
LITTLE WISH.
BUT YOU WROTE US WITH A LITTLE
WISH AS WELL.
>> I DID.
WHAT DID YOU WRITE TO US ABOUT?
>> I WAS TELLING YOU THAT THEY
HAVE THOSE TREADMILLS THAT YOU
COULD WALK ON, I SAID THAT IS
THE ANSWER, BECAUSE YOU JUST
WALK IN THE HOUSE.
>> SO CAN YOU COME HERE FOR A
SECOND?
>> WHAT IN THE WORLD IS IN THIS
BOX?
>> IS IT CHRISTMAS?
>> IS A CHRISTMAS.
>> EVERY YEAR, ONE PERSON GETS
ELECTED.
>> IT IS A TREADMILL, I'M SO
EXCITED.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> WE ARE STILL PEOPLE, NO
MATTER WHAT STANCE OF LIFE YOU
ARE IN, YOU CAN GO THROUGH
SOMETHING IF YOU NEED SOMEONE.
AND IF YOU CAN'T OFFER THAT
ABILITY TO HELP SOMEONE OUT, DO
IT.
>> IT IS SIMPLE, AND THAT IS
THE FIRST OF THE LITTLE WISHES
WE WILL BE GRANTING THIS WEEK
AND WE BRING YOU THE SECOND
LITTLE WISH TONIGHT AT 11:00
AND IF YOU HAVE A LITTLE WISH
YOU WOULD LIKE GRANTED OR YOU
COULD HELP US CREATE A LITTLE
WISH, SEND ME AN EMAIL AT
IMPACT AT WUSA9.COM.
>>> COMING UP, WE TALKED A
LOCAL WOMAN WHO CLAIMS SHE WAS
THE VICTIM OF A RACIST ATTACK
AT A NORTHERN VIRGINIA
SUPERMARKET.
AND ALSO AHEAD, THE CAPITALS
AND WIZARDS OWNER TELLS US
ABOUT HIS PLAN NOW THAT
[phone ringing]
Remember the way we
used to do things?
Hey man...
Like connect with friends?
Dig it!
Or get in shape?
Or sell a house
and pay a real estate
agent a big commission.
[crash]
At Redfin, we charge
you a 1% listing fee.
And because Redfin.com is
America's #1 brokerage site
our agents get more
eyes on your home
so you sell for
thousands more
than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin Agent.
>>> TRENDING THE NIGHT, A
VIRGINIA BREWERY IS BRINGING
IDEAS FROM THE CEREAL AISLE.
THE BREWING COMPANY SET TO
RELEASE THE SATURDAY MORNING
MARSHMALLOW IPA, THE LIMITED
EDITION BEER WILL  READILY
LAUNCH THIS SATURDAY.
IT IS BREWED WITH DEHYDRATED
EXCLUSIVE MARSHMALLOWS AND A
TASTE THAT MAY REMIND YOU OF
THE CEREAL, LUCKY CHARMS.
THE CAN LOOKS LIKE THE CEREAL
BOX THAT FEATURES THE SLOGAN,
MAGICALLY RIDICULOUS.
>> DON'T KNOCK IT UNTIL YOU TRY
IT.
THAT'S ALL I WILL SAY.
>> THOSE TVS ON AIRPLANES,
GREAT TO PASS THE TIME, BUT
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THOSE FEET
BACK SCREENS, IS THERE A CAMERA
LOOKING BACK AT YOU?
THERE IS A VIRAL PICTURE GOING
ON ONLINE ABOUT CAMERAS
INSTALLED IN THOSE IN-FLIGHT
ENTERTAINMENT SYSTEMS.
WE HAD EVER VERIFIED TEAM JASON
PUCKETT FIND OUT IF IT IS TRUE.
>> HERE ARE THE CLAIMS THAT
STARTED IT ALL.
IT SHOWS WHAT LOOKS LIKE A
CAMERA BUILT INTO AN
ENTERTAINMENT SCREEN IN THE
BACK OF AN AIRPLANE SEAT.
THIS SHOWS ONE ON SINGAPORE
AIRLINES, BUT OTHERS INCLUDING
AMERICAN AIRLINES ADMITS THEY
HAVE THESE SYSTEMS AS WELL.
>> AND THEY ADMITTED THEY ARE
CAMERAS.
LET'S BE REAL, THESE CAMERAS
REALLY RECORDED, THEY WOULD
HAVE SOME REALLY WEIRD VIDEOS,
HOPEFULLY OF PEOPLE SLEEPING,
BUT IT IS ALARMING TO THINK
ABOUT ANYONE WATCHING YOU
SLEEPING, THE CAMERAS DON'T
ACTUALLY RECORD, THAT'S WHAT
THE AIRLINES TOLD US DIRECTLY.
ACCORDING TO AMERICAN AIRLINES
PRIVATE JETS, IT FITS IN THEIR
PLANES, THE MAKERS OF THE
SYSTEMS MAKE CAMERAS AND OTHER
PIECES OF TECHNOLOGY, BUT THE
FEATURES ARE NOT BEING FEATURED
ON FLIGHTS.
AMERICANS AS THEY AREN'T BEING
USED AND THEY ARE CONSIDERING
USING THEM EITHER, IT JUST
HAPPENS TO BE PART OF THE
SYSTEM THAT WORKS BEST FOR THE
PLANE.
ARE THERE ACTUALLY CAMERAS ON
IN-FLIGHT ENTERTAINMENT
SCREENS?
YES.
ARE THOSE USED FOR RECORDING
YOU?
NO.
>>
>>> THE NEWS AT FIVE ACTOR
BEGINS WITH THIS QUESTION, WAS
IT A RACIST ATTACK?
FAIRFAX COUNTY POLICE ARE
INVESTIGATING EVERY WOMAN SAYS
SHE WAS TARGETED AT A
SPRINGFIELD GIANT SUPERMARKET.
>> AND IT JUST GOT PHYSICAL.
>> STEPHANIE RAMIREZ HAS SOME
DETAILS FOR US.
>> SHE TELLS US SHE WAS PARKED
IN THE SUPERMARKET PICKUP LANE
JUST LIKE WE ARE AND AT ONE
POINT, THE MAN EVEN REACHED
INTO HER WINDOW TO GRAB A CELL
PHONE.
>> AND I AM WRESTLING WITH HIM,
AND MEANWHILE I'M THINKING OH,
MY GOD, NO ONE IS SEEING THIS
AND I'M REACTING AT THE MOMENT.
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN TO ME.
THIS IS MAKING ME FEEL, JUST IN
SHOCK.
>> AND IT DIDN'T STOP THERE.
THE 53-YEAR-OLD ERICA RIGGS
FROM SPRINGFIELD VIRGINIA IS
OUT OF TOWN DOING WORK FOR THE
ADVERTISING CLUB OF NEW YORK.
WE TALKED ON FACETIME, RIGGS
TELLS US THAT ABOUT 4:30 PM
FEBRUARY 19, SHE DROPPED OFF
HER 80-YEAR-OLD MOTHER AT THIS
SPRINGFIELD GIANT SUPERMARKET
WHEN THIS MAN APPROACHED HER
CAR.
WE ARE NOT SHOWING HIS FACE
BECAUSE HE HAS NOT