WAS BEING ATTACKED BY TWO MEN
IN CHICAGO.
>> HE SHOULD NOT HAVE USED A
HATE CRIME, ESPECIALLY WHEN
YOU'RE PART OF THE LGBT CUTE
COMMUNITY, BECAUSE NOW THE
WHOLE COMMUNITY IS GOING TO
BESIDE I AND YOU.
>>REPORTER: AN ACCOMPLISHED
STYLUS, AND TRANSGENDER
ACTIVIST, CONSULT WAS A VICTIM
OF A CRIME, BACK IN 1990 BEFORE
SHE TRANSITIONED.
>> NEXT AND YOU KNOW, I SAW A
BOTTLE GO TO MY HEAD, I TOOK
COVER, I DID NOT FIGHT BACK,
WHAT I DID, WAS JUST COVERED, I
WENT INTO A FETAL POSITION,
COVERED MY FACE, AND MY BODY,
AND THEN, THEY JUST HIT ME, FOR
15 TO 20 SECONDS, AND THAT IS
WHY, I THINK, LIKE USING THAT
STORY, IS SO HURTFUL TOWARDS
OUR COMMUNITY, BECAUSE PEOPLE
ARE GOING TO BE LIKE THAT DID
NOT HAPPEN, THAT DID NOT HAPPEN,
WHEN IN REALITY IT IS HAPPENING
ALMOST EVERY SINGLE DAY, IF YOU
WERE TO FESS UP AND TELL THE
TRUTH, I THINK PEOPLE WOULD BE
MORE LENIENT WITH HIM, AND SAY
YOU KNOW WHAT HE IS HUMAN, HE
MADE A MISTAKE, A B FOR HIS
CAREER, LIKE, BUT DO NOT HAVE
HIS WHOLE CAREER AWAY.
>> DOES HE NEED TO APOLOGIZE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
YES, HE DOES, BECAUSE AGAIN, IT
IS TAKING TIME FROM REAL CRIMES
THAT ARE HAPPENING IN OUR
COMMUNITY.
>>REPORTER: AND THE BLACK
COMMUNITY, BECAUSE HE PLAYS THE
RECUT AS WELL.
AND THAT IS THE FEAR REAL
VICTIMS, MAY NOT BE BELIEVED IF
SMALL IT STORY PROVES TO BE
FALSE.
JULIA, WUSA 9.
>>> ALL NEW AT 5:3, MAN IS IN
CUSTODY IN CONNECTION WITH A
DEADLY STABBING THAT HAPPENED
THIS MORNING IN NORTHEAST.
IT HAPPENED ON BENNING ROAD
JUST BEFORE 8 AM.
VICTIM HAS BEEN IDENTIFIED AS
39-YEAR-OLD JASON WOULD.
POLICE SAY HE WAS STABBED
MULTIPLE TIMES, POLICE SAY THE
MALE VICTIM, WAS STABBED
MULTIPLE TIMES, 24-YEAR-OLD
DARIUS MURRAY HAS BEEN CHARGED
WITH SECOND-DEGREE MURDER,
WHILE ARMED.
>>> A3 YEAR-LONG EXPERIMENT,
AND SOME DC PUBLIC SCHOOLS, IS
ABOUT TO END.
STARTING IN AUGUST 20 -- 2019,
STARTING THIS AUGUST, LET ME
BACK UP.
STARTING IN AUGUST 2016, 13
CITY SCHOOLS RAN EXTENDED EARS,
THEY HAD CLASSES FOR 200 DAYS,
INSTEAD OF THE MANDATED 180 DAY
MINIMUM.
HOWEVER, POST REPORTS THOSE
SCHOOLS RETURN TO NORMAL
SCHEDULES THIS FALL, THE MAYORS
OF THE EXTENDED CALENDAR COULD
NOT PROVE SIGNIFICANT ACADEMIC
IMPROVEMENT.
>>> THERE IS ANOTHER PROBLEM
ACROSS THE DMZ, GOOD TEACHERS
ARE LEAVING THE CLASSROOM.
THE PEOPLE HURT THE MOST OF THE
CHILDREN, OF THE LAST TWO
MONTHS, MARCELLA ROBINSON HAS
SPENT TIME AT THE ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL IN NORTH -- LOOKING AT
WHY THIS IS HAPPENING, AND
ALONG THE WAY, SHE MET ONE
INCREDIBLE TEACHER, WHO IS
GIVING BACK IN IMMEASURABLE
WAYS.
>> WHEN I GET OLD, I FEEL LIKE
I'M GOING TO SUCCEED IN LIFE,
BECAUSE OF MR. DIAZ.
>>REPORTER: A TON ELEMENTARY,
IS A SMALL SCHOOL.
>> WHERE DID YOU GET THIS?
>> I NEVER REALLY, THOUGHT OF
MYSELF AS A TEACHER.
ESPECIALLY, WITH ALL THE
NEGATIVITY ON THE NEWS YOU HEAR
ABOUT TEACHERS, LOW SALARIES, A
LOT OF TEACHERS SAYING THAT
THEY DO NOT REALLY ENJOY THEIR
JOB.
>> IN THE ROUND, OF THE SPELLING
BEE, RIGHT?
THAT IS PRETTY GOOD.
>>REPORTER: BUT AS A BIG
REPUTATION OF BEING LOW
PERFORMING, THAT IS WHY WE
SPENT THE LAST MONTH HERE,
GETTING TO KNOW THE STUDENTS,
THE TEACHERS.
>> SCHOOL FOR VISIBLE PHYSICAL
THERAPY, I WAS LOOKING FOR
PHYSICAL THERAPY, I FELT LIKE
THAT WAS MY CALLING.
>>REPORTER: MR. DIAZ ENDED UP
LEAVING HIS PHYSICAL THERAPY
PROGRAM, AFTER ANOTHER STUDENT
CALLED HIM THE N-WORD.>> THAT
EXPERIENCE WAS A TURNING POINT
IN MY LIFE.
AND, IT ALLOWED ME TO REALLY
FOCUS ON THE THINGS THAT I
WANTED TO DO, THE THINGS THAT
MADE ME HAPPY, AND YOU KNOW, MY
PURPOSE, AND MY WIFE.
>> OH, OKAY, BUT YOUR HOMEWORK
ON YOUR DESK.
>> AND, THAT IS HONESTLY WHAT
BROUGHT ME TO TEACHING.
>>REPORTER: AND NOW, AT 26
YEARS OLD, MR. DIAZ IS ONE OF
THE MOST VETERAN TEACHERS AT A
TIME ELEMENT APPEARED
>> EVEN THOUGH IT IS HARD, YOU
JUST QUIT, GIVE UP?
NO!
>> I WAS NAMED PRINCIPAL, AND I
WAS COMING HERE, AND IT WAS LIKE
NOTHING BUT BAD THINGS.
LOWEST SCORES, KIDS OUT OF
CONTROL, SCHOOL OUT OF CONTROL,
PARENTS, ALWAYS YOU KNOW,
FUSSING AND FIGHTING WITH THE
STAFF.
AT SO, I JUST HEARD THAT IT WAS
A REALLY HARD PLACE, REALLY
ROUGH.
AND, THE YOU KNOW, SOME CHANGES
NEED TO HAPPEN.
>> SAY IT NOW.
>> NOT!
>>REPORTER: 44% OF THE TEACHERS
TURN OVER EACH YEAR AT A TIME,
THAT IS MORE THAN ANY OTHER
SCHOOL IN THE DISTRICT.
MR. GOLDEN HAS BEEN HERE FOR
FOUR YEARS, WHICH IS LONGER
THAN MOST, BECAUSE IN DC, IT IS
NOT JUST THE TEACHERS LEAVING,
IT'S THE PRINCIPLES TO.
>> SO WHEN I GOT HERE, IT WAS
FUNNY, BECAUSE, IT WAS A
BUILDING ENGINEER, SAID TO ME,
YOU KNOW, NO PRINCIPAL REALLY
LAST HERE.
[ LAUGHTER ] AND HE SAID, THE
KEY IS RELATIONSHIPS.
>>REPORTER: SOME OF THE
STUDENTS HERE DEAL WITH MORE
THAN MOST ADULTS CAN'T EVEN
FATHOM.
>> THE STUFF, WHERE BACK THERE
IN MY DAY, CREEK WAS
CLEAR.>>REPORTER: MYERS SEES IT
EVERYDAY.
>> IT KILLS ME.
IT KILLED ME.
I MEAN, SOMETIMES I AM PRAYING,
THREE OR FOUR TIMES A DAY, I
MIGHT GO TO, AND TAKE A
BATHROOM BREAK, AND I AM THE IN
THERE, YOU KNOW, TALKING TO MY
MAKER, BECAUSE YOU KNOW, I SEE
SO MUCH.
I WENT HERE FROM KINDERGARTEN
TO SIXTH GRADE.
>>REPORTER: WITH ALL THE
TURNOVER -- SHE IS THE ONE
CONSTANT.
34 YEARS UNDER HER BELT HERE AT
A TIME, AS A PROFESSIONAL.
>> SOMETIMES, THIS IS LIKE A
SAFE HAVEN TO GO DOWN.
YOU KNOW, THEY GET LOVE, WE
HAVE TO WEAR SO MANY HATS, YOU
KNOW, WE HAVE TO BE A NURSE,
DOCTOR.
YOU KNOW, A LAWYER.
>> TOMORROW.
>> YEAH, I KNOW, I KNOW.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
>> RINGS.
>> I CAN COME?
>> YEAH, IF YOU WANT.
>> OKAY, WHEN?
>> CAN I COME?
>> SATURDAY, OKAY, I AM GOING
TO BE THERE.
>> HE IS LIKE AN OLDER BROTHER,
OR A DAD.
BECAUSE, MY DAD IS NOT AROUND,
SO HE IS LIKE A DAD.
>> RAISE YOUR HAND IF YOU WOULD
LIKE TO GET ON --
>>REPORTER: EVEN THOUGH HE IS
YOUNG, MR. DIAZ HAS A COMMAND
OVER HIS CLASSROOM.
>> LET'S DO HER MORNING
ROUTINE.
>>REPORTER: HIS STUDENT HAVE
SOME OF THE HIGHEST PROPORTION
IS PERFORMING IN THE SCHOOL.
>> HE TEACHES US MANNERS, AND
MANY MORE THINGS, HOW TO READ
FLUENTLY, YOU KNOW, MOST OF THE
PEOPLE IN THE CLASS ARE PASSED
GRADE LEVEL.
I AM IN THE FOURTH GRADE
LEVEL.>> IT HELPED ME GETTING
INTO SPEECH, BECAUSE I CAN GO
TO COLLEGE COLLEGE -- I COULD
GET A JOB, AND A LOT OF PEOPLE
WILL LOOK AT ME, AND SEE I KNOW
HOW TO READ.
>>REPORTER: THIS IS AFTER HIS
STUDENTS WERE ACCEPTED INTO THE
COLLEGE READING GROUP.
COLLEGE IS A GOAL, HE WANTS TO
MAKE SURE THEY TAKE WITH THEM,
EVEN AFTER HIS CLASS.
>> THEY KNOW THAT IS ON THE
FRONT OF THE LAND, BECAUSE THEY
KNOW THAT NOT EVERYBODY GOES TO
COLLEGE, AND THAT IS A SELECT
FEW FROM WHO THEY SEE, GET TO
GO TO COLLEGE, AND THEY WANT TO
BE A PART OF THAT SELECT
FEW.>>REPORTER: LATE LAST YEAR,
THE DC BOARD OF EDUCATION,
LOOKED AT TEACHER ATTENTION.
THE NUMBERS ARE CLEAR, TEACHERS
ARE LEAVING, BUT WHEN THEY
CANNOT ANSWER, IS WHY.
>> [ MUSIC ]
>> [ LAUGHTER ]
>>REPORTER: THOSE INSIDE THE
SCHOOL THOUGH, SAY THERE ARE
MANY DIFFERENT REASONS.
>> YOU HAVE THOSE OUTSIDE
PRESSURES, WEIGHING ON YOU, YOU
HAVE A SCHOOL THAT IS
CHALLENGING.
SO, SOME PEOPLE QUESTION, IS
EDUCATION, YOU KNOW, THE RIGHT
CHOICE?
DID I MAKE THE RIGHT CHOICE?
>> ALL RIGHT?
>>REPORTER: BUT, THE TEACHERS
WHO STAY, THEIR REASON WHY IS
SIMPLE.
>> YOU KNOW, YOU CAN DODGE
BULLETS ON THEIR WAY TO SCHOOL,
BUT YOU CAN COME TO SCHOOL,
KNOWING THAT YOU KNOW, YOUR MOM
IS BEING ABUSED AT HOME, IF YOU
CAN COME TO SCHOOL, KNOWING
THAT YOU HAVE NOT SHOWERED IN A
FEW DAYS, AND YOU HAVE NOT EVEN
HAD A MEAL, AND COME HERE, AND
STILL RAISE HER HAND, AND
ANSWER QUESTIONS, AND STILL
HAVE YOUR HOMEWORK COMPLETED,
AND STILL BE READY IN A
INSPIRED TO READ, THAT MY
INSPIRATION.>> I AM IN THE
SCHOOL, WHERE I FEEL LIKE
CHILDREN NEED TO BE LOVED.
WE NEED TO GIVE THEM THE BEST
POSSIBLE OPPORTUNITY, HERE, AND
SO, I WOULD NOT TRADE THAT IN,
I WOULD FEEL LIKE A FAILURE, IF
I JUST ABANDONED THEM.
>> THOSE FACES, WHO CAN ABANDON
THOSE FACES?
WE ARE GOING TO GO BACK TO A
TON ELEMENTARY OVER THE COMING
MONTHS, TO BETTER UNDERSTAND
WHY TEACHERS ARE LEAVING, AND
MORE IMPORTANTLY, HOW TO CHANGE
THAT.  STOMACH RIGHT NOW, ON
WUSA9.COM  THERE IS A LINK,
THAT SHOWS THE TEACHER
RETENTION RATE YOUR CHILD'S
SCHOOL AS WELL.
>>> UP NEXT, QUITE TONIGHT, BUT
WE ARE LOOKING AT AN UNSETTLED
WEEKEND,
Jimmy's gotten used to his whole
room smelling like sweaty odors.
Yup, he's gone Noseblind.
He thinks it smells fine, but
his mom smells this...
Luckily for all your
hard-to-wash fabrics...
...there's Febreze
Fabric Refresher.
Febreze doesn't just mask, it
eliminates odors you've...
...gone noseblind to.
And try Febreze
Unstopables for fabric.
With up to twice the fresh scent
power, you'll want to try it...
...again and again and maybe
just one more time.
Indulge in irresistible
freshness.
Febreze Unstopables.
Breathe Happy.
Stronger is blasting
her tumors...
without risking her bones.
It's training her
good cells...
to fight the bad guys.
Stronger is less pain...
new hope...
more fight.
It's doing everything
in your power...
and everything in ours.
Stronger, is changing even
faster than they do.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>>> WELL, AUTHORITIES HAVE
SPENT YEARS WINNING US ABOUT
SCAM ARTIST POSING AS IRS
AGENTS, WILL NOW THEY ARE
POSING TO BE OFFICERS FROM
ANOTHER GOVERNMENT AGENCY,
HEADS UP, FROM KENNETH CRAIG.
>> I FELT LIKE MY IDENTITY HAD
BEEN COMPROMISED, AND I WAS
TRYING TO COMPLY WITH THE
GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS.
>>REPORTER: CARLA PIERCE
RECEIVED A VOICEMAIL MESSAGE
THIS PAST SUMMER.
>> THIS IS OFFICER CHRIS
MORRIS.
>>REPORTER: FROM SOMEONE
CLEANING TO BE FROM THE SOCIAL
SECURITY ADMINISTRATION, WHO
SAID HER IDENTITY HAD BEEN
STOLEN.
BUT, IT WAS ALL A SCAM.
SHE CALLED BACK, AND A FAKE
OFFICER CONVINCED HER TO TURN
OVER PERSONAL INFORMATION, AND
SEND $50,000 FROM HER BANK,
EXPLAINING IT WAS A TEMPORARY
TRANSFER, NEEDED TO VERIFY HER
IDENTITY.
>> THE MONEY WOULD HAVE TO BE
TRANSFERRED IN AND TRANSFERRED
BACK.
>>REPORTER: LATER, CARLA
REALIZED SHE WAS RIPPED OFF.
>> WE WERE JUST STARTING TO
SEE, THE SOCIAL SECURITY
ADMINISTRATION BEING
IMPERSONATED IN A BIG WAY.
>>REPORTER: AND KEVIN HUNT FROM
THE BETTER BUSINESS BUREAU SAYS
CON ARTISTS WILL USE VARIOUS
METHODS TO GET WHAT THEY WANT.
ONE ROBO CALL, THREATENS TO
SUSPEND YOUR SOCIAL SECURITY
NUMBER.
>> IF I DO NOT HEAR A CALL FROM
YOU, WE WILL HAVE TO ISSUE AN
ARREST WARRANT UNDER YOUR NAME.
>>REPORTER: NO MATTER THE
TACTICS, SCAMMERS ULTIMATELY
ARE LOOKING FOR MONEY AND
PERSONAL INFORMATION.
>> THE SOCIAL SECURITY
ADMINISTRATION IS NEVER GOING
TO CALL YOU, AND ASK YOU FOR
YOUR SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER,
THEY KNOW YOUR NUMBER.
>>REPORTER: WHAT DO PEOPLE NEED
TO KNOW?>> THE NUMBER ONE THING
IS, NEVER GIVE OUT INFORMATION
TO PEOPLE, TO PEOPLE WHO HAVE
CONTACTED THE TO YOU.
>> I DO NOT WANT THIS TO HAPPEN
ANY VIDEO.
>>REPORTER: WITH THE HELP OF
FEDERAL AND LOCAL AUTHORITY,
CARLA WAS ABLE TO GET HER MONEY
BACK, WHICH IS EXTREMELY RARE.
AND THE VAST MAJORITY OF CASES,
THE SCAM ARTISTS ARE NEVER
FOUND.
KENNETH CRAIG, CBS NEWS, NEW
YORK.
>> WILL THIS BE FOUND SOON, THE
I think the biggest thing
that I'd like to say
to first responders
is thank you.
Without them,
I wouldn't be here today.
I would just like
to say thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
From the bottom
of my heart, thank you.
♪♪
Stronger is blasting
her tumors...
without risking her bones.
It's training her
good cells...
to fight the bad guys.
Stronger is less pain...
new hope...
more fight.
It's doing everything
in your power...
and everything in ours.
Stronger, is changing even
faster than they do.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>>> WIDESPREAD REPORTING OF THE
PAST FEW DAYS, WITH A SPECIAL
COUNSEL INVESTIGATION.
EXAMINING RUSSIAN INTERVENTION
THE 2016 ELECTIONS, THE
INVESTIGATION COULD BE NEARING
ITS CONCLUSION.
ALLEGATIONS OF RUSSIAN COLLUSION
HAVE PLAGUED THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION FROM THE START,
LET'S BRING IN THE HOST OF
CBS'S FACE THE NATION, MARGARET
BRENNAN, HI MARGARET, SO, WE
ARE HEARING IT IS A POSSIBILITY
THAT THIS REPORT ARE PARTS OF
IT, COULD BE SHIELDED FROM
PUBLIC VIEW.
SO, DO WE HAVE ANY IDEA WHAT IS
GOING TO HAPPEN WHEN BOB
MUELLER AND HIS REPORT AND HIS
REPORT OVER TO THE DEPARTMENT
OF JUSTICE?
>> WELL, WE KNOW THAT IT WILL
THEN BE THE CALL OF THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL, OF BILL BARR,
AS TO WHETHER OR NOT, AT LEAST
SOME OF OR PART OF IT, WILL BE
PUBLIC, AND HOW MUCH TO SHARE
WITH LAWMAKERS HIMSELF.
ONCE YOU DO THAT, DOES THAT
THEN MEAN THE INFORMATION
LEAKS, AND GETS TERRY PICKED
THOUGH, THEN DO YOU ARGUE THAT
IT IS WITH A FULL DISCLOSURE TO
THE PUBLIC, WHAT IS THE
PUBLIC'S RIGHT TO KNOW, THESE
ARE SOME OF THE BIG QUESTIONS,
THAT ARE GOING TO NEXT BE ASKED
AS WE LOOK AT WHAT COULD HAPPEN
HERE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS BEEN ASKED
WHAT HE THINKS SHOULD HAPPEN,
HE SAYS IT IS ALL UP TO THE
AGED, OF COURSE, IF IT IS NOT
MADE PUBLIC, CONGRESS COULD TRY
TO SUBPOENA IT, BUT THEN, YOU
GET LOCKED IN THIS QUESTION OF
WHO ENFORCES THAT SUBPOENA, CAN
YOU FORCE A JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
DO SOMETHING IT DOES NOT WANT
TO DO IN THE FIRST PLACE.
ALL OF THIS MEANS THOUGH, THAT
EITHER, THERE IS THE
OPPORTUNITY TO CLEAR THE AIR,
AND LIVED THE CLOUDS THAT THE
PRESIDENT HAD SAID, HAVE BEEN
OVER HIM SINCE HE BEGAN, BEGAN
HIS TERM IN OFFICE. IF THERE IS
TRULY NOTHING THERE, WHY NOT
MAKE IT PUBLIC, BUT THEN
THERE'S THE QUESTION AS WELL,
OF WHAT THIS MEANS, IN TERMS OF
SITTING PRESIDENT, AND WHAT
THIS MEANS IN TERMS OF WHAT
SHOULD BE SHARED INTO EVENT TO
TRY AND PREVENT IT AGAIN FOR
ANY TYPE OF INTERFERENCE, SO WE
ARE ENTERING WHAT APPEARS TO BE
THE NEXT STAGE OF THE POTENTIAL
IMPACT OF THE MILLER PROBE, BUT
REALLY, NO HARD TIMELINE ON
WHEN THIS COULD COME OUT, IT IS
EXPECTED SOMETIME IN THE NEXT
FEW WEEKS.
>> MARGARET, QUICKLY OF COURSE
THE OPTICS OF TRYING TO KEEP
ANY PART OF IT FROM PUBLIC VIEW
WOULD BE HEAVILY SCRUTINIZED.
>> IT WILL BE HEAVILY
SCRUTINIZED, AND IT WILL BE
MAILED ABLATED BY BOTH SIDES,
THAT IS WHY THE SENATOR,
REPUBLICAN SENATOR JOHN KENNEDY
SAID IT IS GOING TO LEAK
ANYWAY, WHY NOT MAKE PARTS OF
IT PUBLIC.
WE ARE UNLIKELY TO SEE THE FULL
THING, AS THERE ARE THINGS THAT
ARE GOING TO BE KEPT PRIVATE BY
THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT.
BUT OF COURSE, WHAT PEOPLE WANT
TO FOCUS ON, IS WHAT ARE THE
CONNECTIONS BETWEEN THOSE
INDICTMENTS, THOSE GUILTY PLEAS
WE HAVE ALREADY SEEN FOR MANY
OF THE PLAYERS, YOU KNOW, THERE
HAVE BEEN ABOUT 34 OR FIVE
CASES THAT HAVE MOVED FORWARD,
INCLUDING THOSE 25 RUSSIAN
MILITARY INTELLIGENCE OFFICIALS
. IS THERE ANY CONNECTION
BETWEEN THEM AND THE PRESIDENT
HIMSELF, AND THE CAMPAIGN.
THOSE THE PARTS THAT ARE
PERHAPS, MOST RELEVANT TO THE
BIG POLITICAL QUESTION, THAT WE
ARE ALL FACING.
>> A BIG DISCUSSION THAT WILL
CONTINUE TO: THREE SUNDAY
MORNING, FACE THE NATION AND
WUSA 9, MARGARET BRENNER, AS
ALWAYS, THANK YOU.
>>> SO, WE ARE TALKING ABOUT
THE FACT THAT THE SNOW IS GONE,
THE TEMPERATURES ARE GOING UP,
BUT NOW, IT IS THE WIND THAT WE
HAD TO CONTEND WITH.
>> WE HAVE A LOT TO DEAL WITH
THIS WE CAN.
IT IS NOT GOING TO BE SNOWING,
BUT FIRST WHEN, WELL SECOND
WIND, BUT FOR SPRING, GOING TO
START WITH THE WIND, BECAUSE
ONCE YOU GET THE SOGGY GROUND,
HE STARTS RING WINS THAT COULD
BE GUSTING 40, 50, OR MORE,
THEN, WE HAVE GOT SOME
PROBLEMS, POTENTIALLY WITH
INCREASED TREES COMING DOWN,
DECREASED APPETITE OF THESE
AFFECT HERE ARE SOME OF THE
MOMENT, FROM FREDERICK WEST,
HIGHER ELEVATIONS IN THE BLUE
RIDGE, DISCUSSED 50 TO 60, I
WOULD NOT BE SURPRISED THOUGH
IS THIS IT'S EXPANDED MORE
TOWARDS THE METRO, AND IF YOU
WONDERED ABOUT THIS, THIS IS
GOING TO BE A BIG STORM,
BLIZZARD WARNINGS ARE OUT
ACROSS THE PLAINS, IT COULD BE
GUST OF 70s IN WESTERN NEW
YORK.
BUT, BEFORE THAT GETS HERE, WE
HAVE GOT RAIN THAT WE ARE
TRACKING TONIGHT.
SOUTH OF TOWN.
GOING DOWN TO RICHMOND, YOU'RE
GOING TO RUN INTO THIS, MAYBE
HARRISONBURG SOUTH IN THE
VALLEY, BUT AROUND HERE, THIS
WILL STAY SOUTH, WITH HEAVIER
SHOWERS, MOVING INTO RICHMOND,
DO EAST FOR THE MOST PART, SO,
IT IS GOING TO GET ON SOME OF
THAT, BUT REALLY THIS IS WAY
WAY SOUTH OF US, SO A QUIET
NIGHT HERE, WE HAVE GOT CLOUDY
SKIES, TEMPERATURES IN THE
UPPER 40s, WITH A NORTHWEST
WIND, SO A LITTLE BIT OF WIND
CHILL, BUT THE AIR IS DRY,
HUMIDITY IS ONLY 46%, SO THAT
TELLS YOU THE CHANCE FOR RAIN
TONIGHT IS ABOUT THAT.
48 IN TOWN, BUT 40 NOW IN
WINCHESTER, 34 IN OAKLAND,
STILL 46 WITH AN ENABLER
STATION IN SOUTHERN MARYLAND,
AND TOMORROW, WILL FEATURE
CLOUDS IN THE MORNING, MAYBE A
PEAK OF SUN EARLY, LOW 40s,
THAT IS IT, WITH SHOWERS
DEVELOPING IN THE AFTERNOON,
AND THAT COULD BE READY STEADY
RAIN ACTUALLY, PRETTY MODERATE
RAIN AT TIMES, AS FAR AS THE
WEEKEND, LOW 40s TOMORROW, BUT
THEN SUNDAY, AN EARLY SHOWER,
WINDY AND WARMER, IN THE 60s,
MAYBE EVEN UPPER 60s WITH
ENOUGH SUNSHINE.
, THOSE GUSTS ARE GOING TO BE A
PROBLEM, SO WE ARE GOING TO
KEEP THE YELLOW WEATHER ALERT
UP FOR SUNDAY, AND THIS SHOWS
YOU, THE WINTER STORM WARNINGS
IN ARIZONA, NEW MEXICO,
BLIZZARD WARNINGS FOR EASTERN
COLORADO, TO MINNESOTA.
THAT IS HOW BIG A STORM SYSTEM
THIS IS, AND THIS IS THE ONE
DUMPING ALL THE SNOW ON THE
SOUTHWEST, OVER 40 INCHES, I
CANNOT IMAGINE THAT, IN
FLAGSTAFF, SINCE WEDNESDAY.
AND, ALL THE RAIN THAT WILL BE
MOVING IN HERE, STARTING
MIDDAY, IN THE EARLY AFTERNOON
TOMORROW, AS IT MOVES IN FROM
THE SOUTHWEST, BUT NO PROBLEMS
TONIGHT, HERE JUST COMES THAT
RAIN, ONCE WE GET INTO TOMORROW
AFTERNOON, AT TIMES IT WILL BE
LOCALLY HEADY -- HEAVY HEADING
OUR WAY.
TO MECHANICAL, LOW TO MID 30s,
QUIET NIGHT.
WENT NORTHEAST AT FIVE, CLOUDY
AND COLD TONIGHT, WITH SHOWERS
APPROACHING WITH THE SOUTHWEST,
LATE MORNING, 32 TO 40, AND
THEN, REMOVES AND LOCALLY,
HEAVY.
UPPER 30s TO LOW 40s, THAT IS
IT.
HE COULD SEE AN INCH, MAY BE
MORE OF RAIN IN SPOTS, AS WE
GET INTO SATURDAY AFTERNOON.
YELLOW WEATHER ALERT SUNDAY FOR
THE MORNING SHOWERS, THE WINDS,
TEMPERATURES IN THE 60s, BUT
BACK IN THE 40s MONDAY, WITH
WIND, THE WIND CHILLS 20s AND
30s, A COLD, BUT GENERALLY DRY
WEEK UNTIL FRIDAY, WHEN WE HAVE
A CHANCE FOR SHOWERS.>> AND
NOW, WUSA 9 COURT, WITH DARREN ,
BROUGHT TO YOU BY X AFFINITY.
>> I'M DARREN HAYNES AT
NATIONAL SPRING TRAINING.
NOW, MAJOR LEAGUE BASEBALL IS
NOT ALWAYS ABOUT THE HITTING,
PITCHING, STEVE PLAYS A HUGE
FACTOR IN SCORING RUNS.
AND, MY MAN TREY TURNER IS AN
EXAMPLE OF THAT.
TREY TURNER IS ONE OF THE
FASTEST PLAYERS CURRENTLY IN
MAJOR LEAGUE BASEBALL.
ACCORDING TO MLB ADVANCED
MEDIA, TREY TURNER'S 30.1 FEET
PER SECOND, RANKS FIFTH IN THE
MAJORS LAST SEASON.
TURNER WAS CLOCKED AT 22.7
MILES PER HOUR, WHILE LEGGING
OUT A TRIPLE.
IMPRESSIVE.
THE FASTEST BALLCARRIER IN THE
NFL LAST SEASON, WITH ONLY
22.09.
HE ALSO RAN FROM HOME THE FIRST
BASE IN 3.7 SECONDS.
THAT IS ONLY SIX TENTHS OF A
SECOND SLOWER THAN HALL OF
FAMER MICKEY MANTLE'S ALL-TIME
RECORD OF THREE POINT ONE.
WITH THAT SPEED, TURNER COULD
ALMOST FEEL BASES AT WILL.
>> MAKE THEM RUN.
FASTER THAN SOME, NOT ALL, BUT,
YOU KNOW, SOMETHING I HAVE HAD,
SINCE I WAS A LITTLE KID, AND
SINCE WE WERE STILL LOOK AT, SO
I TRY TO USE IT AS MUCH AS I
CAN.
REMAKE HE STOLE 42 BASES LAST
SEASON.
THAT RINGS SECOND IN THE
MAJORS, AND SET A NEW FRANCHISE
RECORD.
>> IT IS EXCITING, YOU KNOW.
AND, WE LET THE RAINS GO, AND HE
IS ON HIS OWN, HE CAN STILL
ENABLE WANTS, HE KNOWS THAT.
WE CAN PUT THE PRESSURE ON HIM
A LITTLE BIT, ABOUT MAY BECOME
HAVING MORE TIMES.
>>REPORTER: TURNER WILL ENTER
HIS FIFTH SEASON, AND HE IS
ALREADY OFF TO A QUICK START.
IS REALLY.>> NAME WHEN HE PLAY
ON A TEAM YOU WANT TO GIVE THE
USER TO
>> TREY TURNER.
>> WHILE.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE HE IS FAST AND
HE LIKES TO DO EVERY THING FAST.
>> NOW, I ASKED TREY TURNER
NAME THE SPORT YOU WISH YOU
COULD PLAY TO UTILIZE YOUR
SPEED, HE SAID TRACK, AND MAKE
SENSE, RIGHT?
BUT THEN, HE TOLD ME, HE IS NOT
DOWN TO PRACTICE WITH THE
KNEES.
I AM FOR SPORTS, WUSA 9 SPORT.
>> COMING UP AT SIX, DEMOCRATS
INTRODUCED A RESOLUTION  TO
BLOCK PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
EMERGENCY DECLARATION FOR A
MEXICAN BORDER WALL.
>>> PLUS, NO HOST, NO PROBLEM!
THE ACADEMY AWARDS, WHO IS
GOING TO WALK AWAY WITH AN
OSCAR, WE GOT A PREVIEW, JUST
AHEAD.
I never thought I'd say this
but I found bladder leak
underwear
that's actually pretty.
Always Discreet Boutique.
Hidden inside is a super
absorbent core
that quickly turns liquid to
gel.
So I feel protected and pretty.
Always Discreet Boutique.
Do I use a toothpaste that
whitens my teeth?
Or one that's good for my teeth?
Now I don't have to choose.
From Crest 3D White.
The Whitening Therapy
Collection.
Now with Charcoal or Coconut
Oil.
It gently whitens.
Plus, it has a fortifying
formula
to protect your enamel.
Crest. Healthy, beautiful smiles
for life.
>>> THERE MAY NOT BE A HOST
THIS YEAR, BUT THERE IS STILL A
LOT OF ANTICIPATION HEAD OF
THIS WEEKEND OSCARS.
CHRIS MARTINEZ HAS A LOOK AT
WHO COULD TAKE HOME HOLLYWOOD'S
BIGGEST HONORS
>>REPORTER: PREPARATIONS ARE
UNDERWAY OUTSIDE THE THEATER,
AS HOLLYWOOD GET READY TO HONOR
ITS VERY BEST.
>> I AM THE QUEEN, BUT YOU ARE
MAD.
REMAKE THIS YEAR, THE FAVORITE,
AND ROMA, WITH 10 NOMINATIONS
EACH.
BOTH FILMS ARE UP FOR BEST
PICTURE, ALONG WITH THE BOOK,
BLACK KLANSMEN, BOHEMIAN
RHAPSODY, A STAR IS BORN, MICE,
AND MARBLED BLACK PANDA.
>> IT IS A REALLY INTERESTING
MAKE MIX, BECAUSE THERE ARE
SOME REALLY POPULAR MOVIES, BUT
ALSO SOME VERY SMALL MOVIES.
>>REPORTER: VARIETY MAGAZINE
AWARD EDITOR, SAYS THIS YEAR NO
ONE FILM IS EXPECTED TO SWEEP
THE AWARDS, WHICH COULD MEAN A
NIGHT OF SURPRISES, WITH
PERHAPS A FEW EXCEPTIONS.
>> I THINK THE CLOSEST THING
YOU GET TO A CONSENSUS, ALFONSO
CLARA DIRECTOR, GLENN CLOSE
PRACTICE, AND SHE'S ACTOR.
>>REPORTER: BUT BEYOND THE
WINNERS, A LOT OF ATTENTION ON
THIS YEAR'S OSCARS WILL FOCUS
ON THE CEREMONY ITSELF.
FOR THE FIRST TIME, IN 30
YEARS, THE SHOW WILL NOT HAVE A
HOST.
INSTEAD, RELYING ON HOLLYWOOD A
LISTERS, LIKE BARBRA STREISAND,
SAMUEL L JACKSON, AND MELISSA
McCARTHY TO HAND OUT TROPHIES.
RAY THINGS A SHORTER SCREEN
LINE SHOW COULD BE A HIT WITH
VIEWERS.
>> SO, WHEN YOU WATCH THE
OSCARS, IT IS LIKE A GOOD 20
MINUTES BEFORE THEY GET TO THE
FIRST AWARD.
SO, THIS COULD, RIGHT AWAY,
THIS IS GOING BE QUICKER.
>>REPORTER: AS FOR WHO COULD
ULTIMATELY TAKE HOME HOLLYWOOD
GOLD, ONLY OSCAR KNOWS.
CHRIS MARTINEZ, CBS NEWS, LOS
ANGELES.
>> THE ACADEMY SAYS MORE THAN
50 CELEBRITIES WILL PRESENT
AWARDS DURING SUNDAY'S SHOW.
>>> RIGHT NOW AT SIX,
>> WE ARE IS EQUALLY STUNNED AS
EVER BAILED.
>> NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS OWNER,
ROBERT KRAFT, CHARGED IN A
FLORIDA PROSTITUTION SCAM.>>
ROBERT KELLY WAS INDICTED BEFORE
COOK COUNTY GRAND JURY ON 10
COUNTS OF AGGRAVATED CRIMINAL
SEXUAL ABUSE, INVOLVING FOUR
VICTIMS.>>> R&B START R KELLY
CHARGED WITH SEXUAL ABUSE,
PROSECUTORS SAY SEVERAL OF THE
VICTIMS WERE MINORS.
>>> AN ACTIVE WEEKEND WITH
PETTER HEADED OUR WAY WITH A
THREAT FOR SOME HEAVY RAIN AND
SOME HIGH WINDS AS WELL.
I WILL TYPE IT OUT FOR YOU.
>> THE NEWS AT SIX, START
NOW.>>> CONGRESS, AND PRESIDENT
TRUMP, HEADING FOR ANOTHER
MAJOR SHOWDOWN, TONIGHT, A
RESOLUTION WAS INTRODUCED TODAY
THAT WOULD BLOCK THE PRESIDENT
FROM DIVERTING MONEY FROM THE
PENTAGON, AND OTHER AGENCIES TO
BUILD THAT BORDER WALL.
NATALIE BRANN HAS THE LATEST
FROM CAPITOL HILL.
>>REPORTER: DEMOCRATIC
CONGRESSMAN, HAS INTRODUCED A
RESOLUTION TO BLOCK THE
PRESIDENT NATIONAL EMERGENCY
DECLARATION.
SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI SAYS THE
HOUSE WILL VOTE ON THE MEASURE,
EARLY NEXT WEEK.
>> THE PRESIDENT HAS MADE VERY
CLEAR THAT HE HAS THE LEGAL
AUTHORITY, AND THE PRACTICAL
NEED,