>>> [ MUSIC ] GOOD AFTERNOON,
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
WE HAVE LOTS GOING ON TODAY,
LET'S GET TO THE BIG THREE
STORIES AT NOON.
>>> DON'T GET TOO COMFORTABLE,
BECAUSE MORE SNOW IS ON THE WAY
JUST IN TIME FOR THE WEEKEND.
WE ARE TIMING OUT THE SNOW.
>>> THERE IS A NEW CRACKDOWN ON
RIGHT TURNS ON RED IN THE CITY
AND IF YOU GET CAUGHT, YOU WILL
GET A HEFTY FINE.
>>> AND ACTOR JUSSIE SMOLLETT
HANDS OVER HIS PHONE RECORDS TO
HELP POLICE FIND THE MAN WHO HE
SAYS  ATTACKED HIM.
THE RECORDS WERE HEAVILY
REDACTED, WHAT THIS MEANS FOR
THE INVESTIGATION.
>>> TODAY'S SUNSHINE MAY BE A
WELCOME SIGHT AFTER THE SNOW
AND SLEET AND ICE, BUT IT WON'T
BE AROUND FOR LONG.
WE ARE TRACKING THREE POTENTIAL
WINTER STORM SYSTEMS HEADING
OUR WAY.
LET'S CHECK IN WITH HOWARD
BERNSTEIN.
WHAT DO WE NEED TO KNOW ABOUT
THE APPROACHING STORMS?
>> THERE IS A LOT OF
UNCERTAINTY.
THERE ARE THREE STORMS I'M
TRACKING RIGHT NOW AS WE GO
INTO THE WEEKEND.
WE ARE LOOKING AT TEMPERATURES
TODAY, NO PROBLEMS INTO THE
40s, BUT LET'S LOOK AT SOME OF
THE MODELS, BECAUSE THEY DO NOT
AGREE.
WHEN THEY DO NOT AGREE, THERE
IS AN UNCERTAINTY FACTOR.
THIS IS NOT A CLASSIC SET UP
FOR SNOW, BUT THE CLASSIC SETUP
IS A BIG HIGH ACROSS NEW
ENGLAND AND A STORM PASSING TO
THE SOUTHEAST.
WE WILL START WITH THE GFS
WHICH STARTS FRIDAY.
WE MAY SEE AN ISOLATED
SHOWERHEAD OF THE FRONT ON
FRIDAY AFTERNOON AND ON
SATURDAY, NOTICE THE BLUE OFF
TO THE SOUTH AND WEST OF US AS
WE GO THROUGH SATURDAY, THIS
NOW, YESTERDAY HAD SNOW, BUT
THIS NOW SLIDES SOUTH OF US AND
THIS WOULD BE A MISS.
THE SECOND SYSTEM ON SUNDAY IS
QUICKLY BEHIND IT IN THE
AFTERNOON AND EVENING.
THIS COULD HAVE ICE, AND NOTICE
THE SNOW TO THE NORTH IN
PENNSYLVANIA AND THEN NUMBER
THREE COMES IN TUESDAY NIGHT
INTO WEDNESDAY.
HERE COMES THE SNOW, AND THIS
ONE HAS QUITE A BIT OF SNOW
OVERNIGHT AND THAT LIFTS TO THE
NORTH AND THIS IS JUST UPDATED
FROM A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
WE WANT TO SHOW YOU THE
EUROPEAN SOLUTION TO ALL OF
THIS, AS WE GO INTO SATURDAY
MORNING, RAIN WITH SOME SNOW
AND THE EUROPEAN, UNLIKE THE
GFS, REALLY CLUBBERS US ON
SATURDAY AND THEN THAT PULLS
AWAY AND STORM 2 MAY BE A MESS,
FREEZING RAIN FOR A WHILE AND
STORM NUMBER THREE ON WEDNESDAY
IS ALSO A LITTLE MIX, BUT
MAINLY A RAIN SYSTEM.
THE STORM AS POSSIBLE SATURDAY
AND SUNDAY AND WEDNESDAY AND
THEN SNOW VERSUS RAIN VERSUS
ICE, SNOW IS LIKELY WITH THE
THREE SYSTEMS, BUT AS I SAID
EARLIER, LOTS OF UNCERTAINTY
AND WE CONTINUE TO CHECK THIS
CAREFULLY AND WE HAVE THE
BREAKDOWN, THE RAKE OUT STORES
ALONG WITH THE REGULAR FORECAST
ON THE APP@TRAN09.COM.
>>> A SCARY SITUATION FOR
RESIDENTS IN THE H STREET
CORRIDOR LAST NIGHT, DOZENS OF
OFFICERS WERE OUT WITH THEIR
GUNS DRAWN AND IT WAS A TENSE
SITUATION AND NOW FOR PEOPLE
ARE UNDER ARREST.
>> Reporter: THINGS ARE PRETTY
MUCH BACK TO NORMAL HERE AT THE
BUSY H STREET CORRIDOR AND THE
INVESTIGATION IS FOCUSED ON
THIS PIZZA SHOP RIGHT HERE
RIGHT BY THE INTERSECTION OF
FIFTH STREET AND EIGHTH STREET
NORTHEAST.
LET'S BREAK DOWN WHAT HAPPENED.
POLICE GOT THE CALL JUST BEFORE
11:00 LAST NIGHT THAT THERE WAS
A MAN WITH A GUN.
THEY SHOW UP AND FIND FOUR
PEOPLE FLEEING THE SCENE IN A
SILVER MINIVAN.
SOMEONE WENT TOWARDS THE
OFFICERS AND NO OFFICERS WERE
HIT AND THEY ARE DOING JUST
FINE.
AND THEN THE MINIVAN GOES DOWN
EIGHTH STREET A COUPLE BLOCKS
AND MAKES A LEFT ON EIGHTH
STREET ANOTHER BLOCK AND THEN
THEY SCATTER.
ALL FOUR OF THESE GUYS GO
RUNNING.
POLICE CHASE THEM ON FOOT AFTER
A FEW MINUTES, THE CATCH ALL
FOUR OF THEM, AND THEY FIND A
GUN, THE BIG QUESTION IS, WHAT
HAPPENED AT THIS PIZZA SHOP?
THEY ARE LOOKING INTO WHETHER
OR NOT THERE MAY HAVE BEEN A
ROBBERY, CHAOTIC SCENE FOR A
LOT OF THE SHOPPERS ON EIGHTH
STREET NORTHEAST.
WE ARE GLAD TO HEAR THE POLICE
OFFICERS ARE DOING JUST FINE.
>>> OFFICERS FOUND A LARGE
AMOUNT OF MARIJUANA IN THE CAR
INCLUDING EDIBLES AND
VAPORIZED.
THEY ARE FACING GUN AND DRUG
CHARGES.
VIRGINIA STATE POLICE HAVE
CLEARED AND ALEXANDER POLICE
OFFICER INVOLVED IN A SHOOTING
LAST DECEMBER.
PEGGY FOX OBTAINED VIDEO NEAR
THE 900 BLOCK OF NORTH PATRICK
STREET.
THE OFFICER FEARED FOR HIS LIFE
WHEN THE 28-YEAR-OLD POINTED A
GUN AT HIM.
THAT MAN IS FACING FIVE
CRIMINAL CHARGES INCLUDING
ATTEMPTED WOUNDING OF AN
OFFICER.
AT LEAST ONE PERSON WAS INJURED
IN A COMMUTER BUS CRASH IN
CLINTON.
THIS HAPPENED ON THE SOUTHBOUND
SIDE OF RANCH AVENUE AT ABOUT
8:00 THIS MORNING AND OFFICIALS
ARE STILL NOT SURE WHAT CAUSED
THE CRASH.
THE BUS DRIVER WAS THE ONLY
PERSON ON THE BUS WHEN
SOMETHING CAUSED IT TO VEER
INTO THE MEDIAN.
THE DRIVER WAS TRAPPED AND HAD
TO BE RESCUED AND WAS FLOWN TO
THE NEAREST HOSPITAL.
AN INVESTIGATION IS CURRENTLY
UNDERWAY.
>>> CONGRESS HAS A DEAL IN
PLACE TO AVOID YET ANOTHER
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN AND THE
DEADLINE IS TWO DAYS AWAY AND
THEY COULD PUT THE MEASURE UP
FOR A VOTE TONIGHT.
THE QUESTION, WILL PRESIDENT
TRUMP SIGN IT?
MATT GREGORY HAS THE STORY.
>> THE PRESIDENT HAS HAD MIXED
REACTIONS TO THE POTENTIAL DEAL
AND EITHER WAY, CONGRESS SAYS
THEY PLAN TO MOVE LOWER TODAY.
>> IF YOU REMEMBER, THIS BATTLE
WAS OVER FUNDING FOR A BORDER
WALL.
IN A DEAL REACHED BY BOTH
PARTIES, CONGRESS OFFERED THE
PRESIDENT ROUGHLY $1.4 BILLION
FOR 55 MILES OF BORDER FENCING,
BUT THAT IS WELL SHORT OF THE
$5 BILLION HE ASKED FOR FOR 200
MILES OF A BORDER WALL.
>> AM I HAPPY AT FIRST GLANCE?
I JUST GOT TO SEE IT, THE
ANSWER IS NO.
>> AUGUST PLANS TO GO AHEAD AND
BOOK THE NIGHT ON THE FUNGUS
AGREEMENT AND THE PRESIDENT
INDICATED HE MAY ACTUALLY SIGN
THE BILL.
>> I DON'T THINK YOU ARE GOING
TO SEE A SHUTDOWN.
>> THE DEADLINE TO GET THE DEAL
DONE WILL BE THIS FRIDAY.
THE LAST PARTIAL GOVERNMENT
SHUTDOWN LASTED 30 DAYS AND
AFFECTED 800,000 FEDERAL
WORKERS.
WHEN I SPOKE WITH THE FEDERAL
WORKER LAST NIGHT, SHE TOLD ME
THAT SHE AND COLLEAGUES ARE ON
"PINS AND NEEDLES WAITING TO
SEE IF THIS DEAL GETS DONE AND
THEY ARE OPTIMISTIC, BUT THEY
DON'T WANT TO GET THEIR HOPES
UP.
IT LOOKS LIKE CONGRESS TONIGHT
PLANS TO MOVE FORWARD WITH SOME
SORT OF VOTE ON THE POTENTIAL
DEAL.
>>> WHILE CONGRESS WORKS OUT
THE NEW BUDGET DEAL, THE
NATIONAL DEBT HAS TOPPLED $22
TRILLION FOR THE FIRST TIME IN
U.S. HISTORY.
THE DEBT LIMIT BY MORE THAN $2
TRILLION IN THE FIRST 2 YEARS
SINCE PRESIDENT TRUMP TOOK
OFFICE AND IT CONTINUED TO
ACCELERATE SINCE TAX CUTS WERE
PASSED IN DECEMBER 2017.
>>> METRO IS LOOKING TO
SUBSIDIZE UBER AND LYFT TRIPS
FOR LATE-NIGHT WORKERS.
THE TRANSIT AGENCY IS DRAFTING
A REQUEST FOR PROPOSALS AND
THEY ARE TRYING TO HELP LATE-
NIGHT WORKERS GET HOME AND GET
TO WORK BETWEEN THE HOURS OF
MIDNIGHT AND 4 AM.
LATE-NIGHT SERVICE ON METRO HAS
BEEN SUSPENDED TO HELP CREWS
CATCH UP ON MAINTENANCE WORK.
THE EXTENSION COULD BE EXTENDED
FOR ANOTHER YEAR.
THE PUBLIC SAFETY BOARD TAKES A
PRELIMINARY VOTE ON THE MEASURE
ON THURSDAY.
THIS NEXT STORY IS FOR DRIVERS.
>>> A RIGHT TURN ON RED WILL
SOON BE A THING OF THE PAST AT
ABOUT 100 INTERSECTIONS IN THE
CITY.
THE NEW BAND BEGINS NEXT WEEK.
WE HAVE A LOOK AT WHAT YOU CAN
EXPECT.
>> YOU WILL START SEEING A LOT
MORE OF THESE SIGNS POPPING UP
IN THE NEXT SIX MONTHS.
THE GOAL IS TO CUT DOWN THE
NUMBER OF PEOPLE DYING IN
TRAFFIC ACCIDENTS.
>> WE BELIEVE THAT TRAFFIC
FATALITIES ARE DEPENDABLE.
SPENT LAST YEAR, 3600 PEOPLE
DIED, 36 PEOPLE DIED IN TRAFFIC
INCIDENTS IN DC.
THAT'S THE HIGHEST NUMBER IN 10
YEARS.
SO THAT IS THE REGION, THAT IS
THE REASON WHY THEY SAY THIS
HAS TO HAPPEN, BUT NOT EVERYONE
AGREES.
>> THIS GOES ON AND IT'S
INHERENTLY WHY I DO THAT.
IN OTHER PLACES THAT YOU HAVE A
HIGH TRAFFIC VOLUME AND HIGH
PEDESTRIAN VOLUME, IT MAY BE A
CATASTROPHIC SITUATION.
>> WHAT IS YOUR BIGGEST FEAR?
>> THAT IT WILL CAUSE MORE
INJURIES AND MORE FATALITIES
AND IT WILL COST MORE REAR END
COLLISIONS IN THE CITY.
>> BUT YOU KNOW BE.SAYS THEY
DID THE RESEARCH AND THEY THINK
THAT THEY HAVE ENOUGH RESEARCH
TO GO BY, THEY THINK THAT THEY
ARE GOOD MOVING FORWARD WITH
THIS.
>> THEY ALWAYS SAY THAT, THAT'S
WHAT YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO SAY.
>> BUT DDOT SAYS IT OPERATES ON
FACTS AND LANDING RIGHT TURNS
ON RED HAS WORKED IN OTHER
CITIES.
>> WE USE THE SCIENTIFIC
APPROACH TO IDENTIFY LOCATIONS
THAT HAVE A PARTICULARLY HIGH
VOLUME OF STRANDS, AND THOSE
ARE THE LOCATIONS FOR WHICH WE
THINK THAT IMPROVING SAFETY IN
THE INTERSECTION IS PARAMOUNT.
>> THIS IS ALL A PART OF THE
MAYOR'S VISION ZERO INITIATIVE.
THE GOAL IS TO GET THE NUMBER
OF TRAFFIC DEATHS DOWN TO ZERO
IN JUST 5 YEARS.
ON THE ROAD, I'M MICHAEL
QUANDER.
>> WHERE ARE ALL OF THESE
INTERSECTIONS WITH THE RULES?
WE HAVE YOU COVERED IN THAT
REGARD, WE POSTED THE FULL LIST
ON THE MOBILE APP AND WEBSITE,
WUSA9.COM.
>>> STILL TO COME, LOCAL WOMAN
SHARES HER STORY AFTER
SUFFERING A HEART
>>> WUSA9 NEWS IS SPONSORED IN
PART BY  GREENSPRING RETIREMENT
COMMUNITY.
>> AS WUSA9 CONTINUES THE
IMPACT HEALTH MATTERS SERIES
THIS MONTH, WE WANT YOU TO KNOW
ABOUT HEART DISEASE AND THE
EFFECT ON  WOMEN, IT IS THE
NUMBER ONE KILLER OF WOMEN IN
THE UNITED STATES.
WE SAT DOWN WITH A FORMER NEWS
REPORTER WHO SUFFERED A HEART
ATTACK AT THE AGE OF 36.
>> THIS IS MY BADGE OF HONOR.
>> THIS GIVES ME POWER.
THIS GIVES ME STRENGTH.
THIS MEANS I'M NOT ALONE.
>> JENNIFER DONNELLAN IS PROUD
TO WEAR THIS RED DRESS IS A
SYMBOL THAT IT'S TIME TO RAISE
AWARENESS ABOUT HEART DISEASE
IN THE DEADLY THREAT AGAINST
WOMEN.
>> A WOMAN NEEDS A CARDIOLOGIST
IN HER LIFE LIKE SHE HAS A
GYNECOLOGIST.
>> BEFORE SHE TOOK HER POST AS
DIRECTOR OF MEDIA RELATIONS FOR
THE PRINCE GEORGES COUNTY
POLICE DEPARTMENT, SHE SPENT 20
YEARS AS A TELEVISION NEWS
REPORTER INCLUDING 10 SPENT
RIGHT HERE REPORTING ON CRIME
THROUGHOUT THE DMZ.
>> IT WAS DIFFICULT, REALLY AT
THE TIME, I HAD BLINDERS ON, IT
WAS ALL ABOUT THE CAREER.
EVERY THING ELSE SORT OF FELL
TO THE WAYSIDE.
YOU WENT TO SLEEP WHEN HE WENT
TO SLEEP AND YOU WOKE UP WHEN
HE WOKE UP AND YOU ATE WHAT YOU
COULD.
>> SHE WAS ALWAYS ON THE GO
UNTIL ONE DAY AFTER A LIFE SHOT
AND CHEST PAIN STOPPED HER.
>> I BEGAN TO FEEL SOMETHING IN
THE MIDDLE OF MY CHEST.
WHEN I SAY IN THE MIDDLE OF MY
CHEST, IT FELT LIKE IT WAS FIVE
MILES AWAY, IT WAS SO DEEP
INSIDE, I TOOK A FEW STEPS IN
THE PAIN GOT WORSE.
>> A FEW MORE STEPS AND THEN MY
LEFT ARM, I WAS ON ALL FOURS AT
THAT POINT.
>> SHE WAS RUSHED TO THE
HOSPITAL AND DOCTORS TOLD HER
SHE WAS HAVING A HEART ATTACK,
SOMETHING SHE NEVER IMAGINED
HAPPENING AT THE AGE OF 36.
SHE WAS ALWAYS WORRIED ABOUT
BREAST CANCER WHICH KILLED HER
GRANDMOTHER.
>> THAT MOMENT WAS SO
TERRIFYING, NOW I AM IN SHOCK,
AND I'M IN FEAR FOR MY LIFE,
WILL I SURVIVE THIS?
>> SHE HAD SOMETHING CALLED A
SPONTANEOUS CORONARY ARTERY
DISSECTION.
>> THE INNER LINING OF MY RIGHT
CORONARY ARTERY TORE LIKE A
PIECE OF FABRIC AND IT BLOCKED
THE ARTERY AND ALL OF THE BLOOD
THAT WAS GOING INSIDE CLOTTED.
>> DOCTORS USED STENTS TO OPEN
ARTERY.
I REMEMBER SAYING IT HURTS, IT
HURTS.
AND THAT WAS IT.
THERE HAS NEVER BEEN A FEELING
LIKE THIS IN MY ENTIRE LIFE.
>> A HEART ATTACK AT THE AGE OF
36 THAT SHE NEVER SAW COMING.
>> THE STRESS THAT THEY, LIKE
STRESS KILLS, THAT'S REAL.
PEOPLE NEED TO UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> JUST GRATEFUL TO BE ALIVE
TODAY.
>> REPORTING IN PRINCE GEORGE'S
COUNTY, WUSA9.
>>> A POWERFUL STORY NO DOUBT,
ACCORDING TO THE CDC, HEART
DISEASE IS RESPONSIBLE FOR THE
DEATHS OF ONE OUT OF FOUR
WOMEN.
AND THAT IS WHY OUR NEXT IMPACT
HEALTH MATTERS EXPO IS SO
IMPORTANT.
WE WILL OFFER FREE HEALTH
SCREENINGS AT THE KILLING
COMMUNITY CENTER IN PRINCE
GEORGES COUNTY ON THURSDAY,
FEBRUARY 21.
THERE WILL BE TWO SESSIONS, ONE
IN THE EARLY MORNING FROM SIX
UNTIL 11 AND ANOTHER IN THE
AFTERNOON FROM TWO UNTIL 7:00.
TO LEARN MORE AND SIGN UP, YOU
CAN GO TO OUR WEBSITE,
WUSA9.COM/HEALTH MATTERS , AND
WE KNOW SO MANY COLLEAGUES HERE
AT THE STATION AND HAD THEIR
OWN EXPERIENCES WITH THIS.
THIS IS REAL.
>> FRIENDS AND FAMILY MEMBERS,
GET YOUR NUMBERS CHECK.
I'VE BEEN CHECKING SINCE 15 OR
17 YEARS AGO, GENETICS IS A
GIFT THAT KEEPS GIVING GOOD OR
BAD.
GET A CHECK AND I SALUTE ALL
THE FOLKS AT AMERICAN HEART
ASSOCIATION TO ERADICATE HEART
DISEASE.
>> PREVENTION GOES A LONG WAY.
>>> WE HAVE A CHANCE FOR WINTRY
WEATHER AS WE GO TO THE
WEEKEND, IF YOU MISSED THE TOP
OF THE BROADCAST, I WILL GO
OVER THIS ONE MORE TIME, THE
GFS, THE AMERICAN MODEL HAS A
SLIGHT CHANCE FOR SHOWERS
FRIDAY.
WE WILL BE WELL IN THE 50s, BUT
LOOK OUT QUICKLY, BY SATURDAY
MORNING, SNOW DEVELOPING AND
NOW TO THE SOUTH, YESTERDAY IT
WAS ON TOP OF US AND THIS WILL
BE A MISSED SATURDAY AND THIS
WILL CHANGE OVER THE DAYS,
STORM NUMBER TWO ON SUNDAY
COULD HAVE SNOW AND THEN IT IS
WAY UP ABOVE I-80 AND SOME
POINTS AND STORM 3 WILL CHECK
FOR TUESDAY NIGHT AND
WEDNESDAY, YOU WILL NOTICE THE
SNOW TO OUR SOUTHWEST OUT
TOWARD HARRISONBURG AND
CHARLOTTESVILLE SOUTH, AND THEN
AS WE GET INTO WEDNESDAY
MORNING, JUST SOME MODERATE
SNOW AND CHANGING TO SLEET AND
FREEZING RAIN AND THEN LIFTING
TERRAIN HERE BY WEDNESDAY
EVENING AND SNOW NORTH, THIS
COULD BE THE BIGGER ONE
ACCORDING TO THE GFS.
THE EUROPEAN MODEL BRINGS US
INTO SATURDAY MORNING AND THAT
IS FRIDAY, BUT SOME SNOW NORTH
AND WEST SWITCHING OVER TO MUCH
MORE SNOW BY MID-DAY AND BY
SATURDAY EVENING, THAT STORM IS
GONE, SO THE EURO HAS SNOW
SATURDAY AND THE GFS IS A MESS
AND STORM 2, WE HAVE A LITTLE
BIT OF A WINTRY MIX AND
FREEZING RAIN OVER TERRAIN AND
GONE AND AND STORM 3 WEDNESDAY
IS MORE OF A RAINMAKER IN THE
EURO, BUT A SNOW MAKER ON THE
GFS.
SNOW POSSIBLE SATURDAY AND
SUNDAY AND WEDNESDAY AND WE
DON'T KNOW WHETHER IT'S SNOW OR
RAIN OR ICE.
IT'S JUST TOO SOON, THESE
DETAILS WORK THEMSELVES OUT
OVER THE NEXT FEW DAYS AND SOME
SNOW IS LIKELY DESPITE OF THE
UNCERTAINTY, AND WE LOOK AT THE
TWO MODELS OVER THE NEXT SEVEN
DAYS, THIS GOES OUT 168 HOURS,
WE LOOK AT THE EUROPEAN, THE
BAND OF SNOW WITH HEAVIEST
STUFF WEST, THAT'S 3+ INCHES
FOR DC AND THE GFS IS IN THE
WHITE, 1 TO 3 WITH HEAVIEST
SNOW SOUTH AND WEST OF US, BUT
FARTHER SOUTH THAN THE HERO,
THE GFS GOING DOWN INTO NORTH
CAROLINA, WE HAVE TO WATCH AND
WE WILL SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
THERE IS SOME SNOW FALLING
WEALTH OF THE NORTH AND EVEN
NOT THAT FAR AWAY ONCE YOU GET
NORTH OF I-70, SNOW SHOWERS
HERE IN PARTS OF WEST VIRGINIA
ACROSS 522 TO HAGERSTOWN AND
OVER TO WESTMINSTER.
AND TALK HIS BILL IN NORTHERN
BALTIMORE COUNTY AND THURMONT
AND EMMITSBURG SEEING A COUPLE
FLAKES, NO BIG DEAL, BUT THERE
ARE SNOW SHOWERS OUT THERE WITH
TEMPERATURES THIS HOUR IN THE
UPPER 30s NORTH AND UPPER 40s
WANTING TO 50 THIS AFTERNOON
AND WE SEE SOME SUNSHINE AND
CLOUDS MIX AND CLEAR SKIES
TONIGHT AND THE BREEZE WILL BE
DIMINISHING.
RIGHT NOW, WE HAVE PARTLY
CLOUDY 48 AND DEW POINTS IN THE
20s AND THE PRESSURE IS RISING
QUICKLY.
THAT'S AFTER BEING PRETTY LOW
THE LAST COUPLE STORMS.
PARTLY TO MOSTLY SUNNY THIS
AFTERNOON AND 44 TO 52 AND WINS
WEST 10 TO 20 AND TONIGHT IS
MOSTLY CLEAR WITH 26 TO 32 AND
THERE MAY BE SOME SLICK SPOTS
WHERE MELTING IS OCCURRING.
BREEZY AT TIMES ON THURSDAY AND
FRIDAY NEAR 60 WITH THE
ISOLATED SHOWER AND COLD
WEATHER RETURNS WITH THE THREAT
FOR WINTRY WEATHER SATURDAY AND
SUNDAY, BUT NEXT WEEK, WE START
CHILLY, BUT WE ARE OKAY UNTIL
TUESDAY NIGHT.
>> DC'S FAVORITE BALD EAGLE,
LIBERTY AND JUSTICE HAVE JUST
LAID THERE FIRST EGG OF THE
YEAR, THEY HAVE BEEN TOGETHER
FOR 14 YEARS, AND THEIR NESTS
SITS HIGH IN THE OAK TREE IN
SOUTHWEST DC.
WE ARE TOLD IT TAKES ANYWHERE
BETWEEN 35
>>> ESQUIRE MAGAZINE IN HOT
WATER THIS AFTERNOON AND YOU
CAN SEE THE PERSON RESPONSIBLE
FOR RUINING YOUR MARRIAGE.
WE ARE TALKING ABOUT THOSE
STORIES AND MORE, LET'S KICK
THINGS OFF WITH ESQUIRE GETTING
A LOT OF ATTENTION ONLINE
PRIMARILY FOR THE MARCH ISSUE.
LOTS OF PEOPLE SAY IT SEEMS TO
MISS THE MARK.
>> THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE THE
AMERICAN BOY, MIDDLE-CLASS
AMERICAN, SO I THINK THE ISSUE
HERE IS PEOPLE JUST SAY, WHY
ARE WE REPRESENTING ANOTHER
WHITE PERSON DURING BLACK
HISTORY MONTH?
>> ABIGAIL SAYS I DON'T MIND
THAT THERE IS AN ARTICLE ABOUT
A WILL YOUNG WHITE BOY WITH
PRIVILEGE, BUT I DO MIND IF IT
COMES OUT IN BLACK HISTORY
MONTH.
>> THAT WAS THE PRINCIPAL
ISSUE, WE HEARD FROM ESQUIRE
AND THEY SAY WE PLANNED ON
PROFILING A LOT OF DIFFERENT
PEOPLE, BUT THIS IS THE ONE
THAT THEY WANTED TO PROFILE
RIGHT NOW.
THERE IS ANOTHER PERSPECTIVE ON
THIS THAT IS A CULTURAL DYNAMIC
IN THE COUNTRY CHANGING AND IT
WARRANTS SOME PERSPECTIVE AND
AT LEAST SOME INVESTIGATION TO
SEE WHAT IS IT LIKE TRYING TO
NAVIGATE THIS SPACE THAT WE ARE
IN NOW AND WE ARE TALKING ABOUT
JUSSIE SMOLLETT WHOSE STORY
CONTINUES TO EVOLVE AND HE HAS
TURNED OVER PHONE RECORDS TO
POLICE AS THEY TRIED TO FIND
THE PEOPLE THAT ALLEGEDLY
ASSAULTED HIM.
THOSE PHONE RECORDS HAVE BEEN
HEAVILY REDACTED AND THEY'VE
BEEN REJECTED BY THE CHICAGO
POLICE DEPARTMENT.
>> I THINK THAT IS WHERE IT IS
CHANGING FOR PEOPLE.
>> WHEN THIS BROKE, PEOPLE WERE
WORRIED THAT SOMETHING LIKE
THIS COULD HAPPEN TO HIM, BUT
NOW TURNING IN THIS
INFORMATION, IT SEEMS LIKE YOU
ARE WITHHOLDING SOMETHING.
IF THE HATE CRIME HAPPENED,
THEY WOULD DO ANYTHING AND
EVERYTHING TO GET JUSTICE.
>> A LOT OF EYEBROWS BEING
RAISED, BECAUSE IT CERTAINLY IS
LEADING TO SOME CONSPIRACY
THEORIES THAT SOMETHING MIGHT
BE LARGER GOING ON, BUT WE DO
NOT KNOW AND WE CERTAINLY DON'T
HAVE INFORMATION, BUT WE DO
KNOW THAT HE HAS BEEN
COOPERATIVE WITH POLICE, BUT IN
THE END, WE WILL FIND OUT WHAT
EXACTLY HAPPENED IN THE
SITUATION.
WE ARE TALKING ABOUT ANOTHER
STORY TRENDING RIGHT NOW ON OUR
WEBSITE, IT IS ABOUT A SERIES
OF STATES THAT HAVE LAWS IN
PLACE THAT ALLOW THOSE THAT
HAVE BROKEN UP IN THEIR
RELATIONSHIPS TO ACTUALLY GO
SUE A MISTRESS OR HOMEWRECKER
OR SIDE PIECE OR WHATEVER THAT
THEY FEEL ORCHID DEMONSTRATE
HAS BEEN INVOLVED AND
RESPONSIBLE FOR THEIR
RELATIONSHIP WHEN THE MARRIAGE
DISSOLVED.
>> MARYLAND AND VIRGINIA ARE
NOT INCLUDED, BUT ALL YOU NEED
IS PROOF, IF YOU FEEL THAT THIS
PERSON INTERRUPTED YOUR
MARRIAGE IN ANY WAY, ALL YOU
NEED IS PROOF, AND THIS WEEK,
THIS IS THE TEASE, THIS IS WHY
I GOT A GOOD DIVORCE SETTLEMENT
SAYS KELLY, BECAUSE MY EX, THEY
OWNED PROPERTY IN NORTH
CAROLINA, SO HE DIDN'T KNOW HOW
LONG THEY HAD THE PRIVATE
INVESTIGATOR.
>> TO LOOK AT THAT.
>> BE CAREFUL OUT THERE.
>> A MESSAGE TO ALL SIDE
Stronger is blasting
her tumors...
without risking her bones.
It's training her
good cells...
to fight the bad guys.
Stronger is less pain...
new hope...
more fight.
It's doing everything
in your power...
and everything in ours.
Stronger, is changing even
faster than they do.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>>> LOOKING PRETTY GOOD THIS
AFTERNOON, LITTLE BREEZY,
LOVELY TOMORROW AND 54 AND
ISOLATED SHOWERS NEAR 60 AND WE
HAVE A CHANCE FOR RAIN OR SNOW
OR A MIXED SATURDAY AND SUNDAY
AND THEN AGAIN ON TUESDAY NIGHT
AND WEDNESDAY, WE WILL KNOW
BETTER AS WE GET CLOSER TO IT,
MODELS ARE NOT IN AGREEMENT, SO
THERE IS A LOT OF UNCERTAINTY
GOING INTO THE WEEKEND.
SATURDAY MAY BE MISSING US TO
THE SOUTH, SO IT COULD BE DRY,
BUT THEN WE STILL HAVE SUNDAY
AND NEXT TUESDAY NIGHT AND
WEDNESDAY TO WORRY ABOUT.
>> AND WE HAVE VALENTINES
TOMORROW.
LOVELY, HAVE A GREAT DAY
EVERYBODY, WILL SEE YOU LATER
TONIGHT ON THE NEWS AT 5:00
When I kept finding myself
smoking in my attic.
Dad!
Hiding when I was
supposed to be quitting.
I thought, I should try
something that works.
I should try Nicorette.
Nicorette Mini relieves
sudden cravings fast.
Anytime. Anywhere.
Nicorette Mini.
You know why. We know how.
When I received the diagnosis,
I knew, whatever it takes,
wherever I have to go... I'm
beating this.
Breast cancer treatment is
continuing to evolve.
CTCA is definitely on the cusp
of those changes.
We really focus on taking the
time
with each individual patient
so they can choose the treatment
appropriate for them.
I empower women with choices.
It's not just picking a
surgeon.
It's picking the care team, and
feeling secure where you are.
Visit cancercenter.com.
Appointments available now.