>>> THE WEEK GETS OFF TO A BUSY
START, THANK YOU FOR JOINING
US.
WE BEGIN IN RICHMOND VIRGINIA
WHERE PRESSURE IS MOUNTING ON
GOVERNOR RALPH NORTHAM TO
RESIGN, PICTURE ON HIS META-
SCHOOL YEARBOOK PAGE SHOWS TWO
MEN, ONE IN BLACKFACE AND THE
OTHER IN A KU KLUX KLAN ROBE.
WHEN THE PICTURE FIRST APPEARED
ON FRIDAY, THE GOVERNOR
APOLOGIZED FOR THE  DECISION HE
MADE.
ON SATURDAY, HE SAID IT WAS NOT
HIM, BUT MEMBERS OF HIS OWN
PARTY ARE CALLING ON HIM TO
STEP DOWN.
>> THERE IS ALWAYS A PLACE FOR
SOMEBODY TO APOLOGIZE AND HAVE
HUMILITY TO SAY, I WAS WRONG
AND I REGRET SOMETHING, THERE
IS ALWAYS A ROLE, WE BELIEVE IN
REDEMPTION AND SOCIETY, BUT I
BELIEVE WHAT IS HAPPENED IN
THIS INSTANCE IS UNTENABLE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW HE CAN GOVERN.
>> WE'VE LEARNED THAT THE
GOVERNOR HELD AN URGENT MEETING
WITH THE STAFF MEMBERS, WE ARE
LIVE FROM RICHMOND WITH THE
LATEST.
>> WE ARE STILL WAITING TO
HEAR.
IT FEELS LIKE WE ARE ON A
RUDDERLESS SHIP IN RICHMOND
WITH NO WORD YET FROM THE
GOVERNOR'S MANSION.
PEOPLE ARE ANGRY AND UPSET AND
THERE HAVE BEEN PROTESTS ALL
WEEKEND.
ONE OF THEM IS STILL GOING ON
RIGHT NOW NEXT TO THE
GOVERNOR'S MANSION, TAKE A
LISTEN.
>> I BELIEVE THEN AND NOW THAT
I AM NOT EITHER OF THE PEOPLE
IN THAT PHOTO.
>> THE GOVERNOR SAID ON
SATURDAY THAT HE WOULD NOT
RESIGN AFTER A RACIST PHOTO
SURFACED FROM HIS 1984 MEDICAL
SCHOOL YEARBOOK PAGE SHOWING A
MAN IN BLACKFACE NEXT TO
ANOTHER PERSON IN A KU KLUX
KLAN  ROBE.
>> AFTER APOLOGIZING ON FRIDAY
AND SAYING THAT HE WAS IN THE
PHOTO, HE BACKTRACKED ON
SATURDAY AND SAID THAT HE WAS
SURE THAT HE WAS NOT IN THE
PHOTO.
A PRESS CONFERENCE ON SATURDAY
THAT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE DAMAGE
CONTROL DID THE OPPOSITE.
NOT ONLY DID HIS STORY CHANGE,
BUT HE ADMITTED THAT HE DID PUT
ON BLACKFACE IN 1984 WHEN HE
DRESSED UP TO LOOK LIKE MICHAEL
JACKSON IN A DANCE CONTEST.
AND WHEN ASKED IF HE WOULD
DEMONSTRATE MOONWALKING, IT WAS
HIS WIFE WHO STOPPED HIM FROM
DOING IT.
SHOCKED DEMOCRATS SAY HE LACKS
THE UNDERSTANDING OF THE
GRAVITY OF THE SITUATION.
OVER THE WEEKEND CAME STATEWIDE
AND NATIONAL CALLS FOR HIS
RESIGNATION.
THE FORMER GOVERNOR DOUG
WILDER, THE VIRGINIA SENATORS
MARK WARNER AND TIM KANE AND
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES, HARRIS
AND CORY BOOKER ALSO FORMER
VICE PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN ALL
CALLING FOR GOVERNOR RALPH
NORTHAM TO RESIGN.
DEMOCRATS SAY HE HAS LOST THE
MORAL AUTHORITY TO LEAD.
MEANWHILE, ANOTHER POTENTIAL
CONTROVERSY CONCERNING THE MAN
WHO WOULD REPLACE NORTHAM,
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR JUSTIN
FAIRFAX SENT OUT AN EARLY
MORNING TWEET DENYING AN
UNVERIFIED SEXUAL ASSAULT
ALLEGATION FROM THE SAME
CONSERVATIVE WEBSITE THAT BROKE
THE STORY ABOUT HIS MEDICAL
YEARBOOK PICTURE.
THE STATEMENT ON TWITTER READ,
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR FAIRFAX HAS
AN OUTSTANDING AND WELL-EARNED
REPUTATION FOR TREATING PEOPLE
WITH DIGNITY AND RESPECT.
HE HAS NEVER ASSAULTED ANYONE
EVER IN ANY WAY SHAPE OR FORM.
>>
>> THE PROTESTS ARE STILL
CONTINUING AND I CAN HEAR THEM
RIGHT NOW.
TAKE A LISTEN TO SOME OF THAT
GOING ON JUST NOW.
>> RESIGN, RALPH, NOW SO YOU
CAN HEAR IT, THERE ARE A FEW
HUNDRED PEOPLE JUST TO THE SIDE
OF THE GOVERNOR'S MANSION AND
THEY'VE BEEN HERE ALL WEEKEND
PROTESTING, SHOUTING, CALLING
FOR RALPH NORTHAM'S
RESIGNATION.
THERE ARE PICTURES SAYING, ONE
PICTURE SAYS YOU CANNOT GET
BLACKFACE OFF AND YOU CAN'T GET
RACISM OFF EITHER, A LOT OF
ANGER HERE TODAY, JUST A SHORT
TIME AGO, WE HEARD FROM THE
HOUSE SPEAKER WHO SAID THEY ARE
NOT MAKING PLANS TO IMPEACH
GOVERNOR NORTHAM, THAT IS THE
THRESHOLD THAT THEY WOULD
DECIDE, THERE WOULD HAVE TO BE
SOME SORT OF MEDICAL NECESSITY
AND IT JUST ISN'T THERE.
THEY AND MANY OTHERS ARE HOPING
THAT THE GOVERNOR RESIGNS AND
AS SOON AS WE HEAR ANYTHING, WE
WILL LET YOU KNOW.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH, WE
APPRECIATE THE UPDATE.
JOINING US TO TALK ABOUT THE
ISSUE AND THE IMPACT THAT IT
WILL HAVE ON THE POTENTIAL,
GOVERNMENT PARTY, WE HAVE THE
PRESIDENT, MARCUS GOODWIN AND
JENNIFER BLOOMER OF THE DC
YOUNG DEMOCRATS.
LET'S START WITH THE BIG
QUESTION, WHAT IMPACT DO YOU
THINK THIS WILL HAVE ON
DEMOCRATS MOVING FORWARD?
>> FIRST, I THINK WE ALREADY
ESTABLISHED THAT DEMOCRATS WANT
HIM TO RESIGN AND HE DOESN'T
HAVE THE MORAL AUTHORITY AND
THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY NEEDS
ACCOUNTABILITY.
IN ORDER FOR THE DEMOCRATIC
BEFORE, HE HAS TO MAKE THE
DECISION TO RESIGN IN ORDER FOR
OTHER LEADERSHIP TO MOVE IN.
>> YOU SEE ANY OTHER WAY TO
MOVE PAST THIS?
>> THE PROTEST OUTSIDE OF THE
GOVERNOR'S MANSION ARE
INDICATIVE OF THE SHAKEN
CONFIDENCE THAT DEMOCRATS HAVE
AND WE NEED TO BE ABLE TO MOVE
FORWARD AS THEY SO ELOQUENTLY
SAID, WITH LEADERSHIP THAT
UNDERSTANDS THE PROBLEMS FACING
US AND THAT HAVE THE SUPPORT OF
THE PEOPLE BEHIND THEM.
>> WHEN WE THINK ABOUT 2020,
GEARING UP FOR THAT, WE ALSO
KNOW THAT THERE IS AN ELECTION
HAPPENING IN THE STATE
LEGISLATURE IN VIRGINIA AS
WELL.
DO DEMOCRATS NEED TO BE
CONCERNED ABOUT WHAT'S
HAPPENING RIGHT NOW FOR FUTURE
ELECTIONS?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
VIRGINIA IS ONE OF THE LARGEST
STATES WHEN WE CONSIDER THE
PRESIDENT OF PRIMARY AND
UNDERSTANDING HOW WE SET
OURSELVES UP FOR THE PAST IN
WINNING THE ELECTORAL COLLEGE,
WE NEED TO KNOW THAT WE HAVE
LEADERSHIP IN PLACE THAT WILL
REGAIN THE CONFIDENCE OF
VIRGINIANS NOT JUST IN THE BIG
CITIES, BUT ALSO IN THE MORE
RURAL AREAS OF THE STATE AND
GETTING LEADERSHIP LIKE
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR JUSTIN
FAIRFAX IN PLACE IS THE FIRST
STEP IN THE PROCESS TO HELP US
HEAL THE WOUNDS AND REGAIN
CONFIDENCE AND HAVE COMPETENT
LEADERSHIP THAT WILL LEAD US
FORWARD.
>> THE LAST QUESTION FOR YOU,
DOES THERE NEED TO BE A BIGGER
CONVERSATION ABOUT BLACK FACE?
WE'VE HAD TWO HIGH-PROFILE
PEOPLE, MEGAN KELLY AND RALPH
NORTHAM GET CAUGHT UP.
>> IT IS VERY EVIDENT THAT A
LOT OF PEOPLE DON'T REALLY
UNDERSTAND THE ORIGINS LIKE
WHAT IT MEANS TO LACK PEOPLE
AND WHAT IT MEANT FOR ACTORS
LIKE BERT WILLIAMS WHO WAS A
BLACK MAN WHO PERFORMED IN
BLACKFACE BECAUSE THEY WOULDN'T
ALLOW BLACK PEOPLE TO PLAY
THEMSELVES.
THERE IS A LONG HISTORY OF HURT
AND DISCRIMINATION,
MISUNDERSTANDING AND WILLFUL
IGNORANCE AND HOPEFULLY WE WILL
GET TO A PLACE WHERE WE HAVE A
LARGER CONVERSATION.
>> THANK BOTH OF YOU FOR
JOINING US.
WE APPRECIATE YOU GREATLY.
>> WE WANT TO LET YOU KNOW THAT
COVERAGE CONTINUES RIGHT NOW
AND WE WILL HAVE MUCH MORE ON
THE GOVERNOR'S ACTION COMING UP
ON THE NEWS AT 5:00.
WE WILL BE LOOKING INTO BIG-
LEAGUE POLITICS, THAT IS THE
SITE THAT PUBLISHED THE PHOTO.
STEPHANIE RAMIREZ GOES INTO THE
HISTORY AND WHY IT IS SO
PAINFUL TODAY AND WE LOOK INTO
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR JUSTIN
FAIRFAX.
>>> LET'S GET A CHECK ON THE
FORECAST.
>> WE WERE TALKING ABOUT SNOW
SEVERAL DAYS WHERE WE WILL HAVE
SOME SNOW SHOWER CHANCES AND A
BIG ARCTIC BLAST.
THIS WEEK IS A COMPLETE
OPPOSITE.
WE ARE TALKING ABOUT A FACE OF
SPRING IN THE MIDDLE OF WINTER.
WE HAVE SUNSHINE OUTSIDE RIGHT
NOW AND WITH THAT, THE
TEMPERATURE STARTING OFF IN THE
20s AND LOW 30s THIS MORNING,
THEY ARE CLIMBING UP INTO THE
50s RAPIDLY AT LUNCHTIME.
51 IN DC AND I WANT TO POINT
OUT THAT WINDS ARE VERY LIGHT,
AND THAT IS A PLAYER FOR HOW
TODAY THE WEATHER WILL END UP
TRANSLATING THIS AFTERNOON IN
TERMS OF THE AIR QUALITY.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT THAT IN JUST A
SECOND, 52 IN LEESBURG AND 56,
ONE OF THE WARMEST SPOTS RIGHT
NOW IN GAITHERSBURG AND YOUR 54
IN WALDORF, SO THESE ARE
ALREADY TEMPERATURES THAT ARE
ABOVE AVERAGE FOR THE HIGHS
THIS TIME OF YEAR.
WE'VE GOT THOSE AT THE LUNCH
HOUR TODAY.
TEMPERATURES RUNNING 5 TO 10
DEGREES WARMER THAN THEY WERE
YESTERDAY.
AND I MENTIONED THE LIGHT
WINDS, THAT IS IMPORTANT TO
WHAT THE AIR QUALITY IS TODAY.
FOR TWO DAYS IN A ROW, WE'VE
HAD FAIRLY LIGHT WIND, SO THAT
TRACKS IN ALL OF THE AIR
POLLUTION AND ALL OF THE
PARTICULATE MATTER IN THE
ATMOSPHERE.
SO WE HAVE A CODE ORANGE AIR-
QUALITY ALERT TODAY, UNHEALTHY
FOR SENSITIVE GROUPS, ELDERLY
AND PEOPLE WITH RESPIRATORY
ILLNESS, AVOID EXCESSIVE TIME
OUTDOORS, BUT FOR THE REST OF
US, WARM TEMPERATURES AND
SUNSHINE, YOU CAN'T COMPLAIN.
WE CLIMB UP INTO THE 50s RIGHT
NOW, 54 AT 3:00 AND THE HIGH
TEMPERATURE TODAY WILL END UP
IN THE MID TO UPPER 50s.
THAT SOUNDS PRETTY NICE,
DOESN'T IT?
IF YOU ARE ENJOYING 50s TODAY,
WE HAVE 60s ON THE WAY THIS
WEEK AND WE WILL TALK ABOUT
THAT AND MORE INFORMATION ON
THAT THIS WEEK.
>>> A MEDICAL SCHOOL EMPLOYEE
WAS SHOT JUST OUTSIDE THE
UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND MEDICAL
CENTER IN BALTIMORE.
IT HAPPENED AROUND 7:15 THIS
MORNING, OFFICIALS SAY THE
VICTIM WAS SHOT IN THE FACE AND
BUTTOCKS OUTSIDE THE AMBULANCE
BAY.
THE CONDITION RIGHT NOW IS
UNKNOWN, POLICE TOOK A 26-YEAR-
OLD MAN INTO CUSTODY AND HAVE
RECOVERED A GUN.
THEY BELIEVE TWO MEN, THEY
BELIEVE THE TWO MEN KNEW EACH
OTHER AND OFFICIALS ARE LOOKING
INTO A POSSIBLE MOTIVE, THE
HOSPITAL IS FUNCTIONING AS
NORMAL.
>> THE NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS ARE
SUPER BOWL CHAMPIONS YET AGAIN.
THE PATRIOTS BEAT THE LA RAMS
13-3 AND THAT WAS IN ATLANTA
LAST NIGHT.
IT WAS THE LOWEST SCORING SUPER
BOWL GAME IN HISTORY.
STILL, THE WIN GAVE THE NEW
ENGLAND PATRIOTS THEIR SIXTH
TROPHY.
THEY WERE ALL LED BY TOM BRADY
AND THE PATRIOTS TIED WITH THE
STEELERS FOR THE MOST SUPER
BOWL WINS BY A FRANCHISE.
THE PATRIOTS WIDE RECEIVER
JULIE SETTLEMENT, JULIAN
EDELMAN EARNED THE MVP TROPHY.
AFTER THE BIG WIN, ATLANTA
RUPTURED WITH FANS GOING INTO
THE STREETS AND EVEN TAKING
PLACE IN BOSTON AS WELL.
CROWDS WERE MOSTLY PEACEFUL,
BUT POLICE SAID TWO PEOPLE WERE
ARRESTED FOR MINOR OFFENSES AND
PATRIOTS FANS CAN NOW LOOK
FORWARD TO A CHAMPIONSHIP
PARADE THAT WILL HAPPEN
SOMETIME THIS WEEK.
>> STILL TO COME, BUT LOOK AT
THE WINNERS AND LOSERS AT LAST
NIGHT SUPER
>>> WUSA9 NEWS IS SPONSORED IN
PART BY GREENSPRING RETIREMENT
COMMUNITY.
>> WELCOME BACK, OFFICIALS ARE
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
CAUSED A SMALL PLANE TO CRASH
INTO A RESIDENTIAL HOME IN
CALIFORNIA YESTERDAY, KILLING
FIVE PEOPLE.
OFFICIALS SAY THE PILOT AND
FOUR OCCUPANTS OF THE HOME, THE
PLANE CRASHED INTO WERE KILLED.
TWO OTHER PEOPLE WERE INJURED
AS WELL.
NEIGHBORS SAID THEY HEARD AN
EXPLOSION AND RAN OUTSIDE TO A
TERRIFYING SIGHT.
>> I SAW THE HOUSE OVER HERE,
DIAGONAL TO ME FULLY ENGULFED
IN FLAMES AND I HEARD GLASS
BREAKING AND PEOPLE YELLING FOR
THEIR LIVES.
>> SCREAMING, GOD HELP ME.
>> IT FELT LIKE AN EARTHQUAKE,
I GRABBED MY KIDS AND WENT INTO
THE HALLWAY UNDER THE DOOR AND
THERE WERE A COUPLE OF BOOMS
AND EXPLOSIONS, AND THEN MY
HUSBAND SAID NO, IT IS A PLANE.
>> OFFICIALS SAY THE PLANE
CRASHED SHORTLY AFTER TAKING
OFF FROM A NEARBY AIRPORT.
DEBRIS IS SCATTERED OVER FOR
BLOCKS AND A NEARBY ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL IS CLOSED AS AUTHORITIES
CONTINUE THEIR INVESTIGATION.
>> WE JUST LEARNED THAT THE
YOUNGER THE RESTLESS STAR HAS
PASSED AWAY.
HE WAS FOUND DEAD INSIDE HIS
LOS ANGELES HOME YESTERDAY.
OFFICIALS SAY THERE DOESN'T
SEEM TO BE ANY SIGNS OF FOUL
PLAY.
HE WAS 52 YEARS OLD.
>> MELISSA NORTH JOINING US
RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE TO TELL YOU, I
CELEBRATED MY BIRTHDAY
YESTERDAY AND IT CONTINUES
TODAY, AND WE HAVE BEEN HAVING
AWESOME WEATHER.
>> JUST FOR YOU.
>> WE BROUGHT PUNXSUTAWNEY PHIL
OVER THE WEEKEND BROUGHT YOU
THE SPRING WEATHER.
>> THAT IS IT.
>> NOT FOR ANYBODY ELSE, JUST
FOR YOU.
>> IT IS REALLY NICE, A LOOK AT
THE SUNSHINE OUTSIDE, WE HAVE A
CODE ORANGE AIR-QUALITY ALERT
AND THAT IS BECAUSE WE HAVE
VERY LIGHT WINDS, THAT'S
TRACKING IN ALL THE POLLUTION
OUT THERE FOR THE PAST COUPLE
DAYS AND YOU CAN KIND OF SEE
THE HAZE AS YOU LOOK AT THE
TOWER CAMERA, BUT LOOK AT THIS,
THIS PUTS THINGS IN
PERSPECTIVE.
THIS AFTERNOON, DC CLIMBS UP
INTO THE 50s UP TO 58 DEGREES,
OUR AVERAGE FOR JANUARY 4 IS
ONLY 45 DEGREES, SO TODAY, WE
ARE ALREADY WITHIN 10 DEGREES
ABOVE AVERAGE AND ABOVE AVERAGE
TREND IS GOING TO LAST ALL WEEK
LONG.
LET ME LOOK AT THE WEATHER A
LITTLE BIT MORE IN DETAIL HOUR
BY HOUR, 51 RIGHT NOW AND BY
3:00 THIS AFTERNOON, WE WILL BE
UP IN THE MID TO UPPER 50s AND
I DON'T THINK ANYBODY WILL BE
STUCK IN THE 40s TODAY.
WE ARE ALREADY CLIMBING WELL
INTO THE 50s, SO IT WILL BE
UNSEASONABLY WARM TODAY.
5:00 JUST BEFORE SUNSET STILL
IN THE LOW 50s IN KIDS AT THE
BUS STOP, MAKE THEM PLAY
OUTSIDE THIS WEEK, IT WILL
REALLY BE THAT NICE FOR YOU.
INTO THE OVERNIGHT, WE SEE
TEMPERATURES FALLING BACK TO
THE 40s AND SOME SPOTS INTO THE
30s, BUT THERE WILL BE AN
ISOLATED SHOWER CHANCE, IT'S A
WARM WEEK AHEAD IN THE WEATHER
HEADLINE, AND BY THE END OF THE
WEEK, IT TURNS A LITTLE BIT
MORE UNSETTLED, SO INSTEAD OF
SEEING PURELY SUNNY DAYS, WE
WILL BE CHECKING SOME SHOWERS
EACH DAY, AND BY THIS WEEKEND,
BACK DOWN TO REALITY BACK IN
THE 40s FOR THE HIGH
TEMPERATURES.
IT ALL COMES DOWN TO THE
PATTERN OF THE JET SPRING.
PEOPLE MAY HEAR THE TERM
JETSTREAM ALL THE TIME, BUT ALL
THAT IS IS REALLY STRONG WENT
ALL THE WAY UP WHERE THE PLANES
FLY OUTSIDE, AND IT IS ALMOST
THE DIVIDING LINE BETWEEN WARM
AIR AND COLD AIR.
THE JETSTREAM WILL DIP DOWN IN
THE WEST AND GO UP NORTH OF US
IN THE EAST.
SO WHAT DOES THIS DO?
IT CREATES COLD TEMPERATURES ON
THE WEST COAST AND FOR THE EAST
COAST, IT IS ALL ABOUT THE
WARMTH.
SO FOR DC OVER THE NEXT SEVERAL
DAYS, WE ARE TALKING ABOUT
ABOVE AVERAGE TEMPERATURES, HOW
MUCH ABOVE AVERAGE?
50s AND 60s FOR US.
WITH ONE DAY BEING THE
EXCEPTION, LOOK AT THE NEXT
FIVE DAYS, 58 DEGREES TODAY AND
TOMORROW, WE ARE IN THE MID
60s, THIS WILL BE A FEW DEGREES
SHY OF SOME OF THE RECORD HIGHS
FOR TOMORROW.
WEDNESDAY IS A LITTLE COOLER
WITH THE FRONT PASSING THROUGH
BRINGING COOLER WEATHER FOR ONE
DAY WITH MORE CLOUDS AND BY
THURSDAY AND FRIDAY, WE WILL BE
BACK IN THE 60s AGAIN.
LAST WEEK, WE WERE TALKING
ABOUT TEMPERATURES 20 DEGREES
BELOW AVERAGE AND THIS WEEK, WE
ARE TALK ABOUT TEMPERATURES 20
DEGREES ABOVE AVERAGE.
SO IT REALLY IS A FLIP IN THE
PATTERN THAT IS ALL COMING DOWN
TO THE JETSTREAM PATTERN.
WE WILL TORN, WE WILL TURN A
LITTLE BIT DIFFERENT, ISOLATED
SHOWERS NORTH OF TOWN AND THE
FRONT COMES THROUGH AND THAT'S
SOUTH OF US SO THAT BRINGS MORE
CLOUDS AND COOLER TEMPERATURES.
TAKING FUTURECAST INTO THURSDAY
AND FRIDAY, WE HAVE MORE
SHOWERS, BUT IT IS NOT A WASHOUT
THE ENTIRE TIME.
THE FRONT MOVES THROUGH FRIDAY
TAKING TEMPERATURES BACK DOWN
INTO THE 40s FOR THE WEEKEND.
ENJOY THE WARM TEMPERATURES.
58 TODAY AND TOMORROW 65 AND WE
HAVE COOL AND MORE CLOUDS AND
40s FOR WEDNESDAY AND 60s ON
THURSDAY AND FRIDAY AND BACK TO
40 DEGREES WITH OVERNIGHT LOWS
IN THE 20s FOR THE WEEKEND.
>> THE BEST WEEK EVER.
>>> FOR SOME PEOPLE, SUPER BOWL
SUNDAY IS REALLY ALL ABOUT THE
GAME, BUT FOR OTHERS, IT'S ALL
ABOUT THE COMMERCIALS AND THERE
WERE SOME CLEAR WINNERS LIKE
THE BUD LIGHT GAME OF THRONES
CROSSOVER.
THIS STARTED AS ONE OF THE DEER
BRAND ADS BUT BECAME A PREVIEW
FOR THE SEASON OF GAME OF
THRONES.
>>> AND ANOTHER COMMERCIAL
PEOPLE COULDN'T TALK ABOUT,
STOP TALKING ABOUT, THE NFL
GATHERING THE PAST SIX DECADES
TICK OFF, TO KICK OFF THE
CELEBRATION.
WHAT HAPPENS IN THE ROOM?
AN IMPROMPTU GAME OF AMERICA
FAVORITE PASTIME.
STOMACH AND MICROSOFT IS MOVING
THE COMMERCIAL WAS ALL THAT
INCLUSIVITY.
IT FEATURED CHILDREN WITH
DISABILITIES WHO TALK ABOUT HOW
MICROSOFT'S NEW ADAPTIVE
CONTROLLER HELPS THEM PLAY
VIDEO GAMES AND EVEN PLAY WITH
ONE ANOTHER.
>> NO MATTER HOW YOUR BODY IS
OR HOW FAST YOU ARE, YOU CAN
PLAY.
IT'S A REALLY GOOD THING TO
HAVE IN THIS WORLD.
>> MICROSOFT'S ADAPTIVE
CONTROLLER IS ON SALE AND YOU
CAN PICK ONE UP FOR JUST $100.
OTHER WINNERS WERE THE AMAZON
DON AWRY AND THE STELLA
COMMERCIAL WITH JEFF BRIDGES
AND CARRIE BRADSHAW.
AND THEN THE BURGER KING AND
ANDY WARHOL ADD DIDN'T SEEM TO
GO WELL WITH PEOPLE AND WENT
WAY OVER THEIR HEADS.
>>> STILL TO COME, A WARNING
FOR MILLIONS OF
Ways to lose
stubborn belly fat:
Metal Vibration Therapy.
( ♪♪ )
(Glass breaking)
(Gasp)
Not cool.
Freezing away fat cells
with CoolSculpting?
Now that's cool!
CoolSculpting safely
freezes and removes fat cells
with little or no downtime
and no surgery.
Results and patient
experience may vary.
Some common side
effects include
temporary numbness,
discomfort, and swelling.
Ask your doctor
if CoolSculpting
is right for you and visit
CoolSculpting.com today
for your chance
to win a free treatment.
(Music blaring)
Stronger is blasting
her tumors...
for your chance
to win a free treatment.
without risking her bones.
It's training her
good cells...
to fight the bad guys.
Stronger is less pain...
new hope...
more fight.
It's doing everything
in your power...
and everything in ours.
Stronger, is changing even
faster than they do.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>>> WELCOME BACK, PAYPAL IS
USED BY MILLIONS TO MAKE
PURCHASES AND PAYMENTS ONLINE,
BUT NOW SCAM ARTISTS ARE USING
THE TRUSTED NAME TO RIP PEOPLE
OFF.
>>> WHEN INDICA MOSLEY AND HER
BROTHER NEEDED CASH, THEY
DECIDED TO SELL SOME OF THEIR
PRICEY SNEAKERS.
>> WE PAY A LOT OF TUITION SO
WE FIGURED WE WOULD GIVE OUR
PARENTS A BREAK AND HELP OUT
WITH GROCERIES AND GAS AND DO
THINGS ON OUR OWN.
>> THEY LISTED 23 SNEAKERS AND
IN THE BLINK OF AN EYE, A BUYER
WAS WILLING TO PAY $3000.
THEIR REACTION WAS EXCITED AND
EAGER.
WHEN THE BUYER SUGGESTED THAT
THEY AVOID THE $180 SERVICE FEE
AND USE PAYPAL INSTEAD, THEY
AGREED.
>> THEY SAID THEY WOULD SEND
THE MONEY OVER.
>> YOU'VE GOT MONEY READ THE
EMAIL.
>> WE SHIPPED THE SHOES AND WE
WAITED FOR THEM TO GET THERE
AND WAITED FOR THE PAYMENT.
>> AND WAITED AND WAITED SOME
MORE.
>> I CALLED THEM AND TEXTED
THEM AND LEFT VOICEMAILS.
>> REALITY SET IN AND THE
PAYPAL EMAIL WAS FAKE.
THEY HAD BEEN SCAMMED OUT OF
PAYMENTS TOTALING NEARLY $3000
FOR THE SNEAKERS.
>> IT BLOWS MY MIND THAT
EVERYTHING WAS FAKE.
>> Reporter: WHAT MADE THIS
EMAIL PICTURE-PERFECT, THE
FLAWLESS BLUE LOGO, NO SPELLING
ERRORS AND THE CORRECT SIZE
FONT AND THE KICKER WAS THE
SECURITY LINK TAKING YOU RIGHT
TO THE OFFICIAL PAYPAL PAGE,
HERE'S WHAT'S FAKE.
THE ADDRESS.
>> YOU CAN SEE ON THE BLUE SIDE
HERE, IT'S IS AT THE END, IT
SAYS AT MAIL.COM, THAT
SHOULD'VE SAID@PAYPAL.COM.
>> NOT THE ONLY ONE FALLING, ON
THE BBB SCAM TRACKER, WE FOUND
NEARLY 100 COMPLAINTS, MOSTLY
SHIFTER STICKERS FROM BATON
ROUGE, LOUISIANA TO McCREE,
ILLINOIS.
SOMEONE AT THIS HOUSE SIGN FOR
THEM.
>> WE ARE LOOKING FOR THE
PEOPLE THAT RECEIVED $3000
WORTH OF SNEAKERS.
AFTER A 10 MINUTE EXCHANGE,
THEY NEVER GOT THE MONEY.
DOES THAT SURPRISE YOU?
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> THEY TOLD US.
>> THEY SAID THERE'S NOTHING
THEY CAN DO TO HELP US BECAUSE
IT DIDN'T COME FROM PAYPAL.
THE COMPANY OFFERS ADVICE ON
THE WEBSITE.
>> IF YOU THINK YOU ARE ON A
SPOOF SITE, JUST EMAIL IT TO
SPOOF AT PAYPAL.COM AND WE WILL
TAKE A LOOK AND REPLY SHORTLY.
>> EVEN IF YOU GET
I'm a concrete mason.
I had severe fatigue, went to
a doctor.
Became diagnosed with
Hodgkin's lymphoma.
I had to put my trust in
somebody.
We recommended chemotherapy,
and then a stem cell transplant.
When his disease progressed,
I thought that he would be a
good candidate
for immunotherapy
to unleash his immune system
against the cancer.
I'm back to working hard.
I've honestly have never felt
this great.
The evolution of cancer care
is here.
Learn more at cancercenter.com
appointments available now.
>>> TODAY WE CELEBRATE THE LIFE
OF CIVIL RIGHTS ACTIVIST ROSA
PARK, BEST KNOWN AS THE WOMAN
WHO REFUSED TO GIVE UP HER SEAT
TO A WHITE PERSON IN 1955.
THIS SPAWNED A BOYCOTT OF THE
MONTGOMERY BUS SYSTEM THAT
WOULD'VE LED TO A LOT OF
SIGNIFICANT CHANGE WHEN WE
THINK ABOUT SOCIAL ACTIVISM AND
CIVIL RIGHTS.
SHE WOULD'VE TURNED 106 YEARS
OLD.
>>> WE ARE WARM THIS WEEK, WE
HAVE 50s TODAY AND 60 TOMORROW
AND SHOWERS STAYING ON THE MILD
SIDE AT THE END OF
When was the last time
you felt...
Free.
It's time to uncover
that feeling again.
With the compassion and
strength of a name...
Most accepted by top doctors
and specialists.
And the power of a card...
that opens doors in
all fifty states.
Giving you the freedom to love
to dream to dance
Like no one is watching.
CareFirst
Blue Cross Blue Shield.
Live fearless.