CHILDREN.
THE NEWS THAT 6:00 STARTS RIGHT
NOW.
>> WE BEGIN WITH THE THREAT OF
WICKED WINTER WEATHER THAT IS
NEARLY AT OUR DOORSTEP.
WHAT IS THE LATEST?
>> WE ARE JUST HOURS FROM SNOW
BREAKING OUT ACROSS THE METRO
AREA, ABOUT 12 HOURS FROM SNOW
IN THE METRO.
LET'S GO OVER THE SNOWFALL
TOTALS AGAIN.
THESE ARE LOWER THAN WHAT WE
SHOWED YOU YESTERDAY THAT DOES
MEAN THE ROADS WILL BE BETTER.
3 TO 5 INCHES IN LEESBURG AND
GAITHERSBURG AND MARTINSBURG
AND POINTS NORTH AND WEST.
WE COULD EXCEED THE 3 TO 5 INCH
MARK.
1 TO 3 IN THE IMMEDIATE METRO
AREA AND DC AND ROCKVILLE IN
BETHESDA AND FAIRFAX AND EVEN
INTO WALDORF.
EXTREME SOUTHERN MARYLAND, WE
ARE TALKING ABOUT A TRACE.
THAT HASN'T CHANGED MUCH, YOU
DON'T HAVE THE COLD AIR IN
PLACE LONG ENOUGH TO MAKE THAT
MUCH SNOW.
SO WHAT ABOUT THE MODELS?
HAVE THEY COME INTO A SIMILAR
WAY OF THINKING?
STILL FOR HALF OF THE P.M., ALL
THE REST OF THE MODELS ARE
UNDER THREE INCHES, SO I THINK
THEY FINALLY GOT A HANDLE ON
HOW MUCH SLEEP IS GOING TO
FALL.
ONCE AGAIN, MODERATE TO HEAVY
SNOW 6 AM TO NOON AND ROADS
WILL BE DANGEROUS, IT WILL
CUMULATE QUICKLY AND ONCE IT
STARTS, IT PICKS UP IN
INTENSITY QUICKLY.
SNOW WILL TURN TO A MIXED NORTH
AND WEST IN THE AFTERNOON AND
IT TURNS TO RAIN IN DC SOUTH
AND EAST IN THE AFTERNOON AND
SOME OF THE RAIN TO THE HEAVY
OVERNIGHT AND EVERYONE GOES TO
RAIN OVERNIGHT AND THEN MORNING
SHOWERS ON THURSDAY AND THEN WE
ARE IN THE 50s.
NO SHORTAGE OF MOISTURE.
THIS IS A TREMENDOUS STORM
STRETCHING ALREADY FROM CAPE
HATTERAS BACK TO KANSAS CITY
AND BACK TO IOWA.
5 AM SNOW ON THE DOORSTEP, BUT
SNOW ALREADY A COUPLE HOURS IN
CULPEPER AND SNOWING ALREADY IN
MANASSAS AND BY 7:00, SNOWING
ACROSS THE METRO AREA AND
PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY AND
BALTIMORE AND BY 10:00, WE
STILL HAVE SNOW WITH THE MIX
DOWN TO THE SOUTH AND THEY
THINK IT IS SLOW ERODING THE
COLD AIR AND I THINK WILL GO TO
THE MIX IN DC BY NOON WITH SNOW
HANGING NORTH OF FREDERICK AND
I-70 AND BY 4:00, JUST RAIN IN
THE DC AREA COME BUT STILL
HANGING ONTO ICE NORTH AND
WEST.
WE COME BACK AND TALK ABOUT THE
POTENTIAL FOR AN ICE STORM
NORTH AND WEST OF TOWN WHEN THE
SNOW TRANSITIONS FROM SNOW AND
FREEZING RAIN.
>> TIME FOR PREPARATIONS
UNDERWAY ALL ACROSS THE DMV FOR
THE WINTER STORM LATE TONIGHT,
SALT AND PLOW TRUCKS WILL BE
STANDBY AT THE READY.
>> THE BLOOMING PANSIES OR
DAFFODILS PUSHING UP COULD FOOL
YOU, LATE FEBRUARY SNOWSTORMS
CAN PACK A PUNCH WITH HUGE
SNOWFALLS.
>> ARE YOU READY FOR THE SNOW?
>> READY OR NOT, IT IS COMING,
HARDWARE STORES STOCKED UP ON
SHOVELS AND SLEDS.
AND IN VIRGINIA, DDOT HAS
ALREADY STARTED TREATING ROADS.
THE STREAKS ON THE ROAD ARE
FROM BRINE OVERNIGHT.
>> THIS IS ONE OF THE 18
FACILITIES ACROSS NORTHERN
VIRGINIA.
IT LOOKS EMPTY NOW, BUT BY
MIDNIGHT, IT WILL BE ROCKING.
>> A CONTINUOUS LINE OF PLOW
TRUCKS PHILIP FROM THE SALT
DOME TO TREAT MAJOR ROADS.
ALLEN, LOCKE US SAYS HE WILL
HAVE 3000 TRUCKS COVERING
14,000 MILES OF ROAD.
>> MOST OF THE FLEET IS A
CONTRACT FLEET, SO THESE TRUCKS
ARE LANDSCAPING TRUCKS OR
CONSTRUCTION TRUCKS, BY DAY,
AND WHEN THEY GO FROM CLARK
KENT TO BEING SUPERMAN AND THEY
BECOME OUR PLOW TRUCKS AT NIGHT
DOES
>> EACH TRUCK NEEDS A SPREADER.
>> IS BETTER MOVES IN AND IT
PACKS IN AND THEY GET A LOAD OF
SALT, AND THEY DRIVE OFF AND AS
THEY DRIVE, IT SPREADS SALT
EVENLY ON THE ROADS.
>> THE TRUCKS DO NOT PLOW RIGHT
AWAY, THEY WAIT FOR A SIGNAL.
AS SOON AS SNOW GETS TWO INCHES
HIGH, BE.PUTS OUT THE CALL.
PLOWS DOWN, AND THEN THINGS GET
EXCITING.
>> WHAT WE ARE ASKING IS FOR
PEOPLE TO STAY OFF THE ROADS ON
WEDNESDAY.
WITH THE AMOUNT OF SNOW WE WILL
BE GETTING AND WITH THE RATE IN
WHICH IT WILL BE FALLING, WE
ARE CONCERNED WITH THAT
ESPECIALLY DURING THE SHOWER.
>> AND FAIRFAX COUNTY, PEGGY
FOX, WUSA9.
>> AND REMINDER BECAUSE OF THE
WINTRY WEATHER WE ARE
EXPECTING, THE WAKE-UP WASHING
THAT HE WILL BE ON EARLY , 4:00
IN THE MORNING WITH THE LATEST
ON CONDITIONS AND CLOSINGS
ACROSS THE AREA.
>>> I'M BERNIE SANDERS AND I'M
RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT.
>> VERMONT SANDERS, VERMONT
SENATOR BERNIE SANDERS NEEDED
OFFICIAL, HE IS JOINING AND IS
THE 10th CANDIDATE TO CHALLENGE
PRESIDENT TRUMP IN THE 2020
ELECTION.
IN AN INTERVIEW WITH JOHN
DICKERSON, THE 77-YEAR-OLD
PROGRESSIVE SAYS HE IS OKAY IF
PEOPLE CALL HIM A RADICAL.
>> I BELIEVE THE PEOPLE ARE
INHERENTLY ENTITLED TO HEALTH
CARE AND INHERENTLY ENTITLED TO
GET THE BEST EDUCATION THEY
CAN.
>> THE TRUMPET MINISTRATION
REACTED TO THE ANNOUNCEMENT
SAYING THE AMERICAN PEOPLE WILL
REJECT AN AGENDA OF SKYHIGH
TAXES AND GOVERNMENT RUN
HEALTHCARE AND CODDLING
DICTATORS LIKE THOSE IN
VENEZUELA.
SANDERS SAYS HE DOESN'T WANT
THE U.S. TO BECOME VENEZUELA
AND HE HOPES AMERICANS DO NOT
BELIEVE WHAT THE PRESIDENT HAS
TO SAY.
>> LEGAL CHALLENGES ARE
MOUNTING TO PRESIDENT TRUMP AND
HIS DECLARATION OF THE NATIONAL
EMERGENCY TO FULLY FUND THE
BORDER WALL.
NATALIE BRAD BREAKS DOWN THE
LEGAL ARGUMENTS AGAINST THE
PRESIDENT'S MOVES.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP IS DEFENDING
HIS NATIONAL EMERGENCY
DECLARATION TO BUILD A SOUTHERN
BORDER WALL.
>> I HAVE AN ABSOLUTE RIGHT TO
CALL NATIONAL SECURITY.
WE NEED STRONG BORDERS AND WE
HAVE TO STOP DRUGS AND CRIME
AND CRIMINALS.
>> BUT PROFESSOR SEIDMAN FROM
GEORGETOWN UNIVERSITY SAYS THE
STATISTICS MAY NOT BE IN THE
PRESIDENT'S FAVOR AS THE
DECLARATION FACES MULTIPLE
LEGAL CHALLENGES.
>> BORDER CROSSINGS ARE WAY
DOWN FROM WHERE THEY WERE
SEVERAL YEARS AGO, MOST OF THE
DRUGS THAT THE PRESENT WORRIES
ABOUT COME THROUGH PORTS OF
ENTRY.
>> 16 STATES INCLUDING
CALIFORNIA ARE ASSUMING
PRESIDENT TRUMP ARGUING THAT HE
DOES NOT HAVE THE
CONSTITUTIONAL AUTHORITY TO
DECLARE THE EMERGENCY.
A SEPARATE LAWSUIT FROM MEMBERS
OF CONGRESS THAT ALSO BECOMING
ON THE SAME GROUNDS.
>> CONGRESS HAS PRETTY MUCH
EXPRESSLY DECIDED NOT TO SPEND
THIS MONEY.
>> MUCH OF THE MONEY WILL COME
FROM THE DEFENSE DEPARTMENT
BUDGET, SPECIALIST SAY DHS IS
ALREADY LOOKING AT CONSTRUCTION
LOCATIONS.
>> WE KNOW THERE WILL BE A
LARGE PORTION OF IT BEING BUILT
IN THE RIO GRANDE VALLEY.
>> WHICH SETS UP ANOTHER LEGAL
BATTLE WITH TEXAS LANDOWNERS,
THREE OF THEM HAVE ALREADY
FILED SUIT OVER POSSIBLE LAND
SEIZURES.
>> THOSE PEOPLE MORE CLEARLY
MAYBE THAN ANYONE ELSE HAVE
STANDINGS TO OBJECT TO WHAT THE
PRESIDENT HAS DONE.
>> LIKE THE PRESENT AND MOST
LEGAL EXPERTS, FOR PFIZER
SEIDMAN SAID THE SUPREME COURT
WILL ULTIMATELY DECIDE THE
ISSUE.
>>> THE NEW NPR PBS NEWS HOUR
SHOWS THAT OVERALL A MAJORITY
OF AMERICANS DISAPPROVE OF THE
PRESIDENT'S USE OF THE NATIONAL
EMERGENCY TO BUILD A WALL.
>> WE ARE FOLLOWING BREAKING
NEWS OUT OF SOUTH DC.
IT IS BEEN A VIOLENT AFTERNOON.
A TEENAGER WAS SHOT ALONG THE
2600 BLOCK OF SANDS ROAD.
DC POLICE SAY THE BOY WAS
CONSCIOUS AND BREATHING WHEN
FIRST RESPONDERS RUSHED INTO
THE HOSPITAL.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT LED UP TO
THE SHOOTING.
POLICE SAY THEY ARE LOOKING FOR
A SUSPECT WEARING A BLUE HOODIE
AND TAN KHAKI PANTS LASTING
HEADING TOWARDS DOUGLAS ROAD.
AND ABOUT 20 MINUTES FROM THERE
EARLIER TODAY, A CRIME ALERT
ABOUT ANOTHER CRIME, THREE
PEOPLE INCLUDING A CHILD WERE
SHOT AND IN THAT INCIDENCE, ELI
PLACE TO THE FORT DuPONT ICE
ARENA, CASINGS COULD BE SEEN
ENTERING THE STREET ALONG WITH
A LEXUS SEDAN WITH WINDOWS SHUT
UP.
ALL BUT ONE OF THE VICTIMS WAS
CONSCIOUS AND BREATHING WHEN
THEY WERE TAKEN TO THE
HOSPITAL.
WE DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT A
MOTIVE OR SUSPECTS IN THAT
INCIDENT.
>>> AN IMPORTANT MEETING AT
WINSTON CHURCHILL HIGH SCHOOL,
PARENTS OF THE MONTGOMERY
COUNTY SCHOOL ART INVITED, ARE
INVITED TO DISCUSS AN EVENT
WHERE STUDENTS HANDED OUT
PASSES GRANTING PERMISSION TO
USE THE N WORD.
THEY WILL ADDRESS A SWASTIKA
DRAWN ON THE DESK EARLIER THIS
YEAR.
THE MEETING IS SET TO BEGIN AT
7:00 TONIGHT.
>>> COMING UP, FREDERICK COUNTY
MOMS DETAINED BY IMMIGRATION
OFFICERS TALK ABOUT HER
NIGHTMARE AND THE LONG-AWAITED
REUNION WITH HER FAMILY.
STOMACH AND VATICAN SECRETS,
DESPITE THE VOW OF CELIBACY,
THE CATHOLIC
>>> A JEWISH CEMETERY WAS FOUND
DESECRATED TODAY IN EASTERN
FRANCE.
SWASTIKAS AND INSCRIPTIONS WERE
FOUND ON SOME 80 GRAVES IN A
VILLAGE LOCATED CLOSE TO
STRASBURG.
THIS COMES TWO MONTHS AFTER
ANOTHER JEWISH CEMETERY WAS
VANDALIZED AND ON THE DAY THAT
FRANCE HELD A LARGE GATHERING
AGAINST TERRACE TO PROTEST.
EMMANUEL MACRON VISITED THE
HOLOCAUST MEMORIAL IN THE CITY.
>>> CBS NEWS CONFIRMED THE
VATICAN HAS KEPT SECRET
GUIDELINES FOR PRIESTS WHO
FATHER CHILDREN.
NEARLY 9 CENTURIES, THE
CATHOLIC CHURCH HAD FORBIDDEN
PRIESTS FROM HAVING SEX AND
GETTING MARRIED.
DARA THOMAS SAYS SHE IS PROOF
THAT PRIESTS SOMETIMES BREAK
THE BOWS AND HER MOTHER WAS
TOLD BY THE CHURCH TO KEEP HER
BIRTHDAY SECRET.
SHE FIRST MET HER FATHER IN
ENGLAND WHEN SHE WAS 14 YEARS
OLD.
>> IT BECAME APPARENT THAT HE
COULDN'T OR WOULDN'T OR WASN'T
ALLOWED TO BE ANY SORT OF A
FATHER TO ME.
>> WHAT WAS THE HARDEST PART OF
ALL OF THIS GROWING UP?
>> FEELING VERY ISOLATED, I
LITERALLY THOUGHT I WAS THE
ONLY PRIEST CHILD IN THE WORLD.
>> THEY PUBLISHED
GROUNDBREAKING GUIDELINES AND
CHURCH OFFICIALS IN AMERICA ARE
LOOKING AT A SIMILAR MODEL.
>> POPE FRANCIS MEETING IN ROME
TO MEET WITH BISHOPS TO TALK
ABOUT SEXUAL ABUSE SCANDALS AND
THE PLAGUE ON MULTIPLE
COMMENTS.
I HAVE AN INTERVIEW WITH A
PRIEST AND CHURCH SCHOLAR
HEADING TO THE MEETING IN ROME.
>> COMING UP, MANNY MacHADO HAS
A NEW TEAM, HOW WILL THAT
IMPACT BRYCE HARPER?
DARREN HAYNES IS MORE FROM THE
TRAINING CAMP IN FLORIDA.
>> YOUR HEALTH MATTERS TO US AT
WUSA9, THAT'S WHY WE ARE
HOLDING FREE HEALTH SCREENINGS
FROM NOON UNTIL 7:00 THIS
THURSDAY, FEBRUARY 21 AT  THE
CANDLE AND MAYBE CENTER.
OUR INITIATIVE IS CALLED IMPACT
HEALTH MATTERS.
>> WE ARE PARTNERING WITH UN
CAPITAL REGION HEALTH AND THE
PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY HEALTH
DEPARTMENT TO PROVIDE ALL SORTS
OF TRAININGS AND DEMOS.
A FEW OF THEM ARE ON YOUR
SCREEN RIGHT NOW, CHOLESTEROL
AND GLUCOSE AND DENTAL
SCREENINGS AND WE HAVE DOCTORS
ON HAND TO ANSWER QUESTIONS AND
YOU CAN GET BACK TO THE
COMMUNITY BY DONATING BLOOD.
>> THE SCREENINGS ARE FREE AND
YOU NEED TO REGISTER FOR SOME
OF THEM AS WELL AS THE BLOOD
DRIVES AT A TIME, YOU CAN DO
THIS BY GOING TO
WUSA9.COM/HEALTH MATTERS.
Stronger is rebuilding
a newborn's heart...
and restoring a
father's faith.
It's standing tall
after one surgery...
not six.
Stronger is being
a typical kid...
despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding
it earlier ...
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is
seeking answers...
And not giving up,
until you find them.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>>> A FREDERICK COUNTY MOM AND
LOCAL CIVIL RIGHTS LEADER AT
THE CENTER OF AN IMMIGRATION
BATTLE IS REUNITED WITH HER
KIDS.
ROXANA SANTOS TALK ABOUT THE
TERROR OF BEING DETAINED BY ICE
FOR NEARLY A MONTH.
DESPITE A FEDERAL JUDGE'S ORDER
BLOCKING HER DEPORTATION.
>> Reporter: ROXANA SANTOS
SPEAKING IN SPANISH SAYS SHE IS
LIVING IN TERROR THAT SHE COULD
BE TAKEN FROM HER FOUR KIDS
AGAIN AT ANY MOMENT, THE THREE
YOUNGEST INCLUDING SIX-YEAR-OLD
TWINS ARE U.S. CITIZENS.
>> I'M HAPPY TO BE WITH MY MOM.
>> I'M REALLY SCARED THEY COULD
SEPARATE ME FROM MY CHILDREN
AGAIN.
>> Reporter: SHE WAS TAKEN BY
ICE AND LOCKED UP IN A RURAL
COUNTY JAIL AND THREATENED WITH
DEPORTATION IN JANUARY,
SPARKING PROTESTS.
SHE WON A CIVIL RIGHTS SUIT FOR
ILLEGALLY PROFILING HER LEADING
TO AN UNJUSTIFIED ARREST IN
2007.
THE FINAL STAGE OF THE CASE IS
STILL IN COURT.
THAT IS THE REASON THE JUDGE
BLOCKED HER DEPORTATION FOR
NOW.
>> IMMIGRATION HAS NO
PRIORITIES ANYMORE, THEY'RE
GOING AFTER MOTHERS AND GOING
AFTER YOUNG PEOPLE.
WE NEED TO PROTECT THEM AND
MAKE SURE THEY ARE COMFORTABLE
INTERACTING WITH THE LOCAL
POLICE AND THAT IS NOT A
PIPELINE TO DEPORTATION.
>> THE FACT IS SHE DID
ILLEGALLY EMIGRATE 14 YEARS AGO
TO FLEE VIOLENCE IN EL
SALVADOR, WHICH MEANS ICE IS
WITHIN ITS RIGHTS TO ATTEMPT TO
SEPARATE THE FAMILY AGAIN.
IN HYATTSVILLE, SCOTT BROOME,
WUSA9.
>> A LOT OF SCHOOLS ARE ALREADY
CALLING IT NOW.
>>> FOR GOOD REASON, THE ROADS
WILL BE A MESS.
BETWEEN 6 AM AND NOON, THAT
WILL BE THE BIG SHOT OF SNOW
AND THE HEAVY SNOW AND IT WILL
ACCUMULATE QUICKLY.
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS YESTERDAY.
WHEN IT STARTS TO SNOW, IT WILL
BECOME A MODERATE TO HEAVY VERY
SOON AND ACCUMULATE QUICKLY.
WE HAVE 3 TO 5 IN LEESBURG AND
GAITHERSBURG AND JUST NORTH OF
ROCKVILLE AND JUST TOUCHING
PARTS OF FAIRFAX COUNTY AND
NORTHERN PRINCE WILLIAM COUNTY.
THERE ARE SPOTS THAT COULD GET
MORE THAN FIVE INCHES.
IN THE METRO AREA, 1 TO 3
INCHES AND WE COULD END UP WITH
TWO INCHES OF SNOW AND AN INCH
OF SLEET.
THAT INCLUDES BETHESDA AND DOWN
TO WALDORF AND FREDERICKSBURG.
TO THE SOUTH OF FREDERICKSBURG
ACROSS INTO THE SOUTHERN
MARYLAND AREA, WE HAVE A TRACE
TO JUST AN INCH, NOT A HUGE
PROBLEM, BUT IF YOU ARE
TRAVELING, HE TRIED TO COME UP
THROUGH SOUTHERN MARYLAND UP 5
OR 301, IN THE CHARLES COUNTY,
DURING THE MORNING IT WILL BE
BAD.
SNOWFALL, 2.8, 2.4, THE
COMPUTERS HAVE COME INTO OUR
WAY OF THINKING.
HERE WE GO, A TREMENDOUS AMOUNT
OF MOISTURE.
MOST OF THIS IS RAIN AND A
LITTLE BIT OF SNOW POPPING UP
IN NORTHWESTERN NORTH CAROLINA
IN THE MOUNTAINS AND THIS IS ON
SCHEDULE FOR BEING ON EITHER
SIDE OF 6:00 TOMORROW.
I LIKE DOING A PURE SNOW ON THE
METER.
BECAUSE IT WILL BE IMPACTFUL
AND DISRUPTIVE, WE WILL MAKE IT
A FIVE.
IT WILL BE A LEGITIMATE STORM
BETWEEN THE SNOW AND ICE AND I
THINK IT WILL BE PLIABLE AND
SLIDABLE.
OUT TOWARDS I-81, ISOLATED
POWER OUTAGES, OKAY, AND
FURTHER WEST FROM HAGERSTOWN
INTO CUMBERLAND, WHERE YOU HAD
THE ICE ABOUT A WEEK AGO, WE
COULD SEE SCATTERED POWER
OUTAGES AND WE ARE A LITTLE
MORE CONCERNED ABOUT POWER
OUTAGES OVER THERE AND HERE IS
WHY.
THIS MODEL HAS VERY LITTLE ICE
AROUND THE METRO AND IT HAS
OKAY AMOUNTS, IT COULD PROBABLY
HANDLE 2/10 IN ROMNEY.
THIS MODEL IS WAY AGGRESSIVE
WITH ALMOST AN INCH IN
CUMBERLAND AND HAGER AND
OAKLAND AND EVEN MORE, .3 IN
LEESBURG AND GAITHERSBURG
LEADING TO LIMBS COMING DOWN
AND POWER OUTAGES.
LET'S TALK ABOUT TYPES OF
PRECIPITATION, IT IS SNOW AND
EVERYTHING IS COLD AND IT
STARTS THAT WAY BUT IT DOESN'T
STAY THAT WAY.
IT ENDS UP WITH A WARM WEDGE
AND THAT TURNS THINGS TO SLEET
WHICH BOUNCES AND THEN WE SEE A
TURN TO FREEZING RAIN AND THAT
IS LIQUID AND FREEZES ON
CONTACT.
THAT IS THE WORST CASE
SCENARIO.
THE ROADS ARE WORSE 6 AM TO
NOON AND IT KICKS TO A MIX AND
RAIN OVERNIGHT AND THEN MORNING
SHOWERS WITH 50s BY THURSDAY.
33 WITH SNOW AT 6 AM, MODERATE
TO HEAVY AT 9:00 AND THINGS
BEGIN TO CHANGE A LITTLE BIT
INTO A MIX.
THE RED WEATHER ALERT TOMORROW,
32 AND 56 ON THURSDAY AND LOOK
AT FRIDAY, WHAT A WAY TO FINISH
THE WEEK.
A LITTLE BIT OF A BLIP ON
SATURDAY, 56 WITH RAIN AND THEN
66 ON SUNDAY.
>>> FOUR WEDDING ANNIVERSARIES
AND ANNIVERSARIES HAVE PASSED
SINCE TIM GIMBEL AND HIS LITTLE
GIRL LOST HER FAMILY.
IT WAS TWO WEEKS BEFORE
CHRISTMAS IN 2014, PLANE
CRASHED INTO THEIR GAITHERSBURG
HOUSE, AND INSIDE WAS MARIE,
HOME ON MATERNITY LEAVE FOUND
CRADLING HER SEVEN-WEEK-OLD SON
AND 3-YEAR-OLD COLE IN AN
UPSTAIRS BATHROOM.
INSTEAD OF LETTING THIS DESTROY
THEM, KEN AND CLARA BELL ARE
LETTING, ARE REBUILDING A PARK.
TONIGHT AT 11:00, HERE ABOUT
THE DESIGN PLANS LITTLE CLARA
BELL HAD TO HONOR
My gums are irritated.
I don't have to worry about
that, do I?
Actually, you do.
Harmful bacteria lurk just below
the gum line.
New Crest Gum Detoxify works
below the gum line
to neutralize harmful plaque
bacteria
and help reverse early gum
damage.
Gum Detoxify, from Crest.
Breathe freely fast, with Vicks
Sinex.
My congestion's gone.
I can breathe again! Ahhhh!
I can breathe again! Ughh!
Vicks Sinex.
Breathe On.
>>> AND NOW WUSA9 SPORTS ,
BROUGHT TO YOU BY XFINITY.
>>> WUSA9 SPORTS DIRECTOR
DARREN HAYNES  HAS SPRING
TRAINING WITH THE NATIONALS AND
THREE THINGS YOU NEED TO KNOW
ABOUT THEM.
>> Reporter: I'M DARREN HAYNES
AT NATIONALS SPRING TRAINING
AND HERE ARE THREE THINGS NEED
TO KNOW, BRYCE HARPER IS NOT IN
WEST PALM BEACH, THE FREE AGENT
STILL HAS YET TO SIGN WITH THE
TEAM.
THE NATIONALS OFFERED HIM A
$300 MILLION DEAL OVER 10
YEARS, THE SAME AS THE PHILLIES
WHO OFFERED HIM A 10 YEAR
CONTRACT FOR $310 MILLION.
>> HOW MUCH DO YOU WANT HIM ON
THE TEAM?
>> I WANT HIM ON THIS TEAM, AND
THE GUYS IN THE CLUBHOUSE WANT
HIM ON THE TEAM, HE'S ONE OF
THE BEST PLAYERS IN THE GAME
RIGHT NOW, AND PEOPLE IN AND
AROUND THIS ORGANIZATION HAVE
HAD A FRONT ROW SEAT TO REALLY
SEE HOW GOOD OF A PLAYER HE IS.
BUT YOU KNOW, AT THE END OF THE
DAY, WE CAN'T BE SITTING AROUND
WAITING FOR HIM TO WALK THROUGH
THOSE DOORS.
>> HERE IS THE SECOND THING YOU
NEED TO KNOW, THERE IS ANOTHER
BIG FREE AGENT OUT THERE.
OR SHOULD I SAY USED TO BE FREE
AGENT, MANNY MacHADO SIGNED A
10 YEAR $300 MILLION CONTRACT
WITH THE PADRES, WHAT DOES THIS
MEAN?
THIS COULD ACCELERATE THINGS
FOR BRYCE HARPER TO SIGN.
I SPOKE TO DAVID MARTINEZ WHO
SAID BRYCE HARPER NEEDS TO
FOCUS ON WHAT'S BEST FOR HIS
FAMILY, BUT ALSO HE WILL FOCUS
ON THE PLAYERS THAT ARE HERE AT
SPRING TRAINING.
SPEAKING OF DAVID MARTINEZ COME
HERE SOMETHING YOU DIDN'T KNOW
ABOUT HIM.
>> HIDDEN TALENT.
>> I CAN PLAY THE BALL GOES.
>> THESE ARE NOT BONGOS, BUT,
CAN YOU?
>> DO A QUICK TAP?
>> SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
>> IT IS TOUGH.
WE LEARNED SOMETHING NEW TODAY.
>> COMING UP AT 11:00 TONIGHT,
WHY WAS TODAY ALMOST LIKE A
FAMILY REUNION FOR MANAGER
DAVEY MARTINEZ?
>>> DARREN WILL BE AT NATIONALS
SPRING TRAINING IN FLORIDA ALL
WEEK LONG AND BRING YOU LIVE
UPDATES ON THE PLAYERS.
>> HE IS MISSING ALL OF THIS
SNOW.
WHAT A SHAME.
>>> SPEAKING OF FACEBOOK LIVE,
HOWARD IS ON THERE IF YOU WANT
TO ASK ANY QUESTIONS.
>>> WE SHOW YOU THE SNOWFALL
MAP AGAIN.
3 TO 5 NORTH AND WEST AND 1 TO
3 IN THE METRO AND UP TO AN
INCH IN THE NORTHERN NECK AND
SOUTHERN MARYLAND.
BUT IF YOU ARE DRIVING UP FROM
SOUTHERN MARYLAND FROM ST.
MARY'S THROUGH CHARLES COUNTY,
AROUND 9:00 OR 10:00, IT WILL
BE BAD.
IT WILL START TO SNOW QUICKLY
AND ACCUMULATE QUICKLY AND
BECOME HEAVY RATHER QUICKLY.
ONCE WE GET THROUGH THAT, WE
ARE OKAY.
56 ON THURSDAY AND 50s ON
FRIDAY AND 66 ON SUNDAY.
>> AS LONG AS HE CAN STAY OFF
THE ROADS FOR ONE DAY.
>>> WE WILL BE BACK AT 7:00.
>>> WE WILL SEE YOU BACK HERE
AT 11:00.
[ MUSIC ]
I never thought I'd say this
but I found bladder leak
underwear
that's actually pretty.
Always Discreet Boutique.
Hidden inside is a super
absorbent core
that quickly turns liquid to
gel.
So I feel protected and pretty.
Always Discreet Boutique.
Do I use a toothpaste that
whitens my teeth?
Or one that's good for my teeth?
Now I don't have to choose.
From Crest 3D White.
The Whitening Therapy
Collection.
Now with Charcoal or Coconut
Oil.
It gently whitens.
Plus, it has a fortifying
formula
to protect your enamel.
Crest. Healthy, beautiful smiles
for life.
Stronger is blasting
her tumors...
without risking her bones.
It's training her
good cells...
to fight the bad guys.
Stronger is less pain...
new hope...
more fight.
It's doing everything
in your power...
and everything in ours.
Stronger, is changing even
faster than they do.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
Captioning sponsored by CBS